Kim Jojo!
Thank you for being alive.
I'll think a bit more...
about what I can do to make you happy.
I just...
wanted you to know how I feel.
I should've just let it ring though.
I should've told you how I felt.
Not being able to see you
made me realize that.
Let's meet up at the schoolyard
at 4 :00 p.m.
I'll be waiting.
Just hear me out from over there.
Thank you...
for everything.
But even if you download Love Alarm,
I can't ring your Love Alarm.
It was all my fault
that Sun-oh and I broke up.
I've already decided...
that I wouldn't ever
like anyone else again.
And I might...
continue to be like that.
Are you okay with that?
Yeah.
All that matters to me...
is that you act on how you truly feel.
If you ignore my texts,
I'll let myself be ignored.
If you stand me up,
I'll let myself be stood up.
And if you dump me,
I'll let myself be dumped.
All of that is romance to me...
because we'd be doing things together...
that I can't do on my own.
The things I can't do on my own.
Being honest about my feelings
and confessing my love.
Sharing the happiness...
and sadness...
instead of running away.
It is emerging
from the basement of one's heart,
and confessing one's true feelings.
Jojo.
Is it okay if I download Love Alarm?
Liking someone...
means mustering up courage.
WILL YOU DOWNLOAD THIS APPLICATION?
CANCEL
DOWNLOAD
LOVE ALARM DOWNLOAD MANAGER
DOWNLOADING APPLICATION NOW
LOVE ALARM
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I rang Kim Jojo's Love Alarm!
I'll ring four years' worth of
Love Alarm right now, Jojo.
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I have no idea
how the members of the Badge Club,
who have their alarms rung
by thousands of people,
must feel.
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
But thanks to a single person...
who is ringing my Love Alarm...
right now,
I now have hope...
that I can be happy.
One is...
bigger than any other number...
in the world.
ONE IS BIGGER THAN ANY OTHER
NUMBER IN THE WORLD
So, what colors do you like?
I like white and I also like green.
What about music?
Are there any songs you listen to a lot?
Do you like watching movies?
-How many more questions are there?
-What?
Sorry. There is just so much
I want to know about you.
Can I ask you just one more thing, though?
What does your name mean?
"Jojo."
It's such a pretty name.
JOJO
It's written like this.
It means "morning" and "bright."
So, "bright morning"? I like that.
What about your name?
My name?
Hand me that. Thanks.
HYE
HYE-YEONG
So your name means "eternal grace"?
Yeah. My mom came up with it.
That's a nice name.
It suits you perfectly.
Why are you taking that?
Your name is written here.
I'll take yours too, then.
HYE-YEONG
So, it was because of you after all.
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I really hoped it wouldn't ring this time.
You still like me, don't you?
Look me in the eye.
You like me.
I used to like you.
And I don't know...
if I'll ever like anyone
as much as I loved you.
But not anymore.
I'm the one who ruined our relationship.
I'm the one who broke your trust.
So how could I possibly like you?
Then...
do you like Hye-yeong?
Hye-yeong...
is a warm and kind guy.
I want to try my best.
What about me?
You couldn't try for me?
I'm sorry, Sun-oh.
I was too immature back then.
But now--
Ring Hye-yeong's Love Alarm
in front of me, then.
Then I'll believe...
everything you just said.
There's no other shield like this
in the entire world.
I figured you might need it.
I don't want you to be heartbroken
like I was.
YOUR CRUSH'S LOVE ALARM WON'T RING
EVEN IF YOUR LOVE ALARM IS ON.
WARNING: ONCE YOU ACTIVATE THE SHIELD,
ONLY THE DEVELOPER CAN REMOVE IT.
WOULD YOU STILL LIKE TO CONTINUE?
I stole Sun-oh's smile away from him...
just so I wouldn't feel any pain.
By the time I regretted what I did,
it was already too late.
Even though I got a new phone...
WILL YOU DOWNLOAD THIS APPLICATION?
...and reinstalled Love Alarm...
DOWNLOADING APPLICATION
...the shield kept reactivating
on its own.
Jojo. Is it okay
if I download Love Alarm?
I need to...
get rid of the shield.
The only way to get rid of the shield...
is to meet the developer of the app.
Ta-da! Hello, everyone.
Welcome to BJ Gul-mi's
awesome shopping mall, Love Mi.
Today, I'll show you colors that match
with warm undertones and cool undertones.
First, if you have a warm undertone,
how about you try a warm color like this?
Yellow is the quintessential color
for warm undertones.
Next, if your skin has cool undertones...
Ta-da!
Blue, of course!
As long as you have just one of each...
RENTAL AGREEMENT
So,
have you found a place to live?
I meant to tell you about it sooner, but--
Does it feel good to just leave...
after using me like that?
I used you?
Yeah.
You used me your whole life.
You looked after a wimp like me
your whole life
so you could feel good about yourself.
This was bound to happen sooner or later.
I can't live here forever.
Is it because of Kim Jojo?
Yes.
You know exactly what Kim Jojo did to me.
Yet how could you, of all people,
do this to me?
I told you.
I still like Kim Jojo.
I trusted you.
Looks like you weren't really
on my side either.
You smile at the mirror every day,
pretending that you're a good guy, right?
But I know...
just how much of a bastard you really are.
Go to Kim Jojo.
And don't ever come back.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Sun-oh seems upset
that I invited you without telling him.
Here. I know you like this.
Thanks.
Make sure you eat up, too.
I was at the department store not long ago
and saw the Badge Club members
getting their Love Alarms rung constantly.
That must be quite irritating
for you, Yuk-jo.
It makes me happy
because the fact
that they're ringing my Love Alarm
means that they like me.
Well, I guess it's nice
when someone whom you like rings it.
Make sure you ring
Yuk-jo's Love Alarm often, okay, Sun-oh?
YEOLRIM HIGH SCHOOL
CONGRATULATIONS ON GRADUATING
KIM JOJO
Is it because of Kim Jojo?
You know exactly what Kim Jojo...
did to me.
Yet how could you, of all people,
do this to me?
KIM JOJO
I always wondered
what your room looked like.
-Yuk-jo.
-Yeah?
Don't worry about my conversation
with Hye-yeong from earlier.
I'll be better to you.
I'll be your friend...
as well as your girlfriend.
I really am on your side.
Let's go to Gangneung tomorrow.
You always said you wanted
to go there in winter.
Let's go there and ride snowboards,
eat some delicious food,
and enjoy the ocean view. Okay?
Next time.
We have plans tomorrow, after all.
What?
You're going to the presentation?
I thought you didn't want to go.
I'll go.
With you.
You can have it.
Here.
Shall I help you up?
-I'll be on your side.
-You piece of...
-That's right, dude.
-On my side?
-You'll ruin my hair!
-Just think of me.
"I'm happy to have Hye-yeong in my life."
1 DAY LEFT UNTIL LAUNCH OF LOVE ALARM 2.0
DEVELOPER WILL BE REVEALED
WOULD YOU LIKE TO ACTIVATE THE SHIELD?
ONCE YOU ACTIVATE THE SHIELD,
ONLY THE DEVELOPER CAN REMOVE IT.
I don't want you to be heartbroken
like I was.
Duk-gu.
Take care, Jojo.
Duk-gu...
is back.
NEW LOVE ALARM 2.0 FEATURE
WILL BE ANNOUNCED
DEVELOPER WILL BE REVEALED
In a moment, the developer of Love Alarm
will reveal himself for the first time
and announce the new feature
of Love Alarm 2.0.
The new feature has remained
a complete mystery until now.
Everyone seems to be
quite eager to find out what it is.
Many people are here near the red carpet
so they can get a glimpse
of the Badge Club members.
It seems that the police are also here
to ensure the safety of the spectators.
-You're so pretty!
-I love you!
-How pretty!
These two are the most famous couple
in the Badge Club.
Mr. Hwang Sun-oh and Ms. Lee Yuk-jo
are making their entrance.
They look even more stunning
and glamorous than usual.
I'm definitely going to make it
into the Badge Club, too.
JOJO
-Look over there.
-Look.
Gosh, look at that.
-Amazing.
-What is that?
That's so pretty.
It's amazing.
Now a Love Alarm cloud
has appeared in the sky.
The Love Alarm C&C department has made
many Love Alarm clouds appear before.
You can see that this cloud
is much bigger and much more beautiful
than any other in the past.
Look at that. Over there.
-What's that?
-Look at that.
-What is it? Isn't that Love Alarm?
If only...
Love Alarm hadn't been launched
back then...
If...
we hadn't realized these kids' feelings,
I wonder...
what we'd be like now.
I deleted Love Alarm a long time ago.
It scared me, you see.
I thought it would complicate things
if I kept ringing your Love Alarm.
Hye-yeong.
I should've just let it ring though.
I should've told you how I felt.
Not being able to see you
made me realize that.
Do you want to kiss?
You're a good boy.
How could you be so sweet?
It makes my heart ache.
Mom!
Sun-oh...
It's fine. I don't feel alone.
That's because
you've felt alone for so long...
that you don't even realize
you feel that way.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't apologize.
I thought of all sorts of scenarios
to hate or to understand you.
Look at me.
Look at me!
It still feels like
you have feelings for me.
Kim Jojo!
I'm off...
to face my feelings head-on.
Look at that.
What?
8 DAYS LEFT UNTIL THE LAUNCH
OF LOVE ALARM 2.0
What kind of person do you think
the developer of Love Alarm is?
I don't know.
A person with a lot of secrets?
He has never shown his face
even once in the past four years.
Why do you ask?
Well,
he developed an app that exposes
people's romantic feelings,
so it's weird that he's hiding
his own identity.
I guess he wanted to
completely conceal himself.
Just like the artist of The Ringing World.
JOJO
THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
ONE IS BIGGER THAN ANY OTHER
NUMBER IN THE WORLD
THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
Jojo.
Love Alarm needs to stop
its numbers game this instant!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Love Alarm needs to stop
its numbers game this instant!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
ANTI-LOVE ALARM
-Stop!
-Hey, get out of the way!
We're against Love Alarm!
The Love Alarm 2.0 presentation
will begin soon
so please make your way to the event hall.
Love Alarm needs to stop collecting data
on our feelings and using them!
Stop it! Stop it!
-Over here!
-Do an affectionate pose for us.
-Please smile at the camera.
-Look over here.
Look over here!
You two look great. I love it!
Over here!
Look over here, please!
We're against Love Alarm!
Can I see your invitation?
ARTIST OF THE RINGING WORLD,
YOU ARE INVITED AS A SPECIAL GUEST
I'm Lee Seon-yeong,
the CSO of Love Alarm's C&C department.
Today is a special day
because we will be presenting
the new feature of Love Alarm 2.0
as well as the developer of Love Alarm.
Four years ago, he was just
an average high school student.
But Love Alarm, which was created
in this shy boy's bedroom,
has now completely changed the world.
MYEONGHYEON-DONG
1,500 days after the launch...
LOVE ALARM
...Love Alarm was able to
not only tell you
if someone nearby likes you,
but has even changed the way
we like others.
Now, I'd like to introduce him
to you for the first time.
Please give a warm round of applause
for the developer of Love Alarm,
Brian Chon.
Love Alarm needs to stop collecting data
on our feelings and using them!
Stop it! Stop it!
Every day for the past four years,
50 million users have rung Love Alarm
in Korea alone.
We've also analyzed the data
on the hearts of 73 billion people.
Nowadays, we can't even know
how others feel
without relying on Love Alarm.
Furthermore, Love Alarm
has now divided people
into those who belong to the Badge Club
and those who don't.
If you don't like it,
just don't download Love Alarm!
Why are you causing a commotion?
We're against Love Alarm!
Get out of here, Anti-Love Alarm!
Let me ask you something.
Are you happy that you can only confess
your feelings through Love Alarm?
Love Alarm will now...
be able to predict...
how one's feelings will develop.
This is...
Love Alarm 2.0.
LOVE ALARM 2.0
We're against Love Alarm!
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Love Alarm 2.0 will now be able to
accurately predict
how one's feelings will develop.
It'll be able to tell you
who will ring whose Love Alarm,
and who won't ring whose Love Alarm.
Jojo!
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I'll introduce the new feature
of Love Alarm 2.0 to you all now.
Allow me to introduce something
that everyone wants to know about...
right now.
"The person you will fall in love with."
THE PERSON YOU WILL FALL IN LOVE WITH
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)