HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN THIS?
IT'S ALL OVER THE WEBSITE.
IS IT KIM JOJO?
YEOLRIM HIGH NEWS
#45553 ANONYMOUS STORY
Hey, Jojo! What did you say?
You think you're better than me?
-You're mooching off my family.
-Get back inside.
She started the fight.
Get back inside.
All of you, go back to your classrooms.
Go back to your classrooms!
Give me your hand.
-Was it you?
-What's her problem?
Why is she so mean to you?
Is that important right now?
Now the whole school knows our secret.
What are you trying to say?
You sent this, didn't you?
Do you think so?
-Then who else?
-Who cares?
It's true that we kissed.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Right.
Lucky you take everything so lightly.
I never said I did.
My Love Alarm isn't on.
Let's trust Love Alarm.
The choice...
is up to Jojo.
LOVE ALARM
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
What about you?
Did your alarm ring as well?
Your phone is on silent mode now, right?
Let me see.
I'll call you later.
I didn't mean to turn it on without you.
-The photos have been--
-It's okay.
What is?
You don't need to explain.
Jojo rang your Love Alarm.
So? That's it?
Are you really okay?
We said we'd trust Love Alarm
and leave the choice to Jojo.
We already agreed to it.
-Hye-yeong--
-My bike chain broke.
I was going to replace it today anyway,
but it completely snapped on my way here.
-No, I don't want to.
-I don't care.
Guys, Jojo is here.
-Oh, really?
-Jojo is here.
-What? Where?
-Over there.
-Wow, she's back.
-I guess she's not even embarrassed.
-Why is she here?
-I'm surprised.
-She has no shame.
-I know, right?
She's really something.
I thought she'd drop out of school.
Jang-go.
Are you mad at me for something?
-Ever since yesterday--
-You're really shameless.
Must you and Sun-oh do that
first thing in the morning?
Il-sik skipped his training today
because of you.
Why are you only worried about Il-sik?
You're my friend.
"Friend"?
Hey, you're the one
who ruined our friendship.
Are you mad
because I didn't tell you about Il-sik?
I was going to tell you.
-Also, it's not because of Sun-oh--
-Hey, Jojo.
Is that really the only thing
you didn't tell me?
What?
The day Il-sik was looking for you...
No.
The day you and Sun-oh kissed,
I went to your academy
because I couldn't get hold of you.
But you weren't even registered there.
You said we're friends.
Then why did you lie to me about that?
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Jeez, you're too much. Goodness.
Gosh, what the hell?
Wow, look at this punk.
I beat him up, and he still likes me.
You asshole, are you getting aroused?
That's gross.
I'm going to beat you up
until this number is gone.
Hey, what are you doing over there?
-Who's that punk?
-Let's go.
Hey, wait. Where are you going?
Let's just go. He'll get us in trouble.
Hey, he's alone.
Fuck! I said, let's just go.
-Dude. You're scared, aren't you?
-Damn.
-Hey.
-What? Are you really scared?
Hey, wait up!
Hey. Damn, are you all right?
He was in my class last year.
I'll report him.
-Just leave him be.
-Bullies like him must be taught a lesson.
It was my fault.
It all happened
because I rang his Love Alarm.
But if you don't report him,
he'll keep harassing you--
I'm disgusted too!
Fuck.
Why am I drawn to a jerk like him?
What can I do to stop my feelings for him?
There's no such thing.
There's no way you can stop
liking someone.
There isn't.
Eat up, guys.
I'm on a diet.
Give me Jojo's number.
I feel so bad for Gul-mi.
JANG-GO
Are you not in the cafeteria?
Where are you now? Why aren't you here?
Did your alarm ring as well?
Let me see.
I'll call you later.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
The moment Sun-oh rang my Love Alarm,
I felt this buzzing sensation
throughout my body.
Why didn't you text me back?
How did you get my number?
I asked you why you didn't text back.
How long did you run for?
Hey, don't come close.
I probably reek of sweat now.
I don't care.
Hey.
What was that?
Why is she so cute?
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
-I bet.
-The timing was awesome.
Our Chinese teacher was nuts today.
Gosh, totally.
Seriously, wasn't he such a nutcase today?
It really was epic. I thought...
Ji-yeon.
Where's Jang-go?
Why ask me about your best friend?
She's not anymore, is she?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Where are you, Jang-go?
I'll come to you.
I don't want to be on bad terms with you.
What does she want from me now
after doing all that with Sun-oh?
Hey, isn't Jojo unbelievable?
She's not even registered at the academy.
But she used that as an excuse
and never hung out with us, you know?
-Why did you do that?
-What do you mean?
It was your fault
that the photos spread all over school.
Hey, that wasn't me.
I only sent them to you.
Did you really think
my friends wouldn't do anything?
Well...
We'd still be together
if it weren't for those photos.
Gosh, I don't even know
what to think anymore.
Hey, Il-sik.
-I did it for your sake.
-Why would you do that for me?
Because we're friends.
Jojo became friends with us later on.
The two of us were friends first.
You aren't my friend anymore either.
I shouldn't have downloaded Love Alarm.
Jojo.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
You're not mad anymore, are you?
I like it now that you have Love Alarm.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
What's going on?
Why isn't Jojo picking up?
WHERE ARE YOU, JANG-GO?
I'LL COME TO YOU
Jojo, what are you doing?
-Table four is ready to order.
-Oh, okay.
Aren't you taking our order?
Two servings of marinated beef,
two whole racks of ribs,
and a serving of beef ribs.
Here's your charcoal.
-Hye-yeong works here too.
-He's not working today.
Really?
Give me your hand.
I want to hold it.
The tongs.
-What?
-Pass me the tongs.
Oh, okay.
My friends don't know that I work here.
Let's keep this secret between you and me.
Hey, start with this.
Why are you grilling
the marinated meat first?
Don't eat it, then.
I'll grill them however I want.
You should start with...
Jeez. Oh, right. I should order some soda.
-Excuse me.
-Go and get it yourself.
Myself? Why should I?
Then do you want to grill this?
I can grab it from the fridge, right?
-Excuse me, I'm taking some soda.
-Okay.
What? What do you want?
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Your Love Alarm isn't on right now, is it?
Let's try again.
I couldn't see it properly earlier.
Why aren't you turning it on?
Turn your Love Alarm on. Please?
For two, please.
So, when are you going
to turn your Love Alarm on?
Jojo.
I need to check whether or not
your Love Alarm rang this morning.
Come on.
Turn it on already.
-I don't want to.
-Why not?
Turn it on. If you don't,
I'll lie down on the ground now.
Do you want me to throw a tantrum?
Jojo.
I want you to like me back.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
You're pretty.
Sun-oh likes me.
The person I like also likes me back.
It's like a miracle.
THE MIRACLE OF TWO PEOPLE
LIKING EACH OTHER
Thirty-eight...
Thirty-nine...
Forty...
Meet me at that place.
No, it's not that.
I didn't know only the assistant director
would be attending.
It's my first time playing a secretary.
Yes, Director.
Yes, I'll go over the script thoroughly.
All right.
Mom!
Mom, I can count in English now.
Hey, can you take Sun-oh?
Mom, look at me.
-Mom.
-Go away.
Drink this.
You never went up there without my help
when we were kids.
Shall I help you up?
It's too high.
It definitely looks higher
now that I'm older.
Are you an old man or what? Come on.
Sun-oh, are you all right?
I'll be on your side.
On my side?
What does that mean?
My mom told me
that it means punishing those
who are mean to you,
eating with you at every meal,
and being by your side when you get sick.
Then what should I give you in return?
The game console?
You don't need to do anything.
Just think of me.
"I'm happy to have Hye-yeong in my life."
That's what you should think.
I used to get scared up here,
thinking that I might fall.
Hey.
"If I'm going to fall anyway,
I might as well look cool."
Thinking like that took the fear away.
You've grown a lot.
What?
-Oh, no!
-Gosh, hey.
Gosh, I'm so relieved to hear that.
Yes.
I was worried because my grandma seemed
to be low in spirits last time I saw her.
Yes, thank you.
I'll be in touch again soon.
Okay.
You can use this.
We used to share things like this,
you know.
Thanks.
When you first came to our place,
I was very fond of you.
That's why I suggested we share a room.
I'm sorry about this morning.
-I didn't mean to--
-Right, you must be sorry.
Then break up with Sun-oh.
-What?
-I had a crush on him first.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
You always say that,
but you don't mean it.
Hey, look at me.
My dad is gone
because of your family's debt,
and my mom drinks every single day.
Why can't you give up even just one thing?
Jojo, I just told you that I like him.
Okay? So end it with him.
-If you break up with him now--
-No.
I can't.
My family and I are in this mess...
because of you.
Jojo, look at this. Ta-da!
-A frog!
-Yes, it's a frog.
-Tap.
Tap.
Oh, my. Great job, Jojo.
One more time.
What happened?
A man in his 30s
who assaulted a woman in her 20s
on her way home
at a park in Seoul last night
has been arrested.
A controversy has arisen over Love Alarm
due to the victim's statement.
Reporter Lee Dong-gyu, tell us more.
Sure.
A man wearing a hat
approaches a woman walking alone.
The woman starts walking faster
and suddenly pulls out her phone
to check something.
Looking relieved, she then
starts walking again at a slower pace.
At that very moment,
the man takes out his weapon
and attacks the woman from behind.
The assailant, Mr. Cha,
had romantic feelings for the victim.
He stated that he assaulted her
because he was angry at her
for not recognizing how he felt about her.
At first, I was scared
because someone was following me.
But right at that moment,
my Love Alarm rang.
Because of that, I let my guard down.
I assumed he was following me
because he was attracted to me.
I see. Meanwhile, C&C,
the company that developed Love Alarm,
has released an official statement
regarding the incident.
LOVE ALARM
THE STABBING CASE IN A PARK
Even before Love Alarm was launched,
crimes like stalking, assault,
and even murder were committed
in the name of love.
So far, there is no case
where Love Alarm misjudged
the users' feelings.
However, when your Love Alarm goes off,
please keep this one thing in mind.
Love Alarm simply lets you know
who is attracted to you.
It does not guarantee
-your safety or happiness.
-Oh, boy.
Love Alarm is the problem.
It rings between people of the same gender
and causes embarrassment.
Even things that you're too shy to confess
are disclosed
when you turn on your Love Alarm.
Please pay extra attention
to this matter, okay?
Oh, dear.
I never liked Love Alarm.
Blindly relying on it
resulted in this kind of tragedy.
I bet this is only the beginning.
Pardon?
We all use Love Alarm,
and yet we blame everything for it
whenever anything happens.
-Come on, sir.
-Why?
I'll say it again. Love Alarm is banned
from our school as of today.
-What do you mean?
-Are you serious?
If you like someone,
just tell that person how you feel.
-How?
-Gosh, this is so annoying.
Open your textbooks!
Question 7 and 8 on page 45.
Gosh, I can't even focus now.
SUN-OH SENT YOU A PHOTO
SILENT MODE
SUN-OH
Let's go together.
Where should we go first?
And here's a gift for you.
-Hey, So-jeong will buy us tteokbokki.
-When did I say that?
You never pay.
Don't you have a conscience?
It's Jojo, Kim Jojo.
-I'll treat you girls today.
-Seriously?
-Gosh.
-You'll spend all your money.
Are you all right?
Why did I think that she'd like me back...
if I showed her how I felt about her?
I shouldn't have rung her Love Alarm.
But there's nothing wrong...
with liking someone.
I know, but it has made her like me
even less now.
Gul-mi, you missed a beat.
That was great.
I want Marx's partner for the opening
performance at JAVA's upcoming concert...
to be Ha-na.
Sure.
Keep up the great work.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
-Hey, that's Marx!
-Seriously?
-Hey, it's for real!
-That's so cool!
We have to take a photo with Marx.
-Let's take a photo.
-Okay.
-One, two...
-Why are they screaming?
-Don't you know JAVA?
-One more!
-One more! One, two, three.
-They're really popular because of Marx.
-He's so handsome.
-Goodness!
-His concert is coming up?
-His face is so tiny.
-Let's go to the concert!
-Don't look.
-Let's go.
-We have to.
All right.
Walking is already tiring.
Why are you studying as well?
Do you give up everything that's "tiring"?
Life is a battle against yourself,
you know?
Why fight against yourself?
You're just like Hye-yeong.
You're always either studying or working.
Hye-yeong?
Oh, the guy you were with
in the schoolyard the other day?
Are you two close?
-What was that about?
-Jealousy.
Don't even look at boy bands,
and don't talk about my friends.
Hey, what's with you?
What if someone sees us?
I'm doing this for people to see
that you're all mine.
Hey, don't be so clingy. It's a turnoff.
Come on, Jojo. Have you forgotten
that you're dating Hwang Sun-oh?
Sun-oh and I are walking on the path
that I used to walk on alone.
The fact that there is a path...
is such a blessing for us,
a couple that's just starting out.
I'm here.
What the heck are you up to these days?
What did you do? Gul-mi doesn't want
to go to school because of you.
I heard you hit her
in front of your classmates.
-Did I raise you so that you can hit her?
-Aunt, that's not what happened.
Gul-mi said that you flirted with a guy,
and he got you a new phone.
Is that a lie too, then?
You're just like your mother, aren't you?
If you want to mess up your life,
do it alone.
Don't drag Gul-mi into your mess.
Did you get a girlfriend?
You've never done this before.
It's quite nice.
Why now?
You'll be in your senior year soon.
What do you think?
-She's young.
-That's it?
-What about her pretty face?
-Being young...
is much better than being pretty.
Don't go overboard.
MY PAST SELF IS A STRANGER TO ME
HEROINE JEONG MI-MI'S LIFE AS AN ACTRESS
JEONG MI-MI
FROM MOM
Are you still working?
No, I finished some time ago.
Then what are you up to now?
I'm going to bed.
Don't say things like, "Dream about me."
Don't dream.
Don't have any dreams.
Just get a restful night's sleep.
I'll see you at school tomorrow.
Thanks.
For what?
For liking me.
Hey, Jojo.
Did you get a good night's sleep?
Yes, what about you?
I didn't sleep well
because I missed you too much.
I want to see you before class.
Meet me on the rooftop.
If you're late,
you have to give me 100 kisses.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Hey.
You jerk.
I wondered why you kept avoiding me.
The guy you beat up
can't even come to school,
and you were just pretending?
So what?
Are you going to tell everyone?
You'd better apologize to him.
What about you?
Aren't you offended?
That I rang your Love Alarm?
What can you do? It's not like
you can control your feelings.
You're so cool about it.
I've been stressed out,
trying to avoid you.
Then keep it turned off.
You're right.
Why did I leave my Love Alarm on?
Maybe I wanted you to find out.
I'm embarrassed,
but relieved at the same time.
So I guess I had been waiting
to run into you.
I'm going to keep avoiding you,
so don't tell anyone.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
NURSE'S OFFICE
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
YOU CAN DEACTIVATE LOVE ALARM TEMPORARILY
IF YOU WANT TO HIDE YOUR FEELINGS.
YOU CAN TOUCH THE SCREEN LIGHTLY
TO REACTIVATE LOVE ALARM.
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)