SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Hye-yeong.
Who did that to you?
Calm down. I fell over on my own.
I heard you fought in the toilet.
Who was it?
Do you think
anyone could hurt me this bad?
You're not a kid.
Why would you fall over on your own?
I know, right?
Why do I act like an idiot these days?
Let's go.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
NURSE'S OFFICE
Hye-yeong?
Oh, the guy you were with
in the schoolyard the other day?
Can you light the grill
for table number six?
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
So you should get a ride in my car
in the morning. Stop being like that.
You said you had to go early today.
Hey, you go home first.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Sorry. Did you wait long?
I know. You must be surprised.
I'm dashing even in the morning.
Let's go and have fun by ourselves
during free time on the school trip.
I'm not going.
What?
Why not?
You don't want to go to Jeju Island
because you're from there. Is that it?
Yes. I mean, you could say that.
Have fun for me.
What are you saying?
No, I won't go either.
Hey, why not? You should go.
It won't be fun without you.
-I'm not going.
-You only just transferred to this school.
Go and make some friends.
I have enough friends already.
I hate to be apart from you.
I almost died yesterday
because I missed you so much.
What?
Everyone is dying to have a chat with me,
but my girlfriend is so indifferent to me.
Don't be like that.
I'll get upset.
"The industry has its eyes on Love Alarm,
an app that has
more than ten million downloads,
for its sales record as well as
its download count records this year."
-My gosh.
-That's crazy.
Isn't it awesome?
The developer must be a romantic.
I know!
Do you know why he made it?
To let his crush know that he likes her.
I am so jealous of that girl.
-I hope he's handsome too.
-Right.
Of course he'd be handsome.
Where are those handsome guys?
If I were her,
I'd go out with him right away.
-I know.
-Of course.
-I'd marry him.
-Hey, Chon Duk-gu.
The teacher wants you.
Hey, Gul-mi.
Does he still ring your Love Alarm?
Are you crazy?
Don't say my name
in the same sentence as his.
It's creepy.
Have you already left school?
Yes, I'm on my way to work.
What about you? Where are you?
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Here.
-Jojo, I need you to come with me.
-I need to go to work.
No, you don't.
What if I get fired?
Don't worry. That won't happen.
Where are we going?
What?
Min-jae,
what are you doing here?
I don't know.
I have no idea what I'm doing here!
I'm sorry.
I let a girl get in the car
in my free time,
and Sun-oh threatened me
with the dashcam footage.
Sun-oh, that jerk.
He's on a date with a girl himself.
-On a date?
-Yes, he went on a date.
Hye-yeong, bring a box of napkins.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, my eyes.
-Why are you smiling when it hurts?
-It doesn't hurt if you smile.
No. It still hurts.
I thought you brought me here
because you were good at this.
I didn't know it'd be this slippery.
Oh, no.
Gosh.
Here.
Fine. I'll go alone.
Hey, don't go.
One, two.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Shall I turn it off?
-What's wrong with it?
-Don't you feel anything?
Other girls are ringing my Love Alarm.
-No.
-Really?
Because you ring mine.
Come on. Hold me.
Stop teasing me.
I won't let go.
It's beautiful.
I didn't know because
I'd never been here at this hour.
-So pretty.
-Right?
Very pretty.
Why are you so pretty?
It makes my heart flutter.
Thank you, Sun-oh.
Jojo. Kim Jojo.
-You can't just leave after that.
-Yes, I can.
-Jojo.
-What?
I really have to go now.
I'll be late again.
We'll see each other again tomorrow.
We hardly see each other.
Can't we meet freely at school as well?
I'm not comfortable with it yet.
I have something to tell you.
IF YOU'RE IN LOVE, RING THE ALARM
WITH SUN-OH
EDIT PROFILE
PROFILE PICTURE HAS BEEN UPDATED
You can smoke.
I'm fine.
Min-jae worked hard grilling meat today.
Is something up?
I don't know if I did the right thing.
Good night.
Hey, finish what you were saying.
Go on. I'm the only one
you can open up to.
No, it's fine.
Is it about Jojo?
What is it?
Did you guys fight?
I want to help her,
but there's nothing I can do.
When I was having a hard time,
you were there for me.
Do the same.
Just be there for her.
There's no such thing.
There's no way
you can stop liking someone.
There isn't.
LOVE ALARM
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
I want to help her,
but there's nothing...
I can do.
DELETE LOVE ALARM
DELETE
YEOLRIM HIGH SCHOOL
LUNCH CARD
Stop dieting,
and don't skip meals, okay?
Yes, sir.
Jojo, let me know anytime
if you want to go on the school trip.
I'll find a way.
You may go.
TEACHERS' ROOM
Hye-yeong.
Did you get everyone's?
-Three will pay tomorrow.
-All right.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
Thanks.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Thank you.
-That's too much.
-Eat up.
-Have a nice lunch.
-Thank you.
-No.
-It tastes terrible.
Do you like pork cutlet? Do you want mine?
-Thanks.
-Take all of it.
Thanks.
-I thought you were on a diet.
-Hey.
What's wrong with you?
-Thanks.
-Can I eat them all?
That's amazing.
Thank you.
Enjoy your lunch.
You too.
Don't take it.
-It's mine.
-Look at them.
-What's going on?
-They're unbelievable.
Are they going out?
What are you doing?
Eat up, kids.
Eat this.
I have mine here.
Eat more. Eat a lot.
Sit on the other side. It's uncomfortable.
No. I prefer sitting next to you.
How can you be so pretty
even when you're eating?
You don't want me to eat?
No. I'm sorry. I'll shut up.
Eat.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Are they going out?
Wake up.
What are you doing here, skipping lunch?
I didn't skip lunch. I had it already.
Let's eat separately from now on.
It'd be awkward to eat with you and Jojo.
Let's go.
MY PAST SELF IS A STRANGER TO ME
HEROINE JEONG MI-MI'S LIFE AS AN ACTRESS
By the time Sun-oh was ready
to go to elementary school,
I was not a mother but an actress
who wanted to start working again.
Sun-oh probably doesn't remember it.
Do you not want to go home?
I don't want to go home, either.
We are well-off,
but my family is embarrassing.
I don't want to talk about them.
What are you reading?
It's just...
Sun-oh's really cool.
Did you ring each other's Love Alarm?
Yes.
You guys look good together.
Are you going to read those books?
-Well, they're just...
-Excuse me.
HWANG JAE-CHEOL
Hello, sir.
You must be very busy.
You're the only one
who isn't busy in this house.
Have a good day, sir.
Are you going to eat too?
Did you enjoy the school lunch?
Yes.
I didn't.
But then, you should enjoy it.
Your boyfriend paid for it.
-What?
-You sent my mom a text, right?
"Thank you, Aunt.
Thank you for the school lunch."
Did you actually think my mom paid for it?
What are you saying?
You're really startled, aren't you?
Sun-oh paid for it.
I didn't know he was that sweet.
To be honest, I thought he'd detest you
if he found out about your situation,
thinking you're beneath him.
But when I asked him to pay
for your school lunch, he did.
How much did you tell him?
I almost told him about Jeju Island,
but I didn't.
You know,
he's even paying for your school lunch.
If I told him everything, he'll probably
pay your college tuition as well.
Do you have to go this far?
Are you embarrassed?
Then go to Sun-oh and ask him.
Ask him why he paid for your lunch.
Ask him why he's treating you
like a beggar, and break up with him.
SUN-OH
JOJO
The person you're calling
is not available at the moment.
Why...
Why did you do it?
It...
It makes me feel so small.
I called your school.
I told them you'll leave school early
for a shoot.
Your dad will be there, so don't be late.
I never agreed to it.
If you're going to keep lazing around,
go back to the US.
That's just mean.
Get your makeup done before the shoot.
MISSED CALL FROM JOJO
SUN-OH
MISSED CALL FROM SUN-OH
I did nothing wrong.
I know I did nothing wrong, but...
Why aren't you picking up?
Did you have dinner?
TO BE DISCARDED
Jojo.
I'll ring your Love Alarm every day.
But why do I keep feeling...
so small?
Are you really not going to Jeju Island?
No.
It'll just be about
taking photos and drinking.
Your mom thinks you're going.
That just shows how little
she actually knows about me.
That's crazy.
Jojo is like a pigeon.
It's like she's pecking at Sun-oh's vomit.
-That's just gross. What's wrong with you?
-Gosh.
-How can she live like that?
-She's pitiful.
-Hey
-What?
-What did you say about Jojo?
What about Jojo?
It's just Gul-mi...
I mean, that's what everyone says.
That little...
Hey.
-Oh, gosh.
-What am I going to do?
I don't want this.
-Is it delicious?
-What is it?
It's tasty.
Tasty? It's too salty.
That's better than too bland.
Jang-go.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you everything.
I gave it some thought,
and I think I would've gotten mad too
if I were you.
I'm not mad.
Eat up, kids.
I just stopped liking you.
I heard you asked Sun-oh
to pay for your lunch.
Hey,
Sun-oh is--
What's going on?
Did you make up with Jojo?
No, it's not like that.
What about Sun-oh?
What?
You were talking about Sun-oh.
Well, he was going somewhere
with Gul-mi. He looked very serious.
I did it for you
so that you'd come to your senses.
You spread the false rumor for me?
She didn't say anything to you
even after she found out, did she?
See?
People like her only think
about how to mooch off us.
"People like her"?
Yes. Those who keep wanting for more.
That's why people like you and me...
should be wary of them.
Sun-oh.
I like you.
I did it because I like you.
Do you know why you like me?
Because I'm rich, my mom's an actress,
and I'm famous.
You like me because you want to use me.
It's not like that, Sun-oh.
-I really think we--
-Use me.
I'll tell others that I'm close to you.
Upload our picture on Instagram.
-Sun-oh.
-You're a trainee at MJ, right?
The CEO is my mom's friend.
I'll arrange a meeting for you.
Do whatever you want. Use me. In return...
never say "we" to me again.
You're so annoying.
Sun-oh.
Sun-oh, look at me.
It's my fault.
I should have asked you first.
I'm sorry.
Jojo.
Don't leave me.
You did nothing wrong.
I would have done the same.
You're a good boy.
How could you be so sweet?
It makes my heart ache.
Why did Sun-oh and Gul-mi fight?
-What?
-Don't you know? It's because of Jojo.
Why else?
That's crazy.
Did Sun-oh pay for her lunch?
-Isn't that great?
-Right?
-What is this?
-What's up?
-What is it?
-Is it Love Alarm?
-It's not mine.
-Whose is it?
-Is it you? Il-sik?
-Isn't it?
-Check yours, Il-sik.
-It's not me.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
-It is Il-sik's.
Who is it?
-Seriously?
-I'm jealous.
Il-sik's Love Alarm rang. Who rang it?
-Why doesn't mine ring?
-Who rang it?
Amazing.
Nice.
I'm so jealous.
What's wrong with you?
What do you mean?
You rang my Love Alarm.
Does it make you that mad?
Is that why you sent me the photo?
To separate me and Jojo?
I told you before.
It's because Jojo betrayed us.
Hey.
Don't ring my Love Alarm.
I can't control it.
Just don't.
It's not like...
I can ring yours back.
It's like we're having a feast.
-Mi-mi, do you often cook for your family?
-Isn't the shoot over yet?
-No. It's taking forever.
-Well...
I try to, as healthy food is important.
Right.
-I love all the food my wife cooks for me,
-That reporter.
-Isn't she so hot?
-but the best is oyster jeon.
-Oyster jeon.
-Is she even human?
How is she so pretty?
Actually, I found myself
not being able to turn my head
to this side.
He was a model for Seventeen, right?
A lot of fans want to know how you're
doing since you're not active these days.
He's focusing on studying these days.
I wonder how he feels though.
Eat up, Sun-oh.
I'm sure working as a model is
a lot more fun than studying.
I'll be honest.
He's very close to my ideal type.
Mom. I'll do it.
Take a seat.
What happened to your arm?
It's nothing.
Sit down.
Gosh, it must have hurt a lot.
It'll heal itself.
No, it won't. You need to treat it.
Okay. I'll put some ointment on it later.
Hye-yeong.
If it hurts, tell me that it does.
Okay.
Eat this.
Mi-mi, you were the best actress
at the time.
I can't imagine how hard
it must have been for you
to put your career on hold
at the peak of it.
Well, I didn't want to miss
a single moment...
of my son's growth.
Well...
shall we take a ten-minute break?
We'll take a break.
Don't cause trouble.
What more do you want?
Are you going to keep this up?
Shall I tell them everything?
Will you be okay? It'll go on the air.
Do you want me to tell them
what I remember?
What do you mean?
How much you found me annoying.
So much that you wanted me gone.
Hey, can you take Sun-oh?
Drink this.
Why didn't you tell me before?
I thought you wouldn't remember.
You wished that I wouldn't.
Don't act like a baby, please.
Let's just pretend to be a happy family.
Don't get greedy for more.
"Pretend"?
Do it properly, then.
Just...
Just say you're sorry. That's all I need.
Sun-oh, you did a good job.
I know, right? They're crazy.
I won't let them be.
Yes.
I'll report Sun-oh for bullying.
What?
I'll just say he pushed me and I got hurt.
SE-JIN
Don't mess with Sun-oh.
You can mess with me, but not him.
Both of you are just...
Do I look like a pushover to you?
Sun-oh feels so sorry for you.
Isn't it great?
This is your chance
to ask him for everything. Right?
The things you want to eat, have,
and do...
Ask for everything.
It's not that he feels sorry for me.
What?
He just wants to...
do those things for me.
You don't know what that feels like.
You're still so stuck up.
I get all you see is Sun-oh.
But when he realizes who you really are,
do you think he'll keep on seeing you?
What kind of person am I?
Is it...
Is it all my fault?
Whose fault is it, then?
Why do you think your mom was in debt?
It was because she had to raise you.
It's all your fault.
That's why you can't date Sun-oh.
You can't eat food that my mom paid for,
and you can't go on the school trip
either. Do you get it?
Hey!
Put that down.
Mom.
You really scare me.
You pretend to be so nice in front of me,
and yet you hit Gul-mi behind my back.
That's not it.
You're two-faced just like your mom.
Look what happened.
She pretended to be just fine,
and then died, leaving all the debt to me.
Aunt.
Still, she was your sister.
Exactly. She was my sister.
That's why I'm letting you stay here.
I...
What more can I do?
If you feel that wronged, get out.
-Aunt.
-Get out, just get out!
Grandma!
THE BEST FEELING IN THE WORLD
IS KNOWING THERE'S SOMEONE ON MY SIDE
LOVE ALARM PROVES THAT
YOU TRULY LIKE THAT PERSON.
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)