Say that again.
We're seniors now.
I want to focus on my studies.
So you're breaking up with me?
I'm exhausted.
And that has changed my feelings for you.
Let's end things here.
You said you liked me.
How can your feelings suddenly change?
I don't know,
but that's what happened.
There must be a reason.
How will I know if you don't tell me?
Don't talk to me from now on.
Go and eat somewhere else.
Will you go on being like this?
-I feel uncomfortable sitting with you.
-What's going on?
-Wait, what's going on?
-What's with them?
I just don't get it.
How can you not like me anymore?
What's going on?
-Were they together?
-I don't know.
Must I say it again...
in front of everyone?
I don't believe you.
It doesn't make sense.
Everyone, get out.
Get out of the ten-meter radius!
-Hwang Sun-oh.
-Didn't you hear me?
Everyone, leave, except for Jojo!
-Is he insane?
-Get out!
Hey, let's go. Let's get out.
Get the hell out!
Gosh, seriously.
-He'll cause a scene at this rate.
-Let's go.
LOVE ALARM
Turn on your Love Alarm.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
-Whose was it?
-Which one rang, his or hers?
-Did only one go off?
-I think so.
Only one of them?
-Did he get dumped?
-I'd be humiliated if I were him.
-This is mortifying.
-Wasn't it the other way around?
No way.
I can't believe it.
How can this be?
-He got dumped.
-That's amazing.
He's the only one in love.
-Gosh.
-Only his alarm rang.
How can this be?
I told you.
I don't like you.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Jojo.
Please love me again.
Please.
-He's doomed.
-He's such a loser.
-That's crazy.
-How will he manage to come to school now?
Sun-oh, where are you going?
My mom must've done something to her.
Hey.
Even if that's true,
you'll only make things worse for her.
So?
Am I supposed to stop seeing her
just like this?
That's not what I mean.
I just don't understand.
How can she change so suddenly?
Hey, Sun-oh.
GO SUN-I
Grandma.
You can't leave me.
If you do,
I'll really be all alone.
Does it show that I'm hiding here?
Most people don't stare at my face
like you do.
What?
You're already talking like me.
Thanks, Sun-oh.
Why are you following me?
You've been following me, right?
Why are you doing this?
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
This is the last time
I'm coming out to see you.
Do you remember this place?
I do.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Turn on your Love Alarm.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
How many times must we do this?
Tell me what I did wrong.
I won't do it anymore.
Sun-oh.
Do you like someone else?
That's not it.
I want to kiss you.
Don't say things like that.
I don't like you anymore.
Look at me.
Look at me!
How much time do you need?
It still feels like
you have feelings for me.
A kiss could bring back those emotions.
Just now,
I came within 9.99m of your lips.
Is it so hard for you
to move a centimeter forward?
You're heartless.
Never...
turn off your Love Alarm again.
And watch...
as my feelings for you change too.
Today's the 50th day
since Love Alarm was launched.
I ended my brief relationship...
with Sun-oh.
Sun-oh.
You dumped me.
No, I didn't dump you.
Then tell me.
Why did you do that to me back then?
Back then, I...
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Let's take another photo.
Time passed...
One, two, three.
...as if nothing had ever happened.
One thing that hasn't changed...
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
...is that Sun-oh...
I still...
ring Jojo's Love Alarm.
Jojo also...
still likes me back.
She likes me back.
So...
why?
THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
Sun-oh...
still rings my Love Alarm,
without knowing that the shield...
is blocking it.
Park Gul-mi.
I received a text that
three million won was transferred.
Yes, ma'am.
The transfer was made at 9:37 a.m. today
at an ATM of the Saebong branch.
I'LL TRANSFER THE MONEY TOMORROW MORNING
Your transaction is being processed.
The following amount
will be wired from your account.
Make sure
the receiver's account number is correct.
Your transaction is being processed.
I'll join the Badge Club.
They'll get to meet the developer.
Can't you only join when your Love Alarm
has been rung by a ton of people?
There's always a way.
The person you're calling
is not available at the moment.
12 DAYS LEFT UNTIL THE LAUNCH
OF LOVE ALARM 2.0
Gul-mi took my money.
And?
Gul-mi stole three million won from me.
Why are you here then?
-Go and talk to her.
-You know it's for my college tuition.
How could you say that?
You should've taken better care
of your precious money.
She's not my problem anymore,
so deal with it on your own.
Damn that girl.
Is something up?
KIM JOJO
IS SOMETHING UP?
You could've just...
asked me for the money.
As if you would've given it to me.
Do you really believe the money
will get you into the Badge Club?
Yes, if joining the Badge Club
gets me a chance to meet the developer
of Love Alarm, then I'll do anything.
What can the developer do for you anyway?
Are you kidding me?
Once I meet the developer,
I'll be able to escape
from this wretched place.
How can you be so sure?
The developer will acknowledge my talent!
I'll pay you back soon.
Once I'm in the Badge Club
and my online shopping site
-hits the jackpot--
-Gul-mi,
get your head out of the clouds.
-What?
-Just look at yourself right now.
Hey.
Do you think you're the only one
trying hard in life?
I've tried hard too.
For six years, I danced every day
at the crack of dawn
to debut as an idol singer.
I stayed at the studio the longest
to practice the same song again and again.
Stop acting like
you know everything about me.
All you want is easy fame.
Whether it's being a singer
or joining the Badge Club,
all you want is to get famous quickly
and live a cushy life.
What's so wrong with that?
Why don't you
take a look at yourself instead?
Instead of lecturing me,
look back on your own life.
You're still mooching off me and my mom.
What can be cushier than that?
You hate me, right?
Then leave.
What are you doing?
-Stop it.
-Let go. Damn!
Stop it.
Leave. Get out.
Just go.
Didn't you hear me?
I did.
I can't leave you
all alone like this, though.
It's fine. I don't feel alone.
That's because
you've felt alone for so long...
that you don't even realize
you feel that way.
And how do you know that?
You don't know me well enough to say so.
How can I not know...
when I see it all so clearly?
Have you been to the Han River
on a snowy day?
Go ahead and scream.
What?
Say whatever's bottled up inside.
But then you'll hear it all.
I won't.
So scream at the top of your lungs.
Can you hear me?
What was that?
You shouldn't have done that.
Just look at me.
I have no parents...
and now I'm all alone.
I feel so lonely.
Mom!
I don't want to work.
I don't want to take time off school.
I don't want to live with Aunt either.
Mom!
Still...
Still, I won't crumble.
I'll survive this!
And...
I'll find happiness!
I promise!
Hye-yeong, say what's on your mind too.
It's quite satisfying.
Kim Jojo!
SOMETHING I'VE BEEN HOLDING BACK
AND CAN ONLY SAY TO YOU
I like going to the cinema late at night.
There are fewer people,
so it's easier to focus on the movie.
I hear the night view
from Namsan is beautiful,
but I've never seen it,
even though I live in Seoul.
Wait, have you been on
a pirate ship ride in winter?
It's quite cold, but...
Hold on.
What are you trying to say?
I was wondering
how I could make you happy.
I'll get going. You should go too.
Jojo.
Thank you for being alive.
I'll think a bit more...
about what I can do to make you happy.
Hye-yeong!
Take this.
Thank you for today.
I'm only borrowing the money.
I'll pay you back.
Damn.
Thank you for being alive.
I'll think a bit more...
about what I can do to make you happy.
Someone who calls my name...
and thinks about...
how to make me happy.
MERRY CHRISTMAS
AREN'T YOU COMING TODAY?
Lee Hye-Yeong.
LEE HYE-YEONG
SAVE
Lee Hye-Yeong.
23,166 LIKES
Can you put that away during meals?
Damn it.
LEE HYE-YEONG
HAVE A GOOD DAY TODAY
Have a good day today.
You too.
Ma'am, I'll eat later.
Sure.
Aunt,
Gul-mi will pay 200,000 won every month
from now on.
What?
That's how you'll pay back what you stole.
Hey.
I told you, I'm just borrowing it.
Also, you'll watch the store for me
when I'm working at the wedding hall.
You'll do that until you pay me back.
Are you insane? Why would I do that?
Mom, what the hell is she saying?
Didn't you hear her?
You'll watch the store for her.
Mom.
I'll be going back to school
next semester.
-Do what you want.
-Mom! Seriously?
Damn it.
Mom, can we find
another place to live now?
Is that what you want?
Yes, we've been living there long enough.
Try this on.
Go on.
You can find another place.
I'm going to stay.
Why?
Why would I live with my full-grown son?
People will talk.
Gosh,
this looks good on you.
Let's buy this one.
We'll take this.
Sure thing.
Mom.
Won't you be lonely?
Hye-yeong,
do you know when the most exciting moment
in my life was?
It's when I kicked open the front gate
and left my old house
after yelling at my mom
that I didn't want to live like her.
Mom.
My heart...
pounded in excitement, and I thought
that I'd be able to do anything.
So don't you ever feel sorry.
You're my pride and joy.
Jojo, look at this.
What is it?
The representative of Anti-Love Alarm
will also be there.
It's like they're saying
they're embracing even their haters.
Unbelievable.
But why is the artist
of The Ringing World invited?
Out of curiosity, I guess.
The artwork is often mentioned
alongside Love Alarm.
If I knew this would happen,
I would've drawn something too.
The Trembling World. What do you think?
The Trembling World?
You tremble at the sight
of the person you like.
You start trembling if that person
comes within a ten-meter radius.
Gosh. Am I a genius or what?
LOVE ALARM HAS SENT YOU A TEXT
ARTIST OF THE RINGING WORLD,
YOU ARE INVITED AS A SPECIAL GUEST
TO THE LOVE ALARM 2.0 PRESENTATION.
DATE: JANUARY 8, 2023
THE ALARM
What are you doing here?
I'm heading to Busan
to sort out my things.
I dropped by before I left.
Get going then.
I...
don't have the time or intention
to date anyone,
-so forget about me and--
-You don't have to like me back...
just because I like you.
How's that fair to you?
-Just receiving your love--
-I just...
wanted you to know how I feel.
THE ALARM
I hope the new Love Alarm feature
is something that lets me know
how many times I rang your Love Alarm.
What should we wear
to the Love Alarm 2.0 presentation?
There's only about a week left now.
Do you have a theme in mind?
Should we just go back to the US?
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
It's just that I'm bored with everything.
I'm not interested in that event either.
The movie will be starting soon.
Then we won't go.
We don't have to go
to the Love Alarm presentation.
I don't like what you don't like.
Actually,
I deleted Love Alarm a long time ago.
It scared me, you see.
I thought it would complicate things
if I kept ringing your Love Alarm.
I should've just let it ring though.
I should've told you how I felt.
Not being able to see you
made me realize that.
So I made up my mind.
I promised myself
that I'd ring your Love Alarm...
if we met again someday.
Hye-yeong.
I...
My Love Alarm can't ring...
anyone else's.
Can I ring...
your Love Alarm?
Wearing cream-colored clothes
underneath in winter
makes your style a lot more fashionable.
Also, it's prettier
with a pair of wide pants.
THIS IS BORING
LET'S SEE HOW FIT YOU ARE
TAKE YOUR CLOTHES OFF
Why should I take my clothes off?
Also, I didn't get plastic surgery.
Stop spreading lies.
I'm not doing this
to beg for your donations.
YOU'D NEVER GET DONATIONS
WHY ARE YOU SUDDENLY SHOUTING?
TARGET DONATION
30,000 REMAINING
I think...
I've been scammed
out of three million won.
No one answers when I call that number.
If I came from a wealthy family,
I'd have easily become an idol singer.
Maybe it's because
my complexion is too dark.
I have no luck.
You know,
I want to join the Badge Club too.
I want to meet
the developer of Love Alarm too.
Please help me.
LUVMIKNIGHT IS SENDING
3,000 DONATIONS
9 DAYS LEFT UNTIL THE LAUNCH
OF LOVE ALARM 2.0
Actually,
I deleted Love Alarm a long time ago.
It scared me, you see.
I thought it would complicate things
if I kept ringing your Love Alarm.
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
You haven't changed one bit.
You just won't tell me anything.
Let's meet up at the schoolyard
at 4:00 p.m.
I'll be waiting.
When is he leaving?
He left right after lunch.
It's not like internships pay much.
So how much is the rent
for studio apartments these days?
Why do you ask? Are you kicking me out?
I never said it was you.
Hye-yeong's the one moving out.
What?
Hye-yeong said he'd tell you.
His work is too far from here.
WHEN LOVE ALARM RINGS, EITHER YOU
OR THE PERSON WHO LIKES YOU IS MOVING.
ONE PERSON CAN RING
YOUR LOVE ALARM CONTINUOUSLY
IF THAT PERSON CONTINUES
TO GO IN AND OUT OF THE 10M RADIUS.
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)