Mom!
Grandma!
CHARCOAL BBQ
HYE-YEONG
Most people don't stare at my face
like you do.
What?
You're already talking like me.
Gosh, who's talking so loudly?
-Stop being so loud.
-What on earth?
When I first saw you,
I thought you were someone
who had loving parents
and a great childhood...
because you seemed so cheerful.
I like it when people tell me...
that I seem cheerful.
Since my parents passed away
on Jeju Island,
I've been emotionally hurt so many times.
Every time I feel hurt,
I consciously try to be more cheerful.
I smile more and study harder...
to make sure I never lose my true self.
From now on, tell me
whenever anyone hurts your feelings.
Don't worry.
I'll continue...
to stay cheerful and strong.
Jojo.
Let's be together starting Monday,
just the two of us.
Are you really not going to go
on the school trip?
Don't even think of spending time
away from me for three days.
Aren't you going to ask why I'm not going?
You can tell me when you want to.
Tell me everything later.
What shall we do together?
Where do you want to go?
What shall we do?
Let's go.
-What?
-Let's go on the school trip.
-No, you don't need to do that for me--
-It's okay.
I don't mind going if I can be with you.
Sun-oh.
Ring my Love Alarm.
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
-Stand there.
-It's weird.
-Gosh, I'm so jealous.
-Come on.
One, two, three.
-Are you okay holding hands in public?
-Yes. I don't care anymore.
When did you come to Seoul?
I came after my grandma got sick.
-I think it was about four years ago.
-I see.
What do you think?
Has this place changed a lot?
I'm not sure.
But the breeze still feels the same.
I'm glad we didn't meet four years ago.
What?
Back then, I had so many pimples.
So? I think you still would've
looked cute.
No, you definitely would've
made fun of me.
Show me a photo next time, okay?
This feels so strange.
You make me want to tell you everything,
including all the little things.
-Why are you suddenly acting all shy?
-Because you're staring at me like that.
Thank you, Sun-oh.
-Hey, wait for me!
-This is so fun.
-What's this?
-Someone's Love Alarm went off.
-My Love Alarm went off.
-What?
-Unbelievable.
-Who rang it?
-It's ringing.
-Should I also get a haircut?
Congratulations.
My gosh.
I thought Jojo wasn't going to come.
-Exactly.
-Everyone, gather here.
-But she's here.
-Hurry up!
Duk-gu.
-Hey.
-This is your spot.
-Gosh, hey.
-What's wrong with you?
Do you want to die?
-Everyone, stop chatting.
-Shoot.
Okay, stand properly.
Make sure we can see all your faces.
-Make sure you're all in.
-Gosh.
Don't blink.
-Shoot.
-Smile, everyone.
One, two, three.
One more time.
-One more time.
-Come on, let's just go.
One, two, three.
Let's go!
She's the only one like this.
Wait, you guys.
You must be crazy.
Ta-da. I prepared this for you guys.
What do you think? Isn't it cute?
-Gosh, no way.
-What?
-Are you going to wear this on stage?
-What is this?
Did we seriously buy this?
Of course.
-Hey, try it on.
-Why does it have to be pink?
-Go ahead and wear this.
-Gosh, forget it.
This is ridiculous.
This stands out way too much.
It's cold.
Let me try it on.
-Try it on. Hurry.
-It'll go well with your skirt.
No way.
I've been wanting to talk to you.
Do you want to know Jojo's secret?
What are you going to wear?
-This. Cool, right?
-What's left? What are you wearing?
-I'm going to wear this.
-This one looks nice.
-Hey.
-What's this?
-No, wait.
-You jerk. You're crazy.
To be honest, I'm really grateful.
I really am.
But look at him smiling.
It's getting on my nerves.
-What's with him?
-His Love Alarm went off on the bus.
-Let's just ignore him and drink this.
-My gosh.
Hey, Sun-oh.
His Love Alarm went off three times.
Why is yours so quiet?
I turned it off because it kept ringing.
-He's so annoying.
-Gosh.
He's making me feel so sad.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you're Sun-oh's best friend.
So,
you want me to pass it on to him?
I like Sun-oh.
How do you expect me to stay quiet
when I know what Jojo is really like?
What's wrong with surviving?
Are you serious?
She left her mom and dad--
They shouldn't have put a child
in that situation.
Jojo did nothing wrong.
YEOLRIM HIGH SCHOOL TRIP
Gosh, they're so loud.
My ears are ringing.
Aren't they so good?
I don't know. I didn't pay attention.
Let's go back inside soon.
Our class is next.
Gosh, it's so boring.
I don't want to watch it.
Why are you outside?
I just needed some air.
Hey, you know Hye-yeong, right?
Yes, he's your friend.
What's with the introduction?
I'll head inside, then.
Hey, let me explain--
You are...
You are really horrible.
-Gul-mi--
-Don't say my name.
The thing is, I just...
You just looked so pretty, so I...
I wasn't going to share it with anyone.
Why would you film a video?
I just hate the fact
that you took a video of me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
Can you please just get out of my sight?
Do you hate me that much?
Yes.
Did you see what the others did to me
when we took the group photo?
They did that because you rang
my Love Alarm.
Do you know how I feel
every time that happens?
I'm sick of you and the sound of you
ringing my Love Alarm.
Why does that thing even exist?
I'm sorry.
Don't ever...
show up in front of me again.
Duk-gu.
-The color's pretty, right?
-A bit more.
-It looks nice on you.
-It's so pretty.
-Does this look nice?
-Isn't it pretty? I bought it.
-Yes, it's pretty.
-Snacks...
-It looks better down.
-We should've bought more snacks.
Let's bring them now.
How's this?
Be careful.
Make sure they don't drop.
-Be careful, okay?
-Don't drop them.
Good job.
Are they cold?
-Yes, totally.
-Nice.
-We should've bought more.
-They'll bring some.
-Didn't we leave the door open?
-Yes, we did.
Hey.
What's this?
-Are you guys ready?
-One, two, three. There.
You said it was only going to be the guys
from class five.
You're friends with Il-sik.
So I asked Seong-jun to bring him along.
Good thinking, right?
It wasn't me!
-Hey.
-Seriously, it wasn't me.
-Have you got your hopes up?
-Look at this.
Are we going to play
a game of truth using Love Alarm?
I'm so excited.
-Hey.
-Am I getting ahead of myself?
Ji-yeon, you start.
Okay, then.
Let's turn it on and show it
on the count of three.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Let's go.
-What's this?
-His alarm went off.
That's cheating.
His alarm went off, too.
-Hey.
-Hey, that's cheating.
Are you here to show off?
Stop overreacting.
-You're being so annoying.
-Why didn't you show yours?
-That's fishy.
-You didn't turn it on.
Il-sik didn't show his cell phone either.
What's with you guys?
Why aren't you guys showing us?
What does that make us?
-Exactly. That's not fair.
-You're unbelievable.
Is it because the other person
might find out?
What are you talking about?
No way. Do you like Il-sik?
-What?
-Does Jang-go like Il-sik?
-Go on a date!
-Cut the crap!
Okay, we're sorry.
-He's drunk.
-We're just kidding.
Don't be like that.
-I'm going to have more.
-I told you I didn't want to do this.
-What's wrong with her?
-I bet she's hiding something.
Seriously?
Really?
Gosh, did you drink a lot?
Forget about her. Let's have fun.
Jang-go.
-Jang-go.
-Let me go. I don't want to talk to you.
Why didn't you tell me
that you like Il-sik?
Why?
So you could let me date him?
But then again, you easily
date and break up with guys.
How can you say that?
Isn't that why you were kissing a guy
you barely knew in the alleyway?
I couldn't believe my eyes
as I took that photo.
You were the one...
who took that photo?
Yes.
I took that photo.
How could you do that to me?
Because I like Il-sik.
Is the person you like
in this room or not?
I'm sleepy.
-Gosh, cut the bullshit.
-Hey, drink up.
Don't be like that.
-Drink up.
-Don't be like that.
-Wait. What's this?
-Just answer the question.
-Just drink.
-Don't do that. You're disappointing me.
If you lie,
you'll be single for three years.
-That's right.
-If you don't answer,
-you have to drink.
-That's right.
Okay, then.
Hey, move! Get up!
Where's the fire extinguisher?
-Hey, get up!
-Fire!
-The fire extinguisher!
-Get up!
Move!
Jojo.
-We need to get out.
-Jojo, what's wrong?
We'll die!
Jojo!
-Did she have a seizure or what?
-I don't know.
Gosh.
Gosh, that was scary.
I'm getting goose bumps.
Are you okay?
Sun-oh.
I'm not okay.
This is so hard for me.
I can't breathe.
I want to get out of here.
Sun-oh.
There's a place I want to go to.
It's been ages since I last came here.
Did you come here often?
Goodness.
Goodness me...
Kind of.
I used to come here sometimes...
whenever I got a low test score.
It's my first time smelling the sea here.
I thought you came here often.
Whenever I came with my parents,
we were either in the car
or at the hotel.
I never wanted to come,
but they brought me here,
always left me alone,
and thought of me as a bother.
They pretended to love me
only when other people were around.
I'm sorry.
I whined too much, didn't I?
No.
I like hearing you talk.
I've told you all my secrets now.
Thank you, Sun-oh.
Sun-oh...
SAE BITT HOSPITAL
Sun-oh, listen to me.
Every time we met, my heart fluttered.
Every moment felt precious.
And you made me feel unbelievably happy.
So I didn't want to let you go.
Because I felt like I would never...
be able to hold onto you again
if I let you go now.
I'll tell everyone.
Jeju Island.
What you did in Jeju Island...
How your mom and dad...
Should I have died then?
Are you saying I should have died then?
But, Sun-oh...
maybe I was here all along
from the very beginning.
I might still be...
locked up in that room...
sound asleep.
Mom!
Mom...
I might have...
just dreamt that I met you.
So, Sun-oh,
please wake up.
Wake up, Sun-oh.
Hello, this is Han Ye-ri's Cinema Heaven.
We started off with a sound
that makes us feel happy.
Recently, Professor Lee Hyeong-jun
of SNU announced
that Love Alarm's alarm sound
actually plays a role
in treating depression.
And the fact that over ten million people
watched The Alarm,
a movie about Love Alarm,
is probably due to the positive effects
of Love Alarm's alarm sound.
Here's a soundtrack song from The Alarm.
It's Bigman's "Love Alarm."
SOUNDTRACK FROM THE ALARM
LOVE ALARM-RELATED BEST SELLERS
SPECIAL EVENT
LOVE ALARM GOLDEN TIME
ALARM TECHNIQUES
HOW TO BECOME RICH WITH HEARTS
We're holding an event to celebrate
the fourth anniversary of Love Alarm!
We have call plans for couples!
Come inside and ring your Love Alarm.
-You have to pat your lips like this...
-Is my Love Alarm even working?
I think it's dead.
You're so pretty! Flash!
Hello, we're Flash.
We oppose Love Alarm!
We oppose!
Last but not least, may your lives
be filled with happiness.
Now, would the bride and the groom
please turn around and face the guests?
You can turn around now.
Let's check to see
if they truly love each other
before they walk down the aisle.
Please give the bride and groom
their cell phones.
I'd like all the guests to turn off
their Love Alarms.
Okay, everyone.
The bride and the groom
are the only ones...
-Please. I hope only one rings.
-...who can ring their alarms.
-Let's all count to...
-Why?
-...three together.
-The groom is totally my type.
-Come on.
-One.
-Two. Three.
Everyone, their alarms went off!
Let's bless the married couple
with a round of applause!
Everyone, the bride and the groom
confirmed their love
through Love Alarm.
Let's give them another round of applause.
Congratulations!
-One, two.
I'm back.
I checked the money you wired.
You wired 100,000 won less.
I'm returning to school next semester.
Goodness.
Why would you live a hard life
by going to college?
If you didn't go to college
and just got a job,
you could have given me more money
and paid off your debt.
I'm looking for another part-time job.
Gosh.
You still have to do everything
you want to do, don't you?
-I packed the underskirt.
-Okay.
The underpants, traditional socks, shoes,
the bride's bag, and her skirt and jacket.
Did you check everything?
-Yes.
-I'll wrap them for you.
BALANCE: 3,850,402 WON
THIS CHRISTMAS,
DECLARE YOUR LOVE WITH LOVE ALARM
Mom. What's that?
-What? What's that?
-What's that? Look at that.
That's so pretty.
That's so big.
-What is it? Love Alarm's Christmas event?
-Wow, it's so cool.
It looks so pretty.
-What's that?
-Isn't it pretty?
Yes, it is.
-Do you want a photo?
-Yes.
-It's pretty. It's huge.
-I know, right? Yes.
That's so cool.
It's so pretty.
My gosh.
That's amazing.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
LOVE ALARM
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Sun-oh.
Sun-oh!
The person you're calling
is not available at the moment.
You will be directed to voicemail
after the beep.
SUN-OH
Sun-oh, I'm at the hospital,
but I can't find you anywhere.
Where are you?
I heard you went back to Seoul.
Are you okay?
How are you feeling? It hurts, doesn't it?
Call me as soon as you turn on the phone.
Is Sun-oh absent again?
Gosh, he must've gotten seriously injured.
I knew he'd get in trouble
because of Jojo.
"Because of Jojo"?
She acted all weird on Jeju Island.
That accident happened
because he kept spending time with her.
Are you serious?
How is that because of Jojo?
Answer me. How is that because of Jojo?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I asked
because I was just curious.
So he didn't come to school.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I only got hurt a little.
Have you seen Sun-oh by any chance?
Ever since his parents came to the ER,
I haven't been able to get hold of him.
He just got discharged,
so things are probably hectic for him.
By any chance,
can you tell me his address?
Give me your cell phone.
What does it mean to like someone?
The person you're calling
is not available at the moment.
You will be directed to voicemail
after the beep.
I thought liking someone...
would be...
something nice and pretty.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
CALL ME AS SOON AS YOU TURN ON THE PHONE
Jojo!
What? Oh, here you go.
I love you.
Every day, I feel as if
I'm fighting a war against myself.
Do you regret...
ringing Sun-oh's Love Alarm?
I'm scared.
I only want Sun-oh to see my good side.
But I keep overthinking things.
Once you start having feelings
for someone, it's hard to turn back.
Do you still like Gul-mi?
She's the first girl I ever liked.
I've never seen anyone as pretty as her.
And it was my first time
wanting to tell someone how I felt.
But of course,
she was also the first person
who hated me that much.
I don't want you to be heartbroken
like I was.
CHON DUK-GU HAS SENT YOU A PHOTO
YOUR CRUSH'S LOVE ALARM WON'T RING
EVEN IF YOUR LOVE ALARM IS ON.
There's no other shield like this
in the entire world.
I figured you might need it.
Take care, Jojo.
SHIELD. YOUR CRUSH'S LOVE ALARM WON'T RING
EVEN IF YOUR LOVE ALARM IS ON.
THERE'S NO OTHER SHIELD LIKE THIS
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
THE WEIGHT OF AFFECTION
Sun-oh's parents are not here.
Can you come now?
Hye-yeong.
Come in.
I'll forgive you
for canceling today's schedule.
But you must come to Hope Orphanage
by 1:00 p.m. tomorrow.
-I'm tired.
-The election is right around the corner.
Tell Sun-oh to upload a family photo
on his social media.
Fine.
If Sun-oh keeps on being useless,
just send him back to the US.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell him to call you.
You should go home for now.
Back then,
I felt smaller the more I liked Sun-oh.
And every day...
I became scared of losing him.
LOVE ALARM
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I don't want you to be heartbroken
like I was.
24 DAYS LEFT UNTIL THE RELEASE
OF LOVE ALARM 2.0
Come in.
Have you sorted out your dorm?
I have to go a few more times.
Why are you going all the way to Busan
when you got into a college in Seoul?
It's so far away.
You already care for so many people.
I want to unburden you a bit.
Thank you for this.
Is it sweet?
Yes, try one.
THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
THE GRAVE OF THE RINGING WORLD
I LOVE THESE DRAWINGS
I CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF THEM
4,019 USERS LOVE HWANG SUN-OH
WELCOME TO THE LOVE ALARM BADGE CLUB
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Why is it so hard to see you?
I might as well go back to the US.
I came outside for a run.
Why are you running out in the cold?
It's not cold if you run.
Gosh.
So how long are you going to run for?
Honey, you look great,
but take one step back.
-Back?
-Yes, just one step.
-Okay.
-What?
Why are there so many cell phones?
-What is it?
-Goodness.
Look.
Honey, what is this? I'm so scared.
Oh, my gosh.
My goodness, what should we do?
There are bodies here.
Please come quickly.
I think I smell gas.
Call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance! Hurry!
So many people are dead here.
Hye-yeong.
What happened?
Call an ambulance!
-I think I smell gas.
-Hye-yeong.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Today's the 1,534th day
since Love Alarm was launched.
It's a world where you can't hide
your feelings of loneliness.
THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
LOVE ALARM ONLY GIVES OUT BADGES TO
THE SELECT FEW THEY HAVE CHOSEN
AND CALLS THIS GROUP
THE LOVE ALARM BADGE CLUB.
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)