THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
RECEPTION ROOM
What are you looking at?
What?
The Ringing World.
A lot of people follow this account.
It's super popular these days.
The illustrations and writings are nice.
This is from Congressman Hwang Jae-cheol.
-Thank you.
Yes, sir.
I just dropped it off.
I'll leave right away.
Yes, sir.
By the way, why are there
so many comments on this one?
THE GRAVE OF THE RINGING WORLD
DID THE ARTIST FORESEE
THE HWAYEONG PARK CASE?
"The Hwayeong Park case"?
Hwayeong Park?
What happened there?
I'm not sure.
23 BODIES FOUND AT HWAYEONG PARK
Earlier today at around 12:35 p.m.,
twenty-three bodies were found
along Trail Five at Hwayeong Park,
-which has utterly shocked the public.
-Over 20?
According to the witnesses at the park,
there were no survivors.
And the deceased's phones were gathered
in one spot near the bodies.
The cause of death
hasn't been determined yet.
The police have stated
that the deceased had created a group chat
called Love Alarm Zero to criticize
the app Love Alarm--
Stop watching it.
Dinner's ready.
Okay.
You don't have to eat
if you don't feel like it.
I'm fine.
Ma'am.
Eat with us.
I'll eat later. Eat up.
Having no one ring your Love Alarm
isn't a big deal. Why take your life?
Young people these days are so weak.
Do you have to talk like that?
I mean, people died.
Nobody told them to die.
It was their choice.
-But 23 people--
-I heard you got an internship.
Which company?
MK Group.
I see.
Buy more stocks.
They've got a government-funded project
for next year.
Hey,
-let's go out.
-Sun-oh.
Why are you sitting here
if you can't even eat?
These folks don't even care
about how shocked you are.
I'm sorry.
I would've taken my own life too.
Can you imagine your Love Alarm
not going off at all your whole life?
It might have.
What?
Maybe not now,
but it might have rung later on
if they had decided to live.
What if it never rings though?
You see,
even if no one ever rings mine,
being able to ring Love Alarm
for the person I like...
will make me happy.
Goodness.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
Hey, let's get out of here. Get ready.
Stop looking it up.
Here.
I wonder about their lives.
Those people who died.
I'm sure they were born
with blessings from their families.
Hey, stop thinking about it.
It'll just upset you.
Hey, Sun-oh! Hye-yeong!
Guys, it's freezing outside.
Today,
we're going to drink every bottle of booze
they have here, okay?
Got it?
I have to go.
You're leaving?
For real?
Hey, I just got here.
Is he really taking off?
Hey, Sun-oh.
Hey, dude!
What the...
He always does
whatever the heck he wants to do.
Oh, right.
I saw that girl
at a wedding earlier today.
What?
You know, that girl.
The girl with long hair.
The girl you both had a crush on.
Kim Jojo?
Yes, Kim Jojo.
I remember she had a unique name.
Well, what was she doing at the wedding?
That I don't know.
You know what though?
I might have been mistaken.
Darn it. We're out of booze.
MASS SUICIDE AT HWAYEONG PARK
POLICE INVESTIGATION RESULTS
TO BE ANNOUNCED THIS WEEK
Hey, Jojo.
-I guess you missed your grandma.
-Yes.
This is for you.
You really don't need to do this.
My grandma was always so grateful to you.
Spend some time with your friends
on your days off, okay?
Okay.
Happy New Year.
Thanks. Same to you.
THE RINGING WORLD BY ??
POSTING
LIVING AS SOMEONE
WHO CAN'T RING IN THE RINGING WORLD
Does this place look nice?
Yes.
When I launch a menswear line next spring,
you'll have to be our model.
-We'll see about that.
-Gosh.
Sun-oh, let me take a photo of you.
Well...
Go stand over there.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
One, two, three.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I wanted to take you out
for something really nice,
but Congressman Hwang
is always so busy at the end of the year.
-Oh, Min-jae.
-Yes?
-The other day, you said you saw Jojo...
-We'll announce the investigation results.
-...at a wedding.
-Yes.
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency
has formed a special task force
dedicated to the Hwayeong Park
mass suicide case
and thoroughly investigated
why the incident took place.
The autopsies, which were carried out
to determine the exact cause of death,
revealed that they overdosed
on a poisonous substance.
The victims were all in their 20s or 30s.
Thus, we have concluded
that they committed suicide together
due to the stress caused by
the unemployment crisis, and therefore,
-we have decided to close the case.
-Hey.
-Who's going to believe that?
-Now, we'll take questions.
Everyone knows they died
because no one ever rang their Love Alarm.
They should've just deleted the app, then.
Why take it to heart
and take their own lives?
I guess they didn't think
deleting the app could be a solution.
But why do you think...
they died in the park?
I mean, it's so cold.
I guess they wanted to tell the world
in their final moments
that they existed.
Come on. Even so,
committing suicide is simply wrong.
I mean, what about their families?
INGEOPPANG
Give me 2,000 won.
I'll be right back.
MR. HWANG SUN-OH, YOU'RE INVITED TO
THE LOVE ALARM 2.0 LAUNCHING PRESENTATION
AS A SPECIAL GUEST.
DATE: JANUARY 8, 2023
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
It's hot.
Here.
Thanks.
How about we delete Love Alarm?
-Why?
-Well,
we don't really need it.
I don't want to.
I like it when your Love Alarm goes off.
Yuk-jo.
I know you can't ring my Love Alarm,
but it's not because you don't love me.
You're 99.999 percent there.
It's just missing a tiny bit,
exactly 0.001 percent.
So you don't need to feel bad.
I'll be better to you.
Do you want some?
I'm a little depressed.
Why? Did something happen?
My grown-up son is stuck at home
on Christmas Eve.
Christmas happens every year.
But this Christmas is different
from next year's.
Every day is a different day, you know.
Do what you like
and live every day to the fullest.
Don't hold back.
Good night.
What about you, Mom?
Are you living like that yourself?
I'm doing what I like to do,
which is looking after you.
Sweet dreams.
Today's number one trending keyword
is "Love Alarm 2.0."
Last night, Love Alarm C&C
announced that there will be
an extensive update
for the first time since the app's launch.
The new features will be revealed
at the Love Alarm 2.0 launching
presentation on January 8...
Jeez, enough about Love Alarm.
What's the big deal?
Take the food on the table to Gul-mi.
She wants to eat downstairs.
Okay.
I'll begin my live broadcast now.
Ta-da! Hello, everyone.
Welcome to BJ Gul-mi's
awesome shopping mall, Love Mi.
Today, I'll be recommending the most
flattering color for your complexion
based on your undertone,
which can be either warm or cold.
All right. If you have warm undertones,
how about a warm color like this?
Yellow is one of the best colors
for warm undertones.
Now, if you have cool undertones...
Ta-da!
Blue is the best color, without a doubt.
A versatile shirt like this
goes with anything, you know.
This shirt and this blouse.
They're both available on Love Mi.
What? Can't you see that I'm practicing?
Jeez. Didn't you ask me
to bring your food down?
Hey, I want to see it too.
See what? Cut it out.
I heard Yuk-jo opened a shop in Hongdae.
She's even going to the launch event.
Will I ever catch up with her?
Gosh, I have to join
the Love Alarm Badge Club soon.
I guess you know her.
Lee Yuk-jo.
She's Hwang Sun-oh's girlfriend.
I heard they met in the States.
Bring the tray back when you're done.
Hey! Don't forget that you have to watch
the convenience store this evening.
Sun-oh!
LEE YUK-JO
LEE YUK-JO, ENTREPRENEUR
COMPANY: LOVE JO (CEO)
IMAGES
Look at the camera!
Perfect.
Now, strike a pose for me!
Great!
Now, I want you to look bubbly. Nice!
That's great.
That's it.
-Thank you for everything.
-Thank you.
Great job today.
Everyone is already
at the Badge Club House.
Too bad.
I was hoping it'd just be the two of us.
It looks like we'll have to
hang out with them today.
Why do you care about
the Badge Club members?
Let's just call Hye-yeong
and chill together.
We'll even spend Christmas with him?
Do you want to go there?
Yes.
All right, then.
Let's go.
Hi, Jojo.
Do you remember me?
I was waiting...
What?
I was waiting for you.
I got to see you,
so I guess I'll get going.
I'll see you around.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
3,276 USERS LOVE LEE YUK-JO
4,038 USERS LOVE HWANG SUN-OH
Yuk-jo!
Hey, how have you been?
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for you.
-Go ahead, Sun-oh. I'll meet you upstairs.
-Okay.
Sun-oh.
My gosh,
Hye-yeong went to the library today.
Wow, going to the library on Christmas?
He's like a pervert, don't you think?
This isn't good.
I should set him up with someone.
Why would you do that?
Because you keep talking about him
even when you're with me.
What's his type?
I'm not sure.
We don't talk about those things.
Really? Don't guys talk about girls?
I'm sure you've at least seen his crushes.
Actually, no.
I've never seen any.
ENTER YOUR MESSAGE
Gosh.
HI, IT'S ME, LEE HYE
IT'S COLD OUTSIDE
Jeez.
Come in.
Hye-yeong, dinner's ready.
Okay, great.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, JOJO
Hey, pay for it first.
Jeez, unbelievable.
What now?
That courier guy who comes every day.
Damn it!
That loser rang my Love Alarm just now.
Oh, that guy with the kind face?
He always has a smile on his face.
Do you look down on me too?
-What?
-Do I look like a joke to you?
Cut it out.
I couldn't debut or get into college.
You look down on me
because I'm just stuck in the basement
trying to become a content creator.
Do you seriously think
a courier guy is good enough for me?
Then what kind of guy
is good enough for you?
I'd say the developer of Love Alarm?
Then I'd consider it.
Hey, how are you even going
to meet that man?
I'll join the Badge Club.
They'll get to meet the developer.
Can't you only join when your Love Alarm
has been rung by a ton of people?
There's always a way.
Hye-yeong.
Hey, Sun-oh.
Hye-yeong went out.
This early?
Where did he go?
Take this seat.
No, it's okay.
Hey, wait...
Here.
What is this about?
Have some coffee.
That's not what I was asking.
You saved a seat for me and got me coffee.
What is all this about?
I texted you too.
That was from you?
Seriously, why are you being like this?
You really don't know the answer?
I'm hitting on you.
This is what people used to do
before Love Alarm was launched.
When someone saves a seat for you
and buys you coffee,
you'd stay up all night wondering
if that guy has a crush on you.
Hey, Hye-yeong.
You remember my name.
I want to try this
the old-school way without Love Alarm.
I can keep coming here
until my internship starts.
Take that time and think about...
how you feel about me.
LIVING AS SOMEONE
WHO CAN'T RING IN THE RINGING WORLD
Hey, you're back.
Hey.
Why did you go to the library
all dressed up?
Because I wanted to impress someone.
What? Who is it?
No way.
Not her, right?
It is her, Kim Jojo.
Do you still have feelings for her?
-No.
-I still have feelings for her.
So, I'll figure out what to do about it.
Hey, you know what Jojo did to me.
Don't you remember?
How can this be?
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I told you.
I don't like you.
How much time do you need?
It still feels like
you have feelings for me.
INCOMING CALL: YUK-JO
Hey.
Sun-oh, are you on your way?
Yes.
I'll call you when I get there.
Okay, sure. Drive safely.
I want to try this
the old-school way without Love Alarm.
I can keep coming here
until my internship starts.
Take that time and think about
how you feel about me.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Hye-yeong wasn't lying.
Sun-oh.
Stay away from Hye-yeong.
I can't see him getting his heart broken.
What did I do?
You dumped me.
No, I didn't dump you.
Then tell me.
Why did you do that to me back then?
Back then, I...
See?
You haven't changed one bit.
You just won't tell me anything.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't apologize.
I thought of all sorts of scenarios
to hate or to understand you.
"I must've done something wrong.
There must've been a reason
why she had to leave me."
So, stay away from Hye-yeong.
Sun-oh.
I'm not okay.
This is so hard for me.
-Jojo, what's wrong?
-We'll die!
-Did she have a seizure or what?
-I knew Jojo would get him in trouble.
"Because of Jojo"?
-She acted all weird on Jeju Island.
-That was scary.
-That accident happened...
-That's freaky.
-because he kept spending time with her.
-Sun-oh.
Have you seen Sun-oh by any chance?
Ever since his parents came to the ER,
I haven't been able to get hold of him.
If Sun-oh keeps on being useless,
just send him back to the US.
FROM CHON DUK-GU
There's no other shield like this
in the entire world.
I figured you might need it.
Every day, I feel as if
I'm fighting a war against myself.
Do you regret...
ringing Sun-oh's Love Alarm?
I'm scared.
THERE'S NO OTHER SHIELD LIKE THIS
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
YOUR CRUSH'S LOVE ALARM WON'T RING
EVEN IF YOUR LOVE ALARM IS ON.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO ACTIVATE THE SHIELD?
CANCEL
CONTINUE
I don't want you to be heartbroken
like I was.
Right, this is for you.
Thanks.
I wanted to make sure you could meet him.
I'm sorry.
I think some people...
take pleasure
in the misfortune of others.
Don't take what others are saying
to heart.
Thanks for taking my side.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Did you enjoy your food?
-The meat was exceptional.
-Great, thank you. Take care.
-Yes, thank you for the great food.
Pack up your stuff and leave.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll never miss any shifts again.
I couldn't call you because--
Don't you see the new part-timer there?
-My gosh, hello.
-Oh, hello.
I guess you're here for a team dinner.
-Hello.
-Over there.
I like it when people tell me...
that I seem cheerful.
Since my parents passed away
on Jeju Island,
I've been emotionally hurt many times.
Every time I feel hurt,
I consciously try to be more cheerful.
I smile more and study harder...
to make sure I never lose my true self.
From now on, tell me
whenever anyone hurts your feelings.
Don't worry.
I'll continue...
to stay cheerful and strong.
You're real.
Of course I'm real.
Sorry you couldn't get hold of me.
It must've hurt a lot.
My face is okay though.
I can go back to school now.
Good.
What's with that reaction?
I thought you'd be stoked.
I am.
So go home and get some rest now.
No.
I want to keep admiring your beauty.
I couldn't see you for a few days.
Get going now.
All right.
I'll call you.
Okay.
Sun-oh!
I like you!
Sun-oh.
It's not because I don't like you.
I'm just scared.
There's a long road ahead of me.
But I'm just too weak.
That's why...
That's why I'm leaving you behind, Sun-oh.
When will Sun-oh come back to school?
See? I told you not to go to Jeju Island.
Enough.
Does Sun-oh know
that your mom and dad tried to kill you?
Don't ever bring him up again.
Why not?
Who are you to tell me what not to do?
And stop being so disrespectful to me.
Make sure you check
the cigarette inventory.
IF YOU'RE IN LOVE, RING THE ALARM
The only way I could leave you behind...
is for me to stop this.
CHON DUK-GU
THERE'S NO OTHER SHIELD LIKE THIS
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
I FIGURED YOU MIGHT NEED IT.
Your crush's Love Alarm won't ring...
even if your Love Alarm is on.
Would you like to activate the shield?
CANCEL
CONTINUE
Once you activate the shield,
only the developer can remove it.
Would you still like to continue?
Your heart is safe now.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
From now on,
I won't make anyone's Love Alarm go off.
Hello.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
If no one comes inside the line
that I've drawn,
I won't have to get hurt
or hurt anyone myself.
And...
I'll be all alone.
LOVE ALARM
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE THE PHOTO?
CANCEL
DELETE
NO ALBUMS
Duk-gu...
disappeared for good,
as if...
he had never existed in the first place.
YOUR HEART IS SAFE NOW
LOVE ALARM SHIELD
YOUR CRUSH'S LOVE ALARM WON'T RING
EVEN IF YOUR LOVE ALARM IS ON.
ONCE YOU ACTIVATE THE SHIELD,
ONLY THE DEVELOPER CAN REMOVE IT.
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)