THIS CHRISTMAS,
DECLARE YOUR LOVE WITH LOVE ALARM
Today's the 1,530th day
since Love Alarm was launched.
-Mom, what's that?
-What?
-What's that?
-Look at that.
-That's so pretty.
-That's so big.
-What is it? Love Alarm's Christmas event?
Wow, it's so cool.
It's a world where you can't hide
your feelings of love.
-That's so big.
-Yes.
That's so pretty.
That's so cool.
-That's so beautiful.
-Very cool.
-It's so white.
-Wow, it's amazing.
-Gosh, it's huge.
-It's really pretty.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
LOVE ALARM
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Hey!
4 YEARS AGO
A WEEK AFTER LOVE ALARM'S LAUNCH
LOVE ALARM
DOWNLOAD COUNT: 9,300,000 - 9,400,000
MYEONGHYEON CHURCH
YEOLRIM HIGH SCHOOL
-Hey, this is too fast!
-Go, keep going.
-Ouch! You jerks!
-Hey!
This is so much fun.
Hey, is he coming? Did you call him?
Gosh, I don't know.
Have you heard from him?
Hey, he's here.
Look over there.
Hey. Since one big stride
is about one meter,
if you get to about there,
you should be within a ten-meter radius.
Right.
Hey, Ji-yeon. Is your Love Alarm on?
I'll turn it on now. Wait.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
What if only mine rings?
Then I'll go inside the radius with you.
Gosh. Hey, that's not a good idea.
Then we won't know whose phone rang.
-Go on. Hurry up.
-You'll be fine.
I'll go, then.
Go.
Good luck!
My gosh!
IF YOU'RE IN LOVE, RING THE ALARM
SOMEONE WHO LOVES YOU RANG LOVE ALARM
Hey, look. It rang.
See? I told you Love Alarm would
go off between Ji-yeon and Seong-jun.
Gosh, I knew their alarms would ring.
-Hey, see?
-I was right. I was totally right.
Oh, my.
Who's going to ring my Love Alarm though?
Hey, don't say that!
You have such a cute smile.
You think I have a cute smile?
In what way, exactly?
-How cute?
-I take it back.
-How cute is it? Tell me.
-No, forget it.
Come on. Tell me.
Hey, how come you don't have Love Alarm?
Is this version incompatible?
I don't need it.
Hey, then what about Il-sik? He can't even
ring Love Alarm with you.
Gosh, why does that matter?
You should break up if it doesn't ring.
Why bother dating him?
Why don't you just ask your mom
to get you a new phone?
Gosh, I want to live away from my mom
like you do.
-Your aunt never nags you, right?
-Gul-mi nags me though.
-Right, I forgot about that.
-That's right.
Hey, you'll visit your parents' place
on our school trip to Jeju, right?
Take me and Il-sik too. Let's get
your mom to cook us something nice.
Hey, you'll be late. You should hurry.
Bye, then.
Oh, right. Hey, you have to transfer
to my academy next month, okay?
All right. Bye.
Isn't it nice to be back after two years?
There's somewhere you have to go, though.
Here.
HWANG JAE-CHEOL
Well, Ms. Jeong asked me
to take just one photo.
So...
Hey, don't.
Do you have to do that here? Gosh.
Where are you?
What are you up to?
What are you doing?
He was number three last time.
How much money did he spend?
I'm Hwang Jae-cheol, candidate number one
from the Future Korea Party!
I wanted to share...
Go, number one!
...my goals and vision with you all.
My dear fellow citizens,
all the values that you wish to protect,
I will protect them for you.
-Please put your faith in me!
-There are many people here.
You can get out now.
I'll break down conservatism
and ideologies,
and I promise you that I'll become
a warmhearted, trustworthy politician
for you all!
HWANG JAE-CHEOL
FUTURE KOREA PARTY
Number one, Hwang Jae-cheol!
Future Korea, Hwang Jae-cheol!
Min-jae.
Where's Hye-yeong?
Where is he now?
-That's how it should be done!
-That's impressive.
-Cheers, everyone!
-Cheers!
-Great work.
-Let's drink up!
Yes. Great job, everyone.
-How about karaoke after this?
-Okay, great!
Eat up.
-This is delicious.
-Try some garlic as well.
Cheers, everyone!
Guys, this is on me.
-The next round is on me, then.
-We'll go to a karaoke bar!
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
Two more servings, please.
-Sure, two more servings?
-Yes, please.
CHARCOAL BBQ
What's this place?
You asked me to take you to Hye-yeong.
He works part-time here, you know.
He works part-time?
Yes.
You didn't know?
Well, I assumed he had told you.
There he is.
I didn't know...
he smoked.
HYE-YEONG
The person you're calling
is not available at the moment...
What?
Why is he going that way?
-Hey!
-Min-jae.
Don't call him.
Right, okay.
COMFORTABLE SEATING
PRIVATE SPACE
Look at you, Sun-oh.
Hey, when did you become so tall?
It's you who hasn't grown.
Why did you ignore my calls and texts?
Come on, why do you think?
SPICY CUP NOODLE
I got the things that you like.
Why are you back so late?
You knew I was coming back today.
I work part-time at a barbecue place.
-Is that the only reason?
-Yes.
How was life in the US?
Jeez, get off me. You stink.
-Doesn't the barbecue smell nice?
-No.
I'm back, so quit that job.
Aren't you coming inside?
Get some rest.
TO BE DISCARDED
IF YOU'RE IN LOVE, RING THE ALARM
-Hye-yeong.
-Yes?
Wake Sun-oh up.
Ms. Jeong is already awake.
Okay.
Hey, you jerk.
Do you have a death wish?
-You piece of...
-You have a huge bed.
-Why sleep here?
-You asshole.
-Hey, stop.
-Hey.
I was sound asleep.
Why, you little...
You jerk!
Isn't that Love Alarm?
-What's going on?
-Is it Love Alarm?
Over there, I think.
-Wasn't that Love Alarm?
-What's up? It's Love Alarm!
Where did it go off?
-Over there.
-Oh, my gosh.
Who's that guy?
My gosh, which class is he in?
Wow, he's so good-looking. Goodness.
Look at him. Gosh.
-Look at that face. Is he for real?
-Seriously.
-He's so hot.
-No wonder Love Alarm is ringing madly.
-Which class?
-Which class is he in?
-He's gorgeous.
-That guy is so good-looking.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
He's really handsome.
-That's Hwang Sun-oh!
-Unbelievable.
-Goodness, look at that guy.
-I know.
Are you all right?
NO GLORY WITHOUT PAIN
Hey, Jojo.
Did you see my hip throw?
What? Yes.
Whatever. I know you didn't see it.
-I'm sure it was great. You're--
-Oh, right. Hold on.
I installed Love Alarm too.
Oh, really?
Everyone's done it.
You should install it too.
Well, my phone's version is--
Let's show our friends
our alarms going off.
Why should we do that?
Everyone does it.
It'd be nice to jump on the bandwagon.
Whatever, cut it out.
The teacher wants to see you.
-Now?
-Yes.
Hey, why do you keep trying
to come between us?
What are you talking about?
Hey, you reek of sweat. Go away.
That's only natural.
I just finished my training session.
Whatever. You stink. Go away.
Why, you little...
-I should just...
-What?
KIM JOJO
So, there's no specific reason.
You don't want to go to Jeju Island
because you're from there. Is that it?
Yes. I mean, you could say that.
The trip isn't mandatory, so fine.
Why do you not eat school lunch?
I'm on a diet.
Keeping this figure
does require some effort, you see.
-You may leave.
-Thank you.
Ms. Lee.
You know Jojo's cousin, right?
The girl who lives with Jojo.
Isn't she in your class?
-You mean Gul-mi?
-Yes.
Did she pay the school lunch fees?
Yes, she did.
Why do you ask?
GRADE 11 SCHOOL TRIP CONSENT FORM
PRINCIPAL OF YEOLRIM HIGH SCHOOL
NOT PARTICIPATING
Hey, Jojo.
Look at this.
Isn't he so hot?
Who knew Hwang Sun-oh
would transfer to our school?
You know who Hwang Sun-oh is, right?
What?
No, I don't.
He was a model for Seventeen.
His mom is Jeong Mi-mi.
I think he looks so-so.
Come on. Il-sik's the one who looks so-so.
Does it taste all right?
It's freaking tasty.
Hey, Han-sol. What's up?
Hey.
-What?
-Why did you install Love Alarm?
-It'll never ring, anyway.
-Hey!
Look who's talking.
Hey, mine is weird though.
Why isn't it ringing?
My friend, your phone isn't the problem.
Guys, can you try ringing me?
Where are you?
The schoolyard.
Why are you there already?
I told you to wait for me.
Hurry up.
Gosh, my back. Why didn't you dodge?
-Because I have you.
-You're crazy.
Hey, if you scar his face, it'll cost you
a fortune. Do you know that?
Oh, right. Hey.
Gosh. Right from the first day.
-How does it feel?
-What about you?
How often does yours ring?
I didn't download it.
Jojo!
Hey, I'm here too.
-It's not for you.
-Jang-go is here too.
-What's that?
-What is it?
-It's for Jojo.
-Give me one.
-Not a chance. Jojo, have a mango.
-Thanks.
-Give me one, too.
-No way. There's none for you.
Do you want mine?
-It's yours, Jojo.
-There's more. I want one.
-This is hers, too.
-I see more. Come on.
Download Love Alarm.
Jojo.
Hey, mine will ring like crazy
if I download it.
But every time it rings,
you'll ask me who--
Just download it
so that I can find out who it is.
-Then what?
-I'll teach her a lesson,
saying, "Who are you to like Hye-yeong?"
Gosh, you're such a stalker.
Hey, let me enjoy some love
from girls too, okay?
Hye-yeong, let go.
Hey, let's go to an internet café.
I changed my LoL skin. It's awesome.
You don't have time for that.
What about the national tournament?
I've got that under control.
Gosh, you're going to be a muscly idiot.
That's what you want, isn't it?
-You're just an idiot. You idiot.
-What the...
ALARM
-Muscly idiot.
-Why, you little...
-Shall I punch you?
-Shut up, buff fatty.
You're a muscly moron.
-Look at that. Over there.
-What's that?
-Look at that.
-What is it? Isn't that Love Alarm?
Where's your phone? Quick.
Gosh, my heart is fluttering.
-That's so cool.
-My gosh.
-That's really cool.
-That's Love Alarm.
-That's so cool.
-Let me take a picture.
Amazing!
-Look.
-Let's take a photo.
-Amazing.
-It's so pretty.
-Hey, what's that? Oh, my.
-What's that?
-Will this be on the news?
-It's so pretty.
Isn't that Love Alarm?
I bet it can be seen most clearly
from our school.
-My gosh.
-Make sure you take good photos.
-What is that?
-That's amazing.
-How is that possible?
-How pretty.
-Incredible.
-How did they make that?
-How could a cloud look like that?
-It's so beautiful.
I did that. I made it.
I drew that cloud in the sky.
-Jojo, look at that.
-What?
That's a heart-shaped cloud there.
-Yes.
-Do you see it?
-I'm looking at it too.
-Well...
Keep looking at it, then.
We can look at it together.
What the heck?
Hey, Ji-hye's Love Alarm rang again.
-Show us.
-Guys, gather here!
-Hey! Gather now or--
-Hurry!
Hey, who is it? Which one of you?
Guys, I know it was one of you.
Hey, show us. Show us your phones!
Come on!
Everyone's going crazy.
Gosh. Remember that cloud we saw earlier?
It was to celebrate ten million downloads.
Love Alarm's promotions
are so large-scale.
Gosh, apparently
it could only be seen from our school.
Seriously? It felt as if the cloud
was giving me a signal.
Hey, wake up.
Had that been a signal,
it would've been for me.
That's Hwang Sun-oh.
-My goodness.
-He's so handsome.
I should download Love Alarm too.
Really? You said trainees can't...
Hey, Duk-gu!
Watch where you're going.
Look at him smirking again.
I can't stand him.
The Tottenham-Liverpool match
is tomorrow, right?
Let's watch it in your room.
I don't think I can watch it.
I'm working tomorrow.
Quit that job.
-I can't.
-Why not?
My bike chain keeps breaking,
so I need a new one.
Just use my bike.
I'd be too scared to ride yours.
It's as expensive as a car.
Then I'll buy you a new one.
Which model do you want?
Why do you always offer to buy me stuff?
It's not like I work for your family.
-Min-jae.
-Yeah?
Follow her.
-Who?
-That girl.
-Hey.
-Oh? Hey, that girl...
The girl Hye-yeong has a crush on.
Am I wrong?
You're wrong.
Even without Love Alarm,
you make it so obvious.
Aren't you driving?
Yes, I am.
What?
Do her parents own that building?
Whoa, Hye-yeong.
I guess she is.
Hye-yeong has high standards.
She has a boyfriend.
What's that got to do with you liking her?
You know what.
They obviously like each other.
Not all couples like each other.
STAFF
KIM JOJO
Hey.
Turn off the lights.
Where's Gul-mi?
She's sleeping.
SCHOOL NEWSLETTER
SCHOOL LUNCH ANNOUNCEMENT
Aunt, I can pay
for my school lunch myself.
But I'll be starting classes
at an academy next month,
so you'll have to hire my replacement.
And this Thursday is the 17th
of the month, so--
You have to...
do everything you want to do, don't you?
Hye-yeong.
Does it feel nice to sweat
so early in the morning?
Yes, feel my muscles.
It wasn't because
you hated coming with me?
How could I hate you?
You'll never hate me? No matter what I do?
That's right, dude.
Hey, don't ruin my hair.
You'll ruin my hair!
Gosh, seriously.
Can you light the grill
for table number six?
You should lose about four kilos.
You look okay in person,
but the camera always adds weight.
Watch what you eat.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't call me "ma'am."
It makes me sound old.
Okay, Ms. Jeong Mi-mi.
SAE BITT HOSPITAL
MS. GO SUN-I'S BILL FOR 504,300 WON
IS OVERDUE
HIGH SCHOOL LITERATURE
MONEY FOR ACADEMY
MONEY FOR GRANDMA
What are you up to?
Homework. My academy teacher
gave us tons of homework.
Want to go grab a bite?
All you do is study.
Let's go to an internet café tomorrow,
us three.
You can give me your items,
and Jang-go can shield me.
Are you sleeping?
I have a supplementary class
at the academy tomorrow.
Can't you skip it just for a day?
-Just one day.
-Hey, Il-sik. Let's go!
Hurry up!
MONEY FOR SCHOOL LUNCH
MONEY FOR ACADEMY
Hey, Hye-yeong!
Hey, Min-jae.
Hey,
when you stormed out of the car
yesterday, I totally thought
you were going to do something.
But what was that?
You want to see me and Sun-oh fight,
don't you?
Cut it out.
If you like that girl, just go for it.
Why do you keep just watching her
from afar?
I told you. You've got the wrong idea.
What are you going to do
if Sun-oh falls for her?
What do you mean?
Who knows?
To tell you the truth,
my biggest worry is
you two falling for the same girl.
I mean, which one of you will give her up?
Min-jae, what are you talking about?
Is a girl an object that you can give up?
That lucky girl will have to choose
one of us.
Aren't you getting in?
I've been working hard to bulk up
my thighs, so I must maintain them.
I'm off.
Oh, right. Come out
as soon as your class is over.
You need to do your hair
before the 5 p.m. appointment.
-The 5 p.m. appointment?
-For Ms. Jeong's book.
She wants you in the interview.
Hey, I heard there will be three cameras.
I must say,
she's a total celebrity, isn't she?
Jeez.
Make eye contact.
You got it, right?
Don't make any more mistakes.
Smile!
Smile.
The strawberry flavor
We have to form a straight line here.
Gosh, Gul-mi's helping them dance
so much better.
What's our class going to do?
Do we have to go that far
for a school trip talent show?
-Look straight ahead.
-They'll upload the video on YouTube.
-They're dancing in unison.
-Form a line here.
Do the wave.
She's so determined.
How could she dance there?
Nice, great.
Seriously, look at her lip color.
Are you zoning out?
Bring me a mirror.
-Everyone will be looking at that.
-Right.
Push it back a little.
No, a little closer.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
He should be almost done now.
Shall I call Sun-oh?
No.
Call Min-jae. Tell him to bring Sun-oh
as soon as possible.
Yes, ma'am.
Could you contour a little more?
Pass me the book.
MY PAST SELF IS A STRANGER TO ME
HEROINE JEONG MI-MI'S LIFE AS AN ACTRESS
Jojo!
Kim Jojo!
Gosh.
I saw you.
Why are you hiding?
Jojo!
Jojo.
Kim Jojo.
Your boyfriend is so loud.
Tell him to be quiet.
Where did she go? Gosh.
Does it show that I'm hiding here?
You're too big to hide behind those trees.
By the way, do you know me?
This is interesting.
Most people don't stare at my face...
like you do.
Jojo!
-Hey, pretend you never saw me.
-Kim Jojo!
Hey.
She's here.
Jojo.
What are you doing here?
Kim Jojo!
Hey, Jojo.
Why were you hiding?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
You really hate internet cafés?
I really can't go today.
Or how about you help me
at the convenience store?
Why the heck would I do that?
What do you mean?
I mean, that's work.
I don't get to have fun.
Right, so you go and have fun
at the internet café. I have to work.
Jojo.
Gosh, what's wrong?
What's your problem?
Come on, Jojo.
Jojo!
Kim Jojo!
MIN-JAE
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
LONG-TERM CARE BENEFIT PAYMENT STATEMENT
Jojo, good to see you.
Oh, yes. Hello.
-Come more often.
-I will.
Oh, ma'am.
-Well, those pears...
-Sorry?
I'm running late, so I have to get going,
but my grandma said she's craving pears.
I'm sorry, but could you
please pick one up for her later?
I'm sorry.
Okay, I'll pick some up
on my way here tomorrow.
Thank you.
Here.
Good.
One more, eat up.
There.
Jojo, where are you?
Hey, why aren't you here yet?
You have a shift today.
You've read my texts.
Why aren't you replying?
I've already told Aunt. Can't you cover...
You'd better run here now,
or my mom will be so mad at you.
POWER OFF
Why are you following me?
You've been following me, right?
Why are you doing that?
Why do you think I'm following you?
I'm going this way too.
Why are you going this way, though?
Aren't you going home?
How do you know where I live?
Do you not want to go home?
I don't want to go home, either.
That's strange.
What's strange?
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Is your Love Alarm off?
-No.
-You're an odd one.
You're being ridiculous.
I'm "odd"
because I don't have a crush on you?
If you keep following me,
I'll assume you're interested in me.
Wait.
I've got something to say.
Let's talk over here.
Go ahead. What do you want to say?
Do you want to kiss?
You must be crazy.
I guess you're joking, but it's not funny.
I'm not joking.
If you have nothing else to say, I'm off.
Where are you going?
I'm busy. I have work today.
Why do you have to work?
There's no one else to do it, that's why.
Right, you probably have no idea
what it's like.
I mean, you live in a mansion.
"Mansion"?
Your family is well-off.
We are, but my family is embarrassing.
I don't want to talk about them.
What about you?
I'm...
I don't have any parents.
So I have to work to support myself.
-You don't have parents?
-That's right.
Not everyone does.
Then don't talk about your family.
No one will know,
unless you talk about it first.
What?
You like me, don't you?
Then why act like you don't?
No, I don't.
If you turn on your Love Alarm again...
Yes, you do.
-Whatever.
-Otherwise, why did you follow me here
without even knowing what I'd do?
That's because you said
you had something to say...
Can I kiss you?
You weren't even listening.
That's all you were thinking about, right?
Right. I wasn't listening.
That was all I was thinking about.
You have beautiful lips.
I have a boyfriend.
I know.
He's also a good fighter.
If Il-sik finds out about this,
he'll beat you to a pulp.
I'll get beaten up, then.
If I had Love Alarm on me then,
would it have gone off?
No.
Both of ours would have stayed silent.
Because the urge to kiss...
came...
before love...
for both of us.
Like the flash of lightning...
before it thunders.
THE FLASH OF LIGHTNING
BEFORE IT THUNDERS
"TO LOVE" MEANS TO HAVE ROMANTIC FEELINGS
FOR SOMEONE
THE OTHER PERSON SHOULD TURN ON LOVE ALARM
IN ORDER FOR YOURS TO RING
ONLY YOU CAN KNOW WHETHER
YOUR LOVE ALARM IS TURNED ON OR NOT
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)