If I had...
Love Alarm on me then,
would it have gone off?
No.
Both of ours would have stayed silent.
Because the urge to kiss...
came before love...
for both of us.
Like the flash of lightning...
before it thunders.
Shoot.
Hi, Mom.
Hye-yeong, are you with Sun-oh?
Is that so?
If you get hold of him,
tell him to get home quickly.
Okay.
It will thunder now.
Gosh.
How did you know?
You learn in grade school
that light travels faster than sound.
Didn't you?
I was a model.
So?
I'm just saying.
Hey, it's raining.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Had you been here
for the last three hours,
I would have made 90,000 won more.
Until when should I suffer
for an old woman I'm not even related to?
I'll work extra shifts on the weekend.
DETAILS OF TRANSACTION
INTEREST PAYMENT
You've been paying me back for 11 years,
but you still have half of it left.
This...
is the debt your mom left behind.
You'll work more on the weekend?
Go on then.
Go in.
My mom wears that
even when she goes to sleep.
Isn't it so tiny?
Can you believe
someone can actually fit into it?
Why are you home so late?
Your mom was upset.
When was she ever not?
Still, you could have been
a good son for an hour.
I don't want to talk about it.
Let's change the subject.
Like what?
You like Jojo, don't you?
You're crazy.
Are you at it again?
Yes. I'll ask until you answer me.
I told you, I don't like her.
Are you sure?
Why do you keep asking?
You won't believe me anyway.
I kissed Jojo.
Get changed. You'll catch a cold.
IL-SIK: OKAY?
3 MISSED CALLS FROM IL-SIK
Jojo, I only spent an hour
at the internet café and then worked out.
Aren't I a good boy?
I'm sorry about earlier.
Okay?
Aren't you going to answer me?
What a persistent jerk.
Will you keep doing this?
Tell me.
Do you really not like Jojo?
What about you?
Why did you kiss her?
I'll answer your question
if you answer mine.
This 1-minute-and-27-second-long video
was uploaded on the afternoon of the 16th
on the internet.
In the video, there's a heart-shaped cloud
above a high school in Seoul.
This cloud was seen from
around 12:30 p.m. until 1 p.m.
for approximately 30 minutes.
Much speculation followed,
and it turned out this cloud was launched
by the application company
that developed Love Alarm to celebrate
its number of users exceeding ten million.
Love Alarm is an application that lets
the user know if someone who loves them
-is present within a 10m radius.
-Good morning.
The developer of this application
remains anonymous to this day.
Experts in application development
predict that Love Alarm will be successful
in the foreign markets as well.
Other kids take acting
and dancing classes.
Why can't I get vocal lessons?
You know they cost a fortune.
Next year. I'll let you take
those lessons next year.
Gosh. Whatever. You always say
we have no money.
Hey.
How many times did it go off?
-What?
-Your Love Alarm.
-How many alerts did you get?
-I didn't get any.
It'll be crazy at school today.
I downloaded Love Alarm.
Why would you download it?
It'll be a bother.
I don't care if losers ring my Love Alarm.
I'm way out of their league, Mom.
I'll see you later.
Hwang Sun-oh.
I would say he's the only one
who suits me.
Who is he?
He's a new student at my school.
He used to be a quite successful model.
Hwang Sun-oh.
He'll ring my Love Alarm today.
Are you all right?
Is this hard?
Hey, when should we go shopping?
We're going to Jeju Island.
Let's get some proper photos.
We take plenty of photos every day.
It's not the same
as taking photos on Jeju Island.
You'll come too, right?
Well, I have to go to the academy.
What's famous in Jeju Island?
You must know a lot.
I don't know much.
What was that?
Was it Love Alarm?
Jojo.
What is he doing here?
-Gosh.
-It's Il-sik.
It was him.
You're not mad anymore, are you?
I like it now that you have Love Alarm.
What?
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
I'll go now.
-Class is starting.
-I'll give it to you later.
See you later.
When did you download Love Alarm?
There's someone
who likes you here too, right?
-No, I didn't...
-I'm sure there is.
Guys like quiet girls like Jojo.
I think this is right for the last one.
-He's so cool.
-Who is he?
-Why is he here?
-He's Hwang Sun-oh.
He's Hwang Sun-oh?
-Is his face for real?
-Oh, my gosh.
-He's so hot.
-I am totally going to marry him.
Hey, get out of the way.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
Gosh, stop it. You're annoying.
Why are you still here?
Let's go.
What are you looking at?
My gosh, it's Sun-oh.
What do I do?
-He's so good looking.
-I know.
Sun-oh is just too handsome, isn't he?
-He's so handsome. It's crazy.
-Hey, stop drooling over him.
-Did you get an alert?
-My gosh.
That's awesome.
-Amazing.
-Is it Sun-oh?
-Seriously? Is it Sun-oh?
-Is it?
-Sun-oh rang Gul-mi's Love Alarm.
-Seriously?
-Who is it?
-Park Gul-mi.
-Park Gul-mi?
-Do you know him?
He must know me.
Similar types of people
attract each other.
I doubt it's him.
His alarm rang so much yesterday,
so a teacher told him to turn it off.
-I'm jealous.
-Look.
His doesn't ring at all
when there are so many girls.
Who is it then?
There must be someone else.
You're popular.
-They make a good couple, though.
-Yes.
Goodness, it's not Sun-oh. It's Duk-gu.
Did Duk-gu ring Gul-mi's Love Alarm?
Gosh.
Look at Gul-mi's face. Oh, no.
What is she going to do?
-Seriously.
-Duk-gu...
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, no.
It's suddenly turned into a tragedy.
Is there a chance for me
to get Sun-oh now?
I feel sorry for Gul-mi now.
-What do you mean, "sorry"?
-Duk-gu is such a loser.
-Sorry, my ass.
-Oh, my gosh.
-I'm doomed.
-It's okay.
Don't you have anything to tell me?
I'm sorry. You go first.
I forgot my textbook.
3RD CLASS IN MUSIC ROOM
That was the bell. Come on!
Gosh, you startled me.
Why are you avoiding me?
When did I ever do that?
You ran away from me earlier.
-Did you see that?
-Yes.
Why?
Because your heart flutters?
I don't even know your number.
Give me your phone.
Wait.
Not now.
Why not?
I have something to do first.
Then when will it be?
Later.
How much later?
Okay, Jojo.
I'll work out hard. See you later.
Is it Il-sik? What's up?
-It's actually--
-Who's talking in class?
Kim Jojo.
Let's go again.
Let me share your book.
I thought you went to get yours.
TOILET
Why won't he go away?
Gosh.
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
Gul-mi, I'm so happy
that I finally get to tell you how I feel.
There's something
I'd like to give to you today.
He must have lost his mind.
Meet me after school at Miso Park.
I'll wait until you come.
Gosh.
What the hell is wrong with him?
I hate this.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
I'd better just turn it off.
No.
I need it so that I can avoid him.
POWER OFF
RESTART
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
IL-SIK, I'M ON MY WAY.
WHERE ARE YOU?
-Bye.
-See you.
Do it properly.
Come out, Hwang Sun-oh!
-What's wrong with him?
-Seriously.
Is this you?
I'm asking. Is this you?
-What if it is?
-Then I'm going to kill you.
What are you doing here?
-Not going to class?
-What?
Il-sik is beating Sun-oh up
in the classroom.
Shoot.
Damn it. Let go!
Someone stop him.
Punch me more. I was expecting it anyway.
You scum. I'll kill you for real.
-Are you crazy? Put your hand down.
-What are you doing?
Leave Sun-oh alone.
-Just back off.
-Don't.
You bastard.
Damn it. I told you to leave him alone!
Stay out of this. He'll only stop
after he's done beating me.
You bastard.
Someone stop him!
-You bastard.
-Stop him. Sun-oh will die at this rate.
Oh, gosh.
-What's going on?
-Please stop him.
Stop him.
IL-SIK
Is Gul-mi not coming?
-What?
-You're her cousin.
You're here instead of her, right?
No, I'm not.
Gul-mi went home in the afternoon.
I see.
Were you guys meant to meet here?
I knew she wouldn't come.
I told her that I like her
on Love Alarm today.
I mean...
-I'm just a bit surprised, that's all.
-It's okay. I wouldn't be happy either.
No...
When I rang Gul-mi's Love Alarm before,
the expression on her face was worse.
Do you know what makes it
even more miserable?
That I still like her.
Even when she was frowning...
she looked so pretty.
I want to stop liking her, but...
You're right.
I think it is so unfair
that we can't do anything about...
what our hearts want.
Why did you let him hit you?
I said I'd fight instead.
I'm the one who kissed Jojo.
See? You like Jojo.
-No, I don't.
-Stop lying.
If you keep lying,
I can't help but think
that all the things you've done for me...
were not from your heart.
So, tell me.
Do you like Jojo or not?
No matter how many times you ask,
my answer will remain the same.
I don't like Jojo...
because you do.
Hey.
If one kiss means I like her,
all the girls I've met--
But this time, you're acting differently.
You make it very obvious too.
This will go on forever
if both of us keep denying it.
You're right.
Let's not ask each other
since we'll keep lying anyway.
Instead...
you should download Love Alarm too.
Take it.
What is it?
Why would you give it to me?
Then throw it away.
I don't need it anymore.
I'll get going.
Hey, Duk-gu.
DOWNLOAD LOVE ALARM NOW
WILL YOU DOWNLOAD THIS APPLICATION?
DOWNLOAD
LOVE ALARM DOWNLOAD MANAGER
DOWNLOADING APPLICATION NOW
THE ALARM WILL GO OFF
IF SOMEONE WHO LOVES YOU
COMES WITHIN A 10M RADIUS OF YOU
WILL YOU SYNC YOUR HEART WITH LOVE ALARM?
SYNCING IN PROGRESS
SYNC COMPLETED
Jang Il-sik and Hwang Sun-oh
had a huge fight.
Why did they fight?
Jang Il-sik must be out of his mind.
Let's trust Love Alarm.
The choice...
is up to Jojo.
I stood you up on purpose.
Why did you come here?
-Il-sik--
-Don't say it.
I know what you are going to say.
-Don't.
-Il-sik.
Let's just forget about the fact...
that you kissed Sun-oh.
I'll let it slide just this once.
-How did you know about it?
-So,
don't break up with me.
I can't do that, so don't say it.
You even rang...
my Love Alarm this morning.
Jojo.
I like it now that you have Love Alarm.
Ring my Love Alarm again.
Please?
-No.
-I'll forget all about it, so please.
It wasn't me.
Back then,
I hadn't even downloaded it yet.
Il-sik,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
I hurt you.
No, it's fine.
It's fine because I like you.
It's okay as long as
one of us likes the other.
My parents don't even like each other,
but they live together just fine.
We have better chances.
Il-sik.
Yours doesn't ring mine either.
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
You...
don't love me either.
Then...
Then why am I feeling this way?
Tell me.
I don't know.
Maybe we are just...
used to each other.
Il-sik.
We're good friends.
Maybe that is...
not enough to ring Love Alarm.
Then what does it mean to love someone?
You used to run away when you were little.
You're a big boy now,
seeing how you're enduring it.
He's not. A big boy wouldn't
get beaten to a pulp like that.
You said you fell. Did someone hit you?
Where was Hye-yeong?
-We got beaten up together.
-Do you think it's funny?
Why get into a fight you'd lose?
I did get beaten up,
but I didn't lose.
Send him to the hospital.
He can't get photographed like this.
Yes, ma'am.
-If you get into a fight next time--
-I won't let them hit my face.
I'll make sure it doesn't show.
Excuse me.
-Hey, try this.
-It's delicious.
-Eat up.
-This is nice.
-Cheers.
-Tables 4 and 6.
-Table 4 and where?
Table 6.
You should work until closing time...
since you came late today.
I'm sorry, but I need to go as soon as--
Can't you see how busy we are today?
-Excuse me.
-Yes, coming.
Customer's calling. Go on.
Hurry up.
Excuse me, could we get more...
-Sir.
-Yes?
I'll stay until closing time.
What?
It's just this once, okay?
SOMEONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
LOVE ALARM
NO ONE WITHIN A 10M RADIUS LOVES YOU
We keep...
falling for someone.
Even when there's no guarantee
that our feelings will be reciprocated.
Still, why do we devote
our time and effort...
to love someone...
with all our hearts...
when that someone is not even ourselves?
THERE'S NOTHING ANYONE CAN DO
WHEN YOU LIKE SOMEONE
IS THE LOVE ALARM DEVELOPER
A GENIUS HIGH SCHOOLER?
LOVE ALARM WILL NOT REVEAL
THE DEVELOPER'S IDENTITY FOR NOW
Gosh, why are there only losers around me?
Damn it.
Hey, what is this?
It's brand new.
Did you steal it?
No.
How else would you get this?
Duk-gu gave it to me.
-Why would you--
-What the hell?
Why would you take it from him?
It's gross.
And you just took it?
I can't believe you, you tramp.
Oh, my gosh.
I hate him.
IF YOU'RE IN LOVE, RING THE ALARM
INSTAGRAM
HWANG SUN-OH
#SUMMER #HAWAIIAN MOOD
#MEMORIES #GOOD LOOKING
#GOOD MORNING
I don't even know your number.
Give me your phone.
Let's just forget about the fact...
that you kissed Sun-oh.
Wait.
Only Sun-oh and I know about it.
My goodness.
If I were the girl,
I'd pick Hye-yeong.
Why?
Instinctively,
a girl is prone to pick
the winner of the fight. Think about it.
If it's you against him,
Hye-yeong will win for sure.
This is why you're single.
What are you saying?
Girls hate it when guys fight.
We now have Love Alarm.
That's all we need.
All right.
IF YOU'RE IN LOVE, RING THE ALARM
Hey, hold on.
I told you.
One, two. One, one.
Why do you keep getting it wrong?
You're just so not up to my level.
Of course we aren't.
That's why guys like Duk-gu...
"Similar types of people
attract each other."
-What was that?
-Did you see it? Did you get it?
-Hey.
-Did we all get it?
-Wait.
-Are they crazy?
-Oh, my gosh.
-Wait.
This is crazy.
-They must be crazy.
-Gosh!
My gosh.
-Everyone got it.
-My gosh.
What is it?
-I'm so jealous.
-Is this for real?
-It's Kim Jojo.
-Who's Kim Jojo?
Really?
Unbelievable, right? Two guys at once.
-Two guys. I was really shocked.
-The one who kissed Hwang Sun-oh?
Hwang Sun-oh?
-I want to date her.
-This is insane.
-I was so shocked.
-Gosh.
-That's crazy.
-I must say, she is quite pretty.
YEOLRIM HIGH NEWS
#45553 ANONYMOUS STORY
IS IT KIM JOJO?
ARE THEY CRAZY?
HWANG SUN-OH AND KIM JOJO ARE SCUM
-What are you doing?
-How much more must you take from me?
Give it back.
My mom bought this for you,
so give it back!
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
You made my family go bankrupt.
Why do you keep stealing from me?
-What have I done now?
-My Love Alarm didn't ring because of you.
Look at you playing innocent again.
This is why everyone thinks
you're the nice one.
Gosh, seriously.
It's not fair.
Only I know how spiteful you are.
I'll tell everyone.
-Tell everyone what?
-Jeju Island.
What you did in Jeju Island.
How your mom and dad--
Should I have died then?
Are you saying I should have died then?
You're a monster if you bring that up.
Has she lost her mind? Hey, Jojo!
What did you say? You think I'm a monster?
-You think so?
-Hey!
You think you're better than me?
Come on! Answer me!
-Go inside now!
-Let go.
Hey!
-What's wrong with you two?
-Let go!
-Let go.
-Let go of me!
-My goodness.
-Answer me!
You're mooching off my family.
She started the fight. Hey, Jojo.
Why don't you go on? Come on!
-I said, stop it.
-What will you say?
Go on. What are you staring at?
Come here. Get out.
-Did you see it?
-Yes.
They grabbed each other's hair.
I see. That's why her hair is like that.
-She's so shameless.
-Where did this happen?
-I can't believe it.
-I know.
Aren't they cousins?
-It's shocking.
-I think we should just...
Jang-go.
Give me your hand.
Why?
I want to hold it.
Did he actually say that?
-Oh, my gosh.
-Seriously?
What the hell?
-What's going on?
-Did you see that?
THE MOMENT YOUR LOVE ALARM RINGS,
THE DISTANCE BETWEEN
YOU AND THAT PERSON IS 10M.
IF THERE ARE MULTIPLE PEOPLE
WITHIN THE 10M RADIUS,
IT IS IMPOSSIBLE TO KNOW WHO LIKES YOU.
IF THE PERSON WHO LIKES YOU
LEAVES THE 10M RADIUS,
THE LOVE ALARM NUMBER DECREASES.
BASED ON LOVE ALARM BY CHON KYE YOUNG
(DAUM WEBTOON)