[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 8]
[Snowfield, Land of Frost]
[Li Mu,
Sword Holder of Mount Heavenly Sword]
I am Li Mu,
asking for permission
to meet The Master of Frost.
I am friends with the Frostwolf tribe
as well as The Master of Frost.
Guys,
can't you feel that?
Did your master
want you to stop me
or attack me?
If I take another step further,
are you two going to attack?
Li Mu requests
to meet the Master of Frost.
How dare you kill my Frostwolf Guards!
The Sword of Wine
will not kill.
They're only drunk.
You came to meet me mad with rage.
I had no choice.
I must greet
an honoured guest from afar properly.
I dare you to stay
in the Frost Land for another 1000 years!
Are you trying to keep me
or trap me here?
Are you really going to be this cruel?
Who's the cruel one here?
[Qin Lie's group on their way
to Xingyun Pavilion]
The snowstorm came all of a sudden.
What on earth is that?
Yu Shi!
Yu Shi.
Qin Lie!
Young Master!
Bu Li.
You came back
after you chose to leave.
How shameless.
There was a time
I trained in the Mountains of Frost
as a young man.
Back then,
you were an ordinary Frostwolf.
We met each other,
and our minds were in sync,
as if we had known each other
for a long time.
So, I kept you by my side
as my companion.
Then,
you abandoned me.
I had to leave.
I couldn't
ascend to a new Realm.
So, I must leave.
I promised you
that I will be back.
All these years,
I have been travelling the world
and experienced numerous dangers
that I almost got to
bath in the rumoured
Central Golden Holy Light.
I've finally achieved something.
As a fulfilment of promise,
I came back for you.
To my surprise,
I'm not the only one who's
made some achievement.
You have become
the lord of Mountains of Frost.
Both of us
have walked our own promising paths.
However,
you can no longer
go beyond your current cultivation.
Am I right?
A spirit beast is still a beast,
after all.
There's just so much you can understand.
Although you've transformed
into human form,
living a secluded life
here alone
make it impossible
for you to understand
the things a human could.
Why don't you come with me?
Let's stay close to each other
like we did back then.
On one condition.
[On the street of Xingyun Pavilion]
Hero!
Oh,
it was you
who killed the Soul Reaping Beast?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
What a pleasure.
I heard that Qisha Valley
is a well-hidden
peaceful and undisturbed valley
that pays no attention to others.
The disciples are only busy practising
fire and water skills
at the bottom of the valley.
That's really relaxing.
It's said that the Palace of Hell
is located within a black stone
with dull environment
and oppressive atmosphere.
The disciples are so combative
that they poke their noses
into whatever battle there is.
When there isn't one,
they create troubles everywhere.
Have a seat.
You're the Profound Heaven Emissary.
You take the seat.
Thanks.
No problem.
Zhong Zheng,
you be the judge.
No.
You're the judge, I'll just watch
without interfering, unless...
Unless there's a need to do so.
And when will there be a need for that?
When you need help
or give the order.
That's when there is this need.
For the murder case in Ling Borough,
Du Shao Yang,
what do you have to say?
I didn't kill him.
Who else if not you?
Shut up!
Du Shao Yang is a suspect,
but he's still
Xingyun Pavilion's young master.
Qin Lie,
Ling Borough is a dependency
of Xingyun Pavilion.
Shouting at him
is an act of disrespecting your superior.
-You...
-What?
You're just an insignificant kid.
Ridiculous!
Qin Lie killed the Soul Reaping Beast
with his thunder.
He's a hero to the far north
and even the entire Chilan Continent.
One should respect and look up to him.
Du Shao Yang,
besides disrespecting the hero,
you were also evoking public wrath.
-You...
-What?
I'm the hero, and you're not.
Lord Pu Jiao is being fair
without favouritism. How admirable.
That's my job.
Lord Pu Jiao,
Blacksmith Hua's death is suspicious.
The thing is, there is not a witness.
Even if there is one,
he's from Ling Borough.
Zhong Zheng
has personally
inspected the scene and the body,
and I believe he'll act impartially,
but,
he came here with someone
from Ling Borough after all.
They might improperly influenced him,
giving him a wrong first impression.
Master Du was right.
I might be prejudiced.
Zhong Zheng,
my son's reputation and life is at stake.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Lord Pu Jiao,
in my opinion,
someone from Xingyun Pavilion
or Palace of Hell
should inspect the scene first
before we make any decisions.
I was thinking about that too.
The reason why I'm here
is to see Ling and Du families
be reconciled.
Qin Lie, you have to understand.
Du Shao Yang is the young master
of the far north.
Du Shao Yang, keep in mind
that Qin Lie is the hero
who killed the Soul Reaping Beast.
Before the case comes to a conclusion,
you have to respect
and be nice to each other.
Yu Xin,
from today on, I'll drink with you
by the window everyday
no matter the time and place.
Yu Shi,
at the hall today,
you seemed like
you were going to collapse.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Good, then.
Uncle Hua told me
to draw these images everyday
as my grandpa instructed it in his dream.
Do you believe that?
Those were Uncle Hua's last words
before he was killed.
This is bizarre.
These words seem more important now.
The words he left behind
confused me even more.
The Silent Abyss is a deep gorge.
How did Yu Xin, an outlander,
make it there?
After the Heavenly Thunder struck,
I was half awake,
but I caught a glimpse of my saviour.
It was Uncle Hua.
It was like
they were there just to save me.
Are all this
related to my grandpa?
Who am I?
Why is this amazing thing
in my memory?
Why did the Master of Frost save me?
How did I push past
my own limits every time?
I'm afraid all the mysteries
can only be solved
after we found my grandpa.
Your grandpa drove off
the spirit tide for us
and left strange formations
on Herb Mountain back then.
Surprisingly, the eight pillars
could channel thunder
and kill the Soul Reaping Beast.
He's obviously not a mortal.
Maybe
he's deliberately hiding
his whereabouts from you.
I know that.
But I can't just sit back and wait.
That's why I want to learn
artefact forging skills.
You want to join the Artefact Forging Sect
and learn more about your grandpa?
Yes.
Young Master.
Young Master,
stop drinking.
You're already drunk.
Let go.
Young Master, this is it!
If Master finds this out,
he'll be furious.
Young Master.
-Young Master, don't...
-Let him go.
Master.
Look at you.
All it takes is some minor problem
to break your spirit.
Are you even the son of Du family?
You have the nerve to go out?
Young Master,
please listen to Master.
He wants the best for you.
Get lost!
Young Master!
If you take one step out,
don't you dare call yourself my son!
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Don't be angry, Master.
Hurry up and get him back.
Yes, Master.
Young Master!
Young Master.
Keep your mouth shut
or get lost.
Get me wine.
What are you doing here?
I heard you're a regular drinker here.
So, I see it as my job to serve you.
Shop owner!
Where are you?
Why are you looking for the owner?
To have you fired.
Too bad.
I'm the owner.
Du Jun, let's go to the next restaurant.
Oops.
I already bought all the restaurants
in Icestone City.
You can duplicate yourself?
No.
Can you keep up with me
if I visit another restaurant?
I just can.
Do you think I can do that?
Who exactly are you?
Why won't you leave
my young master alone?
I'm Tang Si Qi.
Let's cut to the chase.
I like you,
and I wish to have
a proper relationship with you.
Ridiculous!
I happen to be boring
and in need of a companion.
You go back first.
But, Young Master...
You think I can't
even handle a woman?
Leave.
Yes.
Let's go.
Cheers.
I don't know who you are.
How do I know
if the wine isn't poisoned?
Should I call you bold and unconstrained
or just lewd?
I lack the courage
to put my thought into action.
So, what will you call me?
You're just all bark and no bite then.
Coward.
I like your glibness.
All style but indecisive.
Indecisive, you said?
Although having more advantage
in everything,
you're always losing.
You're unhappy with the defeat,
but you couldn't achieve anything.
Who on earth are you?
I'm just an ordinary lady.
You have a striking appearance,
but your eyes are full of sorrows.
So, I made a wild guess.
Did I get it right?
If you don't like the defeat,
then challenge him to a fight.
Winning or losing doesn't matter.
Living is all about
accepting what's happened.
When you're finally convinced,
then only will you be contented.
Are you hideous in appearance?
My beauty has no parallel.
Then why are you wearing a veil?
Take it off.
I won't
do as you say.
You just said
that you want to fall in love with me.
But you won't even show me your face.
How can I love you?
Unlike my heart that matters,
appearance doesn't.
You have enough pretty ladies around you,
Young Master of Xingyun Pavilion.
What you need
is a lady who knows understands you.
She who understands me
must be beautiful as well.
I don't like ugly women.
Nice moves.
Are you sure you want to see my face?
Listen, it's dangerous to do so.
I'm afraid of everything
but danger.
I'll take it off now.
Yes, please do.
I told you it's dangerous.
I'll kill you.
Young Master.
Young Master,
are you all right?
Qin Lie intends to kill
Du Shao Yang already.
Are you sure?
His Realm Mark appeared.
I'm certain.
Originally,
everything was under my control.
But Li Zhong Zheng showed up
and got in my way.
And while I don't know what to do next,
Qin Lie actually rushed into the picture
and gave me a hand.
Good.
Very good.
The moonlight in Icestone City is dim,
but Ling Borough envies them
for having it.
However, the most enviable things
are the Luminous Pillars.
Three hundred years ago,
the Profound Heaven Alliance
sent the strong ones
to build Icestone City
and Xingyun Pavilion here
and govern the disunited people
at the far north.
The most outstanding among them
were chosen
to reside in Icestone City.
After the work is done,
the strong ones stared at the dark sky.
It troubled them
to see the people of Icestone City
walking in the dark at night.
So, they made the Luminous Pillars.
By drawing forth starlight
behind the clouds,
the Luminous Pillars
light up the people's way home.
There's a hazy moon in Icestone City,
but starlight still can't reach here.
The Luminous Pillars
brighten the dark night sky.
Three hundred years ago,
the strong ones' love for the people
were touching.
Did I put up a good show
at the hall today?
You did well.
And so did I.
[Why did you ask me out in secret?]
[What do you think about the incident]
[at the snowfield?]
[I was going to ask you that.]
[I've never seen
such big snowflakes before.]
[The only person
who can create such snow power]
[is The Master of Frost.]
[Maybe]
[she wanted to kill me for you.]
[I almost died too.]
[Moreover,]
[I don't know the Master of Frost.]
[We never even met once.]
[So, you called me out at night]
[to discuss the huge snowflake?]
[You]
[didn't kill Uncle Hua.]
[If I'm not mistaken,]
[someone is trying
to come between our families]
[and make us get hurt]
[by fighting each other.]
[Even if that's true,]
[Ling Borough]
[has only some old people
and children left.]
[Why do you think both families
will get hurt from the fight?]
[The culprit has had things planned out.]
[Having able to eliminate Ling Borough,]
[means he can do the same
to Xingyun Pavilion.]
[It's just that they're trying to
keep a low-profile.]
[Song Ting Yu?]
[In order to kill the Soul Reaping Beast,]
[Song Ting Yu ignored the
northern people's lives.]
[But in the end,]
[she didn't manage
to kill the Beast herself.]
[That woman is domineering]
[and she values her reputation a lot.]
[If someone learns about this,]
[she'll lose her reputation,]
[and maybe got held accountable for it.]
[Are you happy to be at others' mercy?]
[You really believed
that I didn't kill Mr Hua?]
[When someone spills dung all over you,
revenge is a must.]
[But given who you are,]
[you won't kill only an old man]
[but rather the entire Ling Borough.]
[Will you await your doom]
[or resist with me?]
[How can we resist?]
[If the person behind this
really is Song Ting Yu,]
[the Saintess of
Profound Heaven Alliance,]
[not only are we
not her match in a fight,]
[we don't even know where we can go]
[to seek justice.]
[The Profound Heaven Alliance
is on Lofty Cliff.]
[How do we get to that height?]
[By flying?]
[Ling Borough]
[and Xingyun Pavilion]
[are just two dusts
in the land of far north.]
[We can't reach that height.]
[In a fight,]
[of course we'll lose.]
[As for seeking for justice,]
[based on our current capabilities,]
[that's impractical.]
[But it's not in our nature
to do nothing.]
[At least show her]
[that we're no pushover.]
[Maybe]
[we can negotiate with her.]
[Negotiate?]
[What do you want?]
[The right question is,
where do I want to go.]
[The Artefact Forging Sect?]
I was right.
Pu Jiao is here
to cause dispute between us.
Indeed.
He was provoking us with his words.
How obvious.
Why would Song Ting Yu send
a frivolous man for the plan?
A woman's decision...
Qin Lie,
when Song Ting Yu
tried to eliminate Ling Borough,
I sided with her.
Do you really trust me?
Someone wants both our families dead.
We're in the same boat.
Why can't we trust you?
Pu Jiao's sending people
to investigate in Ling Borough
is just a show.
What's next in your plan?
We in the north
love to wear feathered beast fur cloak.
In order to kill
the cunning Feathered Beast,
one must trick it into showing its tail
where its vitality lies.
That's simple.
Shao Yang,
have someone keep an eye on them.
It's an easy task.
Xingyun Pavilion is my territory.
But my father may see through it.
No worries.
We'll join hands
and cover each other's back.
Won't there be more problems
if we take so much time?
You have any idea?
No.
Yu Shi,
lately,
you sometimes look pale,
but other times
your face turns rosy unusually.
Is it because of the Fire Poison?
Don't lie to me.
When did I ever lie to you?
But why do you suddenly
care so much about me?
Did someone teach you that?
No!
I was just teasing you
as you look worried.
I'm fine.
I'm just exhausted from all the things
that have been happening lately.
Are you all right?
Even if I'm not, I can still count on you.
By the way,
any clues on the images
in your dream?
No.
I heard there's
a Spiritual Herb Street in Icestone City.
Even the low-level herbs sold there
are way better than those in Ling Borough.
You can take a look there tomorrow.
Seriously?
Let's go tomorrow.
I thought you're worried about my health?
I'll take a good rest tomorrow
and not go with you.
Okay.
Go and rest now.
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Saintess Song asks for you.
Saintess Song?
Where?
At the place where you guys secretly
planned to rebel just a while ago.
Saintess Song.
The star and cloud were close once.
The light could break
the sincerest friendship.
That's the ancestral teaching
of Icestone City.
Do you know the meaning behind?
In Icestone City,
the Luminous Pillars are a wonderful view.
It's rumoured that
the light leads the way home.
But apart from Xingyun Masters
throughout the ages,
no one knew
that there's a huge secret behind it.
I'm all ears.
Three hundred years ago,
seeing the people here
being disunited without a leader,
and are threatened by spirit beasts,
the Profound Heaven Alliance sent
the strong ones to build Icestone City,
and made a treaty
with the Master of Frost
to give the people
their peaceful life back.
I know that.
The strong ones built
Luminous Pillars at Xingyun Pavilion
to lead the people back home
with starlight drawn.
To prevent the evil tribe from returning,
the strong ones infused
a great power into the Pillars.
Had the the evil tribe
invaded the far north successfully,
the power inside can be used.
What kind of power is that?
It's a secret
passed down to all Masters.
The strong ones spared no effort
to prevent unchangable tyranny.
So, to activate the Luminous Pillars,
we need the powers of both
Thunder and Starlight.
The Master will succeed a Luminous Bead,
and a strong thunder technique user
will be the Vice Master.
The Luminous Pillars can only be activated
with both their permission.
So, "The star and cloud
were close once" indicates
the two powers to activate the Pillars
as well as the Master and the Vice Master
who protect Icestone City
while keeping this secret.
Then,
what about "The light could break
the sincerest friendship"?
The Luminous Bead?
The Bead is supposed to be
held by the Master.
But for some unknown reasons,
it's always been with
the Profound Heaven Alliance.
After so many years,
even the current master
of Xingyun Pavilion
has no idea about
the secret to activating the Pillars.
You only
speak half the truth.
Why?
You
and Qin Lie...
That was a nice show.
Even Pu Jiao
was deceived.
So, it's true.
You sent Pu Jiao
to kill Du and Ling families.
The one I want to kill is Qin Lie.
As for you...
I have another plan for you.
What's that?
I mentioned about the mysterious power
inside the Luminous Pillars.
The person
who obtains it can ascend high
by skipping Realms.
Skipping Realms?
To which Realm will he achieve?
Straight to the Netherpassage Realm.
That being said,
second only to me.
Du Shao Yang,
I want to train you.
What do you know
about the evil tribe?
They live in the Netherworld
and have been in war
with our tribe for thousands of years.
It's said that the most recent Nether War
was 17 years ago.
The human tribe obtained a miserable
victory after suffering a great loss.
The Nether War
happened once every 30 years.
The Profound Heaven Alliance and
Eight Extremes Temple Sanctuary
take turn to supervise the war.
In recent years,
it's Xie Jing Xuan, the Saintess
of the Sanctuary's turn to supervise.
Now that she's dead,
the responsibility falls back on me.
I need an assistant.
You have many capable men.
But none as good as you.
You're telling me to betray Qin Lie?
Betray?
You and Qin Lie
are buddies now?
Why me
instead of Qin Lie?
He's done great thing
by killing the Soul Reaping Beast.
People of Ling Borough
have been living too freely.
And Qin Lie is too unruly.
If you were me,
who would you pick?
Saintess,
will this plan work?
It must work.
But many others
are going to be sacrificed too.
Qin Lie and Du Shao Yang
are heroes
who killed the Soul Reaping Beast.
The entire Icestone City
has learned about that.
Xie Jing Xuan and I
hunted the Beast under order.
She's dead, but I'm alive.
If the Master of the Sanctuary
learns about this,
he'll vent his anger on me.
And if my father learns that
I didn't kill the Beast,
guess what will he do to me?
So, I must seize the chance
to cover the truth.
Done.
I've figured out the name of the shop.
Let's call it Li Ji.
But I really don't get it.
Why must we
open our shop here?
I have my own reasons.
But I don't understand
the reason why I must wear this.
To blend in.
Blend in?
Well...
The greatest hermit
will retreat into the noisiest place.
It's all about retreating.
Look, my Master of Frost
is exceptionally pretty and elegant.
If she shows up at a place like this,
it'll be
too shocking.
Too shocking.
[Li Ji]
Not bad.
So, you didn't forget a single character
that I taught you.
I wrote "Li Ji".
And you intend to write "Shop".
Awesome.
This is great,
I'll write the remaining word later.
Ms Ling, what are you doing here?
You killed Uncle Hua.
As you want to make
Ling and Du families kill each other.
How dare you!
You're falsely accusing me?
Where's your evidence?
I won't come to see you if I have one.
I'm here to warn you.
You'd better stop now.
Why you
and not Qin Lie?
He doesn't believe me.
Instead, he believes the Palace of Hell
will find out the truth.
Ridiculous.
You're the ridiculous one.
You women are full of suspicion
and you love being paranoid.
Really?
I'll get the evidence
and hand it
to the Master of Xingyun Pavilion.
You won't have things your way.
But first of all,
you need available evidences.
Before I expose you with evidence,
there's one thing I want to do first.
What is that?