[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 5]
Yu Shi?
Something's up.
What is?
Emergency at Xingyun Pavilion.
The old master of Xingyun Pavilion,
the whole Ye family
including Ye Yang Qiu,
and two of their closest families,
all wiped out overnight.
Who did it?
The four families of Xingyun Pavilion
got wiped out in just one night.
Not even the servants were spared.
What a coldblooded
and vicious murderer.
It sends chills down my spine.
Qin Lie,
do you know who the murderer is?
Hundreds of lives were taken
silently in just one night.
Could it be
the Soul Reaping Beast?
It's impossible.
The Soul Reaping Beast
was already killed by the Saintess.
This is equivalent to
eradicating Xingyun Pavilion.
I had reported this matter
to the Palace of Hell.
I'll kill this villain once the
actual perpetrator is identified.
Profound Heaven Emissary,
in light of Xingyun Pavilion's misfortune,
I hope you could report it to the Saintess
and help Xingyun Pavilion
weather the storm.
Right!
Please help us with this,
Profound Heaven Emissary.
Alright.
Yu Shi,
where are you going?
Whether the Soul Reaping Beast
is the murderer or not,
I need to stop by Ling Borough.
I'm worried about their safety.
No.
It's too dangerous to go there alone.
I'll go with you.
Qin Lie, how about you?
Nonsense!
I would never tip off
the Alliance and get killed.
Do you think...
It can't be the Soul Reaping Beast.
Let's go.
Xiao Ying!
Hua Yu Xin?
Go back and wait.
Xiao Ying, can I come with you?
No, Master Hua specifically ordered me
not to take you there.
Have you found Xuan Xuan?
Go back and have a rest.
Let us handle this.
Let's go!
-Yes, let's go.
-Yes.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Xuan Xuan.
Yu Xin, what's wrong with you?
Isn't Xuan Xuan back yet?
Several teams have been
searching for her for days
for hundreds of miles of Ling Borough,
but to no avail.
Stop crying. Let's go.
We'll discuss it when we get back.
I... I can walk by myself.
You guys can go back.
Xuan Xuan would be happy
to see someone waiting for her
if she gets back.
Xingyun Pavilion
was almost annihilated in just one night.
There's no need to guess.
It must be the Du family.
Something doesn't feel right.
Not to mention that
the Du family of Xingyun Pavilion
doesn't have the power.
Even if they have the power,
why did they kill all the forces
and left the shell of Xingyun Pavilion?
To build a tavern?
The Ling Borough must be affected
if something has happened
to Xingyun Pavilion.
How about this?
Qin Lie, Gao Yu,
tell them
to alert the whole borough
in addition
to finding Xuan Xuan.
Yes, sir.
Father,
something happened to Xingyun Pavilion.
I know.
Uncle Xiang came here today.
They deserved it.
Father!
Xuan Xuan may be a wilful child,
but this all started
because Du Shao Yang
forced her to marry him.
I would never forgive him
if anything happens to Xuan Xuan.
And Xingyun Pavilion.
[Outside the Far North's borders,
at the foot of Qisha Valley]
This person is really weird.
She's still wearing like that right now.
Right, it's a strange world.
Look at her vacant expression.
Could she be a ditz?
Look at this model.
They both have excellent
material and colour.
Lady,
do you want to buy clothes?
Mr Proprietor,
look, it's very pretty.
Mr Proprietor, how much is this cloth?
It's not expensive.
Only 300 stone coins.
How about this?
That's not expensive either.
Only 130 stone coins.
Then,
which cloth can I buy
with two stone coins?
Two stone coins?
-This...
-I can't buy any of them?
Forget it.
I'll leave then.
Don't leave.
If you just walk out like this
without buying anything,
I'll lose the reputation of my store.
Two stone coins...
Wait here. I'll take it for you now.
-My bag! Stop there!
-Catch the thief!
Catch the thief!
Get out of my way!
-Get out of my way!
-Stop there!
To hell with you!
Stop there!
Watch where you're going!
Xuan Xuan!
Yu Xin has been staying at the South Door
since he came back from Xingyun Pavilion.
He wouldn't eat, drink, sleep,
or go home.
Master Hua is so mad that
he wants to kill someone.
And his wife cried so hard.
Gao Yu,
I tend to think...
Think what?
How do I say it?
It feels like
someone is following us.
What do you mean?
I'm saying that
I think there's a
non-existent person in Ling Borough.
Where?
This is what I think.
There's no one here.
Don't try to scare me.
I must be rattled
as I have a lot on my mind recently.
Let's go.
Let's have a drink with Yu Xin.
Get him drunk
and send him back to have a sleep.
I was thinking the same thing.
We finally get to drink together,
yet we're wallowing in misery.
It was you who dragged me here.
How can I drink
when Xuan Xuan is still missing?
Can you stop talking about Xuan Xuan
just for a while?
With all the things happening,
we hardly had a chance to sit down
and drink together.
If one day, a windstorm comes
and takes one of us away,
we'd never have a gathering again.
What are you crying for?
If I don't cry now,
it would be useless for me to cry
when we can't meet each other.
Qin Lie,
Gao Yu,
thanks, guys.
What's that for?
We grew up together.
As a child, I was timid,
and an outlander to boot.
Yet you guys were willing to
take me as your brother
and look after me.
Beware of getting drunk
as you drank that much.
Come on!
Qin Lie, Gao Yu,
I never thought that
I would dare to fight.
You think Ling Borough is so great?
You think you're all that because
your father is the master?
Go on and cry!
You're a big man?
Cry. No one's going to help you.
Stop!
Why do you pick on Yu Shi?
Beat him up!
-Father, mother!
-Beat him up!
Help me!
I thought you were strong.
Yes.
-I thought you were strong.
-Coward!
-Coward! Coward!
-Bring it on!
-Coward!
-Don't pick on him!
I didn't expect
Yu Xin to be the first one
to fight.
When I arrived,
-I thought I was dreaming.
-True.
Qin Lie, Gao Yu,
that was the first time I fought
and got injured.
But I was happy,
ha...happy.
After that,
you guys took me as your brother.
I still remembered that
Yu Shi was injured that time
and Gao Yu was the first one
to rush to Yu Shi...
This bookworm
drinks like a fish.
How are you going to face Yu Shi?
About the murder in Xingyun Pavilion,
I...I really suspect
the Soul Reaping Beast.
You didn't know it before
or you pretended not to know it.
But now, she's confessed
her feelings to you.
Confessed?
Qin Lie,
Yu Xin already told me.
You're a man.
You couldn't even dare to face a woman?
Either accept her or
set her straight.
Do you like her after all these years?
I drank too much.
Send him home.
I think your conscience is sealed
by the Soul Suppressing Orb.
Why are you still here?
I waited for you all night.
Where were you?
Patrolling.
Something just doesn't feel right.
The one who drank with us last night
was not Yu Xin.
What?
Last night,
when I sent Yu Xin home.
Let's go.
Qin Lie,
Gao Yu,
why am I here?
Is Xuan Xuan back yet?
Yu Xin,
what had happened yesterday
after we left?
I remembered that I met a lady
after you guys went back to town.
She was wearing a purple cloak.
Miss,
did you come from the snowfield?
Then, have you seen a girl?
Her name is Xuan Xuan. She wears a gown
made of animal skin.
I asked her whether
she had seen Xuan Xuan before.
She said she had seen her before.
And then...
Then?
I can't remember what happened after that.
Yu Xin,
you're finally awake.
You scared me to death!
Last night when you came back,
you slept as soon as you laid down.
We couldn't wake you up.
Your father and I thought you were sick.
Turns out you're lovesick.
Madam,
we'll leave for now as
we have something to do.
What do I like to eat the most?
The dishes which Yu Shi cooked.
I have no idea.
Don't do that.
I really don't know.
You usually eat whatever you have.
I've never seen you
so picky about food.
Alright.
It seems you're right that
the Soul Reaping Beast didn't die.
It must've followed us
all the way
after the massacre at Xingyun Pavilion.
Calm down.
Why is it following us?
To kill people?
We are all already dead
if it wants to kill people.
And most of the people in Ling Borough
are outlanders without spiritual powers.
There's no point in eating them.
Then what should we do now?
Tell the master?
Are you sure this is the real master?
Do we need to ask his favourite food too?
The master might be fake.
The elder might be fake too.
Then, every person in Ling Borough
might be fake as well.
The Soul Reaping Beast
can transform into anyone.
It'll cause a panic
if we spread the news now.
There'll be suspicion
and paranoia.
All hell will break loose.
Find more jade plates.
The more the better.
I'll store the thunder energy
in these jade plates
and wait until the
Soul Reaping Beast appears,
thousands of Thunder Storage
Jade Plates will be thrown to it.
This can scare it away
even if it didn't get killed.
Are you sure about this?
Yes, I'm sure.
But I have no money.
Gao Yu! Gao Yu!
Don't go! I really don't have money.
Yu Shi?
You're back.
Why are you still here
at this late hour?
A lot of things have happened recently.
I can't fall asleep.
You can't fall asleep?
Drink some warm water, it'll be better.
Yu Shi,
what's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Look, Qin Lie came to see Yu Shi again.
Yu Shi,
come out here for a second.
I have something to tell you.
You should go.
We have nothing to say.
Stop there.
You just leave as I told you to.
Are you really that sick of me?
You even refuse to look at me.
Then, why did you eat the dishes
that I cooked
and wear the clothes that I made?
Stop there.
You're so rude to Yu Shi.
And you can't even take a scolding.
Qin Lie, you call yourself a man?
She hasn't finished, you can't leave.
Why do you stare at me?
Are you going to hit me?
Alright,
go ahead.
Scold me.
You thought I'm scolding you?
Qin Lie,
I really can't stand it anymore.
I never complain about
the way you treat me.
But you even pushed me away last night
when I devoted myself to you.
Today,
you're standing in front of me
as if nothing happened.
How can I stand it?
Say something! Say it!
What do you want me to say?
Either she kills me
or I kill myself.
Qin Lie,
your house is on fire,
and it's being robbed.
Come back with me.
She's gone nuts!
Do you sense
something off about Yu Shi?
I suspect that she is
the Soul Reaping Beast.
I would rather that she was
the Soul Reaping Beast just now.
It's not funny!
If she really was the incarnation
of the Soul Reaping Beast,
then it could explain why
she was acting abnormally just now.
Was she?
I feel she treated you exactly right.
I'm talking about
the Soul Reaping Beast!
The Soul Reaping Beast
transformed into Yu Xin,
and now
Yu Shi.
What on earth does it want?
It certainly comes after Qin Lie.
Saintess Song!
Profound Heaven Emissary,
how impressive!
I'm just safekeeping it.
Saintess Xie died at the claws
of the Soul Reaping Beast.
If I don't kill the Soul Reaping Beast
on this trip,
I would be ashamed to go back to
the Profound Heaven Alliance.
If you could help me hunt
the Soul Reaping Beast,
I'll let the matter of
the Profound Heaven Badge drop.
Saintess Song, you said that
the Soul Reaping Beast
came after Qin Lie?
The Soul Reaping Beast is very vengeful.
How could it not take revenge on Qin Lie
as he hurt it in the God Trapping Cave?
How is it going to take revenge on me?
Transform into Ling Yu Shi.
Are you sure that this
Yu Shi is the fake one?
It's been a few days since I got here.
I have been lurking and never show up.
That's what I'm saying.
There's a non-existent person
in Ling Borough recently.
I thought it was the Soul Reaping Beast.
It was me.
Once the Soul Reaping Beast
is in the dark,
I'll be in the dark as well.
I've been observing each person
in Ling Borough.
I'm sure that the current Ling Yu Shi
is the Soul Reaping Beast.
Why does it transform into Yu Shi?
Destroying one's soul is more lethal
than killing people.
The power of the
Soul Reaping Beast is that
it can transform into the person
you care the most
to confuse you,
let you destroy the woman
you love the most by your own hand.
I love the most...
It doesn't matter whether she is or not.
She will die anyway.
You mean
you're going to kill this Yu Shi?
Of course.
No.
What if this Yu Shi is the real one?
I'd rather kill the wrong one
than let it go.
Let alone
I can't be wrong.
Let's go.
May I borrow this?
You guys look awful.
Looks like I was right.
If this Yu Shi is the fake one,
where's the real one?
She got eaten.
Then we can't kill her.
Why?
First,
I need sufficient evidence to prove that
this Yu Shi is the fake one.
Second, if she really is the fake one,
I'd need to find out Yu Shi's whereabouts.
Ling Yu Shi is already dead!
-What if she isn't?
-Calm down!
Calm down, everyone.
Someone's here.
Qin Lie,
the master wants to see you.
Uncle Ling,
you wished to see me?
Come here.
Offer an incense for Yu Shi's mother.
[Ancestor's Memorial Tablet]
Come, Qin Lie.
Come.
There's a thing I want to
discuss with you.
Let me know what you think.
I wish to promise Yu Shi to Yu Xin.
What?
What about Xuan Xuan?
Look, Xuan Xuan hasn't been back
for so long.
Yu Xin is heartbroken.
If I betroth Yu Shi to him,
I can make it up to him.
Yu Xin is stubborn.
The one he likes is Xuan Xuan.
He won't be happy even if
he gets to marry Yu Shi.
Once they get married,
she'll grow on him.
Uncle Ling,
is this a joke?
I knew it was a joke.
How can one force love?
So you know love can't be forced.
Looks like I've been joshing
with you so much
that you forgot I'm the master.
Master.
You're not interested in Yu Shi,
yet you never made your feelings
clear to her.
You make Yu Shi suffer.
If it wasn't for your grandfather,
I would have beaten you to death.
What are you doing?
Hitting the unfaithful fiend
and avenging Yu Shi.
Then you should at least
wait until I've finished speaking.
Haven't you finished yet?
It hurts.
Bear with it!
It hurts!
Gao Yu,
I suspect Uncle Ling is
the Soul Reaping Beast.
Is it here?
-Is it here?
-It hurts!
Enough! I'm going to
kill Ling Yu Shi now!
Don't you dare!
Calm down!
Qin Lie,
Saintess Song and I had a discussion
while you were away.
Saintess Song is sensible.
She agreed and said
she will only decide what to do next
after we proved Ling Yu Shi is fake.
How to prove it?
The Soul Reaping Beast may be scary,
but it is naive.
It'll reveal its true colours
once it gets what it wants.
To tell if it's real,
you must make it think
you've fallen into its trap.
How to do it?
No!
I would never say those words to Yu Shi.
Why?
What if
this Yu Shi is the real one?
She's fake.
She is the fake one.
Yu Shi,
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Are you hungry
or are your clothes torn?
She is the fake one...fake.
Yu Shi,
I...
Let go of me.
I like you.
I've liked you since childhood,
but I never had the guts to confess.
I promised my grandfather that
I'll become the Supreme Lord.
I'm afraid that I'll have to leave
Ling Borough someday.
I'm a thunder practitioner.
Every time I ascend to a new realm,
I risk being obliterated.
The Soul Suppressing Orb is still
sealing my memories.
I...
I'm afraid I might
get you into trouble
as I have lots of enemies.
I'm not afraid of missing you
for eternity,
but I'm afraid of letting you wait
for eternity.
Liar.
I can cook,
but I'd rather you cook.
I can sew,
but I'd rather you sew.
I can make money by hunting spirit beasts,
but I'd rather borrow from you.
I want to be with you every day.
I understand.
I'm always the one you trust the most
and care the most.
I swear to heaven and earth.
You are my happiness
and my sadness.
If you wish to have an ordinary life,
I'll abandon my dream
of being the Supreme Lord.
If you're willing to join me
in my path to become the Supreme Lord,
I'll give you all of my achievements.
I only wish to be with you
for the rest of life.
Let us face everything
together in the future.
Really?
Yu Shi,
marry me.
How is it?
Are you sure?
That Yu Shi is the fake one.
She is the Soul Reaping Beast.
How about the real Yu Shi?
Ling Yu Shi
was eaten by the Soul Reaping Beast.
The Soul Reaping Beast
chose Ling Yu Shi
because it knew you couldn't kill her.
Qin Lie, could you?
I'll do it if he can't!
I'll do it!
Tell me.
How to kill it?
Tomorrow morning,
you'll ask the Ling family
for her hand in marriage.
What?
You're back.
Gao Yu,
do you trust Song Ting Yu?
What do you mean?
I don't trust her.
The Soul Reaping Beast is real,
and it's true that she wants to kill it.
But I still don't trust her.
Her mind is too complicated.
It's really hard to keep track.
What is your idea?
I want you to find the Master of Frost.
The Master of Frost?
We've never met
the Master of Frost before,
yet she ordered the frostwolves
to help us.
I think
she is well-intentioned.
Only the Master of Frost
can save the day if things go south.
I don't know if I can find her.
Will they even
bother with me even if I found her?
Moreover,
I can't make it back either
if something happens here.
We're dead already before you
come back if something really happens.
At least you're alive.
You can restore justice for us
after knowing the truth.
Okay.
I'll be quick.
Gao Yu.
Yu Shi?
Why are you here?
Qin Lie asked my father for my hand.
At the moment when my father agrees,
I only know
the one I love isn't him.
It's you.
You're not Ling Yu Shi.
You're Soul Reaping Beast.
I'm Yu Shi.
I'm the Ling Yu Shi that
you've been dreaming of,
the Ling Yu Shi that you love.
Ain't I?
Take me with you.
Take me far away.
Do you know why I spared only you
when I unleashed that bloodbath
in Xingyun Pavilion?
On the surface,
you seem like a suave, easy-going person.
But deep down, you carry
a lot of baggage.
Gao Yu,
I saw your evil side.
You are the one we, the Dark Nether Race,
have been looking for.
Once you're reborn,
you will use the Du family for your cause,
for the Dark Nether Race's cause.
Sweet dreams.
Have a good sleep.