[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 3]
Don't come near me! Go away!
-Don't come near me!
-Qin Lie.
-Don't come near me! Go away!
-Wake up, Qin Lie.
-Go away!
Qin Lei, wake up.
What are you doing?
You were punching and kicking in the air.
I worried that you might hurt yourself.
Why do you treat me so nicely?
Ever since we watched
that meteor shower together,
you've been exceptionally nice to me.
I don't know why either.
When I saw you struggling,
I got worried.
It's upsetting.
I can feel the pain.
Only when you are happy,
I feel much more at ease.
-Therefore...
-Don't fall for me!
I have promised my grandpa.
I am going to become the Supreme Lord.
I am not going to marry.
Young Master.
Young Lady Yu Shi requests to see you.
What is she doing here?
I guess she is here to testify
to Qin Lie's innocence.
Let her in.
Young Master Du.
I know you want to marry me,
but
I don't like you.
It doesn't matter.
I don't like you either.
The Du family is doing everything
to seize power.
If they succeed,
you would inherit the title.
If you don't mind me asking,
are you really
going to limit yourself
to Xingyun Pavilion?
Cut to the chase.
Will you tell me the truth?
You're an iron fist in a velvet glove.
Fine.
Listen.
I aim
higher than Xingyun Pavilion.
In that case,
what is your ambition?
Compared to your lover,
I aim higher
and farther.
I am leaving.
Young Master.
She is...
This lady
is interesting.
Father, Uncles.
Uncle Hua.
Shi Yu.
Why are you here? Anything?
I am willing to get married.
I knew she'd agree to it.
I will marry into Xingyun Pavilion.
Yu Shi.
Father, it's settled then.
Okay?
Yu Shi.
It is a big deal.
Why didn't you discuss with
your father beforehand?
You asked him out of the blue.
How is he supposed to answer it?
No matter who I marry,
my father will get upset.
Uncle Xiang, you've always
looked out for Father.
You have my utmost respect.
After I leave home and marry
to a faraway place,
please cheer up my father for me.
Take away his sorrow.
Look at you.
I can't bear to hear that.
Am I not thinking in
your father's best interest?
Marriage is a big deal.
You are not allowed to make the decision.
This marriage
is not something that can be decided
by the Ling family.
Since we have no choice,
why do we still make things difficult
for our own family?
Uncle Kang.
You are honest and frank.
Moving forward, we'd better
stay away
from unscrupulous fights.
One day,
if Ling Borough is in danger
and needs to be protected by force,
we can only rely on you.
Father.
It's settled then.
Okay?
My dear daughter.
I am useless.
If you are useless,
would I share your burden with you?
Let me ask you a question.
Are you doing this
only because Qin Lie is dead?
We are not
meant for each other.
Du Shao Yang doesn't mind marrying anyone.
For me,
I don't mind marrying anyone, either.
It is not too bad marrying into
Xingyun Pavilion.
Father.
You may let me marry him in peace.
My dear daughter.
On behalf of the Ling family,
I thank you.
My dear daughter.
Thank you for everything.
How dare you?
What is wrong?
I am not properly dressed.
So what?
It's actually not a big deal.
No wonder you were drenched.
You went into the water
to fish for the box.
You threw it away and picked it back.
Is it because your nemesis's
fatal weakness
is hidden in the case?
As a man, you mustn't be too curious.
Especially when it comes to women.
Let me guess. You want to marry me?
Have you married anyone in Ling Borough?
Do you have any lovers?
Give me their names.
I will murder them all.
Even if you kill everyone
in Ling Borough,
I won't marry you.
Don't you want to know
who we are?
In the vast land of Chilan Continent,
there are 57 Bluestone Class factions.
Xingyun Pavilion is just one of them.
After the Bluestone Class
is the Black Iron Class.
There are 15 Black Iron Class
factions in the Continent.
Seven of them are led by my family.
Another seven are led by her family.
You are the Supreme Lord of Red Copper?
Supreme Lord?
Of the Chilan Continent
perhaps.
My nemesis is Song Ting Yu.
She is the daughter of the
Profound Heaven Alliance's Chief.
She is the Saintess
of Profound Heaven Alliance.
My name is Xie Jing Xuan.
I am the Saintess
of the Eight Extreme Sanctuary.
What is wrong?
Are you frightened?
There are 15 Black Iron Class factions.
Each of your families
control seven factions.
What about the last faction?
The last family is the
Artefact Forging Sect.
They have no respect for anyone.
Now that you know my identity,
are you tempted to marry me?
So what if you are the Saintess?
In the Frost Land,
no one is completely safe.
I agree with you.
Song Ting Yu thinks
she is fighting a holy battle.
Actually, she is here to
get herself killed.
Both of you don't get along
on the surface.
However, from what I see,
you are willing to die with her.
Of course.
We grew up together.
What is that
in the case?
It's the most precious thing in her life.
Her lover.
A man who is non-existent.
Why did you throw it
and pick it back again?
We are in grave danger.
If I die,
it would be good news to her.
As for why I threw it
and picked it back,
that is because I wanted to see you
jump into the water to save her.
What is so great about holding a box?
It's better to have a man in her arms.
You are trying to be the matchmaker?
See for yourself.
You claim you're doing it for
the inhabitants of Chilan Continent.
But the way I see it,
you just enjoy the bloodbath.
If the Soul Reaping Beast
sees this, it will laugh.
What are you doing?
So this is how it feels
having a man in my arms.
It is so warm.
Don't ever mention the case again.
What are you thinking?
I am talking to you.
How dare you ignore me?
The Saintess is talking to me.
Of course I must reply.
Since I was little, I've lived
in this harsh, northern hinterland.
I have long heard about the Supreme Lord.
I have been wanting to see
how the elite of the
Chilan Continent behave.
Instead,
I met two uppity Saintesses
from the Red Copper Class.
What do you think?
Nothing.
Nothing impressive?
Nothing special.
Qin,
I don't like you.
I don't like you either.
But I need you.
Just focus on showing us the way.
After I have killed
the Soul Reaping Beast,
I will aid you in sorting out
Lin Borough's problem.
Yu Shi.
Why?
I went to see Du Shao Yang.
His ultimate goal is not Xingyu Pavilion.
The more ambitious he is,
the more willing I am to marry him.
As his wife,
I'll help him reach the highest
and the furthest.
What about Qin Lie?
He will always
remain the same.
Look at the ashes.
They rise in the fire.
I think I have finally started
to understand his mind.
Therefore,
I am going to use my eyes
to see for Qin Lie.
From the lonely mountains,
to the snowfields
and beyond.
I wonder what the scenery looks like.
Xuan Xuan.
I wish Qin Lie
could be part of my life forever.
Why did you stop?
The storm and snow
have changed the landscape.
I can't recognise the road.
That mountain is tall enough.
Let me climb up the mountain to check.
I'll go with you.
Mr Liang.
The road is rough.
Be careful.
It is okay.
Don't worry.
I can tell
you are agile and light on your feet.
You must have at least reached
the Natal Opening Realm.
Wrong.
The Manifestation Realm, then?
Mr Liang.
I would like to learn from you
when you are free.
Please guide me.
Mr Liang.
There is a village not far away.
Let's go and check it out.
Perhaps we can ask someone
for directions.
Is anyone there?
The village is well kept.
It doesn't look like a deserted village.
However, why is there no one to be seen?
[The Gao Family of Mount Zu]
The Gao family of Mount Zu.
There are white lanterns under the roof,
and the staircases are free of snow.
I think it is inhabited.
Is there anyone alive?
[The Gao Family of Mount Zu]
[Gao Yu]
Gao Yu, do it!
If you want to fight,
let me know beforehand.
Didn't I tell you to do it?
Where is Yu Shi?
It happened suddenly.
She is still at Lin Borough.
Please don't blame me.
This concerns the hundreds of lives
at Ling Borough.
I have no choice.
Bring him back to Lin Borough.
The truth of the village massacre
will come to light.
He is the Chief
of Profound Heaven Alliance.
I bet Du Shao Yang
won't do anything to him.
When you are back again,
you can punish me however you like.
Please treat him well
during the journey.
He is not a bad guy.
Where are you going?
Are you not coming with us?
Those people are still
at the foot of the mountain.
I need to take care of them.
Run!
There is a spirit beast in the mountains!
Mr Liang was devoured by the spirit beast!
Run!
Run that way. Run!
What are you waiting for?
That spirit beast has a mouth this big.
It is this tall.
Its teeth are
hundreds of feet long.
Run!
Who is this?
This is Mount Zu.
A Bluestone Class family was living here.
His name is Gao Yu.
He is the last orphan of
the Gao family.
After the Gao family fell,
he grew up with Qin Lie at Ling Borough.
He is back to Mount Zu to
pray to his ancestors.
His sister is the mistress
of Du Hai Tian,
Xingyun Pavilion's Vice Master.
The ancestors of the Gao family thrived
in the harsh, spirit beast-filled
environment.
They accumulated wealth through wars,
and created a legacy that lasted
over 1300 years.
However,
in the last spirit tide, countless
spirit beasts crossed the border.
The Gao family of Mount Zu
was removed from the list.
How do you know so much?
Your best friend is afraid of death.
He told me everything when
we got down from the mountain.
You imbecile!
You couldn't even protect an old man.
He's an old man
from the Netherpassage Realm.
He put me down even before
I could take a closer look.
Netherpassage Realm?
Mr Liang.
You did that on purpose.
I guess so.
Saintesses.
Gao Yu also said,
if we follow Qin Lie's directions,
we will reach Frostwolf Valley.
The back garden of the Master of Frost.
How dare you try to trick a Saintess?
You are so vicious.
You are more vicious.
In order to kill the Soul Reaping Beast
and please your father,
you are willing to
sacrifice 33 villages
and the lives of thousands of people.
Those people's lives don't matter.
I did it
for the Chilan Continent.
You couldn't even protect the people.
You have no right to talk about
protecting Chilan Continent!
Dream on!
Stop fighting.
Fighting would hurt your friendship,
am I right?
You guys want to go
Snow God Valley, right?
I can take you there.
Gao Yu!
Qin Lie!
[Snow God Valley]
This is the place.
We've been here for quite a while,
but have yet to see a spirit beast.
Turns out
all of them are here.
These bones are spotlessly white.
However, they seem to be
rotting at the same time.
I guess they died not long ago.
They were most likely killed by
the Soul Reaping Beast.
After absorbing so many spirits,
the Soul Reaping Beast
has become unimaginably strong.
Since we have reached Snow God Valley,
we have no time to seek help.
We can only hope that the spirits absorbed
by the Soul Reaping Beast
have not been fully digested.
Only then would we have a chance
at killing it.
A team has to stay back to
guard the place.
The rest of you, go into
the cave with me.
Run while you can.
Gao Yu.
Saintess Song.
Saintess Xie.
Mr Liang.
Why did all of them disappear?
Gao Yu!
Saintess Song! Saintess Xie!
Mr Liang!
Qin Lie!
-Qin Lie!
-Yu Shi!
Yu Shi!
You!
Look over there.
Gao...
Stop talking. Look over there.
The Soul Reaping Beast
is absorbing their power.
Is that the Soul Reaping Beast?
That
is the sacrificial altar?
Oh no. He lured us here
to absorb our power.
We fell right into his trap.
The survivor who gave us
the information
must be a bait dropped by
the Soul Reaping Beast.
He lured us here to
complete the sacrificial ritual.
You mean
Gao Yu and the gang are the offerings?
What should we do?
My subordinates
and Xie Jing Xuan
possess the flag
of the Heavenly Fire Formation.
If we place the centre of the formation
on the sacrificial altar,
the Heavenly Fire Formation
will form on its own.
When the formation is complete,
it will attack the coffin first,
prompting Soul Reaping Beast
to guard it.
Then, we'll kill it.
You should go there.
If I go there,
who's going to fight the battle?
-You should go.
-I...
Go now!
Pretend that you are lured.
Play it by ears.
Gao Yu.
Qin Lie, it's time to eat.
Eat up. These are your favourite dishes.
The rice is getting cold.
Let me change it for you.
It's okay.
No way.
I can't let you eat cold food.
Otherwise,
I would be perceived as
an incompetent wife.
Wife?
Yu Shi, when did you marry me?
Put down the bowl.
Put it down.
Qin Lie, put Profound Heaven Seal
on the sacrificial altar.
Heavenly Fire Formation, assemble.
Let go of me!
He used the window of opportunity
to ascend to the Natal Opening Realm
from the Refinement Realm.
Summoning Heavenly Thunder
through ascension.
Why didn't we think of that?
Those who are at the brink
of ascension,
don't hold back.
Summon the Heavenly Thunder.
Now, ascend!
Endure the Heavenly Thunder.
It's your only chance at survival.
Otherwise, I will kill all of you now.
The ascension has
generated Heavenly Thunder.
Only one out of a million
can survive it.
We spent so much time and effort
to cultivate the thunder technique.
We will lose at least half of our power
in this battle.
Even if we die in the end,
it would be worth it if we could kill
the Soul Reaping Beast.
The fire is not strong enough.
You should leave the cave.
Let me fight the beast!
Xie Jing Xuan, do you want to
perish together with the beast?
You must be crazy!
We don't have much time!
Qin Lie!
Qin Lie, get up.
Qin Lie, get up!
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Mistress, the Tianqiong Grass smells good.
When it is mixed with Jade Wine,
the fragrance lingers for a long time.
It suits you well.
Hai Tian loves this scent.
Gao Yu hasn't been back from
Mount Zu for days.
Any news from him?
Young Master.
Shao Yang, you are back.
Mother.
This is...
Greetings. I am Yu Shi.
I went to Mount Zu with
Gao Yu when I was young
and saw you once.
Your hand is frostbitten.
You don't have to suffer anymore
from now on.
Shao Yang, be good to Yu Shi.
Don't upset her.
I will bear it in mind.
A noble girl like you
must be exhausted
after the long journey.
Go get yourself cleaned.
Bring Pei'er here.
Yes.
I am seeking permission to leave.
When the Gao family fell,
I sought refuge with Xingyun Pavilion.
Gao Yu got used to living
in the wilderness.
He couldn't put up with the rules
at Xingyun Pavilion.
He would go out and play
in the snowfield.
Whenever he came back,
he would tell me interesting things
that happened there.
He told me a lot about you.
He wouldn't stop raving about you.
But now that I finally met you,
I can't tell what is so great about you.
When you rejected my little brother's love
and chose to marry Qin Lie,
I kept my peace.
However, you decided to marry
Shao Yang all of a sudden.
I used to be a Bluestone Class master.
I had power in my hand.
I held millions of lives in my hand.
Even then,
I was loyal
wherever I was.
As a woman, we have to be loyal
so that we can be free from guilt.
Don't worry, madam.
I will learn from you.
I will be extremely grateful,
devoted,
and loyal.
Master.
Du Shao Yang brought
Young Lady Yu Shi home.
They plan to get married.
The Du family and the Ling family
will become allies.
Zhuo Qian's murderer, Qin Lie,
is from the Ling Borough.
If we threaten them,
we might be able to stop them
from getting married.
Where is Zhuo Qian's dead body?
During the journey of transporting
Zhuo Qian's body back,
the inn Du Shao Yang was staying in
caught fire.
Pity Zhuo Qian.
She can't even have a proper burial.
Well.
Du Shao Yang.
Very well.
He has no respect for me.
Even if the Ling family
have the permission,
they don't have the guts to kill
anyone from the Ye family.
This is obviously Du Shao Yang's doing.
However, the Du family lost Du Fei too.
That's where the Du family's
brilliance lies.
Xuan Xuan!
Bookworm.
What are you holding?
Since we have decided to leave,
I have to bring more books.
Xuan Xuan, let's go.
My parents will come after us
if they find out about our plan.
It's going to be a long journey.
Are you up to it?
Like I said, from now on,
I will follow you wherever you go.
We will stick together.
Xuan Xuan.
I don't get it.
Since Yu Shi has decided to get married,
why do you still choose to leave?
When I was young,
I thought that as long as
my father and my elders are here,
Ling Borough will stay safe forever.
Since Father and the elders
can no longer protect us,
I must leave and look for a way
to become stronger.
Then, I will come back and save my sister.
[The Master of Frost, Bu Li]
Send them to Ling Borough.
Hua Yu Xin.
How long have we known each other?
It has been 18 years.
Qin Lie hadn't come to Ling Borough yet.
After all these years,
you've never said anything
that made me happy.
Xuan Xuan.
Actually...
Actually, I've been keeping it to myself
for a long time.
I didn't have the chance to tell you.
See?
I am not sure if I should
let you say it out loud.
I am curious,
but I'm worried what you
are going to say
is not something I want to hear.
Bookworm.
Do you feel bored
when you are with me?
Sometimes, I do feel...
Forget it.
Say no more.
Listen to me.
Did you bring these books
to kill time when you are bored?
I knew it.
When you are reading,
what should I do?
You could read with me.
My father said books contain
all kinds of knowledge.
You won't feel bored when you read.
I won't feel bored
because
I have you by my side.
Xuan Xuan!
You must listen to me.
I don't care if you like it or not.
It has been kept in my heart
for many years.
Ling Xuan Xuan.
Reading helps one to ascend.
Xuan Xuan.
Why are you crying? You...
Yu Xin.
Let's play a game, okay?
Sure.
As long as you stop crying,
I will play any game with you.
You've fallen for me
a long time ago,
haven't you?
But I don't trust you.
What should I do?
Xuan Xuan, I...
How about this?
In order to prove your sincerity,
you have to stand here.
Close your eyes.
Xuan Xuan, now what?
Xuan Xuan!
Now,
rehearse what you have been
wanting to tell me
in your mind,
then tell me everything.
You can only open your eyes
when you have finished talking.
Don't try to cheat
or I will beat you up.
I don't have to rehearse.
I can say it now.
I have been keeping it
in my heart for many years.
Xuan Xuan, you know something?
When my mother taught me how to write,
the first word she taught me
was "outlander."
My mother said outlanders
are born without Natal Palaces.
They can't cultivate.
They are the lowest class of all.
She told me to work hard to become
a blacksmith like my father.
I asked my mother,
"Is Xuan Xuan an outlander?"
My mother said, girls
from the Ling family
are gifted in cultivation.
So I thought to myself,
if I couldn't cultivate,
Young Lady Xuan Xuan
wouldn't play with me.
In my dreams,
someone told me
reading is the path to ascension.
Actually, I knew
it was my father talking to me
in disguise.
As you know,
I'm a quiet person.
The truth is, I have been wanting
to tell you all this.
But I didn't have the chance.
Xuan Xuan.
I really like you.
I mean it.
Xuan Xuan, you promised
to take me with you.
Why are you ditching me?
Xuan Xuan.
Yu Xin!
Qin Lie? You are still alive.
So am I.
Gao Yu?
Why are you here?
It is a long story.
Gao Yu!
Back in the God Trapping Cave,
Qin Lie passed out.
The Saintesses left.
Then,
frostwolves appeared out of nowhere.
When I was semiconscious,
I dreamed of a woman
who ordered the frostwolves
to send us back to Ling Borough.
The frostwolves are the masters
of Frost Land.
They are the kings of the snowfield.
Why would they listen to a woman?
Yu Xin.
Why are you here?
It is because...
Is Ling Borough okay?
Ling Borough is fine.
Xuan Xuan left me behind
and went alone.
She said she needs
to become stronger
to save her sister.
What happened to Yu Shi?
In order to protect Ling Borough,
she married into Xingyun Pavilion.
What?
Let's go to Xingyun Pavilion.
Don't leave me behind.
Let's go!