[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 1]
[Qin Lie]
It's Yao Yao's father.
Watch out.
There's a spirit beast.
[Ling Ying, Ling Xin]
Silver Flame Spider.
I think it's the one that
killed Yao Yao's father.
Look out!
[Icestone City]
I heard that at this time of year,
[Young Master of Xingyun Pavilion,
Du Shao Yang]
the moon at Ling Borough is the prettiest
and the brightest.
Have you ever seen it?
If you want to know if it's true or not,
go and find out for yourself.
Father.
[Acting Master of Xingyun Pavilion,
Du Hai Tian]
Shao Yang,
go to Ling Borough and marry a woman.
Yes, Father.
Aren't you curious about
what kind of woman
I'm asking you to marry?
It's just a woman.
[Ling Yu Shi]
Watch out!
He's exhausted his thunder energy.
Qin Lie, use the
Thunder Storage Jade Plate.
Yu Shi.
Yu Shi, what are you doing here?
Yao Yao is sick.
So I went to see her.
I learned that her father and brother
have come to the snowfield
to hunt for beast cores
to cure her illness.
Unfortunately,
I was too late.
She's so silly.
She could've just told us
she needed the beast core.
We'll get it for her.
Yao Yao is an outlander.
She's prideful
and hates being looked down upon.
In this land of ice and snow,
whether you're an outlander
or a cultivator,
the only way to survive
is by helping each other out.
Don't cry.
If you cry,
it means you're
resigning yourself to fate.
Father of Yao Yao,
you were too reckless.
One more day,
and it'll be full moon.
Outlanders
are born without Natal Palaces.
So what?
We're all part of the Ling family.
Come on, let's go home.
Let's watch this year's moon together.
Then we can say our goodbyes.
The spirit tide hasn't receded yet.
It's dangerous in the snowfield.
Besides, you haven't recovered
from the fire poison yet.
Next time...
I'm worried about you.
If I'm really in danger,
worrying about me won't help.
[Ling Borough]
[Hua Yu Xin]
Qin Lie, you're awake.
You again.
Who else would care so much
about you other than me?
Were you having that dream again?
You saw yourself
dressed bizarrely and
standing in front of that palace again?
And there were also those
four puzzling paintings?
The book says
you're having this dream
because you're thinking of moving
into a new house.
The last book said
I was thinking of women.
This time,
it's houses?
My friend,
stop reading that claptrap.
It's messing with your head.
Qin Lie,
do you think maybe your dream
has something to do with
the Soul Suppressing Orb in your head?
This Soul Suppressing Orb is sealing
my memories from before I was ten.
I have no idea who put it in my head.
I need to practise my
artefact forging skill.
And find out
how to seal the orb.
Then I'll use Thunderbolt
to crack it open.
Natal Opening Realm, Manifestation Realm,
Netherpassage Realm.
In each new realm,
one faces a thunder tribulation.
Surviving the thunder tribulation
is one thing.
But with the Soul Suppressing Orb
sealed inside your head,
you might miss it
and strike yourself dead instead.
If I can crack the orb open
before it kills me,
then at least I'll die with my memories.
It's worth it.
You have your reasons,
but I have mine too.
Please listen to me first.
Have you written it?
I have.
What did you write this year?
Xuan Xuan.
Xuan Xuan?
Why would you write Xuan Xuan's name?
I'm sensing hostility.
Hostility?
Qin Lie,
[Ling Xuan Xuan]
let's hunt for Feathered Beasts
in Qiongying Hollow.
Xuan Xuan, the Feathered Beast
is the apex predator
of the Refinement Realm.
Young Lady Xuan Xuan, if you want
to kill yourself, have it your way.
Excuse me, but I intend to live longer.
There's a peddler in town.
The Feathered Beast fur cloak he's
selling can keep out the cold and dust.
I really like it.
But Sister said
you've spent all the money
on the Thunder Storage Jade Plate.
Even so, you should help me
to hunt down the Feathered Beast.
Xuan Xuan, stop. Put it down.
The Thunder Storage Jade Plate
is filled with thunder energy.
It may explode.
Then I'll blow up this shack
for my own satisfaction.
Look, this is Yu Xin's note
for the Moon Ritual tonight.
How could you do this to Xuan Xuan?
I...
I'm so disappointed in you.
Xuan Xuan,
see for yourself.
Hua Yu Xin,
what did you write?
-Let me read it.
-No.
-Hand it over.
Hand it over.
Hua Yu Xin,
what did you write?
Stop there.
Stop right there.
[Ling Borough, Herb Mountain]
Yu Shi,
this is the morning dew collected
from Zhufuqing leaves.
Put it away carefully.
Qiongying fruit is delicate.
Only water it three drops
every six hours.
Its flower takes three years to bloom
and three years to bear fruit.
It's the guiding herb that keeps
Old Master alive.
Ling Ying,
Ling Borough relies on
Xingyun Pavilion for survival.
For generations, we've
grown herbs for a living.
We can't afford any mistakes here.
[Herb Mountain, hillside]
You're here.
You're only at the Refinement Realm,
and you could already produce
so much thunder energy.
It'd probably take me
two years to achieve that.
The incantation Grandpa Qin Shan
gave you is really amazing.
I assume it can only be found
in a high-rank
continent above the Silver Class.
You're envious of me?
I offered to teach you long ago.
But you refused to learn.
I was born with a
water spirit constitution,
and I'm suffering from fire poison.
I can only suppress
with water spirit powers.
As for other types of spirit powers,
forget it.
Here, you must be hungry.
What do we have today?
All your favourite dishes.
Did you have that dream again last night?
The same dream.
That dream has been haunting
you for ten years.
And you've been cultivating
for ten years.
Since I've improved my Thunderbolt skill,
I must improve
my artefact forging skill, too.
I need to open the Soul Suppressing Orb
to find out who I am
and everything that occurred in my dream.
Most importantly,
I need to find my grandfather.
You want to leave Ling Borough that badly?
I must keep cultivating.
I must go higher and farther.
For example,
the Artefact Forging Sect.
So
there is
nothing in Ling Borough
that's worth staying for?
By the way,
do you still have the Yixin
leaf I gave you last year?
I used it up last night.
So I threw it away.
I'm sure you have more.
Your Yixin leaves only last a year.
Why don't you grow leaves
that can last a lifetime?
A lifetime is very long.
It's not that easy to grow
something like that.
At least grow something
that lasts ten years.
By the way, Yu Shi,
it'll be lively
at the town tonight.
Today is the Moon Ritual.
Of course it'll be lively.
After all, Ling Borough only gets
to see the moon once a year.
Have you written it?
I have. You?
I've written mine too.
What did you write?
Only the moon knows it.
But
don't you want to find out what I wrote?
Only the moon knows it.
I'm not finished yet.
You've eaten enough.
You'll be overstuffed if I don't stop you.
If you want to hug him, just do it.
Run to him
and hug him.
The Yixin leaf's spirit fire
burns as brightly as a certain
someone's infatuation.
But all fires go out eventually.
Yet someone here simply
refuses to let it go out.
Although he doesn't even care,
you insist on giving
him a leaf every year.
But don't you realise
he's only treating you as an arm,
which he can cut off
and abandon anytime.
People can't live without their arms.
But people have two arms.
Sister,
he's a Thunderbolt practitioner.
He could be struck dead anytime.
But he is never afraid.
It means he cares
about no one in this world.
Including you.
What do you really like about him?
Ling Borough only sees the
moonlight once a year.
Have you ever seen a shooting star
that only appears once in a century?
Ten years ago,
the shooting star coincided
with the spirit tide, and we were
overwhelmed by spirit beasts.
I was seriously wounded,
so I didn't see it.
I saw it.
With Qin Lie.
[It's the shooting star.]
[Qin Lie, make a wish now.]
[If you have a wish,
you should seize it yourself.]
This man
is looking at the heavens,
yet he asks nothing from it.
I get it now.
Sister,
what this man wants to achieve
isn't in Ling Borough.
If he stays,
I'll stay with him.
If he wants to leave,
I won't hold him back.
Be it the snowfield of the far north,
or the land of gold and silver,
I love him
and only him.
Chief is here.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Today is the day we see the moon
which appears only once
a year in Ling Borough.
Let's hear what our chief
has to say, shall we?
Yes.
Everyone,
I'm not going to make a speech this year.
[Chief of the Ling Family, Ling Cheng Ye]
Instead,
I'm going to sing you all a song.
Yes, yes.
Xingyun Pavilion?
Du Shao Yang, Young Master
of Xingyun Pavilion,
and Zhuo Qian, Deacon of Ye family,
are here.
Where is the chief of the Ling family?
I, Ling Cheng Ye,
greet you, Young Master Du,
on behalf of Ling Borough.
Deacon Zhuo.
Which one of you is Qin Lie?
Seize him.
Stop.
Kneel.
You haven't explained anything.
Why should I kneel?
Kneel.
Three months ago,
on the ninth day of the month,
where were you?
Can you remember
what happened three months ago?
Deacon Zhuo,
did Qin Lie do anything wrong?
All the people of Ling Borough
ever do is plant herbs and hunt beasts.
Nothing else.
As for what we have
done on a certain date,
those are the only things that we did.
If you want a specific answer,
I'm afraid it's a bit difficult
for us to provide it.
Difficult to answer?
That means you have no answer.
In that case,
Qin Lie has no alibi
for slaughtering 33 outlander villages
with Thunderbolt.
33 villages.
Thousands of lives.
All killed by the Thunderbolt skill.
In all of the far north,
the only person who
practices Thunderbolt
is you, Qin Lie from Ling Borough.
The snowfield is vast.
How can you be sure there isn't a
second Thunderbolt cultivator?
Qin Lie,
where were you last night?
We were hunting
in the snowfield last night.
We even killed a Silver Flame Spider.
We, and the spider's corpse,
are your witness and proof.
I was talking to Qin Lie.
Why are you answering?
Young Lady Yu Shi,
you and Qin Lie are close.
It's understandable that
you're covering up for him.
Ling Borough is a tight knit family.
Besides, my sister is telling the truth.
She isn't covering up for him.
Why didn't you say anything?
Aren't you going to defend yourself?
Don't you know what day it is?
I do.
Let's not ruin the festivities.
After tonight,
you can ask me whatever you want.
You won't run away?
I won't.
Good.
No.
Why not?
What if he finds a chance to escape?
Lock him up.
The Lings always were harmonious people.
No one has committed a crime before.
So we don't have any jails here.
Put him in the woodshed.
The men of the Ye family will
guard the inner court.
The men of the Du family will
guard the outer court.
Lead the way.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Recently,
several outlander villagers
have been killed by Thunderbolt.
Everyone
[Ling Xiang, Ling Bo, Ling Kang An]
thought Qin Lie was the murderer.
After the investigation,
Qin Lie was vindicated.
It was just a misunderstanding.
Yes, yes.
Just a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding.
We apologise.
Misunderstanding.
I know you feel indignant.
But to us,
your defence is only a joke.
If Du Shao Yang says you're
the murderer,
then you're the murderer.
The old master is suffering
a serious injury.
The Du and Ye families are fighting
for the new master's seat.
So the Du family wants to gain
the Ling family's support.
If the Ling family wants to protect me,
they have no choice but
to side with the Du family.
So you're not stupid.
Kid, I can save you.
But I have one condition.
No need.
Lock the door.
l'm going to sleep.
-Lock it up.
-Yes.
Yu Xin.
Yu Shi, have you seen Xuan Xuan?
Where is Xuan Xuan?
I'm not dead, bookworm.
Qin Lie has been locked
up in the woodshed.
He...
I suggested the place.
Get what I mean?
You mean the tunnel I used
to meet with you when we were kids?
Later, when no one is looking,
you'll help him escape.
Qin Lie will not come out.
Is he trying to get himself killed?
Qin Lie,
if you don't work with me,
you will have no chance to live.
Qin Lie?
You're pretending to be asleep?
You're going to die, and you're
pretending to sleep?
Qin Lie,
you've escaped.
Come on. Let's leave Ling Borough.
Leave?
Why should I leave?
I sneaked out to see the moon.
Not to run away.
Yu Shi really does know you well.
Xuan Xuan said you're going
to die for sure.
You must leave.
Go back. I have things to think about.
Leave me alone.
Are you waiting for the moon or
are you thinking about things?
Can't I do both?
Why haven't you passed out?
Yu Xin,
carry my message to the chief.
Tell him the Ye family wants to use
me to get Ling Borough's support.
Ask the chief how he wants to handle it.
Go now.
Sneaking out as a suspect
just to see the moon.
Is it worth it?
We can see the moon at
Xingyun Pavilion every night.
I heard the moon at Xingyun Pavilion
is faint
and dim.
Nothing compared to the moon
at Ling Borough
which appears every year
clear and bright.
Where do you set your sights at?
Purple Mist Sea?
Artefact Forging Sect.
That far?
It's just the starting point.
Are you curious what's there?
Here in the far north,
people would kill
to get into Xingyun Pavilion.
They think Xingyun Pavilion
is the most glamorous place
in Chilan Continent.
Little do they know that Xingyun Pavilion
is the lowest
Bluestone Class in Chilan Continent.
People have no idea
how big the world is.
Do you have bigger ambitions?
All my life, I've been looking
for a kindred spirit.
Someone with high aspirations like me.
An equal with whom
I can explore
heaven and hell.
I noticed you
watching from the sidelines.
You obviously came here to convict me,
but you let Deacon Zhuo
do all the talking.
You're a scheming person.
Looking for a kindred spirit?
More like
looking for a
partner in crime.
The Spirit Realm is huge.
The Chilan Continent
is just a little speckle
at the edge of the realm.
And in the vast far north,
your family
is even more insignificant.
What's the use in having
high ambitions?
Without anyone to help you,
you might not even survive tonight,
let alone get out of Ling Borough.
You came all the way here
just to investigate the case?
You have no other purpose?
Why did you change the subject?
Because I don't think
we're hitting it off.
Get back to the woodshed.
Don't make me attack you.