[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 6]
Thank you! Thank you!
Everyone!
We'll drink to our hearts content today!
Great!
Take this for me.
How can they have the mood to get married
with one daughter missing?
We held the marriage for luck.
After that, Xuan Xuan will return.
Am I right?
Yes, that's right!
Then, let's begin.
Alright!
The bride and groom are here!
Come and have a seat.
Hurray!
The bride and groom are here!
[I'll set the formation on the pedestal.]
[It will be ready once you release]
[the Profound Heaven Seal.]
[This method would only harm
the Soul Reaping Beast.]
[To kill your wife's murderer]
[is a way to appease Ling Yu Shi's soul.]
The first bow to the ancient Mistress.
The second bow to the holy spirits.
The third bow to the parents.
What are you doing, Qin Lie?
She's not Yu Shi.
She's a Soul Reaping Beast.
Run!
Run! Get out of here!
Not me.
She's the Soul Reaping Beast.
Run!
My wife!
Mother!
-My wife! My wife!
-Mother!
Mother!
This is not the Heavenly Fire Formation.
This is the Ghost Fire Skull Formation.
Soul Reaping Beast!
You're using the power of thunder?
Use it.
They'll die a worse death under thunder.
I merely disguised as Ling Yu Shi
and played with you.
Then I disguised as Song Ting Yu
to confuse you.
Qin Lie.
Are you willing to concede defeat?
Who did I confess to that night?
The real Ling Yu Shi, of course.
You obviously care about her.
So I gave you a push.
Lastly, I created an illusion
on the mirror.
You're a fool, Qin Lie.
Why didn't you just kill me
at Xingyun Pavilion?
It's not enough to just kill you.
I want to witness you kill your beloved
and everyone at the Ling Borough!
Qin Lie!
Do it!
We'll die no matter what,
but we must take her with us!
Come on.
It's easy to kill, but it's the best
to break your heart!
Come!
Qin Lie.
How do you feel?
Are you happy?
Set formation!
Soul Reaping Beast!
We have the same level of cultivation
now as you were greatly injured
at the Snow God Valley.
How much power will you
recover with all these men?
They might be useless,
but you're useful!
My daughter!
Mother! Mother!
The Saintess gave her order.
No one from the Ling Borough
can leave this place.
Kill them if they do.
Yes!
Du Shao Yang!
What are you doing?
I said I'm acting
on Saintess Song's orders.
The families in the Xingyun Pavilion
had perished.
Your father took the chance
and became the master.
In fear of losing his place,
he immediately joined
Song Ting Yu's forces.
I wanted to befriend you,
but you had too many concerns.
What a pity.
Song Ting Yu wants to kill us?
We're unrelated to the Soul Reaping Beast.
Why are you killing us?
Song Ting Yu planned such a
formation just to hunt
the Soul Reaping Beast
and not caring about our lives.
It's obvious that
the Soul Reaping Beast was
not totally responsible
for the 33 villages that were massacred.
Song Ting Yu must be responsible!
So you want to keep us quiet from murder!
Du Shao Yang!
The Soul Reaping Beast
is really a tough enemy.
Why won't you let us out to fight?
With you?
Why waste our time with them?
-Let's fight our way out, Qin Lie!
-That's right!
Let's fight our way out!
Du Shao Yang.
Did you fight the Soul Reaping
Beast before?
I know you did.
So what?
In the God Trapping Cave,
and here.
I've fought the Soul Reaping Beast twice.
I know it better than you.
It likes to disguise as others
to hide itself.
It has great hatred
and great liking.
The hatred and liking
are both its weakness.
Didn't you want to win
Song Ting Yu's favour?
It hated
me and Song Ting Yu the most.
It would be happy
to see me in pain.
If it can witness our conflict,
it would show itself.
Let me out.
I'll fight the Soul Reaping Beast.
You'll get the credit.
What do you think?
Gong Mu Lie?
Why didn't he look at you?
How long did you love him?
How long did you yearn for him?
You're standing in front of him now.
But why didn't he look at you?
Why?
Because he hates you.
You're a liar!
Song Ting Yu.
He would look at you with disgust.
Are you afraid?
How would it feel to be hated
by your loved one?
Do you dare to look into his eyes?
You wretch!
-Aunt Hua is dead, Uncle Ling is dead.
-Qin Lie!
Everyone of the Ling family is dead!
It's all your fault!
I'll kill you, Song Ting Yu!
How dare you, Qin Lie?
It's him!
What a great fight!
You're not young anymore.
Why are you acting like a child
and showed yourself when we're fighting?
How dare you be insolent?
It was for the plan.
You did it on purpose!
Why are you acting like a child too?
Subdue it first!
Uncle Liang!
Don't worry, we've planted our
men all over the place to
force it to the Silent Abyss.
-After it!
Silent Abyss?
Follow up!
[Silent Abyss]
Saintess, it's in the Silent Abyss.
Let's go down.
-Yes!
Why don't you attack?
You can't use your illusion here, huh?
Skilled masters had duelled here
ten thousand years ago
and broke the balance of the
world with their might.
Therefore, a strong Soul Dispersing
Barrier was cast here.
Every illusion would lose its magic here.
The hunt on the snowing grounds,
Snow God Valley,
the Ling Borough and the Silent Abyss
are all your doings.
You used countless lives
as your trap just to kill me.
Everyone said we're evil.
But the real evil is you, the humans!
Xie Jing Xuan died because of you.
I'll sacrifice you to appease her soul.
Set formation!
How would such thunder power affect me?
Baji Fire Formation!
You can't stand thunder and fire.
You'll die today.
Saintess!
You used the Ghost Fire Skull Formation
on yourself?
It levelled up.
How could this be?
So what with the Soul Dispersing Barrier?
I'm not restricted from any rules
if I use my body as the medium
of the formation.
The Silent Abyss
will be your grave today.
Die!
You should be the one to die!
Qin Lie!
Leave!
Let's go, Saintess.
Let's go!
Let's go.
The Thunder Jade.
Qin Lie was here.
Saintess.
Are you alright, Saintess?
Heavenly Thunder?
Thunder of the Ninth Heaven?
Why is it here?
Hua Yu Xin!
Yu Shi.
Yu Shi!
[Lin Yu Shi enters the memory
from 10,000 years ago]
In the beginning,
the Realm of Ruined Souls
bore sacred stones
with a crystal-like and
exquisite disposition.
It can foresee everything in the world
and relates with promises.
[The Mother of Earth and the
Child of the War God]
[shouldn't fall in love.]
[If made known to evil forces,]
[they won't come to a good end
[before they could be together.]
[But now,]
[you've developed feelings
for each other.]
[Chong Ming]
Do you choose to fight each other
or forget each other?
[You may decide on your own.]
The Soul Dispersing Barrier was broken.
I never thought that
the Thunder of the Ninth Heaven
would be so powerful.
How can Qin Lie summon
the heavenly thunder
and break the rules of the
heaven and earth?
The Soul Reaping Beast is dead.
The Thunderbolt subdues evil.
All evil in the world
can never escape the wrath
of the Thunderbolt.
The Soul Reaping Beast
has been eliminated.
What about Qin Lie?
He must've perished with it.
Du Shao Yang, who exactly is this
Qin Lie?
He's just an average cultivator
from the Ling family.
But I didn't know why he was able to
summon the Thunderbolt.
I don't want word the hunt to get out.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The Ling Borough will be destroyed.
If you accomplish the mission,
I'll name your father as the master
of the Xingyun Pavilion.
Thank you, Saintess.
General Pu Jiao at your service, Saintess.
[Pu Jiao]
Thank goodness you're alright.
Where is the beast?
With my mighty men,
we've set up traps outside to ensure...
What do you want?
Where's my son?
Where did my son go?
Hua Yu Xin
jumped down the Silent Abyss.
Perhaps, he had perished with the
Soul Reaping Beast alongside Qin Lie.
How could they?
Did you kill my son?
-Boss! Boss!
-Give me back my son!
-Calm down!
-My son!
-I... You...
-Calm down.
What a racket!
Calm down, calm down!
Senior Pu Jiao.
The Ling Borough has 147 people.
Excluding those who have died,
there are 47 people left.
29 of them are from the Ling family.
What are you waiting for?
Kill them.
Wait!
I want to see Saintess Song.
We don't have to meet her!
I'd rather
fight you to my death today.
If you kill ten of my people,
I'll bring ten of your men down!
That's right! Bring them down!
-Kill them!
What are you doing?
I'm the master's younger brother!
You want to massacre the Ling Borough?
Aren't you afraid of the Master of Frost?
The Master of Frost?
He saved Qin Lie before
and sent snow wolves to escort
him to the Xingyun Pavilion.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't know.
Besides,
the wolves escorted him.
The Master of Frost did not show herself.
We're not sure
if Qin Lie was indeed friends
with the Master of Frost.
Darn you, Du Shao Yang!
How dare you hide it from us?
Did you think you're able
to fool the Saintess?
Please be appeased, Saintess.
Leave this rascal to me.
How will you punish him?
Saintess Song.
Du Shao Yang deserves to die.
But we would be in trouble
if we annihilated Ling Borough.
Lock him up.
Roger!
Don't punish him, just lock him up.
Yes.
Let's go.
You can leave too.
The Ling Borough...
Leave us.
Yes.
Uncle Liang.
What do you think?
According to Du Shao Yang and Gao Yu,
the Master of Frost did not show herself.
Now that Qin Lie is dead,
no one would know her relation
with Qin Lie.
But rumours said that she never meddled
in mortal world affairs,
-but she helped Qin Lie.
-Qin Lie is dead.
It's none of her concern
even if I kill his family.
Qin Lie belongs to the Ling Borough.
Though she's strong,
she's only formidable in the north.
If she leaves the far north,
the Profound Heaven Alliance is not
to be trifled with.
She's a level seven spirit beast
in match with our strongest man.
It's better to leave her alone.
You scared me to death when you ran away.
I couldn't catch up on you,
so I asked Ling Xin to join me.
[How did I delve into that
piece of memory?]
I have some words for you.
Leave us.
I'm Song Ting Yu,
the Saintess of Profound Heaven Alliance.
Now that we've captured the
Soul Reaping Beast twice,
I can be counted as Qin Lie's friend.
Where's Qin Lie?
He perished with the Soul Reaping Beast.
Qin Lie did well
in the hunt this time.
I'll ask for a reward for him
when I return to the Alliance.
The Alliance will be responsible
for all the damages caused here.
Someone will send other rewards
here to you later.
What about his body?
Qin Lie burned with the Soul
Reaping Beast under
the Thunderbolt.
Qin Lie masters the thunder technique.
How would it harm him?
He must be afraid to face me
and decided to run away.
He would return in a few days.
It's natural to refuse to
accept a sudden death.
Please accept my condolence.
Another matter awaits your
decision, Miss Yu Shi.
Bring him in.
This person has evil thoughts
against the Ling Borough
and have repeatedly threatened you.
You can decide
whether to kill or punish him.
If I kill him today,
his father will come for revenge.
What should
I do then?
Kill his father
like how you killed him.
Miss Yu Shi.
I promise
to not disturb the Ling family again.
The Xingyun Pavilion
will never disturb the Ling family.
[Even if I kill him,]
[should I]
[implicate the Ling family too?]
Leave.
You're releasing him?
Yes.
We wanted her to kill the
boy to build hatred
between themselves.
If that had happened,
they would attack the Ling family
and we could push it onto the Du family.
With that,
we would not only earn fame
but won't offend the Mistress.
This Ling Yu Shi is smart.
She knew they couldn't become enemies.
That's why she let Du Shao Yang go.
The Eight Extreme Sanctuary and
Profound Heaven Alliance
collaborated in capturing
the Soul Reaping Beast.
But the Eight Extremes Temple released the
Soul Reaping Beast
and lost their Saintess, Xie Jing Xuan.
Now that we destroyed the
Soul Reaping Beast,
the entire continent will come to us.
That's why we mustn't spread the news
that Qin Lie killed the
Soul Reaping Beast.
That was why I sent Pu Jiao
to the Xingyun Pavilion.
He would be able to draw hatred
between the two families.
I don't understand.
Why did you send the arrogant
Pu Jiao to do it?
He could fight in a war, but he would
make mistakes at planning.
It would be nice
if he made mistakes.
You wretched thing!
How dare you lie to the Saintess?
You're seeking death!
You're feigning innocence
just by kicking your son?
Are you fooling me, Du Hai Tian?
What intelligence, Lord Emissary.
You saw through
my thoughts easily.
No wonder Saintess Song ordered you
to hold the Profound Heaven Badge
and take charge of the Xingyun Pavilion.
The Chilan Continent
is managed together by us
and the Eight Extremes Temple.
We were equals before,
but the Eight Extremes Temple
lost Saintess Xie.
Saintess Song
got the credit for killing the
Soul Reaping Beast.
Looking at the straits,
we're obviously winning.
The Palace of Hell is one level higher
than the Xingyun Pavilion,
but we're directly managed
by the Profound Heaven Alliance.
Understand?
Yes!
Of course.
Everyone in the Xingyun Pavilion
will listen to Lord Pu Jiao only.
To protect our peace,
Saintess Song wished that the two families
could patch things up.
Our families
had a little misunderstanding.
It's nothing serious.
Of course we would patch things up.
Shao Yang.
Prepare gifts
and send them to the Ling Borough.
Yes, Father.
[Hua Yu Xin]
[Qin Lie]
Qin Lie.
Yu Xin.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for being late.
I'm sorry to you guys.
Soul Reaping Beast!
I was hurt by the Thunderbolt
and will disperse soon.
Sure.
I'll send you off.
With your weak skills?
You failed at mastering thunder,
so you learned to use fire.
You can't even burn an ant with that fire.
Do you think you can hurt me?
This is our sacred ring
made from the previous
Evil God's conscience.
Evil God?
The Evil God was the strongest
being created
ten thousand years ago to protect
the Realm of Ruined Souls.
When the immortals attacked,
the Evil God perished on behalf of men.
Its soul was scattered in the continent.
Three thousand years ago,
the Nether Tribe began to collect
the remnants of the soul.
But with its body destroyed,
the Evil God needed a new host.
It chose you.
Me?
Why me?
Don't you want to become strong?
You must be strong
to win the person you want,
to protect the ones you love,
and get rid of the hatred in your heart.
Do you
want to become the strongest being?
[Do you know what is most
regretful in life?]
[To lose a great chance.]
Yes.
I do.
Good.
That's it!
I found the right person.
It's right.
It's right!
My brother.
I won't spare anyone
that disregarded you
and the Ling family's lives.