[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 2]
Young Master,
all the people of Ling Family
are ungrateful.
I think we should save
the window dressing.
Just arrest all of them.
They will have to submit to us.
If they still refuse to submit to us,
what do we do?
How is that possible?
When you stepped in just now,
how did they react?
Du Fei,
Ling Borough
is located in the extreme north
of Chilan Continent.
It lacks supplies
and is under the threat of spirit beasts.
The villagers here
do not have high qualification,
most of them are humans
with no talent for cultivation.
This kind of people
have nothing to lose.
When they're under extreme stress,
they'll risk it all.
If you fight with them,
both sides will end up in destruction.
I was wrong.
Qin Lie must die,
whether or not he's the murderer
who massacred the villages.
You should know very well
that you are a pawn which means nothing.
For the sake of winning Ling Family over,
Du Shao Yang will keep you.
But the village massacres
definitely need a closure.
Du Shao Yang
will turn his back on you too.
You're so annoying.
So will they keep me or cast me aside?
-You...
-Stand right there.
I'm here to deliver food.
Let her in.
I'm doing you this favour
because you're the daughter
of the chief of Ling Family.
Silly boy,
keep in mind that you owe me a favour.
Go ahead.
Are you hungry?
Here.
Has the moon come up?
The moon comes up very late this year.
Maybe it is also waiting for you.
Come,
give me your hand.
Burn it for me.
No.
Father is figuring a way out.
You will get out of here.
Burn it yourself.
What if I can't get out?
Just listen to me.
How are things out there?
Du Shao Yang doesn't seem
concerned at all.
He is at ease
with letting the Zhuos guard you.
The Zhuos
actually sent two people
to monitor Du Shao Yang.
But those two people
have disappeared into thin air.
What is Du Shao Yang doing right now?
He and his subordinates
are taking a rest now.
Are you trying to say...
Go find Yu Xin.
Tell him not to act rashly.
Go there right now.
Tell him I'll figure out a way
to resolve this crisis.
Do you remember what I said
when I was carrying you
on the snowy field?
You said it's useless to worry.
Alright,
I'll listen to you.
Qin Lie,
if striking can't stun you,
I'll beat you till you pass out.
Ye, come over here.
Have you figured it out?
You don't want to die any more
after seeing your loved one, right?
That is exactly why I let her see you.
I guess you came
from early Natal Opening Realm,
you're not even that skilled.
If you don't wish to die,
take your men and leave immediately.
The two warriors you asked
to guard the Du Family
have been killed by Du Shao Yang.
What are you talking about?
So these people were killed by me,
right?
Yes.
They were killed by your Thunderbolt.
You're suspecting me
for the massacres of the 33 villages.
Now you come to Ling Borough
to arrest me.
That makes sense.
I know the power struggle of
Xingyun Pavilion is involved.
But I still can't figure out
what you have up your sleeve.
Have you figured it out now?
Arresting a suspect for interrogation
will not do you any good.
But a Ling killed a Ye.
The Yes will definitely
condemn them for it.
In order to stop the Ling Family
from submitting to the Du Family,
the Ye Family will take the opportunity
to demolish Ling Borough.
The only family
who can take Ling Family under its wing
is Du Family.
That is why Ling Borough
has no choice but to submit to
the Du Family.
Not only can they force
Ling Borough to yield,
they can also get rid of Zhuo Qian
and deflate the Ye Family.
Should I say that you are despicable
or compliment you for being wise?
I do not want Xingyun Pavilion.
This is only my first step
to help my father
win the position of master.
So what if I was despicable
or wise?
Does that mean anything?
This is only your first step.
Does that mean you'll be fair and square
in the future?
Qin Lie!
What are you doing here?
What is happening?
They killed a Ye member.
Now they're trying to pin it on me.
Du Fei!
Qin Lie, run!
Find Gao Yu.
Let...
Let him go.
Just leave already.
I don't want you to die here either.
I want you to die outside,
die on the vast snow field
till your remains perish.
Will you leave or not?
If you don't leave,
I'll kill him right now.
No!
Qin Lie, run!
I'll leave, I'll leave.
Young Master,
why didn't you kill Qin Lie
to cover it up?
Instead of killing him
and leaving no evidence,
we'll accuse him of fleeing.
He's badly injured.
He won't be able to make it anyway.
In that case,
I will inform the Ling Family right away.
Wait for a little longer.
Yu Shi.
Where is Yu Xin?
Don't worry.
He's an adult.
Do you think he'd get lost?
Does this
belong to Qin Lie?
Let me see.
I just want to see
what Qin Lie wrote in it.
Only the moon knows what you want.
Fine, fine,
I'll find Yu Xin.
Yu Shi,
are you really not curious
about what Qin Lie wrote?
Qin Lie,
the moon has come up.
[I'm as insignificant as a speck of dust,
they hardly spared me a glance.]
[I'll get to the highest, furthest, look
into their eyes, they'll look into mine.]
Bad news!
Bad news, Father!
Bad news.
Father, bad news.
Something happened to Qin Lie.
-Qin Lie!
-Where are you, Qin Lie?
-Yu Shi.
Qin Lie!
Her Fire Poison has flared up.
Let's take her back first.
No.
That day I already knew
he must have noticed something.
I already knew
that he purposely sent me away.
But I still left.
Du Shao Yang intended to frame Qin Lie.
Even if you had stayed,
both of us could've only watched
him being hurt.
Yu Shi,
you haven't rested for two days.
Your body won't be able to take it.
How about this? Ling Ying
and Ling Xin will take you home first.
Yu Xin and I will continue searching.
We will find him no matter what,
alive,
or dead.
No.
The first group who went out to search
last night came back and said
that they saw a corpse
beside the snow cliff.
I must go and see.
-Yu Shi!
Yu Shi.
Last night, I really hated to disturb
your annual moon viewing event.
Hence, I waited until the moon went down
before I asked my subordinate
to announce Qin Lie's murder and escape.
Now that the sky has turned bright.
Do you have any result
after a long night of discussion?
The people of the borough
have all set out to look for Qin Lie.
We will be informed once they find him.
So what will happen
if they can't find him?
Qin Lie will never murder anyone.
If he hadn't killed anyone,
why would he escape?
That's because you wanted to kill him!
Then who is dead now?
Last night, Hua Yu Xin testified
and said he saw Qin Lie kill Du Fei
with his own eyes.
Hua Yu Xin also said
that he did not see
Qin Lie kill Ye Family with his own eyes.
Instead, it was you
who threatened Qin Lie with his life
to force him to leave.
Hua Yu Xin is Qin Lie's best friend.
If he wants to clear his name,
he will naturally make excuses.
I believe all of you have witnessed
how the Ye Family died.
In the entire Ling Borough,
other than Qin Lie,
who else is familiar
with thunder technique?
If no one else in Ling Borough knows,
can you guarantee there's no one out there
or even your people know it?
So you'd rather have
the whole Ling Borough destroyed
to protect Qin Lie.
I will not mention how much Mr Qin
has contributed to Ling Borough,
let's just talk about Qin Lie.
He is frank and upright.
Even if he has really killed them,
I believe
that he was definitely forced to do so.
If Qin Lie can't make it out alive,
the only people who knows the truth
is you, Young Master Du,
right?
The truth is
the Ye member was killed
by thunder technique.
But Qin Lie was the only person there.
As you see it,
what would the Ye Family think?
Then what do we do?
One of our family members
had died too.
I will not hold anyone to account.
But the Ye member
died at the Ling Family.
That's a hard nut to crack.
Even if I wish to stand surety
for the Ling Family,
there are also some difficulties.
Young Master Du, do you have any idea?
Just tell us.
If there's a matrimonial alliance
between the Du and Ling families,
perhaps
it won't be that difficult.
[Land of Frost]
We've inspected this area.
-You may leave now.
-Yes, sir.
Saintess,
my subordinates have inspected this area.
So far everything is fine.
[Song Ting Yu,
Saintess of Profound Heaven Alliance]
[Xie Jing Xuan,
Saintess of Eight Extremes Temple]
Saintess, he's come round.
That leaf is mine.
Give it back to me!
Get him up.
This leaf is a spirit herb.
So you're from Ling Borough.
Who are you?
We are...
Don't tell him.
But I want to tell him.
What is this place?
This place
should be Ice Cliff Forest.
How far is this place
from Snow God Valley?
Snow God Valley?
If you're going to Snow God Valley,
then you've taken the wrong road.
You've been there?
Of course he has, that's how
he knows we've taken the wrong road.
I've never been there,
but I've heard about it.
Snow God Valley is in the North.
But you're heading towards the West.
Since you know,
then you will lead the way.
Why should I?
Because we're here
to capture Soul Reaping Beast.
Soul Reaping Beast is the most evil
spirit beast in the Netherworld.
It devours everything
to enhance its strength.
Ordinary blade and sword skills
can't do anything to it.
Only Thunderbolt can harm it.
Thunderbolt?
Do you guys know Thunderbolt?
How about you?
If you know, I'll take you there too.
Can you stop talking nonsense?
I can lead you there,
but you have to do me a favour.
Ling Borough is in trouble.
You have to help me
save Ling Borough first.
They're just ordinary people.
They all go through birth, ageing,
sickness and death.
So what if they're sacrificed?
But if we don't hunt down
Soul Reaping Beast,
not only Ling Borough,
the entire Chilan Continent
will suffer as well.
Take us to Snow God Valley
to kill Soul Reaping Best first.
Ling Borough
is on the verge of destruction!
I'm killing the spirit beast
for the overall interest.
You just want to make your father happy.
One more word
and I will kill you first.
You're scaring me.
Will you go or not?
I'm badly injured.
I can't walk.
I can heal you anytime,
but I can also take your life anytime.
Lead the way.
Alright.
I'll lead you there,
but you have to return the leaf
to me first.
Let's set out.
I want to marry his daughter,
but he seemed troubled.
Young Master, don't worry.
I've spread the word
regarding Du Family's marriage proposal
to the Lings.
Let his kin pressure him,
then he'll have no choice
but to marry his daughter off.
Sir, may I know your name?
Liang Zhong.
[Liang Zhong, Profound Heaven Alliance]
Mr Liang.
I heard
that you address them as Saintess.
What are you trying to ask?
You better don't try anything funny.
I just want to find out their background.
Where are you from?
I came here with Saintess Song.
The fierce one?
Both of them
don't even know the direction.
Can they even
capture Soul Reaping Beast?
Saintess Song has profound spiritual power
and exquisite art of war.
No one dares to go against her order.
As for Saintess Xie...
I'll remind you something.
If you offend her,
I guarantee
that you will end up miserably.
Yu Shi, I'm back.
Do you feel better?
Did you find him?
We eventually got to Snow Cliff.
There was indeed a corpse there,
but it wasn't Qin Lie.
We wanted to continue searching,
but Yu Xin was freezing,
so we came back first.
But Yu Shi, don't worry.
That corpse really isn't Qin Lie.
Qin Lie is certainly still alive.
The snowy field is freezing,
spirit beasts are raging,
whereas Qin Lie is badly injured.
There's a slim chance that he'll survive.
Xuan Xuan,
deep down,
you have the same thought as well,
haven't you?
When I just arrived,
I realised the borough was deathly quiet.
I am afraid that the tide has turned.
Go and check it out.
I'll go right now.
How dare you run away from us!
Back then, it was you
who massacred the 33 villages.
While we're on our way
to hunt down Soul Reaping Beast,
we passed by mountains and villages.
No matter where we go,
it's inevitable
for the innocents to suffer.
Can you show some emotion when you speak?
So many people have died
but you're still unconcerned.
Qin Lie,
we brought a total of 3,510 people
to kill Soul Reaping Beast.
After several fierce battles,
these people are what we have left.
After going through
several fierce battles,
the saintesses are also suffering
from severe injuries.
Now they haven't recovered yet.
Is Soul Reaping Beast in Snow God Valley?
We dispatched a troop there.
Those who were alive reported
that Snow God Valley is the place
where Soul Reaping Beast recuperates.
I can lead you there.
I can also help you
hunt Soul Reaping Beast down.
Apart from that,
I also practice thunder technique.
But I have one condition.
Back then, you accidentally killed
thirty three villages.
But now, Xingyun Pavilion
is condemning Ling Borough for this.
Send someone over
to clear Ling Borough's name first.
No.
Hunting down Soul Reaping Beast
is an important matter.
If I have one less person,
I'll have less strength.
So I can't lose any of them.
You...
The strong ones are ruthless.
It is true indeed.
Let's go.
They said they'll arrest those
who practice thunder technique.
In fact,
they're coming for us Lings.
In order to win the position of master,
Ye and Du have been
in secret power struggle for years.
Now Du Shao Yang is threatening us
with matrimonial alliance
because he is trying
to make us side with the Du Family.
They said Qin Lie is a murderer.
Who would buy that?
I don't even need to think to know
that it was Du Shao Yang
who hid some men with thunder technique,
killed the people
and pinned it on Qin Lie.
Now he's threatening us.
But so what?
Does he have any proof?
The three of you, get this done for me.
Cover me from the spies of Du Shao Yang.
I'm leaving to meet Ye Yang Qiu.
What?
Since we can't run away from this trouble,
then we should get involved in it.
The Du Family wants to rope us in,
so does the Ye Family.
Cheng Ye,
are you out of your mind?
I bet you have a hidden agenda.
You just want to protect your daughter.
I just want to protect
the pride of the Ling Family.
Our Ling Family
is at the extreme north.
The life we live here is the toughest.
But for over 20,000 years,
our kins
have shielded us from all the troubles.
That's how we came this far.
Think properly.
Since when have we chosen
to not fight back?
to await our doom?
If we were to submit,
we would make the call
as to who we submit to.
Now the Du Family shows us no mercy.
Then we should bring them down first.
Du Hai Tian is a ruthless man.
If he finds out,
Ling Borough will have no choice
but to die.
As for Ye Yang Qiu, the chief of
Ye Family is a wolf in sheep's clothing.
If we rely on him,
it will do no good as well.
You're out of your mind.
You're totally out of your mind!
Chief, why are you
making a big deal out of it?
Isn't marrying your daughter to them
a good thing?
You'll be so proud.
Chief!
You are...
Chief,
we've heard
about the matrimonial alliance.
What's your plan?
As long as you give us an order,
we will stand by you.
Even if we have to fight it out
with the Du Family,
we won't have second thoughts.
Yes, we won't have second thoughts!
But if you're marrying your daughter off,
Yu Shi has to agree first.
Exactly. Ling Borough
will not be threatened by the Dus.
That's right.
As the saying goes, daughter should
be married to a eligible man.
Even if we're marrying off our daughter,
we should walk tall.
Yes, we shouldn't be bullied by the Dus!
Alright, alright.
Folks, I'm very grateful
for all your support.
Thank you.
Thank you to all of you.
[How far can they go?]
[How far do you want them to go?]
Yu Shi.
Xingyun Pavilion is here to force me
to get married.
Yu Shi, you knew.
Are you giving up?
Qin Lie might still be alive.
He will come back.
Xingyun Pavilion is on the warpath.
I can't wait until he comes back.
Hold on.
What's the matter?
Something's wrong with this lake.
You guys, go check it out over there.
-Yes.
This is Hanji Lake.
Wait for order here. Do not go in rashly.
Qin Lie,
what is going on?
There's a Gold Devouring Black Tortoise
in the lake.
What is that?
Gold Devouring Black Tortoise
wakes up every six months
and goes to sleep every six months.
It is spring now.
It should be still asleep now.
How can it eat humans if it's asleep?
I heard about it from someone else.
Gold Devouring Black Tortoise
loves eating metal.
Even when it's asleep,
it can still exude suction to metal.
All of you are wearing iron armours.
Once you step on the ice,
you'll naturally be sucked
by Gold Devouring Black Tortoise.
Remove your armour.
Cross the lake.
Those two weak girls
don't even say a word
although they're freezing.
Weak girls?
What are you doing?
I want to let him know
that we're not weak girls.
Go get it!
Now!
You...
You're already injured.
The lake is freezing.
You won't be able to take it.
How could you mess with her
when you knew she's injured?
Jump in and save her!
Why don't you do it?
It's none of my business.
You're the one who should do it.
Leaving someone for dead
isn't something a gentleman should do.
Saintess.
Saintess. Help her up.
Saintess, the box...
Don't mention the box ever again.
Let's set out.
Set out!
Pervert.