[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 4]
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Are you cold?
I was sent here to serve you.
But since I came,
you've been looking outside.
It's been two hours since then.
What are you looking at?
Somewhere
very far away.
Today is my son, Shao Yang's wedding.
The Dus and Lings are united by marriage.
From now on,
the Fengs govern the south
while the Lings govern the north.
Combining their powers
as well as ours, the Du Family,
we'll serve Xingyun Pavilion.
Excellent.
It's the auspicious time,.
The new couple may enter.
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Smile.
Master Du, congratulations.
I specially come here
for the happy occasion.
Master Ye.
Today is my son's wedding.
It's nothing important.
You are a very busy person.
Your presence is not necessary.
I may be a busy person,
but it's necessary to send you a gift.
Master Ye,
you think we can't afford good wine?
No.
If there's anything that
Master Du and Shao Yang
can't handle by yourselves,
I would be glad to help.
There's nothing that
I can't handle myself.
I heard the murderer of Ye Zhuo Qian
is from Ling Borough.
That's correct.
The person who killed Zhuo Qian
is Qin Lie from Ling Borough.
Qin Lie's surname is Qin, not Ling.
He was injured by me
and he couldn't have survived.
I've sought revenge
on behalf of Ye family.
It's not a big deal.
You don't have to thank me.
I also heard,
Ling Yu Shi and Qin Lie
are in a relationship.
Qin Lie is dead.
Their relationship
has ended.
An old flame
is hard to forget.
I have used the
Flower of Laugh and Forget,
and Break Off Grass to make this wine.
Flower of Laugh and Forget
gives you stomach ache.
Break Off Grass
makes your heart hurt.
These are the aches of a break-up.
I hope the bride will drink this wine,
to forget about the past
and previous relationship.
To spend a harmonious life
with Shao Yang.
Master Ye, I appreciate your presence,
but the gift is not necessary.
Huang'er,
take away the gift.
Su'er.
It's best to drink it now.
Shao Yang killed the bride's ex-lover.
The bride may want revenge.
The marriage is fake,
to murder her husband is real.
If you're not careful,
there'll be bloodshed tonight.
This is for Shao Yang's benefit.
If it's the kindness of an elder,
Yu Shi,
drink it.
Du Shao Yang.
Drink it.
-You!
-Father.
Good, good.
Now, all of you need not worry
about the groom getting murdered tonight.
We can first have a bloodshed
in the wedding hall.
Even if my daughter and I must die here,
it's fine.
Seems like an old flame
is really hard to forget.
Yu Shi.
What do you mean?
This wine breaks off relationship,
but is it my relationship with Qin Lie?
If that's true,
may I ask Master Ye,
what magic did you use to brew this wine?
If there is such magic,
all relationships in this world
would be controlled by you.
If it's not true,
if I am in love with Shao Yang,
must I endure the pain of
breaking off with him?
We're getting married today,
and you want us to break off?
Urgent!
Qin Lie is here to take the bride.
What?
Watch her.
Qin Lie.
You are alive.
Where's Yu Shi?
Qin Lie has entered
the Natal Opening Realm.
He didn't die during energy upgrade.
He has a very bright future.
Hand over Yu Shi.
Otherwise,
I'll reveal the truth
of Zhuo Qian's death.
You can try.
In an hour's time,
if Du Jun doesn't see me,
Ling Yu Shi will die.
All right.
I won't get in the way of
the Du and Ye families,
but let the Ling family go.
How will you explain about
the Ye family then?
What do you care?
You are Qin Lie.
You killed Zhuo Qian.
[Profound Heaven]
The Profound Heaven Badge.
I am the Profound Heaven Emissary.
Kneel before the emissary.
Welcome to Xingyun Pavilion,
Profound Heaven Emissary.
You killed Zhuo Qian?
You'll do anything
to achieve your goals.
You're a fool.
Please don't be upset.
My son was careless.
He has caused your suffering.
You've put up a good show.
He even vomited blood'
It's hard for me to stay angry.
What do you intend to do
about the Ye family's matter?
One,
call off the wedding.
Two,
we go back to Ling Borough.
Three,
never make trouble with the Lings again.
As for the matter with the Ye family,
what's it to do with me?
Fine.
Heaven is my witness.
I am sorry.
You guys killed the Ye member.
Didn't you?
If Qin Lie had exposed you in public,
you would've killed me immediately.
Right?
The emissary is here.
Sir.
The case of the massacre,
I have the duty to investigate
as Head of Criminal Law Department.
I also must get to the bottom of
Zhuo Qian's death.
I hope you...
The Soul Reaping Beast did it.
Zhuo Qian died,
I was injured and fled into the snowfield.
Saintesses from Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple rescued me.
The saintesses came to the north
to capture the Soul Reaping Beast.
I helped in the killing of the beast
and was permitted to take the Badge
to resolve my matters here.
Hold on.
What's a Soul Reaping Beast?
The most evil spirit beast
in the Netherworld
If allowed to roam freely,
a single beast can destroy
the entire Chilan.
Where are the two saintesses?
Why didn't they come with you?
You must be Master Ye?
The Elder of Bluestone Class.
Above you are Masters of
Xingyun Pavilion, Palace of Hell,
Profound Heaven Alliance and
Eight Extremes Temple respectively.
You mean,
you want the saintesses
to come see you personally?
No.
You and the Du family discussed
behind closed doors.
What is it that you can't be frank?
I colluded with the Du family
in the murder of Zhuo Qian
and we discussed position of
master of Xingyun Pavilion
behind closed doors.
Are you happy
with my answer?
The marriage of Du and Ling
is called off.
Yu Shi.
It's safe now, come with me.
What's the matter?
Du Shao Yang said,
you used the truth of Ye's murder
in exchange of my freedom?
Yes.
I asked him
whether you hesitated?
He said,
no.
Of course, I didn't hesitate.
Are you here to take me by force?
Yes, I am taking you by force.
Stop talking, come with me.
Where are we going?
I'm still in my wedding gown.
Take it off.
Where are we going?
Going back to Ling Borough.
Yu Shi.
Are you all right?
Are you frightened?
Go back to Ling Borough.
After that?
After that...
Since you're taking me by force,
after that,
will you marry me?
What?
If you're not marrying me,
why are you taking me by force?
Yu Shi.
What's the matter with you?
[The sky and the moon.]
[The stars.]
[The Spirit Realm.]
[The flowers, trees, and land.]
[The classes and the world.]
[Continent is divided into classes.]
[The celestial has its hierarchy.]
[I live in the most
insignificant wasteland,]
[looking up to the nine heavens.]
[The highest and farthest
point of the sky,]
[who lives amongst thy?]
[Are they looking at me,]
[as I look at them?]
[I am insignificant.]
[I'm going to the
highest and farthest point.]
[Or,]
[I am insignificant like a dust,]
[I am never worthy of them?]
[I am going to the highest
and farthest point in the sky,]
[to look them in the eye,]
[and have them look straight into mine.]
[I am insignificant.]
[I'm going to the
highest and farthest point.]
You have a far-fetch dream,
and I am not in it.
So, why are you taking me by force?
Yu Shi, actually...
I am willing to be your shadow,
chasing after your light.
I can wait
for your return after your journeys.
I shouldn't hope
for you to include me in your world.
I have chosen not to follow you,
to be forgotten by you.
You shouldn't have came back.
You shouldn't have came for me.
I...
Why did you come for me?
What do you want me to do?
Qin Lie, lunch is ready.
I have just eaten.
You can eat again.
How could you ask her
what she wants you to do?
Don't you know to a woman,
it's a heinous thing to say?
You are not a woman,
how do you know?
I've been scolded enough
by Xuan Xuan to know that.
What else could I say?
I never thought about love.
Besides thunder energy,
what's on your mind?
Besides yourself, who doesn't know
she's in love with you?
Why didn't you tell me?
If I told you,
you'd drift further and hurt her more.
Stop it.
You must listen to this.
Yu Shi is soft and gentle.
She mustered up her courage
to confess to you.
Yet you ask her what she wants?
Grief is a woman's nature,
but men can't lose their demeanour.
If a woman is forced into a corner,
who knows what she would do?
So,
I had to interrupt.
You seem to have suddenly understood.
Since when were you so good
with male-female relationships?
Yes.
Xuan Xuan used to scold me everyday.
I couldn't understand.
Now Xuan Xuan is gone,
I finally understood.
Why did Qin Lie come
and not you?
I am Du Shao Yang's uncle.
Unless,
you want me to take my nephew's wife?
What's wrong with that?
You don't like her? You can't take her?
I love you, little brother.
The wedding has been called off.
You can compete with Qin Lie
and you might win.
He's now the Profound Heaven Emissary.
I'll lose.
Even if I win,
Qin Lie is my best friend.
Robbing my best friend's sweetheart?
How could you ask me to do that?
I want you to do just that.
You're the son of the Gao family.
You love Ling Yu Shi, but she ignores you.
Qin Lie doesn't love her,
but she wants to follow him.
Honestly, I don't like Ling Yu Shi.
But if you like her,
you can go get her.
If you don't like her,
I won't go after her.
I'll get someone you like.
-All right?
-Naughty.
You can't forget her.
It hurts me to see you suffer.
They wanted to leave.
It took me a lot of trouble,
a lot of effort,
to keep them for a night.
You have one night
to persuade her to stay on.
My dear sister,
I know you're doing this for me.
Yes, I like Yu Shi.
But I must wait till
she realises Qin Lie doesn't love her
and gives up willingly.
Then I'll confess to her.
My foolish brother,
you don't understand women.
A woman like Ling Yu Shi
often heads into blind alleys.
The more Qin Lie dislikes her,
the more she can't let go.
If Qin Lie doesn't like her forever,
she'll wait for him forever.
Will she do that?
Of course.
Listen to me, go and get her.
Qin Lie doesn't know love.
Even if you take her woman,
he won't feel sad.
[If you're not marrying me,]
[why are you taking me by force?]
[I am willing to be a shadow,]
[chasing after your light.]
[I can wait]
[for your return after your journeys.]
[I shouldn't hope for you
to include me in your world.]
[I have chosen not to follow you,]
[to be forgotten by you.]
[You shouldn't have came back.]
[You shouldn't have came for me.]
[Why did you come for me?]
Emissary.
Now that we've reached an agreement,
can we forget
all our previous grievances?
You speak very well, Young Master Du.
Forget our previous grievances.
After that?
With your character,
you will seek revenge for
what happened today.
It's fine.
I won't let you off anyway.
The night is misty and gloomy
in Xingyun Pavilion.
In Ling Borough,
the moon shines brightly once a year.
But in Xingyun Pavilion,
at least you can
see the moon every night.
If you take a step forward,
the moonlight is even brighter.
Another step forward,
you can see the starry night.
Sky full of stars,
how does it look like?
Black Iron Class is above Bluestone Class.
Above Black Iron is Red Copper.
I envy you.
You met someone from Red Copper Class.
It is said that beyond Chilan Continent,
in a faraway land,
there exists Silver Class.
The Spirit Realm is huge.
One can't find its border
even after thousands of years.
We don't even know
what the legendary
Central Golden Place holds?
I hope one day,
I can witness the legend.
I dislike you,
but I must admit,
what you're thinking
is also what I think.
I've said before.
I've been searching for
a person who has high ambitions like me.
You disdain me,
but I don't want to be your enemy.
Not that I am scared,
but I am unwilling.
I have a gift for you,
to resolve the grievances between us.
I reject.
I know the type of person I am.
I also know who you are.
I won't change,
you won't change too.
People won't change.
But the world is changing.
The power of men may not be able
to hold these external forces.
Unless you are strong enough.
Ling Borough is good,
but it lacks resources.
You need to go higher and farther.
For example,
the Armoury of Xingyun Pavilion.
What gift do you have in mind?
Do you want to be an armourer?
The moonlight maybe dim,
at least it's visible every night.
Farther away,
how would it look like?
It's a pity we're going back tomorrow.
We can't see such moonlight anymore.
I wonder from where Xuan Xuan is,
can she see the moon?
She definitely can.
May God bless her.
She'll be fine.
Yes.
Xuan Xuan is wild.
This is not the first time
she ran away from home.
I hope when she calms down,
she'll return safely.
Father.
Don't you worry.
The news of the
marriage cancellation is out.
When Xuan Xuan hears it,
she'll return immediately.
Uncle Ling.
Yu Shi.
Yu Shi, did you know,
Qin Lie is staying?
What? But why?
Du Shao Yang
is introducing Qin Lie
to the armourer Master Yao.
He's learning to forge artefacts.
No.
Du Shao Yang has bad intention.
It's all right.
I'll be with him in Xingyun Pavilion.
Like it or not, I am Shao Yang's uncle.
Furthermore,
Qin Lie is the
Profound Heaven Emissary.
He did not steal
the Profound Heaven Badge?
I found it.
[Profound Heaven]
Yu Shi,
why don't you stay?
I think,
Qin Lie wants you to stay too.
Why don't you stay?
Father.
You aren't meant to be,
but you love him very much.
Don't leave this life
with any regrets.
Like the moonlight,
although misty and dim,
but if you can see it one more time,
just look at it one more time.
I'll stay on in Xingyun Pavilion.
To keep looking at you if possible.
After all,
Ling Borough doesn't have such moonlight.
Qin Lie,
you asked me
what I want from you.
Yu Shi, I...
I know I shouldn't.
I can tell you now,
what I want from you.
I want you to see the scenery you want,
to reach your highest
and farthest point.
I thought you were dead,
so I had no other thoughts.
In order to save Ling Borough,
I was going to marry
into Xingyun Pavilion.
But I overestimated myself.
On the Chilan Continent,
even if Xingyun Pavilion ranks low,
it's not a place for Ling family.
After I came,
I pretended to be calm.
But actually, I was scared.
Seeing you here,
I couldn't hold myself.
I forgot myself.
Please forgive me.
Qin Lie,
I'm happy
that you came.
My cooking didn't go to waste.
[Armoury]
[The Armoury, Xingyun Pavilion]
Master.
This is the Profound Heaven Emissary,
Qin Lie.
Master Yao.
[Master Yao]
You are in a very unique position,
but the rules of The Armoury
must be obeyed.
Everyone knows forging artefacts
is well respected,
but few people know
the origin of the armourer.
Thousands of years ago,
the founder created
the way of forging artefacts.
When entering The Armoury,
one must first kneel to
worship the founder.
With a sincere attitude,
to ask for protection from the founder.
You took to his liking,
and introduced Master Yao
to the Emissary.
Good job.
Is your wound better?
It has healed.
At first,
I was worried about how to resolve
the hostility of the Emissary.
I didn't expect
you'd start acting on it three days ago.
You are smart,
but too smart.
I'll remember your teaching.
Next time,
don't decide on your own.
Yes.
Yu Shi,
do you think I should add more water?
It seems better with more water.
Gao Yu.
Why do you think after taking a bath,
you think you look better?
Because,
I am clean.
No.
Too much water up here.
Dough is like men's brain.
Too much water,
it turns into paste.
It will stick together.
Fire on the city gate
kills the fish in the moat.
But I'm the only fish in the moat.
Qin Lie,
I'm receiving punishment on your behalf.
Let me send it.
It has already been three days since
he's gone to Master Yao.
You helped send this for three days.
I haven't seen him once.
I want to send it today.
I told you before.
The Armoury is a place for men.
You can't go.
Besides,
you wouldn't want Master Yao
to treat him differently.
All right.
You must make sure he finishes it.
When he concentrates,
he forgets to eat.
If he doesn't eat,
I'll force feed him.
Little brother,
I praised you the day before,
I praised you yesterday.
But today,
I must praise you again.
You used Qin Lie to make Yu Shi stay.
You're smart.
Is it that good?
Yu Shi made it, of course it's nice.
Useless boy.
Qin Lie is busy.
You eat his leftovers,
aren't you ashamed?
Yu Shi's cooking is really nice.
You don't believe?
Try it.
You are a man.
You must act decisively.
You don't cherish the opportunity,
but picking up his leftovers
as if it's something good.
Do you know what's
the most regretful thing?
Missing the opportunity.
Of course, I know.
But Yu Shi's cooking
is really good.
Qin Lie finished his meal this time
and asked for more.
He asked for two more dishes tomorrow.
I told him,
Yu Shi can't cook everything alone.
He looked at me and told me,
I must help you.
So, I said,
I'll help her everyday.
See,
nothing left.
In my cooking today,
I added seasoning he doesn't like.
On normal days,
he won't even touch it.
He focused on forging artefacts
so he didn't touch the food.
Am I right?
Indeed,
you are cunning.
Slightly smarter than you.
That's right.
He was so focused on his work.
Every time,
I finished the food secretly.
I lied to you
because I want you to be happy.
Gao Yu.
You don't have to.
Then why do you do it?
He can forget food and sleep.
He didn't eat your food.
He can't even remember you.
But you are always looking at him.
You can only see him,
ever since you're little.
You...
How dare you bully Yu Shi?
Stop right there!
-Don't chase.
-Qin Lie, don't stop me.
They'll definitely come back.
We are injured.
Why don't we get prepared
and beat them up nicely?
Don't chase after them.
Yu Shi.
You're injured. Is it painful?
Here.
I'll carry you.
Since young,
you've only cared about Qin Lie.
-Do you know...
-And I will continue to.
I don't want to be like this,
but I can't help it.
Why do you laugh?
I am not laughing at you.
I am laughing at myself.
I thought
I could get your attention this time.
Unfortunately,
I was rejected before I could ask.
Gao Yu, can you be serious?
I want to be serious.
But don't you think
being serious is boring?
Yes.
Being serious bores me.
Qin Lie doesn't understand feelings.
When is he going to get it?
If a girl
cooks for me everyday,
I will eat everything
until she goes bankrupt.
so that she can't leave me.
Eat until a girl goes bankrupt?
You're really smart.
Gao Yu.
Thank you.
If you want to thank me,
stop torturing yourself.
You try it.
What's the matter?
These patterns,
I've seen them in my dreams.
I have the same dream every night.
[I dreamt of myself in a palace,]
[with four paintings on the wall.]
[The criss-crossed lines]
[seem messy,]
[but orderly.]
It's exactly these patterns.
What?
You dreamt about the Spiritual Array?
This is the Spiritual Array?
Life and growth in nature
continue in endless succession.
The Spiritual Array is the foundation.
The armourer uses his power
to understand the Spiritual Array.
Through painting,
injects spiritual power
in the weapons forged.
An ordinary weapon will then become
a magical weapon.
The more powerful the armourer is,
the stronger the spiritual
power in the painting.
The magical weapon forged
will become extremely powerful.
Just now you said,
you dreamt about the
Spiritual Array every night.
What's that about?
I don't know either.
I know that
since I was ten,
I have had the same dream every night.
Master,
I have a question.
Have you heard of Qin Shan?
Qin Shan?
Who is he?
Qin Shan is my grandfather.
Thirteen years ago,
during the sudden spirit tide
and the attack of beasts,
he and I were passing by Ling Borough.
Grandfather forged weapons
and helped to defeat the spirit beasts.
He settled in Ling Borough,
but he disappeared later.
I have been searching for him.
You thought since I am an armourer,
I might know your grandfather?
Chilan Continent is huge,
but the armourers are few.
In my life,
besides my classmates,
I don't know any other armourers.
Where did you learn your skill?
The sacred hall of armourer,
the place where ultimate
spirit material is stored.
Half of the wealth on Chilan Continent
belongs there.
The Artefact Forging Sect.
Have you heard of it?
A little.
The armourers of Chilan Continent
are pupils of Artefact Forging Sect.
If you want to find your grandfather,
you should go there.
Can you refer me to them?
According to its rules,
if you want to be a pupil of
the Artefact Forging Sect,
you must rely on your skill, understand?