[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 7]
Qin Lie.
I brought you some food.
I'm not hungry.
I'll stay with you.
No need.
After my sister married Du Hai Tian,
she brought me to Xingyun Pavilion.
But,
I'd still spend a few days
in Ling Borough every month.
And I was so absorbed
in cultivation everyday
that I forgot to take a break.
While you
would cook for me everyday.
It's nothing.
The food may be nothing,
but it was about
our friendship.
[You're all the same.]
[You forgot to eat
once you start cultivating.]
[I bet]
[you'll starve to death one day.]
[The unfair life in Xingyun Pavilion]
[brought you back to Ling Borough
for a breath of fresh air, isn't it?]
[You're imagining things.]
[Looks like there's not much fun
in becoming a young master there.]
[Did they talk about
the patronage you got at your back,]
[and despise you?]
[I told you,]
[you're imagining things.]
[Don't give me that.]
[Everyone needs someone to rely on.]
[Qin Lie is your close friend.]
[You can talk to him.]
[He doesn't need to know
what's in my mind.]
[I just need you to know that.]
[Whenever I have nowhere]
to pour out the sorrow in my heart,
you're the only one
who understands how I feel.
And you're the only one
who would lend me a shoulder.
I've never forgotten
what you did for me.
Now that
Qin Lie's no longer around...
He's still alive.
He'll be back.
He promised to stay with me till the end.
There's no way he'll break it.
That was my promise.
Everything Qin Lie confessed to you
was my thought.
I wrote
every word of it.
So,
this was what happened.
Yes.
The same words,
when spoken by another person,
made a great difference.
Since you're going to wait for him,
then the more
you should take care of yourself.
It is true
that I have thought
about replacing Qin Lie one day.
But I also know that
I won't get the chance from you.
You'll wait for him
no matter how long it will be, right?
I will always wait for him.
-So, Gao Yu, please stop...
-Don't stop me...
From waiting for my buddy.
Come on.
Let's grab a bite first.
I, the young master of Xingyun Pavilion,
have actually become an abandoned pawn.
In order to make my father
the Master,
I sacrificed all the people
of Ling Borough.
Yet in the end, everyone hates me.
The Master knows that you've suffered.
However,
the Profound Heaven Emissary is here.
He has to focus on the bigger picture.
Qin Lie was right.
I am a very calculating man.
He chose Ling Borough
and became a hero.
I chose Song Ting Yu...
You're a man who aims high.
Of course you'd choose Saintess Song
over Ling Borough.
You're not calculating.
You're just decisive enough
to survive in this world.
Saintess Song is like that.
You, too.
That's bullshit.
We're just plotting against each other
for our own agenda.
I am like this.
So is Song Ting Yu.
In order to not offend the Master of Gelid
and please Ling Borough,
she punished me.
How shameful.
How shameful!
I hate Song Ting Yu.
And I loathe Qin Lie!
How is he better than me?
Get him here.
I'll settle the score with him.
Young Master, you're drunk.
Qin Lie died in Silent Abyss.
Qin Lie died?
Qin Lie is dead?
He became a great hero
no one can ever surpass.
I'll never be able to beat him,
as
I can't compete with a dead man.
There's no more wine. Get me some wine.
You've drunk all the wine here,
Young Master.
Let's go back.
I want wine. Get me more wine.
Hurry up!
Yes, Young Master.
Qin Lie is dead.
Who else can be my competitor?
Song Ting Yu?
-That wench...
-Stop following me.
-Qi Qi. Qi Qi.
-Stop following me around.
Don't go.
Stop there.
I swear I'm fond of you.
It's over between us, okay?
It's not okay, Qi Qi.
You hit on me first.
And now you're telling me
that you no longer like me
before I even get to look at your face.
Why, Qi Qi?
Don't call me Qi Qi.
How'd you like me to call you?
Tang Tang? Si Si?
Qi Qi,
tell me. I'll change it.
Are you going to let go of me?
Never!
Get up.
Get up and talk.
Wipe away your tears.
Wailing baby, are you even a man?
Why are you pestering me
when I no longer like you?
Such submission to a woman...
If all men are as useless as you,
women would be doomed to die alone.
Get lost!
Qi Qi. Qi Qi!
Why are you following me?
Are you
charmed by me too?
-This is on behalf of that man!
-One for you too!
How dare you slap me.
How dare you smack me!
Young Master!
Young Master.
An assumed well-dressed beast
turned out to be a sad man.
He actually had the nerve to slap me.
Father!
Xuan Xuan.
Father.
-I missed you a lot.
-Luckily.
I've grown stronger, Father.
They are...
I'm Li Zhong Zheng,
a disciple of Qisha Valley.
This is my sister in the Valley, Lu Li.
I was travelling around as instructed,
and met your daughter
whom I wished to recruit.
Xuan Xuan was given a chance
to cultivate at Qisha Valley,
but there was news about
bad things happening in Ling Borough.
Xuan Xuan's negative thought might be
an obstacle in her path to ascend,
so, my master told us
to come back with Xuan Xuan.
But we were too late.
All of us in Ling Borough
are grateful to your master
for his kindness.
Xuan Xuan is indeed lucky to be able
to join Qisha Valley.
She came back
more mature and calm.
That's good news.
Exactly.
Xuan Xuan's been long stuck
in mid-Kaiyuan Realm.
But in less than a month,
she has almost conquered it.
As expected from Qisha Valley.
Thank you.
There aren't many people left
in Ling Borough,
but we do have talented people.
Maybe you could pick one or two of them
to receive your guidance at Qisha Valley.
Not having many people,
but not short of talented ones.
I'm surprised to learn
that Ling Borough in this arid land
has a wealth of talents.
Lu Li.
You must be
Xuan Xuan's older sister, Yu Shi,
[Qisha Valley, Li Zhong Zheng]
whom she kept mentioning.
Yes, I am.
Are you suffering from a poisoned wound,
Miss Yu Shi?
I grew up with Fire Poison inside of me.
We couldn't find a cure all this years.
May I check it?
What a strange Fire Poison.
I've never seen it.
But there's a spirit skill in Qisha Valley
that can revive one's energy with spirit.
As water can be turned into
Heavenly Water,
one can cleanse everything
if she can cleanse herself.
Why don't you come to Qisha Valley with me
after we're done here?
Maybe practising the spirit skills
of Water Valley
will help relieve your condition.
I heard that in Qisha Valley,
skies are blue
and clouds are white.
If it's such a beautiful place,
you have to go there.
But if I do,
you'll be left alone, Father.
In the past
when Mr Qin Shan was still around,
he could use his Heavenly Power
to restrain the Fire Poison in you.
But his whereabouts is unknown now,
and your poison has been attacking.
-If you're not treated...
-If I'm not treated,
I'll die.
That's why I'm going to Qisha Valley,
not only to be treated,
but also to become stronger.
By the time I return,
I'll be able to protect Ling Borough.
Don't do it for Ling Borough.
Do it for yourself.
Yu Shi,
I know that you're a good daughter.
But seeing you struggling
and forcing yourself
pains my heart as a father.
I'm your eldest daughter.
It's only right
that I do all this.
In that case,
why did you hesitate?
I don't think Qin Lie is dead.
If he comes back
and I'm not around...
Actually, if you're in his heart,
he'll come for you.
But if there's not your room
in his heart,
it makes no difference
whether you meet each other or not.
There was once Xuan Xuan
left Yu Xin in pain.
She is finally back,
but just to find out she's lost him.
You've never had Qin Lie.
You can't call this losing.
Don't stay back
or leave for anyone's sake.
Whatever decision you make,
make it for yourself.
Just go.
Be a better you,
and become someone you'll like.
Uncle Hua, please open the door.
Just go home.
Yu Xin is dead.
There's no use kneeling here.
The Fire Poison is extremely strange.
Rather than a poisoned wound,
it's more like a...
A what?
A pure energy.
A peculiar power of the fire spirit.
It's complicated.
As if something is sealed inside.
Why is there such a seal?
A seal made from spiritual power?
That's impossible.
Such seal only exists
in the Golden Central Land.
The Golden Central Land?
In my years of cultivation,
I've been travelling a lot,
but I never made it out of
Chilan Continent.
I wouldn't even dare to think about
bathing in the Golden Holy Light.
Chilan Continent
is just an isolated land
at the edge of the world.
Why is such spiritual power found here?
Upon passing by their medicine garden,
I noticed a spiritual herb
that's almost impossible to grow.
But in this arid land,
it is growing abundantly.
That blind lady from Wood Valley
who's reached the peak of Ruyi Realm
has been growing spiritual herbs
for 2000 years.
Even she can't do that.
But this Kaiyuan Realm beginner,
Ling Yu Shi, did it.
Are you sure it was Ling Yu Shi?
I've asked a lot of people along the way.
I won't be mistaken.
Are you sure it's not because
she's pretty?
No matter how pretty she is,
you're still better-looking.
As if I'll believe that.
Xuan Xuan,
go back and take a rest.
You're weak.
You should go back first.
I'll stay here.
This changes nothing.
I'll kneel with you.
Maybe Uncle Hua will soften
and open the door.
I was reckless. I left,
instead of staying back
and protect Ling Borough
and Yu Xin.
I deserve the punishment.
You didn't just leave.
You were looking for a solution
for Ling Borough.
And where
is the solution?
It's in our hands,
as well as our hearts.
Yu Shi,
you don't think Qin Lie is dead?
His body isn't found.
Why should I believe he's dead?
I, too, will not believe Yu Xin's dead
before I see his dead body.
Qin Lie has returned.
It was all my fault.
I was tricked by the Soul Reaping Beast,
and mistook Yu Shi as the Beast,
causing so many lives.
Yu Shi was hurt as well.
Qin Lie,
are you a man of Ling Borough?
I am.
Then, don't be on your knees.
You killed the Soul Reaping Beast
and avenged the villagers.
All of us
-owe you our lives.
-That's right.
-You saved our lives.
-Absolutely.
Qin Lie, you did a good job.
Yeah, well done.
-Well done!
Come on.
Qin Lie.
Where's Yu Xin?
[Ancestral Tablet]
It's all thanks to our ancestors
that you survived the grave danger.
Uncle Ling,
as for Yu Xin...
I couldn't bring him back.
You're not to blame.
Tell me what happened back then.
All I remember is
when the thunder struck,
Yu Xin threw himself at me
and took it in my place.
Silent Abyss was surrounded
by Thunderbolts.
What was he, an outlander, doing there?
That was a deep abyss.
Anyone would be smashed to pieces
from the jump.
But he managed to land on me and saved me.
This is indeed strange.
Furthermore,
when I woke up,
I vaguely saw a weird person
beside me.
He was an old man.
Could it be
that Mr Qin Shan has returned?
I was heavily wounded.
Although I didn't see his face clearly,
I'm certain he is someone familiar.
Maybe...
No.
It can't be him.
But I'm sure
that he wasn't my grandpa.
Then,
after God knows how long,
by the time I woke up again,
I found myself
at the gate of Ling Borough.
Don't exhaust your mind.
You're home now. Take a good rest.
Ling Borough
is counting on you from now on.
This is my home.
I'll do my best.
Where's Song Ting Yu?
She left
with Xingyun Pavilion's men the other day.
But, I heard that
she had someone stayed back
to look after the Pavilion.
Stayed back to look after
Xingyun Pavilion?
Song Ting Yu wants us dead?
Don't think too much. Get a good rest.
We can't afford
to pick on Xingyun Pavilion,
what's more Saintess Song.
Qin Lie.
Gao Yu!
[The Mother of Land]
[and the son of the God of War
can't fall in love.]
[If the evil people find it out,]
[before they can even
enjoy the relationship,]
[troubles have already been awaiting.]
[But now,]
[love is already born between you two.]
[You want a fierce battle]
[or you'll breakup?]
[It's your choice.]
Who was the Mother of Land?
And who was that son of God of War?
Was it me?
Or was it him?
A fierce battle?
A breakup?
What does that mean?
Yu Shi.
What are you doing here?
Look at you mumbling.
Are you trying to apologize?
I thought the Soul Reaping Beast got you.
That's why I proposed marriage
from the Chief
as an arrangement to kill the Beast.
So, I...
I've forgiven you.
At least
I get to marry you as I wished.
Yu Shi.
What? You want to break your promise?
That's not it.
The marriage...
I was just kidding.
Since it was a strategy,
then we can't take the marriage seriously.
I haven't finished yet.
Actually, when I decided to take the beast
down with me at Silent Abyss,
-the last thing in my mind was...
-I've decided to cultivate at Qisha Valley.
Why the sudden decision?
Was it your Fire Poison?
No,
but it must be eliminated eventually.
Curing it
may help me cultivate.
Can it really be cured?
Awesome.
I used to think
that when I'm as powerful as my grandpa,
I'll restrain the Fire Poison for you too.
I was worried
that my progress was too slow.
Lucky for us.
If you can recover fully,
I'll be extremely relieved.
From now on, I can share the burden
of Ling Borough with you.
Okay.
I'll teach you Qin family's
Thunder Incantation by then.
When you can conjure thunder,
I guarantee everything's bearable for you.
Who cares to learn
your Thunder Incantation?
Why, you're eager to be my master?
Of course.
If I'm your master,
I won't have to feel indebted to you
for all the food.
In case I'll feel guilty and ashamed
when you mock me with it in the future.
As a man,
dignity matters a lot.
Nonsense.
Did you treat Xuan Xuan like a girl
after swallowing the food she made?
Is that even food?
With her temper and cooking skills,
only Yu Xin
can control her.
Uncle Hua.
You're back?
Uncle Hua,
I'll take care of you from now on.
You're my father now.
The ground is cold.
You should sleep on the bed.
Come on.
Did you memorize the images?
What?
The images in your mind.
How did you know about that?
Did Yu Xin tell you before?
Memorize them when you're dreaming,
and draw them out after you woke up.
Try to remember as much as you can.
Draw them out everyday,
and practise every night.
You tend to become violent easily.
Practising that
is good for you.
Did those words come from you
or someone is telling me through you?
Uncle Hua.
Uncle Hua!
What are you doing?
What exactly are those four images?
What image?
Who asked you
to tell me all this?
Qin Shan.
Grandpa?
Grandpa was here?
In my dream. He told me that in my dream.
In your dream?
Yes.
In my dream.
Du Shao Yang is here.
-He has the guts to show up?
-Yeah.
How dare you come here!
Du Shao Yang, how dare you show up here!
I'm here this time
to apologize.
May I see Chief Ling?
-Why should we let you?
-Why?
Who do you think you are?
You want to see the Chief?
Take my punch first.
So, can I see him now?
Chief. Elders.
Du Shao Yang came with a gift,
saying he's here to apologize.
Let him come in.
You guard the door.
Okay.
Let them in.
We'll wait here
and see what he's got up his sleeve.
Chief Ling,
my Young Master is here
in order for Du and Ling families
to be reconciled.
Here's a treasure from Xingyun Pavilion
to show our sincerity.
The first time this Du guy came,
he was swollen with arrogance,
wanting to kill Qin Lie.
He even kidnapped Yu Shi.
For the second time,
he showed up in a magnificent appearance,
and many villagers in Ling Borough
died or were wounded.
As for the third time,
what will he do?
Kill the entire village?
Or getting himself killed?
You don't have to seek death from us.
Saintess Song may do it herself.
That's right.
Saintess Song
wanted to kill him back then.
But Yu Shi was too nice
and let him go.
His life is being controlled by women.
What did he come to us for?
He's our guest.
Don't be angry, Young Master Du.
Looks like I've underestimated Chief Ling.
I thought you're a polite and honest man.
Turns out you're cunning.
For stepping up only after
they're done cursing me.
You won't die from all the harsh words.
The Ling Borough
has suffered a great loss.
It's only right
to let them vent their anger.
What can you get from an argument?
At the end of the day,
we're still nothing but pawns.
What brings you here?
The instruction of
the Profound Heaven Emissary
to restore the relationship
with Ling family with a gift.
It's up to all of you
whether Ling and Du families
will be abandoned or supported this time.
Many of us have died or wounded.
Ling Borough is almost destroyed.
We're too busy thinking about
rebuilding our home
to be occupied by other matters.
So, you don't mind us?
It's not that
I don't want to care about you.
Go and ask them
whether I should accept the gift.
I'll leave it here.
Good bye.
Get the heck out of here.
You're not welcomed here.
Leave!
-Leave!
-Get out of here.
-Get lost!
-Leave!
-You're not welcomed here.
-Leave, get out of here.
-Nice!
-Good job!
Good job!
What is this?
He lost his wife and son because of you.
What do you think that means?
Get out of here now!
-Get out of here!
Let's go.
-Get lost!
Ling Xin, take care of Mr Hua.
Yes, Chief.
Come.
I'll kill all of them one day.
Surround them.
Trying to escape after murdering someone?
I've been kneeling here.
There was no noise.
Uncle Hua.
Someone broke Uncle Hua's skull
and killed him with this wooden pail.
-Did they get Du Shao Yang?
-No.
Qin Lie?
You're alive?
I stayed alive
to take your life.
Du Shao Yang,
I thought you were just a dirty dog.
Little did I know
that you're dirtier than a dog.
Du Shao Yang,
I shouldn't have let you live.
Du Shao Yang!
How ruthless you are!
He only splashed dung all over you,
but you took his life?
No one would believe me if I deny it.
If I was really going to kill him,
I wouldn't use
that filthy pail.
Many of you
saw us walking out of the south gate.
We didn't have the time to kill him.
You didn't?
With his capabilities,
it'd only take a moment to sneak back
and kill an outlander.
Do you have a witness?
Did anyone see that?
Who found the body?
It was me.
Maybe you killed him
and shift the blame to my young master.
Enough, Du Jun.
Since they've jumped to conclusions,
explanations won't help.
Looks like there's no way
I can step out of Ling Borough today.
Du Shao Yang!
Xuan Xuan,
mind your manners.
I see, you have someone behind you.
Qisha Valley is a Black Iron,
but the snowfield at far north
is under Palace of Hell's jurisdiction.
Zhong Zheng,
are you sure you want to intervene?
Qisha Valley seeks the truth with reasons.
We don't simply back anybody up,
let alone sticking our noses
into others' businesses.
However, we won't sit by idly too
when there's a bullying situation.
I heard that
the Palace of Hell's warrior, Pu Jiao,
is at Xingyun Pavilion.
Why don't we let him be the judge?
Any objection?
Okay.
I have Master of Gelid at my back.
They dare not do anything to me.
In fact, they'll be constrained.
Chief,
let me go.
We'll show them
that Ling Borough is also
backed by someone great.
I'm going too.
Although I'm a young master
at Xingyun Pavilion's,
I'm also one of Ling Borough.
I have a feeling that
there's more to this matter
than what we saw.
We'll deal with it carefully.
I'll go to Xingyun Pavilion
with you two tomorrow.
No.
I'll be worried if you go alone.
Gao Yu is with me.
He
is a member of Xingyun Pavilion,
after all.
He's also a member of Ling Borough.
He won't beset me.
Yes, he won't.
But do you want him
to be caught in the middle?
Yu Shi treats me best.
I'm going no matter what you say.
You can't stop me.
Let her go.
One more person
means more perspectives.
Maybe you'll gain something different.