THE UNCANNY COUNTER
CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, INCIDENTS
AND OCCUPATIONS ARE FICTITIOUS
Watch and see
what happens to your parents.
No!
No.
Get up.
Get up!
I said, get up!
Ji Cheong-sin is dead.
That means Mun's parents
and Cheol-jung are also…
No.
No, that can't be.
Ms. Chu.
Ms. Chu, help me. Ms. Chu!
Mun.
There's no pulse.
Hey, get up.
Get up. I don't believe this.
This can't be happening. Hey!
Hey, get up!
Get up! Get the hell up!
Get up…
Hey…
No!
Back off, all of you!
Do you want the kid to die?
-Let the kid go.
-Let him go!
Don't come near me. I'll kill you all.
Damn it!
GYEONGIN POLICE STATION
How dare they…
do this to me.
Right here. This is the climax.
Mr. Shin.
I believe
life is all about making choices.
I am dying to know
what you will choose to do.
Can we really keep on
interrogating Shin Myeong-hwi?
What will happen to us
if he ends up winning the election?
That's why we have to uncover the truth.
We cannot let a murderer
become the next president.
I know that, but…
Come on. Let's go.
INVESTIGATION ROOM
Hey, call an ambulance.
-Go. Call them now!
-Yes, sir.
-Jeez.
-This is insane.
119 EMERGENCY RESPONSE
EPISODE 14
You said
they were immortal.
You said level-four evil spirits
never die.
Because he was inside the barrier,
the ability to be immortal
was probably deactivated.
Mun, as you know,
when a host dies,
both the evil spirit
and all the other spirits
that were locked inside die with it.
No.
That can't be right.
No way.
There's no way my parents' souls
dissipated in vain like that.
You see,
I can still feel them.
I know they're still somewhere
in this realm!
I'm sorry
I couldn't keep my promise, Mun.
Mun.
Hey, Mun!
Hey, lazybones. You're still in bed?
Hey, Mun. Wake up.
Your grandma has been cooking up a storm
in the kitchen the whole morning.
Come on. Get up.
Are you that tired?
How is it?
Your grandma put her cooking skills to use
to make your favorite dishes.
Is it good?
Yes, Grandma.
It's good. It's very tasty.
I'd been so busy grieving
my daughter's death
that I hadn't been able
to cook a proper meal for my grandson.
I'm really sorry, Mun.
No. It's okay, Grandma.
You have no reason
to be sorry.
I'm sure your mom's waiting for me
in heaven,
so I should just take good care of you
until I can see her again.
Here, eat as much as you want.
This is delicious.
What a busy winter break for you.
The contest deadline is coming up.
I'll see you later.
All right, good luck.
Make sure you eat lunch.
And be nice to your friends.
Okay.
Don't force yourself to smile.
I'm sorry.
That's not what I meant.
We're really okay.
All right.
EONNI'S NOODLES
We all had those days.
How are the kids at the children's home?
All okay?
Yes, of course.
They'll be protected at the best facility
and will grow up just fine.
Okay.
But I wonder where Baek Hyang-hui went.
I'm sure that crazy girl
is going to cause trouble sooner or later.
-Mun.
-You see,
I won't give up like this.
You may think I'm crazy,
but I can really feel them.
I can still feel my parents' presence
in this realm.
I'll keep going. I have to,
for the sake of my grandparents.
Mun.
No, just give me some time.
I'll take a little break
from my job as a Counter.
I promise you I'll find
the evil spirit that has vanished.
-Mun.
-Don't try to change my mind.
-Ha-na, I--
-If you're right,
upon leaving Ji Cheong-sin's body,
it found a host
with the same vibrational frequency.
In other words, it must've gone
to someone who's that evil.
Ha-na.
Mun has a point.
That was a level-four evil spirit.
There's a possibility that the evil spirit
killed the host and found itself
a new host upon becoming complete.
If that is what happened,
we'll need to spot
the evil spirit in its new host,
so summon our territory
at a place where it may show up.
Then I'll try to spot it.
All right.
We'll do it even if there's only
a one-in-a-million chance.
Let's do everything we can.
-Right?
-Yes! Of course, we should.
That was my plan anyway.
You should've said so before.
Yes, it's too late.
Is it?
Do you really mean it?
Yes, I do.
Don't cry.
-You silly goose, why are you crying?
-Goodness.
If you cry, the rainbow--
Hey, enough.
Don't ever say you quit.
JUNGJIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Hello, I'm here to check in on Mr. Shin.
What happened?
I saved you.
You saved me?
Don't you remember?
You asked me to save you.
You desperately called out to me.
-Now, we must
-protect each other.
Some suspect that Mayor Shin
might have tried
to take his own life because
he was unable to cope with the stress
of being interrogated as a suspect.
INCOMING CALL
MAYOR SHIN MYEONG-HWI
My gosh!
I was sad about how we ended things.
I'm so glad I got to see you
one more time, Mr. Mayor.
You said you wanted the City of Jungjin.
You've always coveted my position.
I'll let you have it.
Have you lost your mind
now that you've come back from the dead?
Look, do you realize that--
How… How did you…
I'll let you have it
if you stay on your knees in front of me.
Let's take care of the urgent stuff first.
You're turning yourself in
for the murder of Kim Yeong-nim?
Yes, I killed her.
Kim Yeong-nim.
Mayor Shin is a useless card to us now.
So why should I do that?
I have no idea what happened to him,
but he has the powers
that Ji Cheong-sin had.
We have no choice now.
When the time is right,
I'll get you out on parole.
This is surely enough
to get you locked up.
I cannot let Mayor Shin
be wrongfully convicted.
Noh Hang-gyu of Taesin
turned himself in for the murder
that took place seven years ago.
Noh stated that Mayor Shin Myeong-hwi
had nothing to do with the murder
and has confessed that
he killed the victim
and abandoned the body all by himself.
Even though Mayor Shin
managed to clear his name,
he has expressed his intention to resign…
Shin Myeong-hwi got away once again.
Shin Myeong-hwi…
I'll be sure to catch you this time,
for Mun's sake.
Oh my.
What's going on? Is it…
Level one, near the mall.
-Let's go.
-No.
You stay here.
It's just a level-one spirit.
All evil spirits make me shudder now,
regardless of their levels.
Let's go.
-No.
-Gosh, please.
You should take it easy today.
It's today.
Su-ho's death anniversary.
She'll be here soon, you know.
See you.
-Be safe.
-All right.
See you later.
My gosh.
Jeez, what is wrong with me?
I kept telling her not to come.
Why am I waiting for her? Goodness.
I'm crazy, aren't I?
Mother.
Sorry I'm late.
Gosh, I told you not to come.
You're so stubborn.
You've been well, right?
Yes, of course. You must be cold.
You don't even have time to eat?
What's wrong with that company?
You should just quit.
The end of the year is always busy.
Try to eat well.
Don't skip meals.
Okay.
All right, you can tell me now.
Sorry?
You've been hesitating whether or not
you should tell me something.
I know you, Jeong-eun.
My gosh, congratulations.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Gosh, why are you sorry? Don't be.
Come on.
I'm happy to see you moving on finally.
Su-ho is in a good place now.
I'm sure he's totally forgotten about us.
It's about time you moved on
and lived your life.
I'm sorry.
Yes, you should be.
I want to get married too.
Look at you ditching me.
He's good to you, right?
I'm sure he's a sweet guy.
I know you're a good judge of character.
I mean, that's why you chose Su-ho.
You have a good eye.
He's just an average guy.
I don't have to try to be someone else
when I'm with him.
He makes me feel at ease.
That's the best.
Great, I'm so happy for you.
Bring him here before your wedding.
Don't tell him anything else.
Noodles symbolize a long, happy life.
I'll make you some delicious noodles.
Gosh, why are you crying?
I know that you have
a happy, great life ahead of you,
Jeong-eun.
You deserve to be happy. You really do.
Are you sad?
I always felt bad,
so I'm happy for her.
Thank you, Mom.
Is Jang-mul good to you?
My gosh, what did you say?
What are you saying?
Come on. I saw everything.
What did you see? My goodness.
Gosh.
What on earth are you talking about?
-I saw everything.
-Goodness.
I have high standards, you see.
He's not here.
He isn't here either.
TAESIN GROUP
Ji Cheong-sin.
Where on earth is he?
You see, hope is…
It's such a cruel beast.
I know,
but it's what keeps us going.
My, look at this mansion.
What a nice house.
Will Hang-gyu be okay though?
Come on. I'm sure he has a plan.
You know the kind of person he is.
He told us not to worry,
so we have nothing to worry about.
But why did the chairman tell us
to come all the way to Mayor Shin's place?
My brother is taking the fall for him,
so I guess he wants
to give us something in return.
My brother must've already
cut a deal with him.
Why is it so dark in here?
Is he over there?
-Mr. Mayor, I heard you asked for us.
-Hello, sir.
Is he not at home?
-Jeez.
-My gosh.
We cannot let anyone find out about us
until we've fully recovered.
What do you want?
You… You're back.
We should eat up that punk too.
No, don't touch him.
Why not? Because he's your son?
That little prick tried to kill you
at the hospital.
I bet you had no idea.
Still, we can't kill him yet.
Now isn't the time.
No, not yet.
Are you really gone?
Are you, Mom?
Is it really true, Dad?
Hey, you said your dad is at home.
Ask him for more pocket money.
-Hey.
-Say something!
What are you doing?
Get up.
-What?
-Your father, Shin Myeong-hwi…
Where is he now?
-What?
-Where is he?
It's them.
No, not yet.
Right now, we mustn't get caught.
Mun, stop.
Ha-na.
-In there--
-Can't you feel it?
Shin Myeong-hwi isn't there now.
He's already fled.
Shin Myeong-hwi.
That human trash.
I can't believe
the evil spirit went to him.
We're dealing with pure evil here.
But I wonder why he's been quiet
all this time.
No movement detected so far,
as if he's in hiding.
That's because he now knows
we can trap him using the barrier.
Mun, I'm sure we can find
Shin Myeong-hwi.
We'll track him down.
I'm not upset.
I'm happy.
This means we still have a chance.
I'm happy to know it's not over yet.
EONNI'S NOODLES
First, let's find out
where Shin Myeong-hwi could be hiding.
His son is that kid at your school, right?
Yes.
He must have a vacation home.
I'll find out.
-Look who's here.
-My gosh!
-Hi, So-eun.
-So-eun.
-Hello.
Hi, So-eun. What brings you here?
So-eun is doing a lot better now.
She missed you, Mun.
-My gosh.
-We came for some noodles,
-but I guess you're closed today?
-Oh.
His brother is Kwon Jin-seung
at Love Jungjin.
-Oh, I see.
-Hello, I'm Kwon Jin-ho.
This is his brother's daughter.
Hello, I'm Kwon So-eun.
My gosh, you're So-eun.
It's so nice to meet you.
-Mo-tak, boil water for some noodles.
-Okay.
-It's cold. Come on in.
-Thank you.
-Come on in.
-All right.
Have some noodles. Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Here's yours, So-eun.
Here, I'll stir it for you.
My gosh, I'm very glad to see So-eun
looking so healthy.
I'm proud of her.
I'm relieved that she's doing better now,
but a lot of the kids
are still struggling.
That's no surprise. They drank
and bathed in that water for so long.
Are those jerks at Taesin
still playing dumb?
Yes. But thanks to your help,
we have many supporters now.
As soon as we have the results
from So-eun's heavy metals analysis,
we'll schedule a press conference.
Good. We're really almost there now.
You see, about the press conference…
Do it at my hotel.
Let's use the media to our advantage.
We should really take down
those scumbags once and for all.
He loves to spend a ton of money
for a good cause.
-What? I do?
-Yes, a hell of a lot of money.
Watch it. There's a kid here.
Oh, my bad.
-Forget what I said.
-Eat up.
If they insist that the kid's body
is evidence
and living proof in and of itself,
the ICT project will face
yet another roadblock.
I think environmental organizations
have their backs.
A kid who's bound to die should just die.
But Hang-gyu and Chang-gyu aren't around,
so I have no one to entrust
with such a task.
What do I do? The cops are looking for me.
Damn it! Why did that lunatic
have to shoot himself in the head?
Hey! Turn down the TV volume!
Do you think you own this inn?
Jeez, are your ears plugged?
You do this all the time.
Do I sound like a barking dog?
Open the door, you piece of shit!
Hey, gorgeous. This would've been
nice to know.
What did I say I'd do
if you caused trouble again?
-What? Who are you?
-I'm…
I'm Kim Deok-sik.
I have a job for you.
What?
You're alive?
I want to stay alive.
Damn it.
Is that blood?
What did you say?
Your family must have a vacation home.
Is Mayor Shin…
I mean, your father. Where is he now?
Well, why do you need to know?
Because I have to meet him now.
I'm baffled because you look so serious.
Hey.
You act up at school and think you're it?
Is my dad just some guy next door?
He has no time for you.
Just get lost.
Haven't you
noticed anything different about him?
You saw it too.
Those eyes.
You know
that your dad
is in danger now.
Hey, So-eun. Pork or beef?
Pork.
Beef is expensive.
Come on. It's fine.
We'll have beef today, okay?
Excuse me. What's good today?
I want Korean beef, not pork.
I see that you also hate studying.
OUR FLIGHT WILL LAST FOREVER
Check upstairs.
Will do.
He's not here.
No sign of him
visiting this place recently.
He's not here.
How many vacation homes does he have?
We don't have a lot of time.
You see, life is tough.
I thought you at least cared about kids.
I guess you don't anymore.
I spotted one.
Who? Shin Myeong-hwi?
No, Baek Hyang-hui.
But she's with So-eun.
So-eun? Why is she with So-eun?
If Shin found out, he wouldn't want
the press conference to happen.
And to do that…
So-eun! She's in danger.
Shit! Damn it.
I just drove by their fog.
Can't I just eat this kid now?
I need that kid gone without a trace.
If you think you can completely
get rid of her, go ahead.
Do you think I'm a zombie or what?
How could they do this to a kid?
And she's not well.
Think about all the things they've done.
They're not even human.
She was driving along Highway 26.
Can you keep our territory up on the way?
I'll try.
Who would have known Shin Myeong-hwi
would be his new host?
He couldn't have picked a better host.
Now, he even has full control over you,
Chairman Cho.
You're all done, right?
Get going, then.
Where's my pay?
I can't leave until I get paid.
Looks like I'll get to see some flames
today. Fun! It's been too long.
But you're getting me a new car, right?
Go ahead and pour it.
Shit.
-What is this?
-Back off!
Damn it. Guys, whack them.
Oh, boy. I told him to go easy on them.
That old man's not here.
I guess you can't use the staff
without him.
That little girl is ill.
How could you do this to a kid?
Damn it.
Shit.
So-eun. So-eun! Are you okay?
Mun…
Yes, So-eun. You're safe now.
Ga Mo-tak!
No, I mean… Detective Ga.
I didn't do anything.
Shin Myeong-hwi told me--
This is what worthless scumbags
like you deserve.
-Detective Ga.
-This is my motto.
"Beat them up to a pulp
but don't kill them."
I'm one of the top 50 business tycoons
in this country--
Even a criminal like you
is this clever and savvy.
It makes me think
that we really need to smarten up.
Hey, stay with me.
No, get up. Come on.
All right, 12 more punches to go.
I'll make you suffer, you bastard.
Hey, enough!
You'll break his nose.
It's so annoying to waste my power
on healing jerks like him.
Well, I just couldn't control my anger.
Hey, do you realize who
you're dealing with here? I'm Cho Tae-sin!
It'll be a lot of work anyway.
One punch won't make a difference.
All right!
We'll erase these jerks' memories
as well as So-eun's
and say that So-eun called the police.
Wait, where's Ha-na?
What?
You're one persistent bitch.
Is it because you survived that alone?
Shut your mouth.
Those guys probably have no idea
how you survived that day.
I said, shut your mouth!
Go ask your mommy
for some more breast milk.
Oh, she's dead, right?
Shit.
You persistent bitch.
Damn it!
JUNGJIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
All done.
Does it mean those men will be punished?
Yes, of course.
Thanks to you,
who bravely told us everything.
Thank you.
Get some rest. I'll visit you again.
My gosh. You're amazing, So-eun.
Thanks, Mun.
For what?
I had a dream last night.
In my dream, you beat up those bad guys
and saved me. You were so cool.
It makes me anxious even now.
Had anything bad happened to her,
I would have…
I'd…
In the end,
So-eun helped us catch…
Cho Tae-sin.
-Get lost!
-Take responsibility!
-It's all on you!
-Be responsible!
-Take down Taesin!
-This is our basic right!
-He's coming out!
-A comment, please!
-Say a few words.
-Do you admit to the charges?
A comment, please!
-Sir!
-Over here!
Any comment as the chairman of Taesin?
Apologize to the kids!
This is a mere conspiracy
against me and Taesin Group.
I'll cooperate with the investigation.
-Sir!
-Is everything true?
A comment, please!
-Sir!
-Do you admit to the charges?
-Look over here!
-Hey!
-My gosh!
-What was that?
What happened?
-Let's get out of here.
-Everyone!
-What's going on?
-Huge articles on the front page, please!
That evil son of a bitch
doesn't even deserve to be called human.
We can put up with all kinds of jerks,
but not those who hurt our children!
-Get down.
-I'm counting on you reporters!
Our old man's trying hard.
-Goodness.
-What the…
Jeez! Enough!
-Calm down.
-You piece of…
-Out of the way!
-Move back!
A comment, please!
-How do you feel?
-A comment, please.
They'll finally reassess
the entire ICT project.
The kids…
can finally drink clean water.
-Sir!
-Do you admit to everything?
-Look here!
-Say a few words!
-Sir!
-Get lost!
-You bastard!
-Let's go.
-Hold on!
-Convict him!
-Take responsibility!
That girl can't do anything alone,
but if those rats show up together
with their staffs, we'll be screwed.
If you don't have a plan,
we should just leave.
Come on!
Jeez. Cho Tae-sin's been arrested,
so we have no money. What now?
We're almost there. Let's hang in there.
When will we get there?
Soon.
Is Ha-na really okay?
Is she hiding somewhere
beating herself up
for losing Baek Hyang-hui?
Even so, it's strange
that she hasn't contacted us.
They say some people experience
teenage angst later on in life.
-Hey!
-You guys are here.
Hey, what happened? We were all worried.
Where have you been?
-I told you not to wander alone--
-I'm sorry.
How's So-eun?
Oh, she's back in the hospital,
safe and sound.
And those jerks got arrested.
Are you okay?
Are you all right, Ha-na?
I found Shin Myeong-hwi.
Seriously?
For real?
Where is he now?
Damn it!
I'm asking you where he is!
Sit down.
Yes, calm down.
Let's listen to what Ha-na has to tell us.
Baek Hyang-hui has become stronger.
Even if we were to activate the barrier,
it may not be enough for both of them.
They know what cards we're holding,
but we have no way of gauging
what they can really do.
Is there a way
we can summon Shin when she's not around?
That'd be nice,
but how do we separate her from him?
One good thing is that
it seems like the barrier
hurt Shin Myeong-hwi.
That's why he's trying to recover
in hiding.
If he's trying to recover in hiding…
My gosh.
More lives are being sacrificed.
I bet Cho Tae-sin has been helping him.
Now that Cho's out of the picture,
the only one who can help him is…
Baek Hyang-hui.
Why don't we wait until
that crazy wench steps out and attack him?
Let's give it a shot.
Then we can summon the spirit.
The evil spirit inside Shin Myeong-hwi.
If we do that,
we can free my parents' souls
as well as all the other souls
that are locked inside him now.
We must do it as soon as we can,
before Shin Myeong-hwi
becomes even stronger.
I really shouldn't let him
boss me around like this.
How many more lives must I kill
to outpower him?
Let's pull this off.
This may be our last chance.
Stay calm and focused.
-We've done this once, you know.
-All right, let's go.
It's good to see you here.
Don't be delusional.
It's not like I wanted to see you!
If I kill one of you,
this will go to shit, right?
Then I should probably kill you.
We're screwed. Those persistent little...
Who tailed you?
They're here?
All of them?
No, not all of them.
Someone followed you
and is eavesdropping on our conversation.
What do we do now?
Where can we go?
If they barge in here with their staffs…
We just need to kill one of them.
I know who to target.
That bitch will be an easy one.
Am I wrong?
Should I kill everyone but you?
Like what happened to your family.
No, the barrier…
No!
-The barrier…
-It got deactivated.
Is this fun for you?
What's so fun about this? Answer me! Hey!
Hey, by the way…
Did you know?
That your whole family would die?
Perhaps you secretly wanted
all of them dead.
Am I wrong?
He can't use his psychokinetic abilities
inside the barrier.
What's going on?
Looks like your pathetic little prank
has ended.
Then shall we begin the real fight now?
What will you do now?
I've become even stronger,
and it's now time for you to give up.
Says who?
Who the hell says
it's time for me to give up?
THE UNCANNY COUNTER
We were both doomed to be alone
with no family.
Do we have to finish each other off?
Don't you dare compare me to you!
We just have to get Shin Myeong-Hwi now.
Please don't kill me.
Let's kill them, one by one.
What are you?
A Counter?
Wait, what? Coun... Who are you?
You said we should bring this to an end.
Is this the end?
I'll be the one putting an end to it,
you bastard.
Let's win today, no matter what.
I pray that no one else dies.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs