[English subtitles are available]
Falco...
Where are you going at this hour?
I forgot something. I'm on my way back
to headquarters to get it.
Excuse me!
Falco. I need you to do me a favor.
What is it, Mr. Kruger?
I want to send out letters.
But they will look at the content
if I send it from this internment zone, right?
Yeah.
If they read the letter, they will know
that I'm faking my illness.
So I want you to put this
in the mailbox outside the internment zone.
Alright. Is it for your family?
Yeah... I just wanted to tell them
I'm doing fine here.
[Attack on Titan]
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Children cling to their very last coins ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
[#63 From One Hand to Another]
Hey, what's with all the noises?
The entire Tybur family has come for a visit!
What did you say?
They're not from the Marleyan army.
They're Tybur family's personal guards...
Come in.
I'm sorry for dropping by unannounced.
I'm Willy, the head of Tybur family.
I'm Theo Magath, the Warrior Unit Commander.
It's an honor to meet you, Lord Tybur.
Nice to meet you, Commander Magath.
Well then, allow me to introduce you
to the rest of the Tybur family.
You're the guy who’s been managing
the Warrior Unit since it was first formed.
Can you tell which one of them has
the War Hammer Titan?
No, I don't have a clue.
Nor am I sure if that person is even here.
You're as tactful as people say.
However, he is here.
The War Hammer Titan is right among us.
I came here to see the statue of Helos.
Hundred years ago, in spite of being a mere
human, he defeated the Devil of All Earth.
The honorable Marleyan hero who saved the world.
His gallant act
was an incredible feat.
Brave, graceful, and unwounded.
Truly, the personification of Marleyan soul.
Yes, indeed.
That bronze statue is hollow, after all.
Quite scathing, Commander.
Rumors say you might be working
to reinstate conscription systems for Marley.
War to Marleyans is something
that only exists on their newspaper.
They only need to read them,
and the next thing they know,
their borders expanded.
Even better for them if the ones
who get showered by bullets
are the descendants of devils
they tamed or enemy soldiers.
Even if you have some
Marleyans’ ears grazed by bullets,
this country won't stop its march towards war
until the day it self-destructs.
If there's someone controlling Marley
behind the shadow,
I want to say this to them,
"It's already too late."
You're indeed merciless, Commander.
I can't even talk back.
As you have guessed,
this country is under the authority of Tybur.
But it was none other than Marley itself
that took this path to militarism.
We simply gave Marley the freedom and power
they needed as an act of atonement…
As a result, both Eldia and Marley
were tossed into darkness.
That responsibility lies with the Tybur family.
I'm planning to reveal all the truth
to the world on the upcoming festival.
I was not lying when I said I came
to see the hero statue.
Marley needs a hero once again.
Theo Magath.
Can you please shake this hand once again?
Good morning, Pock.
Pieck... what are you doing?
It's much easier for me to walk this way.
Did I surprise you?
Just walk normally with two legs, okay?
The Titans will come from the south.
Based on this fact,
the further into north, the weaker their defense.
So we should attack from the north?
Yes, that's an option.
However, the pier to the south remains
to be the only place we can dock large ships.
If we want to utilize our material advantages, then…
We have to attack from the south?
Again, we lost our scout ships on the south shore,
meaning the enemies have their eyes focused there.
There's a possibility that the docks have been destroyed…
Then what are you trying to say?!
I just want to provide the information I have as reference…
I got it. That's enough.
It was a mistake letting the Eldian speak to us.
The Paradis island operation is going well, huh?
We have awfully brilliant officials leading us.
I can't wait to see what kind of strategy
they will force on us.
Like
entrusting the entire thing to four kids, maybe?
Huh? He passed her...
Falco passed Gabi!
They're cheering over just one victory.
Sheesh,
if only they knew what we were going through.
It doesn't matter how much Falco tries
to improve his grades,
it's already too late for him to overtake Gabi.
The final sprint…
Oh, what's with
you kiddos today?
Falco just beat Gabi for the first time!
Really? In grades?
No, just in race.
This is a historic achievement!
Just stop it already. You're embarrassing me.
Well, that's amazing!
Guess you will be the next Armored, huh, kid?
O-Ouch!
It's already way too late for you to even catch up to me!
I made achievement in war and
contributed to our homeland, after all!
You're right.
But the Army still hasn’t announced
who will inherit the Armored.
I will just do what I can do
until that day comes.
Hey, look, he's acting cool and all.
Your brother will inherit the Beast anyway!
Your whole family gets to be
Honorary Marleyan regardless!
So why are you still working so hard?
I'm doing this for you!
Oh my... Hey, he finally said it!
You're saying you're getting in my way for my sake?!
You're making no sense!
Damn, she didn't get it…
What's wrong with him? Sheesh!
Oh, welcome home, our little warriors!
Gabi!
I heard what you did, Gabi!
You're our savior! Gabi!
No, I'm Zofia, so...
What are you doing,
getting drunk during the day and hugging girls?
You old geezer!
Shut up you old hag!
What's wrong with praising a hero?!
No one will be happy getting praised by you!
There, go back home to your mom already!
And you kids, here, take this.
Eat well and become as big as Deputy Chief Braun!
Thank you very much!
So they will really declare war in this internment zone?
It's like a theater.
They say the whole world will be on
our side if we hold this "festival" thing
while gathering all leaders here from different countries.
If so!
All Marley's problems will be over
and it will be great!
You don't think it will work?
You think it will, Gabi?
The countries from Mid-East Allied Forces
we had war with just a month ago will also be there.
My family came here from the interment zone
of other country, so I know.
It was awful.
The hostility that the Eldian face here is nothing
compared to outside.
Then, even more so, we must do something.
They must've chosen this place
to have the world understand more about the Eldian!
To convince them that we're not devils.
But how?
Smile!
I get how you feel about them, very well.
Just acting servile won't do a thing.
Also, Zofia,
stop playing such a weird character.
No, that’s just who I am.
So what will you change about yourself?
I can simply act the way I normally do!
I'm cute and smart, after all!
I'm sure I will get all the higher-ups'
attention, boosting my valuation.
She is starting to sound like a real devil.
I'm going to make you cry if you
take Falco's side again, okay?
You really are a devil!
It's Commander Magath.
Here it is.
Large scale demolition required, huh?
It has become severely aged.
Congratulations, General.
The Army now belongs to you.
No, the Army belongs to the country.
And this country's Commander-in-chief is you.
Not exactly.
I'm simply holding the steering wheel.
I now understand why none of my predecessors
even tried to hold it.
It's too heavy.
I'd like to let it go if I could,
but I have to grip onto this firmly more than ever.
It just happened to be me.
This moment just happened to come during my turn.
The house is on the verge of collapse,
but there are some posts still usable.
According to them,
there is already a rat infestation.
You did great, Falco.
It's all thanks to you, Mr. Kruger.
To be honest, I don’t think
I’d be able to outperform Gabi at this point.
But at least, I now can go
forward without doubts.
Really? But I'm the one who should be thanking you.
You helped with all those letters.
I'm saved thanks to you.
It's nothing.
Is that from your family?
They said life in hospital must be boring.
It was hard for me with this body, though.
I must move forward, too.
I will go back to my hometown once the festival is over.
I see...
The doctor is here.
I'll go now.
Hey, may I sit next to you?
Yeah. As you please.
Then excuse me.
I'm a physician in this district. My name is Yeager.
I come here to drink tea occasionally.
Nice to meet you. My name is Kruger.
Nice to meet you, Kruger.
Seems like you're on good terms with that boy just now.
I am.
Yeah? I'm sure I'd get along with him.
I'm also sitting on this bench looking for someone to talk to.
That boy's uncle was a leader of the Eldia restorationist.
The restorationist were sent to "paradise,"
including their family.
The boy, along with his brother, volunteered
to be a warrior to protect their family.
With his brother earning
the right to inherit the Beast,
the Grice family finally found peace.
Why... are you telling me that?
Stop asking that boy to do stuff for you.
The Grice family's effort will be
all for nothing if he gets suspected by people.
If your mind has recovered,
hurry up and return to your family.
It will be too late to regret it once you lose them for good.
Regret... huh...
Seems like you have regret
regarding your own family.
There has never been a day
I haven’t regretted it.
That day my son went outside the wall with his sister.
It's all because I was too harsh on him,
forcing him to take after me as a doctor.
It's me...
it's all my fault!
Ah!!!
Mr. Yeager!
Don't leave on your own like that!
I'm sorry, I took my eyes
off him for a moment, so he...
Come on, Mr. Yeager.
I'm sure you will get better.
[The available intelligence for now]
[The Tybur family]
[The aristocracy overthrown by the uprising of the Eldian 100 years ago during the war of Titan]
[The Tyburs joined hands with the Marleyan hero Helos during the war and reached a truce agreement behind the back of the Eldian.]
[“The War Hammer Titan” of every generation belongs to them. With such power,]
[though noble, they are also the vanguard of the military state Marley, and have great influence both at home and abroad.]
[The current head of the family is Willy Tybur.]
It's amazing.
It's all people I see on newspaper!
Don't make idle chitchat.
We're going to serve them as we trained.
Look, there are some empty glasses!
Move out!
Falco, another!
Here!
Oh, look. The filthy blood is carrying the plates.
No wonder the food here stinks!
I-I'm very sorry…
Shush. Don't make a scene.
B-But... Your beautiful garment...!
Madame, is there something wrong?
How embarrassing!
I spilled wine on my kimono by accident,
so I was asking for his help.
Thank you.
Oh my goodness!
Please, this way.
W-Why...?
Who knows what would've happened to you?
Are you okay?
Yeah... She saved me.
All while knowing that I'm an Eldian.
That person... She must be someone
from the Eastern nation of Hizuru.
It's Willy!
Willy! The descendant of the Savior!
It's been long, Ambassador Ogweno!
Nambia! I haven't met you since we were little!
I still remember all those times I made you cry.
Do you remember me, Willy?
Oh! That must be the scar from when you fell from that tree!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you all my sincere thanks for coming here today.
Just a few days ago, some of our people engaged
in an unsightly dispute over resources.
However, yesterday's enemies are today's enemies, too!
Oh, excuse me.
Yesterday's enemies are today's friends!
Let’s flush all what happened in the past
along with the wine we have tonight,
and join me for a toast for tomorrow?
Well then, for many years of peace!
Thank you so much.
What a refined joke it was, Ambassador.
However, it seems our guests weren't able
to understand what you said in common language.
So please, let me handle the rest.
That's it, Willy!
The Descendant of the Savior!
Tomorrow, I invite you all to the
Liberio internment zone.
There live the descendants of those who
once massacred the people of many nations.
The race whose blood runs in my veins as well.
It is the home of the devils known as the Eldian.
Marley, they who were once oppressed the most by them,
are now using that very devil to oppress other nations.
Thus, repeating the tragedy.
I understand very well the feeling
of wanting the extermination of all Eldians.
Thus, I finally arrived at a single answer
to this endless question.
Tomorrow, I will reveal that answer
at my first ever stage production.
To the great dramatist and the witnesses of history!
What?!
What is this?!
Gabi! You finally woke up!
What's this situation?
It's a festival!
A lot of people from outside came
to this internment zone
and opened all kinds of stores!
Eat!
So this is a festival?!
Let's go!
♫ In an instant ♫
It hurts....!
It's your fault for being such a glutton.
They should make everyday a festival.
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
Yeah.
Somehow, so many things have happened
to me for the first time recently.
♫ If you can fly ♫
Yeah.
It feels like... something might change soon.
♫ Please tell him ♫
Yeah... You're right.
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes ♫
♫ I will be immortal ♫
Did you all have fun?
Huh? Where's Falco?
He said he found someone he knew
and ran off somewhere just now.
Is that guy okay?
C'mon, don't be so uptight on a good day like this!
So many people...
Oh look, he's back.
Deputy Chief Braun!
Where did you go off to?
Can you follow me just for a moment?
Right now?
It’s okay.
We still have time before the opening.
This way, please.
Just what are you up to?
You will know once you're there.
Over here!
He's here!
Hey. It's been four years. Reiner.
...Eren!
[Preview]
Reiner meets Eren in a dark basement room.
When the people were shocked hearing Willy's speech,
Eren spoke up.
"I'm the same as you."
Next Episode: Declaration of War
[Declaration of War]