♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 30
Animal characters made by CG
Hongyu!
Be careful. Don’t scare it.
Animal characters made by CG
Finally, I got you!
Let go of Hongyu.
You hurt it.
Animal characters made by CG
Let me have it for a couple of days.
Bonehead!
What?
Li Sheng?
You hurt me!
You feel it?
I heard you shouting far away.
Tell me.
Why are you here?
He took me here.
Me?
Nonsense!
Who would bring a burden like you?
Burden?
You all take me as a burden.
But he doesn’t!
He asked me to lead the way for him.
That’s why I come to the Assembly.
Right?
Let go of her.
She saved my life.
She’s a heroine
with the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
You can’t do this to her.
Let go of her.
Heroine?
I’m her brother.
You... You!
You’re Li Yan
who ran away this morning?
Wait.
Why are you coming behind me?
Because when we came this morning...
All right. All right.
Let’s not stand here or argue.
We’re lost. Let’s go find a way out.
I’ll deal with you later.
That’s it.
You’ve returned the favor. We’re even.
Give Hongyu back to me.
Let me have it for a couple of days.
When I just walked into the forest,
I realized it was designed
according to Qi Men Dun Jia Formation.
It can stop everyone except me.
Come with me.
Seems like we started off early,
but arrived late.
Tortoise Master.
Here comes the girl
with the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
You’re the girl
who interfered in Lingling Inn, right?
Who are you?
No matter how naughty
my subordinates were,
you had no right to teach them a lesson.
Why do you think you can ask who I am?
Want a fight?
Tortoise Master,
I don’t think you come to take revenge,
do you?
Well, this beautiful girl sounds nice.
Why was it so disgusting
when he said the word beautiful?
Fine.
I’ll get even with you
for what happened in Lingling Inn
after the Demon-Extermination Assembly.
Uh, that pavilion looks nice.
Let’s go over there.
Fei, go.
Go.
Look at it.
Is this the Assembly of Martial Artists
or the Malicious Banquet?
Those with invitations have been taken
to the waterside pavilion.
Those without invitations
are here with us.
No wonder
Huo Liantao wrote names
on the invitations.
When I was in the dungeon
of the Huo family,
I realized that
Huo Liantao thought strangely.
We can’t estimate him in a normal way.
Turns out he only sent invitations
to his supporters.
Everybody.
Thank you for coming.
It is my great honor!
I’m so grateful!
So grateful!
People always say
our martial world is declining
where there’s no leader
for martial artists
and there are no real heroes.
That’s nonsense!
Today, I gather you here,
just to persuade you
to get rid of prejudice
against different sects
and make concerted efforts
with each other!
Today,
if we can find a real hero
among so many people
to command the martial world,
Auspicious Omen and Luck
I will follow him
and give him my heirloom!
Heirloom? So generous?
Why is Huo Liantao suddenly so generous?
Does he really know
what the ripple pattern is?
The rumor has spread all over the towns.
If he still didn’t know
what the Color of Ocean and Heaven was,
I’m afraid
his brain could be a stupid chamber pot.
This is what we carved
on the Seal of Cautiousness.
This seal is the object,
representing the master of our sect.
I’ve been ignorant for years.
Not until recently
did I know the greatness of the pattern.
Demons are running amuck everywhere.
I know how slight my talent is.
I want to find a talented man out of you
to take over the Seal of Cautiousness
so that we can find
the Color of Ocean and Heaven
and fight against Demons together!
-Bravo!
Is Huo Liantao really so good
at persuading people?
No wonder even Phoenix Master
was bought over.
This is the confidence and charm
to call on everyone.
When you learn a little bit,
you can deceive people with it.
Master Huo doesn’t look like a bad man.
Will he really pick a master
of the Martial World?
Martial arts Huo Liantao has
are not half as good
as Old Master Huo’s.
I really wonder
who taught him the deceiving skills.
The best way to deceive people
is to tell the truth and lies together.
Unlike someone
who makes up everything
and sounds obviously deceptive.
She can fool no one, but idiots.
Seems like you’ve got a lot to learn.
Who...? Who is the idiot?
Huo Liantao, are you telling the truth?
Well, pick our Tortoise Master, then!
Give us the Seal!
-Pick Tortoise Master!
When he appeared,
he showed the ripple pattern
and said it was the heirloom
of his family.
What exactly does he want?
Demons have kept an eye on him.
Besides, he offended many men
in the dungeon.
He didn’t have a choice,
but to expose
the Color of Ocean and Heaven
and see who wants to take over the Seal.
In this way,
he can draw the Demons’ attention off.
I think there’s more of it.
I guess
Huo Liantao is up to something else.
Why must we pick him
as the Master of Martial World?
Does he deserve it?
Come and compete if you dare!
Let’s decide with our martial arts.
Fine, then!
Come on. Come up.
Master Huo!
We all know
the ripple pattern is extraordinary.
But do you know
what the Color of Ocean and Heaven
truly represents?
The treasure is known
as the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
During the mutiny of the former dynasty,
all martial artists felt insecure.
Demons used dirty tricks
to persecute the faithful men!
Over the past few years,
many relics of heroes
and many achievements of masters
would be ruined
in the calamity.
Then my brother contacted many people
to fight side by side,
including Mr. Yin Wenlan, Mr. Li Zheng,
and seniors of Qi School.
Led by my brother,
they formed an alliance,
known as the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
It was set up,
to rescue orphans of different sects
and protect their relics.
The Color of Ocean and Heaven is
the hope to recover the martial world.
Whoever has it will master the world.
To get it, Demons attacked Yin’s Mansion
several times
and massacred
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Even people with Qi School
stayed in seclusion.
You can imagine how powerful
the Color of Ocean and Heaven is!
What did I tell you?
Huo Liantao failed to figure out
what the Color of Ocean and Heaven was.
Then, he pretended he knew it
and held the Assembly.
How did you know he figured out nothing?
Because he’s made up
a similar story to mine.
Made up?
Fei.
What did you tell Yang Jin?
How... How bad you are!
Bonehead, calm down.
I...
If you act on impulse again,
I’ll ask Hongyu to bite you.
You’re from the south.
Why are you scared of a snake?
I’m even scared of coldness.
Be nice to Hongyu.
Don’t bully it.
Stop, all of you!
Your Highness.
Something feels wrong.
Stop moving forward.
You must be the Third Prince.
I’ve heard a lot about you.
Very good!
Master Huo.
What you said sounds great.
Whoever hears it can take part.
I’d like to do something.
Let me be the Master of Martial World
and take over the Seal of Cautiousness.
Junior Master Huo.
Like you just said,
we’re having the Assembly today.
Since so,
we should compete in martial arts.
Who has the best martial arts
can get the Seal of Cautiousness!
Without the competition,
why do you think you can get the Seal?
-Yeah!
-Without the competition,
why do you think you can get the Seal?
Everybody.
Show some mercy in the competition.
Don’t kill each other.
We’ll compete, without doubt.
Fight, or be cowards.
Since we’d like to compete,
let’s kill Ding Kui first.
Such an evil man like him
has openly come
to the Demon-Extermination Assembly.
Master Huo, don’t you do something?
-Kill him!
-Yes! Kill Ding Kui!
-Kill him! Kill Ding Kui!
-Kill him!
Does he want these martial artists
to kill each other?
After a short while,
Huo Liantao became the backbone.
No one remembers
what he did in the dungeon.
It’s so easy for him to buy people over.
Brother.
Are they really going to fight?
Don’t worry.
When Master Huo is here,
nothing will go wrong.
Huo Liantao.
You’re giving them a chance
to take revenge on me.
I’m not scared of such weak men.
But,
before you fight me,
why don’t you ask Huo Liantao something?
If the Color of Ocean and Heaven
is really something great,
why didn’t his family mention it before?
-Yeah.
-He makes some sense. He’s right.
Good question.
Since the Color of Ocean and Heaven
was a good cause,
why did those founders
keep it secret from others?
Well, let me explain.
Even if some sects were destroyed,
they must have left
some treasures,
such as sharp weapons,
long-lost recipes, prescriptions,
or even martial books
handed down through ages.
There were 63 sects, big or small.
They accounted for
nearly half of the martial world,
having treasures
many men are crazy about.
Now, Demons are running amuck.
If we can’t find the treasures
to defend the martial world
and protect the people,
we’ll be too ashamed to live on!
Yeah, Master Huo is right.
He makes sense. Makes sense.
What a beautiful lady!
Why is she coming?
Master.
She came to question us
a couple of days ago.
I thought she was like Ding Kui.
So, I didn’t tell you.
Idiot!
We can hide the news
about the Color of Ocean and Heaven
from everyone except her.
Master Huo.
If the Color of Ocean and Heaven
is real treasure,
heirs of Li Zheng, the South Blade,
should command all martial artists.
It’s not your turn.
Fei?
Here we meet again.
Who are those people in the pavilion?
Master Huo.
They’re heirs of the South Blade,
Miss Zhou Fei
and Mr. Li Sheng.
They saved me in Lingling Inn.
Really?
Why is Madam Nichang on our side?
Does she not have the invitation,
either?
She is a close friend
of Old Master Huo.
But I wonder
why Huo Liantao invited her
after he made trouble.
What exactly is
the Color of Ocean and Heaven?
No one knows?
Everybody, don’t be fooled by him.
If you die
for some unknown treasure,
does it make any sense?
In such a martial world,
people strive for different things.
What kind of treasure is it
that makes so many people strive for it,
at whatever cost?
Madam Nichang.
You don’t decide
whether the Color of Ocean and Heaven
is a real treasure.
I hear the young generation
of the Fortress of the Forty-Eight
are present.
How about asking them
why the Demons attacked them
again and again?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. Why?
They can’t explain, huh?
You come to see the fun,
but get involved.
There’s real fun to see.
Everybody.
I’m Li Sheng,
with the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
The Fortress of the Forty-Eight
has no other options?
Why did they send such a young man?
Why did the Demons attack us?
To risk their neck.
If anyone wants the same thing,
come and try.
Fei, what are you talking about?
Heroes present
can’t be as shameless
as the Demons.
I heard there was a great heir
of the South Blade
who saved General Wu’s daughter,
stirred up trouble in Huarong
and killed Dragon Master Zheng Luosheng.
This delicate pretty girl
must be General Wu Fei’s daughter.
Fine. Expect those dead men,
everyone involved
with the Color of Ocean and Heaven
has been right here.
You can finally explain to us
what it is,
can’t you?
The thing you asked about...
I’ve never heard of it
from my seniors.
But I don’t think
my grandfather would hide it
from my aunt
when he let her take over
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
My father didn’t say anything, either.
I’m not a martial artist.
Now I’m even homeless.
I won’t interfere with your things.
I’m not sure
what the Color of Ocean and Heaven is.
But most of the people
who had the ripple pattern
have been dead.
Under such circumstances,
do you still want to look for it?
Don’t move. Behave yourselves.
I didn’t expect Huo Liantao
to collude with the Demons!
Why do you think he can collude with me?
He’s my dog!
The Demon-Extermination Assembly
turns out to be a plot of the Demons!
You want martial artists
who hate the Demons
to kill each other
so that you can take advantage of that!
Your Highness.
Looks like
your subordinate is much smarter.
But that’s not completely right.
Having those insignificant men
kill each other
is a mere plan of Huo Liantao.
I just made use of his plan.
Lord Chu.
It’s your problem with Huo Liantao.
It has nothing to do
with the Third Prince.
It’s his own fault.
Instead of being the prince,
he insists on interfering
with the martial world!
Or how is the Huo family so arrogant?
Just because they think
they can rely on the court.
Huo Liantao offended
all martial artists.
Being hunted by us,
he could only hide in this damn forest.
When you’re no longer his friend,
he and his family
will totally disappear, right?
So,
having the Third Prince
be hurt or killed
in his mansion
can be the last thing he wants.
What exactly do you want?
Why don’t you be specific?
I’m just going to exchange your prince
for what I want.
Keep an eye on them
and wait for my command.
If Huo Liantao refuses
to give me the real Seal,
kill them!
-Aye.
Your Highness.
I’d like to ask you something.
If the Color of Ocean and Heaven
isn’t a real treasure,
what are you going to do?
So many people died for it.
Can you make amends for them?
Madam Nichang.
For the sake
you’re the head of Yuyi Troupe,
I respect you.
But don’t push it.
Heirs of the Fortress of the Forty-Eight
don’t know about it,
because their elders
find them unreliable
and don’t want to tell them.
My brother entrusted me
with the Seal of Cautiousness.
You have nothing to do
with what it really is.
How dare he say we’re unreliable!
He’s the most unreliable man!
Don’t make trouble.
Animal characters made by CG
I’ll go check on her.
Let Yang Jin go.
He’s more worried.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Animal characters made by CG
Go away!
Hongyu.
At last, Hongyu.
Since you saw it, I must kill you.
What do you want?
How dare you bully her!
Why are there
so many buckets of kerosene?
What is Huo Liantao up to?
Fire his forest?
If there’s a fire
and it’s hard to walk
through the forest,
we’ll all die in the fire.
He wants to kill us all
who don’t have an invitation.
How shameless they are!
Burn us when failing to defeat us?
Is this a competition
in martial arts or evilness?
I’ll go find my brother
and get everybody out.
Okay. I’ll go with you.
Idiot.
What if someone lights a fire again?
Stay and keep an eye.
You make sense.
Come back quickly.
I see.
I can prove
if this thing exists.
Chu Tianyu?
Eunuch Chu.
They haven’t made it clear yet.
You’d better not take rash action.
The same to your snake.
The Color of Ocean and Heaven
is a real treasure.
During the rebellion
against the former dynasty,
a collection of treasures
was taken out of the palace
and guarded by some martial artists.
I witnessed that!
I’m a eunuch from the palace.
Under the command of the Third Prince,
I come to be Master Huo’s witness.
Everybody.
You can check this badge.
It’s Zichen’s badge.
What’s wrong?
Do you know who he is?
What are you going to fight him with?
How do you have the badge
of the Third Prince?
Well,
I won some respect.
It’s really the badge
of the Third Prince.
I invited the Third Prince
to visit your mansion.
You don’t mind, do you?
Uh...
Huo Liantao.
You have the Third Prince
as your backer.
Are you going to bring our business
to the court?
Now, even a eunuch can be my witness.
Nichang.
What else do you have to say?
Elimination of Considerations
Mr. Ying.
Think carefully about it.
If you die,
the Big Medicine Valley
will be thoroughly ruined.
Big Medicine Valley?
You knew him?
I didn’t.
But not many living people
can recognize Bone-chilling at once
and know very well
the property of Reborn Pill.
Mr. Ying.
It’s hard to hold back your anger.
But you must swallow it.
Junior Master Huo.
Since the treasure is real,
take out the Seal of Cautiousness.
Whoever has the best martial arts
will get it.
Looks like
they’ll fight.
Don’t break your promise!
-Yeah, yeah!
-Yeah!
-Don’t break your promise!
-Keep your promise.
-Yeah.
What are you doing?
Fei.
I think he’s an old friend.
I’ll go see him.
Did you see the crossbows
around their waists?
However great footwork you have,
when you rush out abruptly,
you will be shot like a sieve.
Let’s go around the forest, then.
Fine. I’ll go with you.
Where are you going?
He’s got a sunstroke.
I’m going to find a cool place for him.
Keep an eye on Mr. Ying.
Treasured Site
We’re finally out.
What’s wrong?
Where are the girls who led the way?
They’re all gone.
Now, no one is around.
You can tell me
why you’re going there, huh?
You saw that.
The eunuch held
Zichen’s badge.
Zichen may be in danger.
Before that eunuch appeared,
you had looked weird.
I can hide nothing from you.
Yes.
That man is a eunuch.
But he once worked for my dynasty.
You knew him?
All men with the Demons
had been famous in the martial world
before they sought refuge
with Shen Tianshu.
Chu Tianyu was an exception.
He went to our palace,
because he couldn’t survive.
He was a clever man.
So, he worked for my father.
When my father was young,
he studied and practiced martial arts.
He usually took this eunuch with him.
Unexpectedly,
my father didn’t do well
in education or martial arts.
But his eunuch
learnt a lot secretly.
During the rebellion against my dynasty,
he was bribed by traitors
and then betrayed my father
so that my father was drowned
during the war.
Because of this,
Yu Wenzhi recommended him to the Demons
and then he became Sparrow.
As he’s a eunuch,
he isn’t well-known
to the martial world.
He killed your father?
I’ll kill him for you.
Fei.
After being castrated,
Chu Tianyu became more vicious.
He punches fiercely.
If he had been more interested
in travelling around,
Shen Tianshu wouldn’t have been
the Head of Demons.
Are you not going
only because he has great martial arts?
If I don’t go,
I’ll be too ashamed
to meet my father in the lower world.
That’s it.
Let’s go.
Otherwise, the Assembly would be over.
Treasured Site
Master Huo.
Why don’t you take the Seal out
so that we can have a look?
-Yeah. Take it out!
-Take it out!
Eunuch Chu, you!
-Yeah.
-Let’s have a look.
Be very careful when you take it out.
Don’t get it switched accidentally.
If I’m annoyed,
the Third Prince
will suffer.
Go get it.
It’s about time.
It’s an imperial article.
It’s probably from Zichen’s badge.
Can he be locked here?
Look.
They’re dressed like eunuchs.
But their weapons...
Demons?
Chu Tianyu locked Zichen in this place.
First,
he could get the badge from Zichen
and pretend as a eunuch of this dynasty.
Second,
he could threaten Huo Liantao.
Two birds with one stone!
Fei.
Now,
unlock me, will you?
Eunuch Chu is confronting Huo Liantao.
Here are only some of his subordinates.
I don’t need your help
to kill them.
Xie Yun!
Are you alright?
How do you feel?
Is the Assembly fun?
Is it like what you read in books?
Thank you, Xie Yun.
And thank you, Miss.
All right. This is a dangerous place.
Take him away.
Mr. Xie, where are you going?
The old eunuch is extremely wicked.
He also colludes with Huo Liantao.
You can’t let down your guard.
Shall we
go out together?
Take care of the Third Prince
so that he won’t make more trouble.
As for him...
I’ll take care of him.
Why is the Poisoner missing, too?
I had meant
to figure out
how Old Master Huo died
so that I could tell Mr. Chongxiao.
Unexpectedly,
such men all made trouble.
What happened?
The signal was sent.
But no response has come
from the foot of the mountain.
Go check it!
Aye.
Master Huo.
You must be kidding, Eunuch Chu.
As a member of the Huo family,
I will never break my promise!
We agreed to compete for the Seal.
You’d better calm down.
Yeah.
Everybody,
why don’t you wait
until I make sure the Seal is real?
Master Huo.
Don’t keep the Third Prince
waiting so long.
Phoenix Master, what brings you here?
This is great!
Great!
How wonderful!
You praise yourself as a decent sect.
When failing to seek refuge
with the court,
you want us to help you against enemies.
What Seal of Cautiousness?
Funny!
Ding Kui, shut up!
You!
Good point!
Phoenix Master.
Take down these people
who cast greedy eyes on my treasure!
Huo Liantao.
You’ve made great fun.
You... You!
Mu Xiaoqiao.
My brother has just died.
You’ve already forgotten
how he helped you?
Shut up!
How dare you call my name?
-You...
-You have the nerve to bring Mr. Huo up?
Who are you?
Didn’t I just see this tree?
Why am I still here?
No way.
I can’t panic.
Yang Jin is waiting for me.
I must go back to my brother quickly.
Animal characters made by CG
Hongyu?
You know the way?
Bring him up.
Raise your head.
Look at him.
Can you recognize him?
This is...?
Junior Master! Junior Master!
Help... Help me!
I’m Xiaoliu who grows flowers for you.
You praised me for doing a good job.
Help me!
Junior Master Huo.
It’s your family problem.
You don’t need to solve it
in front of us, do you?
Junior Master Huo.
You have such a poor memory.
This man is Qian Xiaoliu,
a gardener at Huo’s Manor.
Oh,
he grows flowers perfectly.
He took care of flowers
in the gardens and backyards
of Huo’s Manor.
Phoenix Master.
We’re here for a great thing.
Did you break in crazily
just for this gardener?
You’re wrong.
This isn’t an ordinary gardener.
When I caught him,
he confessed
that he saw Junior Master Huo
moving out family properties long ago.
Old Master Huo who paralyzed in bed,
was left at the Manor alone,
waiting for the Demons.
Non... Nonsense!
Junior Master Huo.
Do you dare to swear
you had meant
to take away Old Master Huo,
who was paralyzed in bed,
when you ran away to Lingling Town?
I had, of course!
But...
But my brother didn’t want
to go with me.
Didn’t he want to go with you?
Qian Xiaoliu.
Tell him!
I saw...
I looked for the Seal of Cautiousness
for years!
It’s right in front of me.
Give it back to me.
Go away!
Shortly after Huo Liantao escaped
from Huo’s Manor,
Mr. Chongxiao and I arrived.
We saw Old Master Huo before he died.
Nonsense! Nonsense!
Phoenix Master, where did you find
this man
who kept talking nonsense?
He made up the lie
to deceive all the heroes!
He’s making me
a heartless man, isn’t he?
Huo Liantao!
I never expected that!
How shameless you are!
You colluded with the Demons.
You even abandoned your own brother!
Tell me.
Who made you brave enough
to stand here
and call yourself Master Huo?
Colluded with the Demons?
What does that mean?
Lord Chu.
I guess you don’t work
for the Third Prince,
but for Lord Shen of Demons Manor.
Handsome boy.
It’s been days.
You’ve made much progress.
You recognized him, too?
He is Chu Tianyu,
a lackey with Demons Manor.
Why do they turn up
wherever there’s news
about the Color of Ocean and Heaven?
Just like dogs after meat.
Shame on them!
Huo Liantao.
How dare you collude with the Demons!
Everybody.
Everybody, let me explain!
Let me explain!
Collude?
What a joke!
Huo Liantao is nothing,
but a dog of mine!
I...
Seems like
Chu Tianyu will fall out
with Huo Liantao
before killing people with his help.
Liantao.
I knew you were stupid
since you were little.
After so many years,
I didn’t expect you
to have learnt nothing!
You are as stupid as you were.
You collude with the Demons!
I can’t help suspecting
how your brother died.
How was he poisoned?
That time...
I hadn’t colluded with the Demons
back at that time.
Master.
He acknowledged it.
I’m afraid
there’ll be a desperate fight.
Fei, I’m serious.
Unlock me. I won’t run away.
I acknowledge
what Qian Xiaoliu said.
But... The poison...
It wasn’t me.
Poison?
However heartless I was,
I wouldn’t poison my own brother!
Old Master Huo
was poisoned?
Among the Demons,
only Pathetic Clam could
poison Old Master Huo.
Sheng! Sheng!
Bad news!
Someone is lighting a fire
in the forest!
On fire? On fire?
On fire? Go. Hurry.
Run! Go!
Huo Liantao, don’t try to run away!
Stop!
Screwed! There’s all kerosene
in the forest!
Fei, hurry.
Chu Tianyu is running away.
Don’t move.
Miss Zhou. Miss Zhou.
Miss Zhou.
Go!
Zichen ran towards the back
of the mansion.
Let’s go pick him up.
Give me the Seal!
Catch him!
Huo
Sparrow
Wanna run?
Bonehead.
Finally, you’re back.
Are you alright?
You’re here. I’d certainly come back!
I made marks all the way.
Yang Jin.
Take Chuchu and Yan
out of the forest
by following Hongyu.
What about you?
I must go back.
Those martial artists can’t come out,
unless someone leads the way.
Let me help you.
Two girls and a snake.
Don’t you worry about them?
Well, be very careful, then.
Sheng.
Be careful.
Uh... Uh...
Why are we back
after going around?
You misled us
when you didn’t know the way.
Go to hell!
Stop!
Tortoise Master.
We’re in the same trouble.
Let’s get out of this place first.
He wasted so much time.
What if I insist on killing him?
Tortoise Master.
You really can’t
distinguish the right from the wrong.
Do you really want to reject me
and trap everyone in this forest
filled with kerosene?
Uh...
Are you so eager to be a public enemy?
Public enemy?
Of whom?
Weak men like you?
Mr. Li.
I haven’t asked you
for the Color of Ocean and Heaven yet.
Can’t you see that?
Who has the Color of Ocean and Heaven
will be the public enemy.
Shut your mouth.
Flies have got in.
Fine. If anyone wants the treasure,
kill me now.
If anyone wants to live,
follow me!
Mr. Li?
When I met you in Lingling Inn,
I was too busy to say hello.
You’re Li Zheng’s grandson?
You can walk through the forest?
Yes.
I learnt some Qi Men Dun Jia skills
from Mr. Chongxiao.
Fine! I’ll go with you.
Follow us if you want to live.
Otherwise,
stay and wait to die!
Let’s go.
Who dares to leave before I agree?
Take them out first.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪