♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 29
Other than those
of the Big Medicine Valley,
manuals of other sects
abound,
such as that of the Mountain Sword,
-The Mountain Sword?
-and
the South Blade
my grandfather practiced.
Sounds like
a collection
of all sects, right?
Manuals.
Your grandfather’s blade.
A collection of all sects.
Where are they?
The Demon-Extermination Assembly
held by Huo Liantao.
Let’s go.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Alright. I’ll go pack up.
He can be a hired muscle.
Only Yang Jin
would buy such nonsense.
Food is ready.
Looking good.
Why is everything cold?
I’ve checked.
You’d better eat cold food,
because anything hot
may lead to a quicker death
by poisoning.
Which quack told you that?
Poisoner Ying Hecong.
Why?
Was he wrong?
What else did he say?
Reborn Pill of
the Big Medicine Valley...
That’s useless to me.
You knew that already?
Hey,
do you think
I’m after that Bracelet
for the Reborn Pill?
I’m only doing it
as per my ancestor’s will.
Think about it.
That valley was gone a long time ago.
Pills Mr. Yutai took
were the ones
found outside.
You weren’t even born
at that time.
Since then,
so many years have passed.
Those pills would’ve gone bad.
And they weren’t the elixir of life,
right?
You have a point.
Bring me something hot next time.
These are as bad
as the buns I had
in the dungeon.
Would you rather die sooner?
No.
But I would
if you feed me these every day.
I’ll eat them with you.
Fei, you don’t need to do this.
I don’t regret
what happened to me.
It has nothing to do with you.
Aren’t you curious
why I own so much energy?
I’ve never seen anyone
with more energy than you.
So far,
I only know two people
that might be your match.
Yellow and Green Palm, Duan Jiuniang
and the head of Demons Manor,
Shen Tianshu.
You must think I’m too young
to have reached this level,
right?
I’m sure you’ve figured it out.
Technically speaking,
that’s not my energy.
My uncle forcibly expanded
my meridian channels
and transfused
all his energy to me.
You must’ve learned
at home
once the energy
was drained,
one would only end up dead.
Basically, that’s a life for a life.
Correct. I’m a murderer
because someone died to save me.
As long as I’m alive,
General Wang Lin’s Anping Army
won’t stop the fight
because they believe
the Xiaos’ offspring
is the hope
to restore the reign.
So
I’m also a threat to the state.
As a murderer and a threat,
I’m living on borrowed time,
don’t you agree?
Who the ruler is
doesn’t matter to the masses
as long as they can live well.
Back in the dungeon,
if you hadn’t come,
I would’ve gotten myself out.
Thanks to you,
I’ve lived one more year.
Consider what I did for the Fortress
a thank-you gift.
Don’t feel guilty.
So you’ve said all that
to relieve my guilt?
Would I turn a blind eye to you
if you weren’t poisoned because of me?
Your business is also mine!
What are you looking at?
Stop talking,
and start eating now or never.
I believe there’s always a way out.
Without the Reborn Pill,
there must be something else.
If I were you,
whether it’s the Big Medicine Valley
or that Bracelet,
I won’t give up any hope.
Even if I fail eventually,
I’ll die with no regrets
and rest in peace.
Don’t ever
say that again,
or I’ll whack you!
♪The sun and the moon still shine on♪
♪The world is big♪
♪Why not explore it♪
♪I’m wild and proud♪
♪I may win or lose♪
♪But I won’t back off♪
♪So what if I’m young♪
♪Horse and sword keep me going on♪
♪Need no money or fame in my purse♪
♪All for a clear conscience♪
It hurts!
My hand and foot are bruised.
Help!
How could I eat?
I can’t eat on my own.
You again.
I thought you were asleep at this hour.
What do you want?
I haven’t had a good night’s sleep
since I arrived in Lingling.
And I was too busy
hiding from the Route Gang
to bathe over the past few days.
Smell it.
I’m sweaty and stinky.
You smell fine.
I’m a renowned figure
after all.
Please do me a favor
and bring me some bathwater.
Alright.
Well...
The lock...
You can bathe with it.
Don’t worry.
It won’t rust.
The quality of Madam Nichang’s product
is guaranteed.
She runs an honest business.
You know that, don’t you?
My hand...
One hand is inconvenient.
Inconvenient how?
It’s...
It’s hard to do things with one hand.
You can use extra hands.
Won’t that be too much trouble?
Not at all.
I don’t want to be a bother.
I’ll ask Li Sheng to help you.
Fei! Fei!
Fei, I can’t bathe in front of him!
No peeking,
or I’ll tell Chuchu
you’re a pervert.
Why would I peek?
And what’s that
to do with Chuchu?
Why would you tell her?
So you two are like sisters.
Sisters?
When did I...?
Are you crazy?
Where are you going?
Unlock me.
It just came to me
that Fei had told me repeatedly
you’d try everything
to drive me away.
I won’t fall for your tricks.
Let’s go.
I won’t drive you away.
Make it quick.
What... what are you doing?
I can’t bathe like this.
Give me a hand.
What are you? A mandarin duck?
Stop dabbling!
Don’t you bathe like this?
I can only use one hand.
It’s inconvenient.
Give me yours,
or I can’t do this.
Feels good!
Hey, isn’t this awkward?
Don’t forget I’ll have to get dressed.
Hold... Hold on.
I’ll go to the back
and wait for you behind the screen.
How could I get dressed with one hand?
I’ll unlock you.
Really?
Yes, I will.
Alright. Thanks.
Mr. Xie,
Zhou Fei is more stubborn
than she seems.
She’s stubborn as a mule.
Everyone in our Fortress
knows that.
You can say that again!
It’s fine
if she’s just stubborn.
But ever since she met you,
she’s become evil.
What’s that supposed to mean?
Seeing that
she tied your hand
with your feet yesterday,
I’ve been wondering
if the disciple has outsmarted
the master
and if he’s digging his own grave.
Mr. Xie.
Are you mad?
What’s taking you so long?
Are you done?
Crap!
What are the odds?
Are you also out to see the moon?
When you were bathing,
I knew
I’d find you here.
Your cousin is right.
I am
digging my own grave.
Don’t move!
Fine. I won’t.
Behave yourself.
Good night.
Take care.
Get some rest.
Have a sweet dream.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
What about me?
You?
I’m going to bed.
Don’t.
I’m not done serving you.
-What are you doing?
-Come on.
I’m sorry, Mr. Li. I was wrong.
-I’m sorry.
-How could you be wrong?
Stop, please. I’m sorry.
I really am.
Behave yourself.
Miss Zhou.
Miss Zhou?
Miss Zhou, are you in?
Are you there?
Sir,
are you looking for Miss Zhou?
You’re awake.
You know me?
We all saw you when Miss Zhou
carried you back yesterday.
Oh, that.
That was a prank.
Sorry about it.
One of my friends is a foodie
from Jiankang.
Fei, do you mean Mr. Xie?
May I ask
if you’re surnamed Xie?
You know that, too?
Are you from Jiankang?
You aren’t
some fortuneteller, are you?
No. I’m Zhu Chen with Xingnan Sect.
Miss Zhou once did me a favor.
I know you
because she told me a lot
about a friend of hers surnamed Xie.
Is that duck stuffed with sticky rice
Jiankang’s specialty?
Yes.
Jiankang is also my hometown.
Miss Zhou said
she’d like to try the specialties there,
so I made this for her.
Mr. Xie,
would you like some?
No, I’m good.
Thank you.
From now on,
serve all his food cold
and bring it to my room.
I’ll give it to him.
Yes.
What’s up?
Miss Zhou,
is Mr. Xie
in poor health?
He seems unwell.
I’ve seen rarities
when traveling with others.
I can keep
fine herbs for you
if you need.
Thank you,
but no need.
I...
This...
I can explain.
I didn’t run away.
I left to cook
duck stuffed with sticky rice for you.
Try it.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
What do you think?
Is it good?
Which one is better?
Mine
or Mr. Zhu’s?
I don’t know.
I didn’t eat his.
Li Yan did.
You can ask her.
It’s tasty, right?
Just because you cooked this for me
doesn’t mean I’m going to unlock you.
I won’t run away again.
I swear.
What game are you playing now?
I should ask Madam Nichang
if there’s a way to shorten the chain
to stop you from escaping forever.
I couldn’t even stand her
eating someone else’s dish.
How could I leave her?
What do you want?
After you die,
may I keep your body?
Look,
the Bone-chilling poison
didn’t kill you
and you could give yourself
the Soul-searching Needle.
You’re one of a kind
and too valuable to be buried.
Don’t you agree?
Who the heck is he?
I promise
that I’ll
preserve your body well
for future studies.
Do we have a deal?
By the way,
did Hu Tianying
poison you?
I’ve been looking for her.
Can you let her know
you’re still alive
to lure her out?
Then I’ll be able to...
What’s wrong with them?
Don’t they have manners?
Auspicious Cranes
and Propitious Clouds
Lingling Inn
Today, Huo Liantao is holding
the Demon-Extermination Assembly
at this place.
Chuchu and I will go have a look
and ask around
about Old Master Huo
for Taoist Priest Chongxiao.
Do as you see fit.
Take care of Chuchu.
Take me with you.
If I continue lying in bed,
I won’t be able to walk again.
You can’t go.
Just stay put.
I agree.
Mr. Xie, you’re still weak.
Better stay here with Fei
and keep an eye on Li Yan.
Once Chuchu and I get back,
I’ll take her home.
Too late.
She’s long gone.
She’s gone?
My egg!
When did she leave? How did you know?
This morning, I was up early
and I saw your sister
dragged Mr. Yang out
to some Assembly.
Why didn’t you stop her?
I...
Sheng,
you know Yan well.
Who could make her stay?
What if she’s in danger?
She’s with that bonehead.
That guy will only make things worse.
I must get her back.
I’ll go with him.
Excuse me.
Coming.
Sir.
Miss Zhou here
can’t stop eating your pine nuts.
Can we have more, please?
Sure. Coming right up.
Here you are.
Do you also want to go there?
It’s a pity to miss it.
Besides,
despite what you said,
I guess
you can’t help worrying about them,
can you?
Don’t pretend you know me so well.
I know you came all the way
for the Assembly.
You can attend it only under my watch.
But I’m warning you.
Do not try to escape
or engage in a fight again.
Sure. We have a deal.
And
can you
unlock me, please?
Alright.
No problem.
Thanks.
I swear I won’t run away.
Miss Zhou,
didn’t you say you’d unlock me?
I did say that,
but I can
lock you again in another way.
You win.
What happened to them?
Are they escaped prisoners?
A man and a woman.
Have a look.
-Take a look.
-Are you sure to walk around like this?
We might get arrested
before arriving at the Assembly.
I dare them!
Luojin Ready-to-wear Clothes
How about
we get changed first?
This way.
Luojin Ready-to-wear Clothes
May I have a look at that one?
That one?
Looking good.
Sir, how much is it?
That one is a bit pricey.
I like this one.
-You have good taste, ma’am.
-Let’s take this one.
It suits your husband perfectly.
Sir, you’re mistaken.
He...
It’s great. I love it.
Right,
dear...?
It’s made of the finest cotton.
The price is a bit...
That’s fine. We can afford it.
I understand.
Are you done?
We got a problem.
Fei, you...
Could you unlock me?
I can’t get changed like this
on my own.
I promise
I won’t escape.
Fei,
I swear to heaven.
Please. I mean it.
Unlock me now.
I’ll trust you this once.
What are you doing?
Do you want to be seen
with me like this?
No peeking.
Close your eyes.
Is it open?
It’s taking longer than I thought.
Didn’t Li Sheng open it at once?
How come?
I’ve studied
this Eight-trigram Lock.
One must know Eight Trigrams
and the tips
to open it easily.
Think again.
You’ve studied it?
Is this what they call
to hold hands
and grow old together?
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
Luojin Ready-to-wear Clothes
Hadn’t I heard them talking about
a locked couple in the street,
I wouldn’t have known you are out.
Mr. Xie,
you’ve got changed quickly.
But how,
I wonder?
Let’s go.
Luojin Ready-to-wear Clothes
Huo’s Manor
Stop.
Do you have an invitation?
Yes.
May I have a look?
Please.
The invited can go this way.
Stop.
Do you have an invitation?
No.
Hold on.
No invitation.
Please.
The uninvited go this way, please.
Stop. Do you have an invitation?
Yes.
Please.
Bonehead,
what to do?
They all have invitations.
How about
we steal one?
No.
The one Mr. Zhu received
has his name on it.
Others’ must be the same.
We can’t use
any of them.
Since when did you become so smart?
I always am.
Follow me.
Lord asks for you.
Excuse me, do you have invitations?
Of course!
Where are they?
Bonehead,
do you have them?
You didn’t give them to me.
I did back in the inn.
Find them.
You didn’t.
Yes, I have them.
Give me a minute.
I’m sorry.
My friend here
is a bit slow.
Please bear with him.
It’s fine if you don’t have them.
This way, please.
I’m sorry
but seats at
the waterside pavilion are limited.
As per Lord’s order,
the uninvited go this way, please.
You’ll be seated over there.
Alright.
We aren’t picky.
Please.
Take it away.
I’ve had better food in the palace.
How dare you serve me such trash!
I’m sorry.
On my way to Lingling House
to pick up braised seedpod-shaped pork,
I overheard
the Third Prince,
Chen Zichen, is also in town.
And that concerns me how?
I’m not his mother.
His whereabouts aren’t my business.
Yes. I understand.
Wait.
What’s he doing here
at this moment?
He can’t be here
for the Assembly, can he?
Lord Chu,
Lord Huo and the Third Prince
go way back.
Very well.
Let’s go
pay His Highness a visit
and invite him over.
Lord Chu,
that won’t be necessary.
Lord Huo has promised
to give you the Seal of Cautiousness.
In case he changes his mind
and gives me a fake one instead,
I’m going to need His Highness
as leverage.
After all,
the last thing Huo Liantao wants
is to see a prince die at his place.
He’s made enough enemies.
If the court is also on to him,
I’m afraid
the Huo family will stop at him.
Your Highness,
I agree with Mr. Xie.
We’d better
stay away from the Assembly.
We’re already here.
So are talents across the state.
We can take this chance
to hire the best ones to work for us.
If we miss it,
who knows when such
a once-in-a-lifetime chance
will come again?
But...
Your Highness.
Your Highness, Lord Huo
has sent a carriage to pick you up.
How did he...?
He’s made the gesture.
If we refuse to go,
won’t that be disrespectful?
Let’s go.
Do you have invitations?
No.
Huo’s Manor
This way, please.
Do you have invitations?
I have.
They’re with me.
This way, please.
The invited go this way.
-This way, please.
-Do you have invitations?
What?
I can’t go in without one?
You can.
This way, please.
It’s been a while.
Indeed, Mr. Zhuang Bi.
So invitations aren’t necessary.
The uninvited go that way.
Are the guests divided into two groups?
Maybe they’re seated separately.
Are there two sessions?
One for each group?
Huo’s Manor
The waterside pavilion isn’t big enough.
As per Lord’s order,
the uninvited go this way, please.
Your seats are over there.
Fine.
I’ll
see you later.
Guests are separated by invitations?
Miss Zhou, Mr. Xie,
we can go together.
No, thanks.
My cousins should be over there.
We’ll join them.
Thank you, Mr. Zhu.
Thank you.
Please.
Let’s go.
What is Huo Liantao up to?
Be quiet.
I’m memorizing the direction.
This forest
is a maze.
It’s hard to get out once we’re in.
Don’t you think something is odd?
Odd?
These trees look fine to me.
How are they odd?
I mean,
isn’t this place...
Over there.
Li Yan.
What are you doing?
There might be a snake.
Snake!
Where is it?
Animal characters made by CG
It’s gone.
Wait... wait for me!
Animal characters made by CG
Stop!
Don’t touch me,
or there will be dire consequences.
What is he doing here?
Who is it?
He seems to be
that Poisoner with Mr. Xie.
How dare you
release a snake!
I did that
to punish Ding Kui
for bullying a waitress.
It’s the master’s order
to separate the invited
and uninvited guests.
Go to him if you have a problem with it.
Why bully a girl?
You’re playing the hero.
Let’s see
how tough you are!
Who are you?
Yang Jin from the Cloud Ravine.
And me,
Li Yan from the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight.
Wait for it.
This isn’t over!
I’ll report to Tortoise Master
to teach you a lesson.
Let’s go.
I learned that move from your cousin.
Didn’t I do it faster
and better than her?
How are your hands?
Am I more skilled than her?
Thanks for your help.
Step back, please. Thanks.
Are you from the Small Medicine Valley?
Yes.
But he knows nothing about medicine.
Must you add that?
Hey, why didn’t you
attack them with your snakes?
My snakes?
They’re my babies
and worth much more
than their lives.
My snake!
Hongyu.
-Hongyu?
-Hongyu.
Hongyu.
Hongyu. Hongyu.
We’ve already saved him.
Why help him find his snake?
Hey,
is a big man like you
afraid of snakes?
I’m not. I...
What is that?
I raised those snakes.
They can recognize
the sound of my flute.
But right after
entering in the woods,
they ran wild
as if something scared them.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪