Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 2
Please.
Please wait a moment.
I’ll go to inform Young Master.
Ban Heng.
Pay attention to your appearance.
Why did Your Grace
come to my mansion today?
This man is annoying,
but he is indeed good-looking.
Sorry about my abrupt visit.
Greetings, Count Cheng’an.
Greetings.
May I ask,
what brings you here?
Thank you
for exonerating my family
in court earlier.
This is a little something
to show our gratitude.
I appreciate that,
but your gift is...
Take it.
It... It means a lot to me,
but I want you to have it.
Alright then.
That’s too generous of you.
Don’t mention it.
Come here.
Look.
King
and Flame.
Both crickets have swept the board
in all six sites in the city.
They’re invincible!
Enough. Stop embarrassing yourself.
Let Young Master Ban continue.
I can’t wait to hear more.
I know you have a good taste.
King
is highbred and beautiful
with a perfect body and a sharp mouth.
No one
can survive under his attack.
He’s won 40 times in a row
in the East Division.
Flame
was born a fighter
with a lot of potential.
He’s a steady winner,
a legend with 38 victories
in the South Division.
When those two are together,
the war is on. Only one can win.
Bite him. Why are you so quiet?
Weren’t you two
eager to kill each other last time?
Why are you all polite now?
Maybe King feels sorry
about hurting the other
last time
and he’s thinking of a way to apologize.
The other cricket
reeks of old books.
That’s why King is avoiding him.
Bite him!
Flame is innocent
but being blamed for no reason
by someone with no sense of guilt.
Poor thing!
That stinky cricket
assumes he’s so hot
that the whole world loves him.
That’s right.
He’s one of a kind.
Or he wouldn’t be so expensive.
Shut up!
You must apologize!
King bit the other first.
So he should apologize to Flame.
Go on! They’re battling.
I don’t have all day
to bicker with you.
Calm down, Baroness.
Alright.
Do you dare play?
The loser must apologize.
Have a try, Count Cheng’an.
Fine.
Please do it for me, Young Master Ban.
I won’t let you down.
Watch out, sister!
Whose side are you on?
The war concerns no kinship. Bite him!
Bite him!
Go on. Do it!
Yes, good boy!
Go ahead!
Bite again!
You cheated!
Whatever. Anything to win.
Bite him!
Butler Rong
Go, go, go!
Do it. Come on! Go ahead.
Bite him!
I won!
I won.
Admit it.
Useless!
I apologize.
-Apology accepted.
-You’re good as always.
Let’s go, Ban Heng.
We can play again next time.
Crickets are surprisingly fun.
I hate Count Cheng’an. I hate him!
Don’t be mad, Baroness.
Calm down.
Let me burn some soothing incense.
Celebratory Bedding and Clothing
Him again?
What kind of person is he?
He doesn’t deserve such a good look.
I’m so pissed!
If Count Cheng’an
is there to buy fabrics,
Mother will believe my words,
won’t she?
Mother!
Celebratory Bedding and Clothing
-Look at this color.
-Sure.
How could he come
to pick up fabrics himself?
I’m curious, too.
You know, a dream
isn’t reality.
Mother, just be patient.
This isn’t too bad, though.
If you and Xie Qilin
got married,
you couldn’t even afford new fabrics.
I’ll take them all.
Deliver them to
Marquis Jingting’s Mansion.
Yes. You’ll receive them later today.
I’m needed elsewhere
and I have to go.
Mother...
Go home once you’re done shopping.
Don’t drain yourself.
Good day, Madam.
Celebratory Bedding and Clothing
Is that a coincidence?
Count Cheng’an!
What are the odds, Baroness?
You’re here!
Baroness, please let him go.
Please
don’t hurt him.
You’re mistaken, Baroness.
I’m on my way to pick up brushes and ink
and simply passing by.
Stay here. Don’t go anywhere.
I’ll go get my mother.
I’ll be right back.
Why does she want her mother to see me?
Young Master, let’s go,
or we’ll be late.
Please.
How come Baroness Ban
is wherever we are?
Was she stalking you?
Isn’t that what I wish for?
I know.
Still, I think
she’s a threat.
What if you’re too close
to the Ban family
to get rid of them later?
I need to be on better terms with them
to find out the truth.
That’s our carriage.
Baroness.
Have a seat.
Where’s Mother?
Look,
last night, I dreamed about
seeing Count Cheng’an
at the fabric store
and it came true.
Hua,
are you obsessed with him?
She means
her dream came true again.
It did?
So is Xie Qilin going to be blind?
Are you an idiot?
If so,
our family will be doomed, you know?
How about this?
You two go home. I’ll go find Mother.
Sure.
Father, I heard Xie Qilin is back.
He is?
Is he blind?
They didn’t say.
Your sister’s dream...
Father, are you saying...?
Let’s go find out at the Xie’s Mansion.
Is he blind?
Not yet.
He’s with a girl.
A girl?
It must be that harlot.
No. Doesn’t seem like one.
Is it Xie Wanyu?
That’s not her dressing style.
How do you know
what she dresses?
That brat.
He eloped a few days ago
and came back seeing someone so quickly.
How come she left?
He isn’t blind.
“Nature draws without ink.
-Rain plays songs with bamboos”.
-He’s fine.
What a shame!
Beautiful lines.
Young Master! Are you alright?
Did you get hurt, Young Master?
Let’s go. Come on.
Jump together on my count.
One, two, three.
Who are you?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Darling, I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have brought Heng to peek
at the Xie’s Mansion.
I’ll deal with you
once I get Heng out.
Darling. I won’t get up
until you forgive me.
I know I made a mistake.
I shouldn’t have acted on my own,
darling.
Kneel
all you want.
Darling! Darling!
I’m in serious trouble!
Count Xie will definitely make a fuss
after his son being injured by Ban Heng.
He’ll take action tomorrow in court.
Are you saying...?
Pass my order.
Stay away from it.
Check the Xie family in secret.
Yes.
Moonlight through the Cloud
Sky-holding Gate
Your Majesty, the Bans are lawless.
My son’s blind in one eye
because of Ban Heng.
Please bring the assailant to justice,
Your Majesty!
Ban’s Mansion
Madam ChangPrincess Royal,
Emperor Yunqing’s Aunt, Ban Hua’s Grandmother
Mother.
The court
is divided by
the Shis, Xies and Yans.
Heng’s case must be handled carefully.
Don’t act rashly.
Mother, this is between us and the Xies.
The other two families
won’t interfere, will they?
We don’t know for sure.
Be extra careful
in case we’re attacked from all sides.
The Bans and the Xies are equally
rich and powerful,
more so than others.
If the wrong one tries this case,
Heng will
definitely be in trouble.
But Count Cheng’an
can turn things around.
That guy again!
He’s the sole heir to the Rongs
and close to His Majesty
instead of the big three families.
He won’t take sides.
And he’s a role model for all scholars.
I’m sure he won’t risk his reputation.
Only he
can uphold justice
and prove Heng innocent.
What’s wrong?
You’re on it.
No, no, no. I can’t do it.
We’re enemies. I don’t want to see him.
Open it.
Look at you, Ban Heng.
Are you in custody or on vacation?
The prison guard is kind.
Act like a prisoner.
If Mr. Shi
sees you having a feast in jail,
will he help with your case?
Relax. Once he’s here,
I’ll look miserable.
By the way, Hua,
did you bring me my crickets?
You’re the best!
-Greetings, Mr. Shi.
Come on!
Greetings, Mr. Shi.
Shi Jin, Eldest Grandson of Prime Minister,
First Military General in Daye
Greetings, Baroness.
My mother is worried about Ban Heng
and she had me bring him some food.
What are these?
Is there meat?
I haven’t had any for days.
This place is hell.
I don’t even have clean clothes to wear.
Hua, catch it!
Baron... Baroness.
This is an accident.
I’m sorry.
It’s... It’s fine.
I’m ordered to investigate this case.
Baroness Ban,
could you give us a minute?
Sure. My brother is innocent.
We’ll know the truth
if he and Xie Qilin tell us everything.
I’ll leave you two alone
and wait outside.
My back hurts!
It’s been a while
since I last saw Shi Jin.
He’s become even more handsome.
Baroness.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
I’m sorry for troubling you
with Heng’s case.
That’s part of my job.
I assure you
that the truth will come out.
That’s great.
They all say
you’re inflexible,
but in my eyes,
you’re
as real as me
and easygoing.
What’s wrong?
Thank you, Baroness.
No need.
Listen. You can
be yourself in front of me.
Don’t be restrained.
Thank you in advance
for dealing with Heng’s case.
Sure.
Young Master,
here’s the book Xie Qilin sleeps with.
I see.
Collection of Poems
Nature draws without ink.
Rain plays songs with bamboos.
“Nature draws without ink”.
The view here is extraordinary.
Such beautiful scenery
deserves well-written couplets.
You first, Count Cheng’an.
Nature draws without ink.
Anyone?
Count Cheng’an,
that one is too difficult
for us.
Rain plays songs with bamboos.
Your Grace.
Feixian and Count Cheng’an
are talented.
Nature draws without ink...
Well-matched in poems.
That day, I saw
Xie Qilin and a woman doing couplets.
I’m nowhere near Count Cheng’an’s level.
You’re too modest, Miss Shi.
I’m lucky enough
to have met you here, Your Grace.
Whoever
marries Miss Shi
must be the real lucky one.
Unlike the one who takes that Baroness,
he must be cursed.
He is cursed.
Or Xie Qilin wouldn’t have eloped
and suffered a huge loss.
He’s a blind fool!
Ban Hua!
I thought
you wouldn’t come to such gatherings.
I wouldn’t,
but Miss Li wouldn’t leave me out of it.
You’re wrong about one thing, though.
He’s too blind to choose wisely,
but that has nothing to do with me.
Things didn’t go well between you two,
but he’s already blind.
I don’t think it’s appropriate
to rub it in.
Who are you to judge?
We’re here to do poems
as entertainment.
No need to be so hostile.
The investigation into Mr. Xie’s injury
is still ongoing.
Justice will be served eventually.
Let’s focus on poems now.
I agree with Count Cheng’an.
Why would a fine young man
fall for Shi Feixian?
I don’t get it.
It beats me.
Focus.
Hit on what he likes.
Ban Heng’s case is the priority.
I’m really in need of help.
May I have a word with you
if it’s not too much trouble?
We can
talk here, Baroness.
I’m afraid we can’t.
I’d really appreciate it
if we can talk in private.
I wonder...
If we…
Can find...
Let’s talk somewhere else.
Why is she suddenly so polite?
What’s gotten into her?
Goodness!
Feel free to speak your mind.
You’re making me uncomfortable.
If you don’t go with me,
I’ll continue talking like this.
It’s my pleasure
to speak to you, Count.
Please excuse me.
I’m sorry.
Thank you, Count.
Please follow me.
Baroness,
where are you taking me?
If it’s not too much trouble...
Drop your act.
What is this about?
Uh...
Oh, right.
Listen,
gentlemen value justice
while the crooked men cling on benefits.
Gentlemen know right and wrong.
They’re selfless and considerate.
I believe
you, Count Cheng’an,
are a gentleman.
Gentlemen are aboveboard
while the crooked men...
The... The crooked men...
The crooked men...
Gentlemen are aboveboard,
while the crooked men...
Rocky!
The crooked men are rocky.
What do you want?
Just cut to the chase.
Or are you really picking a fight?
If there’s nothing else, I’m off.
Wait.
Forget it. Read it yourself.
I can save my breath.
Gentlemen value justice...
The crooked men are sneaky.
Young Master.
I understand why you’re here.
But I’m needed elsewhere.
Please excuse me.
Will you help me or not?
Sorry.
He didn’t give me an answer.
I’m so sick of his tone.
Sir,
I learned you have
valuable books in stock.
Is Collection of Poems in them?
Collection of Poems.
I remember that one.
There’s only one copy.
Someone paid a fortune
for it months ago.
Only one copy? What a shame!
Collection of Poems
Purity Teahouse
Welcome.
Count Cheng’an, what a coincidence!
Purity Teahouse
Are you also here for tea?
No.
I’m here for you.
I demand an answer.
Will you help
with my brother’s case or not?
If I interfere
and stick my nose into others’ business,
that won’t benefit any of us.
I’m sorry.
I think you don’t know
what you’re doing.
Let me give you a hand.
Baroness,
please stop.
Why should I?
This road isn’t yours.
Why can’t I take it?
It’s fine.
You’re right.
Everyone can take this road,
but better not
go in the wrong direction.
Sir, how much is this weasel hair brush?
I need this brush.
I’ll take it.
I’ll take it and pay you double.
These, too.
I’ll pay you double.
I’ll take it and pay you double.
Gentlemen are selfless and considerate.
If you’re interested in calligraphy,
I can give them to you.
Your Grace,
if you want them back,
just say the word.
I’ll give them all to you.
Sir, bag it.
I’ll pay you tenfold.
Young Master,
aren’t you only going to buy a brush?
Li’s Stationer
You...
You tricked me!
Xie’s Mansion
Mr. Shi, greetings.
Were there visitors
when Mr. Xie was injured?
No.
Miss Xie,
where were you that day?
At home working on a recipe
without going out.
Was there a witness?
My maid Yun was with me all day.
She can testify for me.
That day,
Miss Xie was studying how to cook...
the mixed stew.
She didn’t leave the house.
This way, please.
Are books
more attractive than me?
What a nerd!
Actually,
he’s a hot nerd.
Still nothing?
Let me show you what I’ve got.
You may leave.
Your Grace,
how could you say no to me?
Baroness, you...
You’re wearing
too much makeup.
Honestly,
it’s too strong for you.
Wanyu,
go talk to Shi Feixian.
Father,
must she hide the truth?
Qilin already said
it has nothing to do with her.
Better leave her out of it
in case of more trouble.
I understand.
Feixian.
What brings you here?
I need a favor.
Please don’t tell others
that you went to see Qilin that day.
Where is he?
Crap!
Stop!
How was your nap?
None of your business.
Can you
focus on what’s important?
You dozed off
because you were worried too much
about your family
to sleep at night, right?
Your help can make me sleep better.
Your Grace, here’s the thing.
Only if you help me
will I let you go.
Please behave yourself in public.
Reputation matters to good people.
Mine is too bad
to be saved.
But you’re different.
Do you want to be like me?
What are you doing?
I’ve finished it and I’m going home.
You can’t!
Young Master!
Please go back and wait for the news.
What do you mean?
If you keep badgering me,
I can’t help you even if I want to.
Am I right?
So is that a yes?
His answer is too ambiguous
to relieve any stress.
Will he help me or not?
Guess I can only
rely on myself.
Xie’s Mansion
Check over there.
You again!
Your family must have a thing
with walls.
You think I don’t want to use the door?
What are you doing here?
Has Xie Qilin
bought you over?
I caught you red-handed!
Calm down, Baroness.
I’m here this late for the case.
In the middle of the night?
You’d only come at this hour
for some dirty dealing.
Aren’t you also here?
I’ve given you my promise
and I’ll certainly
do my best to give you an answer.
Have you found anything?
Not yet.
Why did I believe you?
Goodbye.
You’re going to see Xie Qilin, right?
The easiest way
is to make him correct himself.
Don’t stand in my way
unless you have other ideas.
I’m not stopping you,
but are you sure
this will work?
I’ll have to try it first.
Here’s a friendly reminder.
Don’t try any rough stuff
with him.
Rough stuff?
Am I that kind of person?
Baroness Ban!
Be quiet!
They say
a wrong marriage begets misfortune.
Both of us are victims.
I admit that I hurt you.
I deserve this.
Relax. Bastards always live long.
I’m not here to kill you
but to ask you for a favor.
By... Holding a dagger against my neck?
That’s unique.
Or would you listen to me?
What do you want?
It’s time for me to rest.
Please let Ban Heng go.
Mr. Shi has taken this case.
You’ve come to the wrong person.
We grew up together.
You all think he’s an underachiever
and a troublemaker,
but I know
he’s good for one thing.
That is, he never lies.
If he injured your eye,
he’d admit it.
Are you accusing me
of lying then?
You tell me.
I’m here
to ask you
to tell the truth.
If my brother is to blame,
we won’t cover for him.
But if you’re venting your anger on him
for smashing your place,
then come to me.
I started the whole thing
and I’ll take full responsibility.
How?
Can you give me another eye?
Sure, if that’s what you want.
Take it yourself.
Are you done?
You should go.
I need to rest.
Xie Qilin.
Don’t.
Leave, or I’ll shout.
I’ll say you harass me.
Please don’t.
I’m not that desperate.
This is Count Cheng’an’s letter to you.
He said to read it
and you’ll know what to do.
Go west. Guards are fewer there.
“I have Collection of Poems.
Can we meet, Mr. Xie?”
Send Shi Jin in.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Long live, Your Majesty!
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Shi Jin, how’s the investigation going?
Tell us everything.
After three days of investigation,
I’ve found more to the case.
What is it?
To be fair,
I want the victim Xie Qilin
to repeat what happened that day.
Say it. Go ahead.
Mr. Shi,
I’m afraid
I don’t remember.
You don’t remember?
You...
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪