Sub by kisscambodia
In the early autumn of
the 18th year of Daye Zhenwu,
everyone in the Ban family
is busy preparing for
Baroness Ban’s wedding
with Young Master of the Xie family.
Pay attention to the notes!
Why do you always play the wrong notes?
And the one outside!
Get it done mindfully.
Don’t make any mistakes.
Yes, Master.
Where is Ban Heng?
Ban Heng!
Young Master!
Madam!
We got everything ready
including the things flying in the sky,
running on the ground,
even buried under the land.
Good.
Ten strings of South Sea Pearls.
Forty pairs of
mutton-fat jade bracelets.
Fifty luminous pearls.
Remember it well.
Baroness Ban’s wedding is pending.
Everyone should be mindful.
The bride’s escort team has arrived!
Come to help. Hurry!
Dress up Baroness Ban.
Speaking of the bride, Ban Hua,
what she is most famous for
is not only her outstanding appearance,
the generous personality,
but also her trend-setting
fashion taste.
She is basically the top character
in the capital of Daye.
Am I late?
Not at all. You’re just in time.
Come on, push it!
But in terms of
the appearance and talent
of Xie Qilin,
this bridegroom is unremarkable.
With the coming of the wedding day,
all the people are
looking forward to it.
It’s just what they want to see
is not how luxurious this wedding is.
They want to know
whether this wedding
can be held successfully.
Hua!
I, Xie Qilin,
will never marry you
even I have to die alone!
The bridegroom is not Xie Qilin.
What’s wrong?
Why are my dreams so strange these days?
Wedding
I, Xie Qilin, will break off
the engagement with Baroness Ban today
The Xie family broke off the engagement?
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 1
Make way!
Step aside! It’s Baroness Ban!
Take care of my horse.
Ban Hua, Eldest Daughter
of the Bans, Noblest Lady in Daye
The same carriage.
Seems like this is the place
in my dream.
Steamed bun restaurant.
Vegetable noodles
Vegetable noodles.
That’s right. Xie Qilin is here.
Xie Qilin, Second Son of the Xies,
Second Fiancé of Ban Hua
Baroness Ban! Run!
Don’t run!
Make way!
Stop!
What’s happening?
Xie Qilin!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Du Jiu, Personal Bodyguard of Rong Xia
Du Jiu. What’s the noise?
It’s Baroness Ban of the Ban family
creating the disturbance.
Ban Hua.
Could it be
that her wedding is canceled again?
If this marriage doesn’t work,
Baroness Ban
can hurt those beautiful men again.
Listen!
I, Xie Qilin,
will never marry you
even I will die alone!
You... Don’t come over!
I can’t go back with you!
I’m not here
to get you back to marry me.
She is here to beat him.
I’m afraid Young Master Xie
won’t make it this time.
Xie...
Qi…
Lin.
He broke off the engagement with you
because of me.
Just vent your anger on me.
Please don’t hurt Mr. Xie.
Don’t hurt my Yun.
Just come at me.
Well, these two people
are deeply in love.
Looks like
she is going to
break up this couple.
Exactly.
Look! Look all the money.
It’s money! Money!
I was born with beauty and wealth.
I can live a comfortable life
by myself.
If it wasn’t for the Xie family
to beg our Ban family,
how would you have the luck to marry me?
How dare you say that about me?
Shut up!
Xie Qilin betrayed me today.
I’m afraid he will also
betray you one day.
Take the money
as my thank-you gift
for letting me know who he is.
Xie Qilin will betray you,
but money won’t.
Keep the money.
In case you will need it.
I wish you a happy life forever.
Rong Xia, Count Cheng’an,
First Gentleman in Daye
Who is this guy?
Why does he look so familiar?
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free live♪
This face is a masterwork in Daye.
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
Young Master, cover your face.
I heard that she judges people
by appearance.
You will be doomed
if she has a crush on you.
Ridiculous.
It’s not like I had never seen a man.
Neither gentle nor virtuous.
She is not like a woman.
Du Jiu.
Since ancient times,
the etiquette never says
that women have to be
gentle and virtuous.
Baroness Ban came here alone
but got the upper hand.
That’s very interesting.
Interesting?
Young Master, why is that interesting?
This woman is fierce and doughty.
It’s not interesting at all.
This Baroness Ban
is not an ordinary girl.
It’s all your fault!
Ban’s Mansion
Well...
And you!
Ban’s Mansion
-Me? -What did I say?
-Me?
-What did I say?
I told you the Xie family
was not strong and reliable enough.
You had to say it was.
You must be happy now!
Hua, where have you been?
I went to see Xie Qilin.
Ban Heng, Second Son of the Bans
He... Is he still alive?
First Gourmet in Daye
Father, Mother.
Have you heard
that some people
can dream about the future?
Ban Huai, Marquis Jingting,
First Hedonist in Daye
Yin, Ban Hua’s Mother
We...
We don’t understand what you mean.
For example,
Xie Qilin broke off the engagement
and fled with someone.
I seem to have dreamed about
all of these things.
Dear, she lost her mind.
She must have been shocked.
What’s wrong with Hua?
Hua, it’s like this.
Hua.
Isn’t it amazing?
Yeah. Yeah.
Is it? Is it?
Yeah. It is.
Hua, listen.
It’s like this.
For me,
the marriage is important.
But your health and happiness
are the top priorities.
Yeah.
Right?
Exactly.
He just broke off the engagement.
Don’t take it personally.
Yeah.
Mother is right.
Hua, there are men everywhere.
Look,
this is the album of
beautiful men I just got.
Just tell me the one you like.
I’ll tie him up
and get him for you if I need to.
Hua, look at Count Cheng’an.
He is way better than Xie Qilin.
And his parents are gone.
If you marry him,
you can live a comfortable life without
in-laws meddling in your affairs.
You can’t understand it.
Madam and Master
are still worried
that you are upset about it.
A little Xie Qilin can’t hurt me.
I would be sad if I married him.
Rocky, Ban Hua’s Handmaid
-Yeah. -Rocky.
Get someone to dress me up.
Softy, Ban Hua’s Handmaid
Baroness, are you gonna go out?
I’ll go to Anle’s chrysanthemum
appreciation banquet tonight.
But I think those ladies
are busy gossiping behind your back
about what happened today.
I think,
why don’t you pass
the chrysanthemum banquet?
I’m going.
Why would I pass it?
I’ll go there beautifully.
I want them to know
that even he broke it off with me,
I’m still the most beautiful one.
Rocky.
The floral decals.
Baroness.
These are the most popular
floral decals.
Pick one.
I want peony.
Peony?
But recently, those ladies think
peach blossom and peony
are cheesy.
They think it’s cheesy
because they can’t hold it.
But I am
a tacky person.
For a woman,
it’s not that the more gold
and silver, the better.
Her stuff must be exquisite.
Look at those stuff
I wear for fun.
They have never seen them.
And they said I was showing off.
I don’t even have enough time
to take care of my face.
Why would I show off to them?
What are you waiting for?
Dress me up.
Dress up!
Rong’an Mansion
Baroness Ban has arrived!
Hurry up. Get ready.
Don’t miss anything
on her.
Hurry up.
Send this to the owner of Auspicious
Clothing Store to draw a design.
It will sell well.
Have you heard that Baroness Ban
was dumped again?
Baroness Ban might not
show up this time.
She must be crying at home.
How would she have nerve to come here?
Long time no see.
You haven’t changed at all.
Most of you are phony,
and few of you are sincere.
You still got the nerve to come?
I’ve got nothing to hide.
Why not coming?
However,
Xie family raised
a lascivious son
who eloped with someone.
-You...!
-Why should Ban family apologize for it?
Xie Wanyu, Youngest Daughter of the Xies
If not for your extravagance,
First Female Cook in Daye
how could my brother be scared away?
Scared away by me?
He can go anywhere he wants.
But he ran to the brothel to meet girls!
Wanyu.
No matter what,
Xie family
are all cowards.
You...!
Baroness, please calm down.
If Xie Qilin didn’t elope with someone,
Shi Feixian, Granddaughter of Prime Minister
Wanyu would become your sister-in-law.
Most Talented Lady in Daye
In the end, you are still a family.
She doesn’t deserve to be my family.
Feixian, never mind.
We are here to recite poems
and admire flowers.
Let’s ignore those
irrelevant people.
Who is the irrelevant person?
Anle!
Hua, you didn’t let me down.
I knew you would come.
Of course.
It’s your invitation.
I have to come even the sky is falling.
What were you arguing about?
She is too rude.
I’m sure no one dares to marry her.
How do you know
that no one will marry me?
Who will marry you?
The most talented man, Count Cheng’an.
When did this happen?
How could I not know it?
Count Cheng’an is
the most talented man in Daye.
He was selected by the Emperor
and entered the Palace since childhood
to study with the Crown Prince.
He is His Majesty’s apple of the eye.
Your Grace, you can’t believe
that Count Cheng’an
will fall in love with you, right?
Everyone, you don’t know
that I happened to meet Count Cheng’an
a few days ago.
We had a great conversation.
He
spoke with fervor and assurance.
Based on how he behaved,
I’m sure he admires me.
Couldn’t he be Count Cheng’an?
I don’t know we’ve met before.
He is really Count Cheng’an.
This is embarrassing now.
Baroness Ban is really not
an ordinary woman.
You don’t care about
that your engagement is broken off.
Now you can even make up
a new marriage out of nothing.
You give yourself too much credit.
Count Cheng’an is mine.
This is going to be interesting.
Count Cheng’an is so handsome.
It’s embarrassing.
I can’t lose to those snobs.
Looks like
I have to use my final move.
Rong Xia.
You claim to be a good example
for all the scholars.
Don’t let me down.
Your Grace, how can you
make up our stories?
Don’t be so stingy.
Could it be
that you have a crush on me?
It’s your honor if I have crush on you.
Well...
Is it proper?
Count Cheng’an, think about it.
We
gazed at each other affectionately.
It’s beyond words.
I can’t remember at all.
Perhaps you misunderstood me.
The crab feast is ready.
Please take a rest
and move to the banquet hall.
Now her face is totally lost.
It’s too embarrassing to eat crab.
I didn’t invite you.
Why did you come to my mansion?
Greetings to Princess Anle.
His Majesty asked me
to bring the finest
gold chrysanthemum to you.
Thank you.
Why don’t you
stay to taste the crab with us?
Thank you for your hospitality.
I have something important to do.
Maybe next time.
I will ask someone to
send the flowers to the backyard.
I’m so pissed off.
No. If I leave like this,
those sluts must be happy as hell.
Why is he again?
It’s such a small world.
Since we met,
now I can vent my anger.
Young Master, let’s go.
Don’t be afraid.
Please make way!
What do you want?
You just embarrassed me in the garden.
Now you block my way.
Did I somehow offend you?
I won’t do it again, is that okay?
Glib.
Why do you like to curse people so much?
Shut up!
Well-educated and knowledgeable.
And a role model for all the scholars?
What’s wrong with you?
You just saw a weak woman
being bullied
and you didn’t offer your help.
I even begged you
and you didn’t help me out.
Do you know
saving a life is better than
building a seven-level pageant?
It’s pagoda.
Your Grace.
Today I showed up without notice
and caused inconvenience for you.
I’m sorry about that.
It’s too late.
Actually, I did sense
your trouble today.
It’s just
that I’ve been reading books of sages
since childhood.
I’m not good at lying.
Please forgive me.
Such a dull goose.
Are you really the top talent
in the capital?
It’s just a bubble name.
It’s not as real as your reputation.
What’s my reputation?
A graceful lady.
Bold
and unconstrained.
Step aside! Waste my time
for eating crabs.
Scholars are all jackasses.
Ban Hua, Baroness Ban.
Moonlight through the Cloud
Spirit tablet
Father, Mother.
Brother.
Although I was young
and escaped from death,
I will never forget
to avenge your death.
What’s happening?
Who are you?
Step aside!
How dare you?
What do you want?
Mother!
Father, Mother.
Please trust me.
The truth won’t stay silent.
Getting close to the Ban family
is the first step in my plan.
I will find out what happened back then,
punish the vicious sycophants
and get justice for our Rong family.
Spirit tablet
Young Master, what’s next?
Go with the trend.
He dared to hurt Baroness Ban!
Let’s smash Xie’s Mansion!
Yeah!
-Give Xie Qilin to us!
-Let’s smash Xie’s Mansion!
-Yeah, let’s go!
The people from the Ban family are here.
I’ll inform Master. Close the door!
Xie’s Mansion
Xie Qilin, I know you are inside!
Brothers.
Get the eggs ready.
Throw it!
Xie Qilin, get out!
Xie’s Mansion
-Get out!
Xie Qilin, get out!
Master! Master!
Did you find him?
No.
You didn’t?
-What to do?
-We will break in if you don’t come out!
Count Xie, Count Zhongping,
Meanest Man in Daye
Master, what are we waiting for?
Let’s go out and fight with them.
No! No.
Let’s hold out a little longer!
Bastard Xie!
Xie Qilin, get out!
-Bastard Xie!
-Get out!
Bastard Xie!
If you keep messing around,
I will beat you hard!
Come on!
Go out and fight them!
Brothers, let’s fight!
Xie’s Mansion
Brothers, let’s do it!
Baroness Ban has arrived!
She still got the nerve to come.
The fat crab in autumn
is the finest of the world.
It can be used to gag you.
You...!
Come on, Hua. Have mine.
Thank you.
Miss Xie, be careful.
Don’t crack your teeth.
Baroness Ban, you seem to
have lost some weight these days.
Take care of yourself.
Li Xiaoru, Noble Lady in Daye
Don’t hold back if anything bothers you.
Staying angry will hurt your health.
That’s weird. In such a feast,
why are there freeloaders gossiping?
This is Mr. Li’s daughter, Li Xiaoru.
We often hang out together.
How can you call her a freeloader?
Maybe it’s because
Miss Li’s clothes are too plain.
I enjoy crowds.
I can’t remember
those who are unremarkable.
Your Grace, you are from a noble family.
Why do you pick on Xiaoru?
Anle, you know what?
These crab-eating tools
are quite useful.
Count Cheng’an is thoughtful.
He sent me the silver tongs
some time ago.
The crab’s shell is thin and crisp.
It’s better to peel it by hand.
I don’t need the crab-eating tools.
If I remember it correctly,
these crabs
were also sent by Count Cheng’an.
She can swagger around
only because
her grandmother is Princess Royal.
Anle.
Grandma missed you a lot these days.
Why don’t you go back to visit her
with me in a few days?
Sure.
Childish.
Xie’s Mansion
I’ll punish Xie Qilin hard
if I find him!
-No!
I told you, he is not here!
-Xie Qilin is not here.
-You...!
Ban Huai.
How did I offend you?
Why do you do this to me? Ban Huai!
Old bastard.
I will let you go today.
We will settle this another day!
Did you hear that?
Heng.
Go! Hurry up!
-Ban Huai!
-You...!
You are robbers, bandits!
Loyal Family
I won’t let you go!
Father!
Mother!
By the grace of God,
His Majesty announces:
Marquis Jingting, Ban Huai,
broke the law
and committed disgraceful conduct.
It has been verified.
Today, the title of marquis is removed,
and the salary is withdrawn.
There is collective punishment
for his family.
Family property will be
handed over to the treasury.
Everyone in the Ban family
is demoted to common people.
Ban Hua, run!
Get her!
Hurry up!
Father!
Father! Mother!
I dreamed that our mansion
got searched and confiscated!
You all got arrested!
Confiscated?
Who got the nerve to do that
to our Ban family?
I mean, you said we were all arrested.
What about you?
I... I ran away.
Run...?
Good, you are indeed my sister.
You ran away alone without me.
That’s not the point.
The point is I dreamed
that Xie Qilin was blind.
Great, that’s my daughter.
You made the Xie family suffer
even in your dream.
Xie Qilin deserves it.
My good girl.
Hua.
You dreamed what you had been
thinking in the daytime.
Don’t be angry.
I will punch him every time I see him.
Hua, don’t worry.
The reality is usually
opposite to the dream.
Mother, my dream of
the broken engagement came true.
If he really becomes blind,
then we...
Don’t be afraid.
Except for His Majesty,
who else is able to hurt our family?
Exactly.
We still got your grandmother.
Even if His Majesty
doesn’t care about me,
he’ll still show some respect
to the Princess Royal.
Don’t be afraid.
Hua.
Why can’t they understand?
If you want to forget someone...
Am I thinking too much about it?
Then you have to find a new one.
Forget it.
-Hua!
-Baroness!
You haven’t had the cubilose!
There are still a lot of it!
Go ahead.
Long live Your Majesty!
Emperor Yunqing
You may rise.
In the meeting today, I want to...
Minister Xie.
What’s wrong with your forehead?
Your Majesty, death cannot
atone for my offense!
What offense?
I’m incompetent.
I failed to protect
the plaque of Royal Family you gave me!
It’s outrageous!
Who stole the plaque?
No one stole it!
It was smashed!
Really?
It was really smashed?
Who is so bold?
Your Majesty, please take a look.
I remember I didn’t smash the plaque.
Who did it?
Ban Huai and his son,
and a bunch of bandits!
Royal Family
Ban Huai, what happened?
Your Majesty.
His son broke off
the engagement with Hua.
He eloped with a brothel woman.
Hua was furious and ran away.
We were worried
that she would go to Xie’s Mansion
and make mistakes.
So I took someone to visit Count Xie.
But Count Xie stayed
behind closed doors.
Your Majesty, it was my fault.
If you want to blame anyone,
just blame Count Xie.
You...! Your Majesty!
All right.
Your Majesty.
Count Cheng’an, you always act fair.
What do you think about this?
Your Majesty.
If I remember it correctly,
it was the Xie family
who proposed the marriage,
and now the Xie family
unilaterally broke it off.
They not only broke their words,
but also hurt Baroness Ban’s reputation.
In the final analysis,
the Xie family is indeed unrighteous.
It’s understandable
that Marquis Jingting and his son
got furious about it.
Your Majesty, Count Cheng’an is right!
But... But he broke
the plaque you gave me in person!
All right.
I’ve got the answer.
You arranged someone
to keep watch on the Ban family,
and something odd happened.
His Majesty didn’t
punish the Ban family.
Instead, he sent
a carriage of playthings
to Marquis Jingting’s Mansion.
Looks like the Princess Royal
is behind this.
I didn’t expect His Majesty
Wang Qu, Brainman in the Rongs
to still have scruples
about the Princess Royal.
If it wasn’t for the Princess Royal
and her husband General Ban
assisting His Majesty all the way,
I’m afraid Daye
would have been taken away by others.
Young Master!
Young Master.
Go ahead. What did you find?
After my public
and private investigation,
I finally found one
old subordinate of the Ban family.
It turns out that the General Ban
was poisoned and stayed sick
in bed for years.
Did you find out how he was poisoned?
There are rumors but no evidence.
Young Master, do you think
His Majesty has anything to do with it?
If so,
I’m afraid Tiger Tally
can’t get away with
what happened back then.
Here is the imperial decree!
Xie Qilin, the son of Xie Chengyan,
is lascivious.
He broke the royal covenant
and committed an unforgivable sin.
With immediate effect,
he is dismissed as a senior licentiate.
He is not allowed to take the test.
Respect this.
Receive the decree.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Royal Family
If that dream comes true
and our family gets kicked out
of this house,
let along this mahogany bed,
agarwood chair,
and the shell window...
By that time,
I can’t even afford a piece of cloth.
I have to wear broken linen
with stitches.
If I meet
Xie Wanyu and Shi Feixian...
Sisters, go ahead!
Stop!
What... What are you doing?
What’s wrong, Baroness?
What happened?
Hua!
Our mansion can’t be confiscated.
Otherwise,
I might as well die.
Hua, don’t be upset.
There is a new tea house
in the east of the city.
Why don’t you go to taste the tea?
Yeah, you should go.
I don’t have the mood.
Hua.
Mother gave me the task.
She asked me to take you out to relax.
Otherwise she will deduct
my money this month.
Just go.
Only four hours.
Two hours.
Go to relax yourself, Baroness.
All right.
You are the best.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Where are Father and Mother?
Father...
Listen,
it matters your sister’s marriage.
Count Cheng’an, Rong Xia
Don’t make any mistakes.
If you screw it up,
Count Cheng’an, Rong Xia
I’ll punish you hard!
They are really
concerned about your dream.
They lost their appetite.
Now they are discussing about it.
Really?
They should study it.
Let’s go.
Go, go, go.
Hua, you should be happy
being out there.
Shut up.
Look at this clear sky.
The cloudless blue sky
with white clouds.
I’m going back if you keep nagging.
I’ll shut up.
Rong’s Mansion
Rong’s Mansion?
We are not going to the tea house.
How dare you lie to me?
No, no, no.
Hua.
A few days ago, Count Cheng’an
pleaded for me in court.
Father asked me to
send gifts to thank him.
If you don’t believe me, take a look.
I have the presents ready.
Just for a while, we will leave
after we give him the gifts.
Do it by yourself.
Hua, you dare not go there.
Do you have a crush on Count Cheng’an?
What are you talking about?
Then... You are afraid to be shy
when you see him.
You...!
I...!
Hold on! You have a crush
on him if you don’t go!
You have to mess with me, right?
I’ll go.
Please.
Please wait a moment.
I’ll go to inform Young Master.
Ban Heng.
Pay attention to your appearance.
Why did Your Grace
come to my mansion today?
This man is annoying,
but he is indeed good-looking.
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪