Sub by kisscambodia
♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 44
What happened?
Aunt!
She had fainted
when I arrived.
The suspect is gone.
How’s my mother?
She’s poisoned
with something unknown yet.
Thankfully,
it hasn’t damaged her heart vessels
and only put her into a coma.
We must know what it is
in order to remove it.
Who could break in
and poison her?
Who did this?
I saw a woman.
She was fast.
Most people couldn’t have done that.
The poison
must’ve been planted in the candle.
Luckily, Aunt found out
and cut it.
It’s the same method
Pathetic Clam used
to kill Mu Xiaoqiao.
Candle.
That snake keeper said
the Big Medicine Valley
invented such a poisoning method.
This needle
is also the same as
what Pathetic Clam used
back at the Small Medicine Valley.
Wasn’t she
killed by Phoenix?
Obviously,
she’s still alive.
Plus Phoenix did say
he didn’t see her face clearly
when he killed her.
Why would she
Poison Madam Li?
She could fail
and get caught by us.
All for the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Nine Moves of the Snow-breaking Blade
To Zhou Fei
Fei.
This is Aunt’s letter to you.
Fei,
all the five tokens
are in Yitang’s favorite weiqi set.
The hidden compartment
has been emptied.
We can’t remove the poison
but only suppress it for now.
According to that snake keeper,
she only makes the poison
but not the antidote.
I don’t buy it.
Once we seize that habitual poisoner,
there must be a solution.
We had the gate closed
on our way here.
She might still be here.
Sheng, let’s split up.
You go to the front gate
while I check the other routes.
Sure.
Let’s go.
Take care of my mother.
Pass my order.
Form search teams.
Don’t act alone,
or they might be in danger.
Yes.
Don’t worry. I’m here to help.
I was just told to search the area...
Hold on.
That can’t be right.
Let’s go to the Hall of Elders.
Close the gate to seize suspects.
Be patient.
You guys check the front side.
You people go to the riverside.
Check carefully.
Leave no stone unturned.
-Yes.
-Lord,
we should’ve left earlier.
Now, they’re on alert.
We can’t leave.
Don’t worry.
Wait until
they catch that useless prince.
That’ll be our best chance to escape.
The rest of you
go to the front gate with me.
Yes!
Wait. I still feel worried.
Take some men with you
and check that route again.
The one taken by the enemies last time?
Outsiders couldn’t have found it.
Check again, just in case.
-Yes.
-Let’s go.
Come.
This is it. Guard the exit.
Yes!
I meant to leave in disguise
but they left me no choice.
They had it coming.
Insightful and Open-minded
How could this happen?
What to do?
Sheng,
is Madam really...
Yang Jin, tell them everything
about what happened
in the Hall of Elders.
I was practicing skills with others
before hearing
the Hall of Elders was robbed
and came over.
After searching,
that Mountain-River Jade
was lost.
Who’s the guard there today?
-It’s... It’s...
-Is it you?
It’s me.
How dare you stop the Third Prince!
This is an act of treason!
We’re following Madam’s order.
The gate is locked for tonight.
No one shall leave.
Young man,
His Highness
is Madam Li’s guest.
There must be a misunderstanding
for you to hold us up.
Here’s the thing, Mr. Bai,
a thief broke in
and stole Madam’s birthday gift
from His Highness,
hence the lockdown
to capture that person.
I’m the last person you should halt.
Would I take back
what I had given to others?
I apologize, Your Highness.
Before the truth comes out,
no one is allowed to leave.
Alright.
Since you’re on a search mission,
search us first.
If we don’t have
what you’re looking for,
please
report to Madam Li and Miss Zhou
to let us leave.
I’m sorry.
Go!
Yes!
It’s alright.
Let them do their job.
We have nothing to hide.
This is it!
Found it!
Mountain-River Jade!
Take them to the Hall of Elders.
-Yes.
Smells like knockout drops.
Knockout drops?
From whom?
Knockout drops.
What happened before you passed out?
I think
I saw a girl.
She was a new face
and couldn’t be our own member.
Hey, you.
Mr. Xie.
What happened here?
Where’s Zhou Fei?
Madam...
Madam was poisoned.
Miss Zhou is looking for the poisoner.
Poisoned?
Yes, by the Demons.
Elder Zhang has had all members
search for those bad people.
Oh, no!
Zichen!
The gate is closed.
This is the only exit.
Pathetic Clam.
Seize them all!
They colluded with Pathetic Clam
and poisoned Madam
Please calm down.
There must be a mistake.
We can explain
to Madam Li.
You evil thieves!
No wonder you were in a rush to leave.
That explains it.
Seize them!
Go!
Hold on.
Xie Yun.
Mr. Xie,
what are you doing?
Elder Zhang,
I can vouch for him with my life.
The Third Prince knows nothing about it.
Mr. Xie, you don’t know.
I’ve just found out
that he took Pathetic Clam here
who poisoned Madam.
You... Move!
Elder Zhang, think about it.
They were never on bad terms.
Why would a prince
hurt her?
The rich and powerful
are a bunch of evil bastards.
Who knows what they’re up to?
Speak!
Did your father
give you the order?
I’m here to propose marriage.
I swear I mean no harm.
That’s your excuse
to bring Pathetic Clam in
to poison Madam.
You’re in cahoots. Stop denying it!
-No way.
-I...
There’s a long-running feud
between the Chens and the Demons.
That woman must’ve
set the Third Prince up.
Xie Yun,
step aside,
or you’re leaving me no choice
but to kill you, too!
Us colluding with Demons
is utter nonsense!
That aside,
why are you blaming Xie Yun, too?
Zichen,
enough. Just go.
Now!
Capture them!
Master Zhang.
Sheng.
Mr. Xie meant well.
Drop your spear.
Sheng,
he did help us out once,
but Madam was poisoned
by his friend.
How could you trust him?
Master Zhang,
don’t jump to conclusions.
Calm down.
Your Highness,
where are the two doctors?
They left to wait for us outside.
Your Highness, in this case,
that doctor who showed up uninvited
must be Pathetic Clam.
She disguised herself
and sneaked in
in the name of
treating the Third Prince.
She stole the tokens,
and poisoned Aunt,
pinning everything
on the Third Prince
to play us off against each other
in favor of her.
If her plot worked
that the court and our Fortress
were against each other,
the masses would suffer.
Your Highness,
you may leave.
I’m really sorry.
And I’ll make it up to you.
Pathetic Clam is well-prepared
and must’ve been long gone.
Fei is out looking for her.
We’re going to help her
catch that woman.
She’s there alone?
Yes. I’m not sure where she is now
and I’m worried.
Mr. Xie!
My lady, let’s take a break.
We’ve been on the move almost all night.
No one is behind us.
We’ve gotten rid of
those of the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight.
With the tokens on me,
the quicker we get back, the better.
Once we get out of this area,
reinforcements will come.
Do you think I’m afraid of the hunters?
It’s the so-called reinforcements.
We can’t afford to lose the tokens.
Once we’re out of the woods,
contact our agents immediately
and ask them to report to Lord.
Yes.
Rest here for a while.
I’ll go get water.
Miss Zhou,
without me,
your mother will die.
Let me go
in exchange for the antidote
to Worry-burying.
So that’s what she’s with.
Aren’t you said
to only make the poison
but not the antidote?
That said,
still...
Cut to the chase.
Give me the antidote
if you want to live.
Wait.
There’s a cure.
Tell me about it.
I’ll make my own judgment.
The Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Find the treasure.
That’ll cure your mother.
That again!
Don’t you have anything new?
I’m telling you the truth.
Years of working with poison
is killing me slowly.
That treasure is my only cure.
That’s why I need the tokens.
Where are they?
Drop your blade
and I’ll give them to you.
Here they are.
Animal characters made by CG
Fei.
Fei!
It’s my fault.
I failed to protect Madam
and got her poisoned.
Don’t be too hard on yourself, Dan.
Nobody could
anticipate that.
No.
I should have.
I knew they had attempted
to kill Lord Gantang,
and they would
take further action here.
Uncle was under attack?
What happened?
Yesterday,
Yu Wenzhi’s spy was caught outside
who failed to assassinate Lord Gantang
and was there
searching for him.
Lord asked us to keep it from you
and look for him secretly
to contain panic.
In this case,
the theft and the assassination
must be related.
They can’t be a coincidence.
They must’ve plotted all that long ago.
I thought so.
I interrogated that spy, too.
But he claimed that
he wasn’t aware of the theft.
Didn’t Madam and Lord Gantang
have a pact?
He’s survived
and so will Madam.
She certainly will.
You good-for-nothing!
I’m sorry. Please calm down.
Don’t be mad.
The old and new dynasties
are supposed to be mortal enemies.
How come Xiao Chuan
is unaffected?
That walking dead
keeps spoiling my plan.
Xiao Chuan!
Send a message to Shen Tianshu
that I’ll agree to his condition
if he gets rid of Xiao Chuan for me.
Lord Shen has arrived at Hanshui Town.
I heard
Lord Hu had obtained
all five tokens.
He’s there to pick her up.
I knew Tianying would make it.
Xiao Chuan!
Madam is still in a coma.
Her condition is critical.
I’m entrusting the Fortress to you.
No need to tell us that.
It’s our job.
Where’s Fei?
She’s left to capture Pathetic Clam.
I’m going to join her.
Sure.
I’ll go with you.
Here are a few things
that require your attention.
Pathetic Clam managed to escape
but she might not have gone far.
It’s still our territory outside.
But the Demons might’ve
arranged people to get her out.
Those bastards!
They should know
we aren’t afraid of them!
Yes. We aren’t.
We’ll fight them to the end!
Elder Zhang,
what if Shen Tianshu comes in person?
Yang Jin and I
will leave with our crack troops
to join Fei to capture Pathetic Clam.
It’s not safe inside or outside.
I have great respect for you.
Please guard the Fortress with others
to prevent another attack.
Thank you.
No need.
That’s what we should do.
Consider it done.
That’s our duty.
Chuchu.
Take care of my aunt.
I will.
Where are Xie Yun and Yan?
Mr. Xie has left to find Fei.
There’s still no news from him.
I’m worried.
As for Yan, wasn’t she out shopping?
Mr. Xie said
she’d be back today.
I hope she’ll be fine.
That girl.
How’s she?
Her pulse is as weak as yesterday.
Right now, it’s only a coma,
but it might get worse tomorrow.
Back then
when Old Master was poisoned
by Pathetic Clam,
there was nothing
our physicians could do.
Don’t give up hope yet.
The tougher the situation is,
the more united we should be.
All we can do is to guard the fort
to not hold Zhou Fei and Li Sheng back.
Yes!
Sub by Dramacool.ae
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪I dare not ask if you’re doing well♪
♪The first time I’ve felt terrified♪
♪Youth is like a sweet dream♪
♪The hope in heart♪
Hi, Sleeping Beauty.
♪Never fades♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
Pathetic Clam...
That cunning woman
has managed to escape again.
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
Are... are you alright?
Don’t worry.
Nothing can hurt me
because of the Bone-chilling.
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
Look,
I’ve sucked out some of the poison,
but the rest of it
will make you relapse into a coma.
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
Pathetic Clam...
She said...
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
The Color of Ocean and Heaven
can cure my mother.
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
Is there a cure in it?
That I’ve never heard of.
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
Whether it’s true or not,
we must get the tokens back.
Fei,
you haven’t rested for two days.
Take a nap first.
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
Don’t worry.
Li Sheng and the disciples are out, too.
The Route Gang
will also help us with the search.
Once they find something,
we can set out.
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
Hanshui Town
-Stop!
-Stop there!
Go! Move!
Behave yourself!
It must be tough
following me all the way here.
I’ll spare you
so that you can
report back to your leader
to leave me alone.
Or the Route Gang will soon be gone.
Yes. Yes.
Piss off!
Lord.
The Route Gang never dared to offend us.
This time...
That was for the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight.
Urge Gu Tianxian
to come quickly with his force.
Yes.
Mr. Li.
You again!
What are you still doing here?
Mr. Bai,
have you found those female doctors?
Mr. Li,
it was my negligence
that led to
Madam being poisoned.
My death isn’t enough
to cover the damage.
But the Third Prince asked me
to help you
to redeem myself.
Whatever you need me to do,
I won’t say no to it.
How can I trust you?
I was the head of the White Bat
of the Route Gang.
Its business covers the entire state.
I still have influence
in the Gang.
What can you
do for me?
The Route Gang
isn’t known for its force,
but it excels at
gathering information.
News just came in
that Shen Tianshu of Demons Manor
is heading this way.
How many people are there with him?
Only enough to form a squad,
but Gu Tianxian
and the main force is right behind.
It seems that
they’re meeting in Hanshui Town.
Luckily, Yang Jin
has left to contact our secret service.
Mr. Bai,
please come with me.
I’m going to need your help.
Mr. Li,
I’m asked
to do my best to help you.
Whatever you need,
just let me know.
Search this place!
Find that girl of the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight
even if you have to
tear this town apart.
Yes!
East Point
-This way.
-Let’s go.
-Follow me.
-Yes.
Take that way.
Over there.
That girl of the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight?
Do they mean Fei?
Is she also here?
Have you checked that way?
-Come here.
-Yes.
Sir.
Come here.
Found anything in the front?
The Demons are all over the place.
You aren’t a local, are you?
No.
Listen,
here isn’t safe lately.
Don’t wander about at night.
Search it!
Come in.
Where are we?
Those Demons
show up out of the blue.
Demons?
They’re our Fortress’s mortal enemies.
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Just now, you were out there alone,
looking around.
What if they saw you
and caught you?
Don’t worry.
They wouldn’t dare.
Those notorious villains
would catch everyone in sight
regardless of who they are.
Are you afraid of them?
Our people can deal with them.
As experienced as they seem,
my brother and cousin
killed three of them
soon after they left home.
Now, only four Demons are left.
Why are you hiding here?
I...
I’m outnumbered.
We can hide here for now.
I’ll take you
to our secret meeting point later.
We’ll be safe there.
It was dangerous!
The minute the map popped open,
it burned my hands.
Who else was there?
Poisoner Ying Hecong,
that bonehead of the Cloud Ravine
and a girl of the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight.
She cared a lot
about that map.
Liu Youliang risked his own life
to help them escape.
Is she that girl
Tong Tianyang said?
How come
they sent you here alone?
Don’t be scared.
It’s not the same.
What if I ran into Shen Tianshu?
You don’t know how scary he is, do you?
Alright.
Tell me about it.
How is he scary?
It’s said that man
is invincible.
He’s a highly skilled killing machine
and an evil
ringleader.
Sir,
if you see him,
run as fast as you can.
I’m starving.
Try it.
It’s the specialty here.
Just take it.
You seem old.
Why are you out alone?
Aren’t your family worried?
I have none.
They all died
because of the war years back.
Oh.
I’m sorry.
Are you sad all these years?
There are other ways
to gain happiness
other than being with family.
Isn’t it also fun to gain power?
They’re two different things.
To gain power,
you have to fight for what you want.
Even if you win the whole world,
it comes at a price.
That’s different
from being loved and cared for.
Take my cousin
and cousin-in-law as an example.
Before she said
what she wanted,
my cousin-in-law had found it for her.
When he was sick,
my cousin would save him with her life.
Only you naive kids
would believe that.
That’s not true.
Sir,
you would, too, if you were there.
I envy them.
Your cousin-in-law probably wouldn’t.
Are you a veteran?
How so?
Things you said about power
gave you away.
Why are you here?
I used to
serve in the Anping Army.
I’m here
to visit an old comrade.
Anping Army?
No way!
That’s my uncle’s...
♪Enlisted at 15♪
♪Only to return at 80♪
♪Asked a townsman on the way back♪
♪Who’s left back home♪
What’s that song?
It’s beautiful.
Song of Anping.
How come it sounds familiar?
It’s been over 20 years.
Things in the army
have become vague
except for this song.
I still remember it.
Oh, no!
The Demons are nearby.
What if they heard the song
and came in this direction?
They wouldn’t.
Let’s go.
Come.
Alright.
I’ll drop you
at our meeting point first.
It’s safer there.
Stop.
Where are you going this late?
Sirs,
my grandfather and I
are going to the morning market.
Are you going there, too?
Yes.
What a coincidence!
We’re leaving.
What’s going on?
How do you feel?
Better now?
Much better.
The Route Gang said
they had found traces of Pathetic Clam.
She seems to be heading to Hanshui Town.
Fei,
you must be the only one
who can still be so energetic
after being poisoned by Pathetic Clam.
I’m afraid
there’s also bad news.
Shen Tianshu is there already.
He’s fast.
Look,
we must get rid of her
before Shen Tianshu finds her.
Or it’ll be more difficult
once they get together.
Fei,
it’s too risky
to act alone.
Why don’t we
go back to the Fortress
to join the others first?
They left after us.
It’d be too late when they arrived.
Let’s go
and try to stop her halfway.
Even if we failed,
that’d still buy us time
to wait for backups.
Alright. You have a point.
I know you’re worried about me.
That woman is nothing
without her tricks and poison.
As long as I stay alert
and protect myself from them,
there’s a chance to win.
Her poison won’t be a problem.
You have me.
I’m your anti-poison armor.
You’re the sharp blade
while I’m the unbreakable shield.
Use her poison
against her
to not waste
the deadliest Bone-chilling she gave me.
Fine. Next time, when we see her,
we’ll waste no time
and take care of her first.
Deal.
Xie Yun,
hypothetically,
if one day,
I died,
what would you do?
That’d be my bliss.
I’d
have fun in every possible way
together with your share.
Live my life to the fullest
to not waste any second.
Bastard!
Fei,
you know
I’m a coward
struggling to live in chaos.
But after being through
so much with you,
I’ve got used to
putting my life on the line
and I’ve grown more guts.
Really?
Let me see.
Show me.
Wait... wait until they grow even more.
Intelligent and Ingenious
Senior Master Li.
Goodness!
Why are you still here?
You know what,
I almost got caught before the gate
and managed to pull through.
By the way, I got an elder out, too.
Look.
What’s wrong?
My mouth is dry after all the hiding.
We’re safe here.
We can rest at Senior Master Li’s store.
He once
fought against Shen Tianshu.
Really?
Of course.
Hey,
didn’t you say
you’re here to visit an old comrade?
Who is he?
Liu Youliang.
You...
You’re Timber Wolf, Shen Tianshu!
Young lady,
I wish
you didn’t recognize me.
Go, Yan!
Hello, dear.
Where are you going?
Wood Workshop
I poisoned Li Jinrong
to get the tokens out.
Her people
will soon find us.
We’d better leave now.
Not yet.
Gu Tianxian is on the way.
I need some answers
before we go.
Mr. Li, Mr. Yang,
we tried to follow him
but he’s too skilled.
I even lost a man
but still couldn’t get close to him.
Thank you.
Is something else bothering you?
I’m afraid
Yu Wenzhi’s force might also...
Yu Wenzhi?
Yes.
Him again.
One of my contacts
is Yu Wenzhi’s groom.
He told me a while ago
that Pathetic Clam
was incited by Yu Wenzhi.
He even
came to Shen Tianshu for it.
Unexpectedly,
Shen Tianshu used
Pathetic Clam’s life as leverage
and they almost fell out.
In that sense,
Pathetic Clam and Yu Wenzhi
worked together to steal the tokens
behind Shen Tianshu’s back.
Correct. All I know
is that Shen Tianshu
was so mad at Yu Wenzhi
that he almost refused
to come to save Pathetic Clam.
Mr. Li,
there’s nothing new
from my contact.
My concern is
if Yu Wenzhi’s force joins them,
our people
won’t be their match.
I can’t wait for a bigger mess.
Once he’s here,
he won’t let Shen Tianshu
take the tokens so easily
after all that he’s done.
When it’s dog-eat-dog between them,
we can take advantage of it.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪