[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 21]
Qin Lie.
I can't hold out much longer.
I'm destined to die here.
Before I die,
can I pretend that you are Gong Mu Lie?
I am sorry.
Song Ting Yu.
Song Ting Yu, stay awake!
You are fond of Qin Lie, aren't you?
Do you really think that
he will remember you forever
if you die in his arms?
He won't remember you.
He saved you out of ethics.
He has no feelings for you.
He will forget about what happened today
in a blink of an eye.
You said that you can't
hold out any longer.
It's exactly what I am hoping for.
You are never a threat to me
but it's good to have one less person
to jump at the chance.
If you die here,
be it Qin Lie or Gong Mu Lie,
both of them are mine.
You can dream on.
Let's go.
[Pu Ci Residence]
Shao Yang.
Why do you send the medicine by yourself?
We are short-handed. I am here to help.
Okay.
Du Shao Yang.
Come out.
Yes.
You are meritorious in the battle
to kill Di Shi Jiu.
We are facing great difficulties
yet you didn't back off.
You patrol around without taking a rest.
Furthermore, you are determined.
I have the heart to promote you.
Thank you.
I went to see Mo Hai.
He's almost done making
the Terminator Profound Bombs.
That means
we will initiate a war against
the Dark Nether Race soon.
I plead to fight for the war.
Shao Yang.
The moment the war starts,
we will be fighting to death.
Although we have
Terminator Profound Bombs,
the person who was taken by
the Dark Nether Race
still worries me.
I can tell that
you are an ambitious person.
You are on par with Qin Lie.
If we lose in the war,
I want you to run away alive
at all cost.
So that one day you may reestablish
the Bloody Spear Guard.
Got it.
I will live up to your trust.
[Tea]
We do nothing but waiting idly
in the village.
We wait from day time to night time,
from night time to dawn.
Why hasn't the war started yet?
I am bored.
I plan to show you around
but there is nothing interesting to see.
It is just like a dead town.
Do you know of
any interesting places?
What?
Demon aura?
That's right.
Since Jing Xuan
was put in charge of the Nether War
over a hundred years ago,
I've never been to the Nether Battlefield.
I almost forgot
how it feels to be surrounded
by demon aura.
Why don't we check it out?
I knew that you would like it.
Let's go.
Time to eat.
Stand there.
There are only commoners
who are in distress.
You should check on the guardians.
What are you doing here?
Please hear me out.
We are from the Palace of Hell.
We are ordered by
the Master of the Palace of Hell
to check if the residents in the building
are doing well.
Everyone in there are doing well.
There is nothing to check.
People inside the building
were injured by the demon aura.
Without master's order,
no one is allowed to enter.
We are working in the same field.
Please give me some leeway.
I just want to take a look.
Go away.
Leave now.
Fine.
I will leave now.
It's time to eat. Why are you still here?
I am not hungry. I don't want to eat.
That is impossible.
[Pu Ci Residence]
Something is unusual in the passageway.
Send out the warning!
Get ready!
Don't attack us.
I am Qin Lie of Lin Borough.
Quick, come and rescue Saintess Song.
It's Saintess Song.
Hurry up, help him out.
Here.
Finally we are back to Chilan Continent.
Qin Lie, what is wrong with you?
Qin Lie.
You are almost done with Natal Opening
Realm and will ascend to a new realm soon.
If you successfully ascend to
a new realm, you will...
You will reach the pinnacle
of the Manifestation Realm.
Go away now! The Heavenly Thunder
is coming.
It's as strong as the
Thunder of the Ninth Heaven
that killed the Soul Reaping Beasts,
if not more.
She is poisoned.
Even after taking the medicine,
her condition remains the same.
You were an apprentice at Water Moon Sect.
You are the best medicine practitioner
in the Purple Mist Sea.
Please save her.
Since medicine is not effective on her,
do you have any other idea?
She is poisoned by the demon aura.
We just have to find someone
proficient in the Dark Nether Race's arts
to absorb the demon aura out of her body.
We have been fighting against
the Nether Race for three centuries.
The Nether Race fights
bravely but ruthlessly.
They would rather die than yielding.
Once they are captured,
they would kill themselves.
Why would they cure the Saintess,
who is a human.
Doctor.
For how long more she can live?
We shall see if she can survive the night.
I'll inform the Profound Heaven Alliance
at once.
Please take care of her.
Don't go.
Gong Mu Lie, I don't want you to go there.
Mother of Land will kill you.
Mother of Land?
Song Ting Yu, what are you trying to say?
We grew up together.
We are so close with each other.
Why are you going to see her?
I am reluctant to accept it, Gong Mu Lie.
Song Ting Yu.
I am Qin Lie.
Qin Lie?
Have you not awakened?
Don't go against Song Yu.
Please don't do it.
It is as if Song Ting Yu
has changed into another person.
She mentioned the Mother of Land.
Could it be the same person
in the prophecy?
Mother of Land and the son
of the God of War.
Could Gong Mu Lie
be the son of the God of War?
Are you...
It is impossible.
If she wants to pretend
I'm Gong Mu Lie, fine.
Then I'll pretend
she's infatuated with Gong Mu Lie.
However, she said that
she grew up with me.
That is sheer ridiculous.
Perhaps just like me,
she is related to your background.
However, what did she mean
by "awakened"?
Yu Shi.
Take good care of her.
I will think of another way.
Sure.
Blood Progenitor, Xue Li.
What do you want?
Xue Li.
Do you know of any method
to save Saintess Song from the demon aura?
Her body is attacked by the demon aura.
It depends on her own making
if she can survive the night.
It is impossible that there is
no way at all to save her.
You should take care of
your own business first.
Think about it.
So many people are after you.
Qin Lie, after you have got the insight
of the last Spiritual Lines Pillar,
my physique is back.
Therefore,
I have to go.
Where are you going?
That is rubbish.
Of course I am going to
Heavenly Calamity Continent
to look for my family.
By the way,
don't forget to
keep Spiritual Lines Pillars properly.
It will be useful to you.
It doesn't belong to the
Artefact Forging Sect.
It belongs to the Heavenly Armament Sect
of Heavenly Calamity Continent.
But...
They are huge. How do I keep them?
You have got an insight of...
all 12 Spiritual Lines Pillars.
They are just like your children now.
You can keep them as you wish.
Take care, lad.
See you again,
Xue Li.
The demon aura is fatal to her.
Why do I feel so comfortable
after absorbing the demon aura?
Who am I?
Surprisingly, she recovered
without any cure.
She is Saintess Song after all.
She doesn't hold the title for no reason.
She has her own ways.
It is such a miracle.
Just treat it as a miracle.
When will
my miracle be here?
What is your miracle?
My grandpa.
The eight stone pillars
left behind by my grandpa.
Why are they so powerful?
They can even trigger Heavenly Thunder.
They are so similar to
the 12 Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Is everything
left behind by my grandpa to me?
The Blood Progenitor, Xue Li once said,
The Spiritual Lines Pillars belong to
the Heavenly Armament Sect.
I remember that my master too once said,
The Heavenly Armament Sect
are the true master artificers.
Was your grandpa part of the
Heavenly Armament Sect?
The Nether Tribe claimed that
they are indebted to my grandpa.
However, why did my grandpa help them out?
Don't forget about the Master of Frost.
He also received help from
your grandpa, Qin Shan.
So my grandpa is a god?
If your grandpa is a god,
doesn't that make you the son
of the God of War?
Qin Lie.
The myth
can only be solved by your grandpa.
However, we are clear that
we won't be able to find
a big shot like him.
We can only wait for him to come back.
I believe that he will
come home one day soon.
You can't remember anything?
You mentioned Gong Mu Lie
and Mother of Land.
You also said something about awakening
and you told me not to go against my dad.
Have you forgotten all of them?
When the demon aura attacked my body,
I felt something different.
I had a weird dream.
However,
I don't remember what I've said.
What did you see in your dream?
In the Mirror Realm,
there was a clear lake.
When Gong Mu Lie wasn't cultivating,
he would take a stroll around the lake.
At high tide in the morning,
Gong Mu Lie would be waiting for
the sunrise by the lakeside.
At low tide at night,
Gong Mu Lie would take a break
under the moonlight.
However,
with his back turned on me,
I couldn't see his face clearly.
He had been with a lady.
I think
that is part of the content
in The Tale of Gong Mu Lie.
Who is that lady?
Could you see her face?
Saintess Song is safe and sound.
It is indeed a blessing for
Chilan Continent.
Thank you for taking care of me,
Guardian Xie.
Once I am back to
the Profound Heaven Alliance,
I will request the Chief to reward you.
You don't have to do so, Saintess.
Thank you, Uncle Xie.
I appreciate your respect for me.
Armoury City is on its last stand.
Once we lose it,
the entire Chilan Continent
will be in danger.
I wish I could fly there to help out.
However, this place
is the exit of the nether passageway.
We have to stay back and guard this place.
Golden Fire Cloud Canvas?
This magical item...
They say there are less than
three of them in Chilan Continent.
Thank you for lending me
the magical item.
I will return it to you for sure
the next time we see each other.
Don't mention it.
Chilan Continent is my homeland.
I will never allow any foreign tribe
to take a share on it.
I swear on my life that
I will protect it.
I will chase Dark Nether Race
back to the underground.
After taking the medicine,
they look so much better.
We're running out of
Demon Cleansing Pills.
If they don't get better,
they will die soon.
Dear daughter!
Dear daughter, can you hear me?
What are you doing?
Both of you should be
going on a patrol now.
[Pu Ci Residence]
Why are you screaming?
I came here yesterday.
I heard my daughter's voice
coming from the building.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am really serious.
However, my daughter died a long time ago.
Since she is dead,
why are you fooling around? Go away.
My dear daughter, I really miss you.
-Why are you so cruel...
-Hold on.
How could you dump me?
My stomach is not feeling well.
Please take me to the outhouse.
-Fine, come with me.
-Sure.
It is over there.
My dear daughter!
Where are you?
Can you hear me?
I struggled a lot
when I was looking for you.
Hey.
Can I ask you a question?
Have you seen my daughter?
My daughter is dead.
Hey.
Why aren't you talking?
Master Xie!
I am dressing in a different attire
yet you still can recognise me.
It was an honour meeting you
at the Profound Heaven Alliance.
How could I forget?
What a sweet talker. I like you.
Get up.
Master Xie, why are you dressed like this?
What's the occasion?
Do you need my help?
There is no occasion.
I was bored, so I came out
for a walk.
What is your name?
My name is Du Shao Yang.
Du Shao Yang.
What a good name.
Not bad.
Where is that lad?
He has gone missing in a blink of an eye.
Si Qi!
Shao Yang!
It was so dangerous.
I have the same thought.
I am so scared.
Si Qi.
Where did you go?
I struggled a lot looking for you.
I went to see Chief Song.
Then, I heard that my dad was coming.
I planned to leave.
However, I want to see you
for the one last time.
I was waiting for you every night
at this place
but you never appeared.
You were here on that night.
Am I right?
I come here to see you
but when I see you,
I feel really reluctant to leave.
I struggled a lot looking for you.
In order to hide away from my dad,
I could only push my luck
at the warehouse.
I went to that warehouse.
Why didn't I see you?
I am sorry.
Sorry to have made you worried.
I can't blame you.
Ever since I met your dad,
I can totally understand your feelings.
Your dad is insane.
Si Qi.
If your dad found you,
what would he do to you?
He would turn me into
a heartless servant.
A heartless servant?
His escort...
How foolish.
I am surprised that you tried to run away.
Are you not willing to serve me?
Am I so scary?
I won't do it again.
Please pardon me.
Look at me.
Come here.
Master Xie.
Please pardon me.
What a handsome looking face.
You look good when you smile.
Here, give me a smile.
The smile doesn't look good.
Give me another smile.
Your smile is hideous. Try again.
Please pardon me, Master Xie.
Please pardon me.
You don't even know how to smile!
What can your brain do?
Please pardon me, Master Xie.
Please pardon me.
If you can't smile from the heart,
why do you need a heart?
His name is Mo He.
He was my dad's bodyguard.
He was vicious.
He was the cream of the Eight Extreme
Temple warriors.
How could he?
After he became a heartless man,
his spiritual power remained the same
but he did not care.
He is always at the commander's service.
If he were told to murder someone,
he would do it.
If he were told to commit suicide,
Is there no cure?
Only the commander can cure him.
Shao Yang.
I can't stay any longer.
I will put you in trouble.
Even if I die,
they will find my body.
It will eventually put you into trouble.
Si Qi.
I am sorry.
Lang Xie said that
he will promote me.
When I am dead,
you must destroy my body.
You must not let my dad find any body part
of me, including my finger.
I will pretend that I am falling asleep.
I will be in your arms
and take an eternal nap.
Well done.
It is indeed well done.
What a bitter lover.
It makes my heart leap.
I almost cried.
Du Shao Yang.
You are chicken-hearted.
How can you be the successor of
the Bloody Spear Guard?
Jing Xuan.
No.
You are known as Tang Si Qi here, right?
Si Qi.
Dad.
Can you let us go?
I am not hungry. I don't want to eat.
At the first instance,
I recognized your voice.
I was thinking
my daughter faked her death.
What a great episode.
I have to be part of the episode.
So, I waited outside the warehouse.
However, you didn't come out.
I have no other way
but to lure you out.
I saw you running and walking around.
I felt really sorry for you.
I was such an evil.
My own daughter
is terrified of me.
In the end, this lad came out
and got you out of the trouble.
I got puzzled. Could it be
you and this lad got engaged
without permission?
Don't do that!
You are getting bolder.
Please spare him, dad.
It's my fault.
I will let go of him
but I won't let go of you.
Si Qi!
Do you want her to come back?
Do you want to marry her?
It's over.
Look.
What is that?
Isn't that Thunderbolt Formation
that I use during cultivation?
Why did it become like this?
This is...
A Teleportation Formation.
I can recognize this crystal.
It is the Nightmare Crystal
of the Nether Realm.
When we were in the Nether Realm,
through the power of the
Nightmare Crystal,
I saw...
I saw you and her...
If I am not mistaken,
the Dark Nether Beasts
escaped from the Abyss
but they didn't go anywhere
as there was an agenda.
Through the power of Nightmare Crystal,
they've changed the Thunderbolt Formation
into a Teleportation Formation.
They used their life force to
charge the portal.
Nightmare Crystal
is an essential component
of a Teleportation Formation.
What should we do?
Should we destroy it?
The portal is not fully opened yet.
I think it is still lacking something.
What is it?
I am not sure.
I need to ask my dad.
Look, what is that?
Qin Lie!
The evil force is strong.
I think
there is some hidden information in it.
Can you open it?
Let me try.
Sage.
Like you asked, I brought you
the first volume
of the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
However, those who are not
royalty of the Nether Tribe
can't cultivate it.
If it is cultivated by a foreign tribe,
the cultivator will be killed.
I heard a voice.
Who are the Royalty of the Nether Tribe?
What is the Scripture of the Nine Hells?
The Royalty of the Nether Tribe
is the common master of
all the tribes in Nether Realm.
They are the royal family.
Even the Evil God obeys them.
The Scripture of the Nine Hells
is their secret incantation.
In that case,
the Sage
must have found the
Royalty of the Nether Tribe.
That's why he was looking
for the scripture.
The messenger said "you humans."
It means
the Sage is a human, too.
If that is the case,
why did he help his enemies
to attack his own people?
The Scripture of the Nine Hells
has three volumes in total.
It is the source of all secret powers
in the Nether Realm.
Even the secret power possessed by
the Evil God
derived from the scripture.
He was looking for the first volume
of the scripture.
It means the royal bloodline of
the Nether Tribe has awakened.
As long as we found...
Song Ting Yu, what are you doing?
The scripture is written in
the ancient language of the Nether Realm.
It means
the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
You are part of
Royalty of the Nether Tribe.
You absorbed the demon aura from her body.
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
That is because I was scared.
Even if so,
it doesn't mean that she is part of
the Royalty of the Nether Tribe.
Back in the Abyss,
I was confused.
The Abyss was full of demon aura.
I was attacked by the demon aura
as I was injured.
It was only reasonable.
Qin Lie had Demon Cleansing Pills.
He could fight off the demon aura.
That was reasonable too.
However, you, on the other hand,
after absorbing so much demon aura,
nothing happened to you.
So, I observed you in secret
until we are back to the ground.
How ridiculous.
Even in that case,
it can be explained in some other ways!
The Scripture of the Nine Hells
is connected to her.
It recognizes her as its master.
How can it be justified?
Let go of us first.
No way.
Before we found out the truth,
no one is allowed to leave.
Qin Lie.
What she said
might be true.
When we were in the Abyss,
I was puzzled too.
After absorbing so much of demon aura,
I didn't feel uncomfortable.
In contrast, I felt at ease.
However, am I really
the Royalty of the Nether Tribe?
I am not sure.
I only know that
even since I joined Qisha Valley
and started cultivating with the
Heavenly Water Spirit Record,
part of me has changed.
I became more sensitive
towards evil power.
Sometimes,
my hair and eyes turned purple.
Why didn't you tell me about that?
I don't want you to worry.
Furthermore, I asked my master before.
She said that it usually happened
during cultivation.
I believe that you are not lying.
Since you trust her,
why don't you let go of her?
Don't forget that
Yu Shi saved your life before.
I know.
I never forgot her kindness.
However,
I still suspect that she is part of
the Royalty of the Nether Tribe.
Before I found out the truth,
you won't run away, right?
No.
I really want to know
what is going on.
I have a request.
Before we found out the truth,
don't tell Song Yu about this.
Sure, I promise.
However, the Scripture of the Nine Hells
will be kept in my possession.
Ting Yu?