[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 22]
It's been a while, Master Lang Xie.
News from the Purple Mist Sea
said that you're all safe.
Qin Lie.
I've heard that you have a charmed life.
So it's true.
Qin Lie.
Why did you take the
Spiritual Lines Pillars?
From what I know,
the Spiritual Lines Pillars
don't belong to you
but the Artefact Forging Sect.
Nonsense!
The Spiritual Lines Pillars
had been with us
since the beginning of our sect.
I won't listen to your rubbish.
I'm occupied.
How dare you?
You're not the sect master, Qin Lie.
On Chief Song's orders,
the Artefact Forging Sect
had been passed to Master Ying.
You joined the Profound Heaven Alliance.
Never mind.
I have no time for you.
Hand the pillars out!
Take them from me if you can.
Saintess Song.
Please help the Artefact Forging Sect.
This is your internal affair.
I can't help you, nor do I have the time.
I have only one question.
Is Jiu Liu Yu of the Qisha Valley
still here?
Saintess.
Master Jiu Liu Yu
was assassinated last night.
[Tea]
Jiu Liu Yu's death was suspicious.
Indeed.
Seems like there's a great secret on you.
That's why someone wanted to kill you.
Senior Li Zhong Zheng must know about it.
They're back at the Qisha Valley.
I'll go back and ask them.
Are you planning to escape?
I need to inform
my father about the portal.
Don't think of running away.
Otherwise, I'll reveal the truth.
Then,
you'll be hunted by every sect.
You'll have nowhere to go
in the entire Chilan Continent.
How can a portal exist in the
herb mountain at the Ling Borough?
We can't be certain that it's just
the herb mountain.
Who placed the Scripture of the
Nine Hells there?
Who was it prepared for?
Who was the Sage?
Chief, the message said that the
Scripture of the Nine Hells
will combine with the Nether
Realm's royal blood.
What's different
with the Royal Nether Race?
The God Race,
Bo Tian.
Ting Yu.
The powerful Bo Tian Tribe claimed
themselves as gods.
When they attacked 30, 000 years ago,
the royals led the Abyss
and various human races to fight.
The war lasted for more
than thousand years.
Many great masters were killed.
These were the histories
written in ancient scriptures.
Chief, I've read a book about it.
The Royal Nether Race had
purple hair and eyes.
Is it true?
The Tale of Gong Mu Lie?
When will you stop your obsession?
I'm not obsessed!
You're the Saintess.
You've shamed us
from falling into the Abyss
and got poisoned by the demon aura.
Brother, the Nether underground
is a dangerous place.
Ting Yu was capable to leave unscathed.
Where's Qin Lie?
Why didn't you bring him here?
He was preoccupied.
I'm waiting for a chance.
I don't want your explanation!
If he could manage to
tame the twelve Spiritual Lines Pillars,
he must join my forces!
Kill him if he refuse!
Yes.
You're tired.
Get some sleep.
You have plenty of things to do.
Leave me be.
Nothing is more important than you.
How can I compare myself to the
crisis of Chilan Continent?
Qin Lie.
I know you're worried that
Song Ting Yu would harm me.
But I trust her.
Before the truth is found,
she won't do anything to me.
You believe her,
but I don't.
This woman is a hard nut to crack.
How is she hard to crack?
She likes you.
You're too kind, Yu Shi.
Everything she said or does
are all her conspiracies.
Besides, I only care
about you.
Yu Shi.
I'm sorry.
We were underground for so long and
I didn't see that the aura
doesn't affect you.
It's obvious that I have neglected you.
In your heart,
I'm not a reliable person.
That must be why you're being secretive.
I didn't tell you
to spare you from worrying.
So what for purple hair and eyes?
Even if you're a nether demon,
your enemies
are my enemies.
If the whole Chilan Continent
becomes your enemy,
I'll be enemies with the whole
Chilan Continent.
You can't speak like that.
The consequences will be severe.
Besides, don't feel guilty for me...
It's not guilt.
I'm willing to do this
for you.
That's enough for me.
Qin Lie.
Senior Feng Rong met with a mishap.
Master Mo Hai had to suppress his sadness
to cultivate more magic tools.
Check on him
and see if you can help.
You should follow me.
I can't leave you alone.
I'm tired.
I need some rest.
Come back soon when you can.
Master Mo Hai.
You're back?
I'm waiting for you.
Yes?
Master Lang Xie.
Saintess Song.
Do you know where Qin Lie is?
I saw him speaking to Mo Hai.
[Zhao Xi.]
[If I can return safely,]
[I might fight with your people in turn.]
[Don't you regret saving me?]
[I should've killed you]
[or take you in for a reward.]
[But I can't do it.]
[Miss Yu Shi.]
[The Dark Nether Race]
[is not as wicked as you think.]
Remember, I'm Zhao Xi.
This spiritual herb
is the Nether Devil Fruit.
Like me, i had never seen sunlight before.
When you return to the ground,
can you place it under the sun
and call out my name?
Perhaps that way,
I can feel the warmth of the sun too.
Zhao Xi.
Who is it?
Where is Qin Lie?
He went to Master Mo Hai.
I want to speak to you.
I see that you're close
to that Zhao Xi.
He saved me.
And he was kind to me.
Seems like we had different encounters
underground.
The Dark Nether Race I met
were all cruel murderers
of the human race.
I didn't see that.
They were like us.
They were kind and desired peace.
They dreamed to lead a better life.
Did you forget that Zhao Xi
wanted to kill me?
That was because you
killed his family and friends.
No one is completely good or evil.
If we massacre each other for
various motives,
goodness will ultimately turn evil.
We think that the Dark Nether Race is evil
but we are the evildoers
in their perspective.
Seems like you do empathize them.
If you're the Royal Nether Race,
will you join forces with them
and fight the human race?
Are you sounding me out?
I'm merely asking.
I don't care if I'm human
or the Royal Nether Race.
I blame myself for being too weak.
If I'm invincible,
I can dissolve the enmity myself.
When I found out
we were allies with the Nether Race,
I shared the same thought as you.
But the Nether War lasted so long
which intensified our feud.
I had no way
to dissolve it.
But you're the Saintess.
I'm a useless daughter of my father.
My title as the Saintess
has no actual affect.
Besides, it's too late now.
Master Mo Hai
had made plenty of Terminator
Profound Bombs.
Tomorrow morning,
my father will wage war
on the Dark Nether Race.
So fast?
With countless Terminator Profound Bombs,
the Dark Nether Race won't
be able to survive wherever they hide.
My father was delighted.
So he planned to held a feast tonight
to celebrate his victory tomorrow.
I knew you would come.
You plotted against me?
So,
these Terminator Profound Bombs
are fake?
Capture her.
How dare you!
You summoned me late at night
with a thorough plan.
I lied that the Terminator Profound
Bombs were made
and we'll fight the Dark Nether
Race tomorrow.
I wanted to see
her reaction.
As expected,
you're a Royal Nether Race.
Royal Nether Race?
Impossible.
The Royal Nether Race was eliminated
few thousand years ago.
Legend says that the Royal Nether Race
had purple hair and eyes.
Ling Yu Shi, you once said
that your hair and eyes would turn purple,
right?
Miss Ling, you...
You're a Royal Nether Race?
Master Mo Hai.
I'm not sure if I'm of
the Royal Nether Race.
It's not important to me.
I grew up in the the far north.
I spoke the human language and
practised the human spirit art.
The spiritual herbs I planted
were for human use too.
No matter if I'm human
or demon,
I refuse to see wars between the tribes.
We're not killing each other.
They were brutal lots.
Master Lang Xie.
If you had to live
underground and never see daylight,
how would you feel?
A Nether Race youngster saved me
when I fell into the netherworld.
What I saw and felt
was different than how we imagined.
We're merely different
in our origins.
They have emotions.
They want to live in peace too.
Yu Shi.
What is your plan after
stealing the bombs?
I'll hide them.
Then I'll try to appease
everyone's hatred.
You may think that I'm naive.
We do not know how much power we possess.
No one can determine
what we can achieve
or not achieve.
What do you plan to do?
Qin Lie, you saw her stealing...
I asked what your plan was.
I'll hand Ling Yu Shi to my father.
Good.
Keep them apart!
Qin Lie has a space magic tool!
The peak of Manifestation Realm?
You've levelled up again after a few days.
Don't lose yourself, kid!
He absorbed the power
of the thunder pool in the
Evil God Mountains.
He formed his energy source with my help.
Qin Lie, listen to Master Lang Xie!
Don't lose yourself!
Qin Lie!
Leave me here! Go!
You want to trap me?
Try me!
Qin Lie! You traitor!
Move, Master Lang Xie! I'll kill him!
You let them off on purpose!
How dare you?
I asked you to move!
Why should I move?
I almost got them!
You would've got them if you could!
I was scared that they would escape!
Stop arguing.
Elder Mo Hai, why didn't you attack them?
Yu Shi.
Did I scare you?
No.
I was too agitated
and felt that my hair and eyes
were changing.
I contained it
in fear that they would see me.
So what if they see you?
You look prettier
like this.
Is it worth it to anger the human race
for me?
If I'm really a Royal Nether Race,
won't you blame me for stealing the bombs
to help the Abyss?
I don't care who you are.
You're always my Ling Yu Shi.
But you're wrong to steal the
Terminator Profound Bombs.
You should've asked me to do it.
You can stay in your room
and wait for me to retrieve them.
Yu Shi.
If you're really a Royal Nether Race,
what would you do?
I'll accept myself as a Royal Nether Race
If I truly am one.
But it doesn't mean that
I'll submit to my fate.
Right?
Yes.
If I'm a Royal Nether Race,
would my father
and everyone in the Ling Borough...
People of the Ling Borough
are in Qisha Valley!
Would they be in danger?
We'll go right away!
Song Ting Yu would've guessed it.
But the Qisha Valley is too far from here.
We might not make it.
We can.
This is?
I planned ahead of Song Ting Yu.
That's why I made a magic tool
at the Artefact Forging Sect.
I failed many times
before I finally got it.
Let's go.
Why did no one tell me about Ling Yu Shi
being the Royal Nether Race?
I wanted to prove it.
You should let your father prove it.
What to do now that things
turned out this way?
It's so awkward.
Your father would be angry later.
Chief.
Qin Lie will bring Ling Yu Shi back
to Qisha Valley.
Please allow me to make amends
and bring men to the Qisha Valley.
Grand Priestess.
Why are you here, Grand Priestess?
On the holy ritual of the Holy Gods,
I sensed a peculiar spiritual energy.
If I was right,
the owner of the spiritual power
belongs to the Royal Nether Race.
The royals are back?
It was said that the Royal Nether Race
had perished
in the war with the God Race.
But we had hoped
for the royal bloodline
to exist in the world.
If it was,
it would be our time to rise again.
The king of the Gods,
the Royal Nether Race!
North!
-Fight!
-Yes!
Fight!
Go!
Bring the royal bloodline back safely!
Yes!
[Qisha Valley Village]
They have been inside the whole time?
I asked the disciples taking care of them.
They didn't show up lately.
The Profound Heaven Alliance
ordered to kill.
Ling Yu Shi is a Royal Nether Race.
No one in the Ling Borough
shall be spared.
-Do it.
-Yes!
Hide!
Ling Ying!
Ling Ying,
I'm back.
Yu Shi.
Are we really the Dark Nether Race?
[Sage of the Nether Tribe]
[Mirror of Souls, Jungle of Gems]
[Ten thousand years ago,]
[our people and the human race]
[lived together in this spirit realm.]
[We divided the lands to north and west.]
[The West belonged to the
Nether Continent.]
[It was the most mysterious]
[and magical land in the spirit realm.]
[Sunlight and rain nurtured our people,]
[nourished the land and
cultivated spiritual gems.]
[Our people and the human
race kept in contact]
[by sharing cultivation materials
and co-lived in harmony.]
[We kept peace together.]
The Nether Tribe was ruled
by the Royal Nether Race.
[When the God Race attacked us
ten thousand years ago,]
[we fought together with the human race
[and exterminated them.]
[But the Royal Nether Race
perished in the war.]
[We lost our stronghold,]
which caused confusion and
distress among our people.
Aside from this tragedy,
the human race prospered.
The human race couldn't survive
on the Eastern Lands.
Therefore,
they began to exploit the
lands of the west.
[Our ally became our enemy.]
[Finally, we lost greatly.]
[The human race forced us
to the underground.]
[Sunlight was never seen in the Abyss.]
Water was scarce.
We used up our resources within a year.
Our people began to lose themselves
as they lived in great darkness.
[Gradually, they became monsters.]
I was the last Sage
of the Royal Nether Race
3,000 years ago.
I strongly believe
that the Royal Nether Race
would never cease to exist.
Therefore, I leave my remnants of powers
in the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
If the bloodline of the Royal Nether Race
survived,
[the Scripture of the Nine Hells
will find them.]
[And they need to know that]
[the Nether Tribe of the past]
[were all benign beings who
appreciated the world]
[and dreamed of peace and love.]
Are we done with the nonsense?
Let's stop standing here.
Let's fight!
Attack!
I want some wine!
Hold me captive! Hurry!
I'll kill her if you don't stop!
Palm of Great God!
Spare them, Brother Xie.
Xie Yi!
That was fun! Let's continue!
Hurry and leave!
The Saintess is in my hands!
Back down!
Back!
Just a pretence.
She saved us.
I didn't know why you did it,
but I thank you.
Hail to the Queen!
I'm the Queen?
Now that the Scripture of the Nine Hells
acknowledged its master,
you shall become the new Queen.
You're willing to acknowledge me?
This is heaven's will.
We'll oblige to it
and see you as our ruler.
I always thought I was human.
I grew up as a human.
I drank their water,
ate their food,
and made friends with them.
Only now I know
that I'm a Royal Nether Race.
I won't avoid my identity.
Are you willing to take the risk
and believe in me?
Yes!
Rise, everyone.
We're all equal.
You don't have to kneel for me.
I know my existence
brought you hope.
I don't know how much I can change
the current situation.
But I'll try my best.
I hope I can bring my people
back to the world filled
with love and peace.
There shall be no war
and no hatred.
Good!
The Mother of Lands can contain
everything!
The Mother of Lands?
The highest monarchy of the
Royal Nether Race
shall be the Mother of Lands!
What should we do with the two humans?
What's with that look?
Are you scared that we'll be different?
Will we?
I only know that
no matter you're the Queen
or a disciple of the Qisha Valley,
you're my Ling Yu Shi.
And I'm your Qin Lie.
Of course.
I'm Qin Lie.
I killed your people before.
However,
you killed plenty of my people too.
I don't know
if we could become friends
and end our feud.
However, I promise that
Ling Yu Shi is my utmost importance
besides my grandfather.
I'll fight anyone
who stands against her.
Including everyone here!
Good!
What about her?
The Saintess of the Alliance.
If we're putting down hatred
and asking for peace,
we shall stop our massacre.
Besides, she saved us.
We'll release her.
If she tries to harm us after this,
we'll see her on the battlefield!