# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 11
What's the English song you sang just now?
Someone like you.
Sounds good.
Didn't expect that you're such a good singer.
Really?
Yes.
Has anyone said that your voice is beautiful?
It's just good.
I think if you practice more,
you'll sing very well.
Really?
Do you know abdominal phonation?
Ab.. Ab what?
Abdomen. Here. Touch here.
Almost like this.
Are you soprano or mezzo-soprano?
I don't know.
Make a sound.
Again.
I think you should be soprano.
Really?
Another song?
I think this picture is very interesting, right?
Ye Muxi.
Yes. The one in the picture.
This is Ye Muxi.
I'm Ye Muxi. Do we know each other?
No. No. We don't.
[ Popular New Star Tastes The Forbidden Fruit? ]
Who are you?
Do I know you?
Why following me?
Playing wooden man on the street?
What are you doing, superstar?
Who's the superstar?
Listen to me.
Listen to me, I don't know why.
But it's so weird today.
I feel there are so many people stalking me.
So you still don't know that?
Don't know what?
This...
[ Taste Of First Love ]
[ Who's Xue Xiaodong's Mysterious Girlfriend? ]
[ Sweet Date In A Rainy Night ]
[ Young Idol X High School Classmate ]
[ Is This His Choice!? ]
What the hell is this?! I...
Wait.
This is my phone.
This... How could this happen?
So, you're really seeing each other?
How could I possibly date him?! I...
Media are just like this, spreading rumors.
As long as there's some news,
they won't care about anything else.
That... Paparazzi, right?
I'll go teach them a good lesson.
Calm down first.
You should discuss with Xue Xiaodong first.
What should I do right now?
What else could you do? Go to school.
Xiaodong is not around. No one helps me.
Lucky that I've got Shanqi.
Shanqi will definitely believe me.
What's wrong?
There's killing spirit.
Shanqi, what are you doing here?
Waiting.
For what?
Ye Muxi.
Liao Danyi.
You've also seen that news, right?
Ye Muxi won't betray me, right?
They're not seeing each other, right?
Shanqi...
Right?
At such a moment,
you gotta calm down and be rational.
Ye Muxi.
Shanqi.
You two again!
I remember you two!
How many times has it been?!
What do you want?
Calm down.
Rest easy. We won't hurt you.
I just wanna talk with you.
About what?!
I can go talk with her.
I know what happened!
Sorry.
Xue Xiaodong.
What happened to you again?
Sorry. It's all my fault.
This is a plot of those paparazzi.
I know this is...
That... Paparazzi...
I can go end them myself! I...
Calm down.
All my fault.
If you're mad at me,
just beat me.
Xiaodong, easy.
Now, it's not a personal problem of your own.
But related to our company's interests.
Now, you must listen to me.
Okay, sis Annie.
You gotta put an end to this thing.
Rest easy.
You only need to do as I say.
Miss Ye.
Let's talk about terms and conditions.
What terms and conditions?
What can make you stay away from Xiaodong?
So he can walk out of this gossip crisis?
I'm the victim. Me!
You gotta know,
whether you truly love him or not,
this affair between you and Xiaodong
indeed has made you well-known.
I don't care whether you want to profit from it.
But you gotta know, by working with me,
you can get more benefits.
I also want to nail this problem!
I'll end them right now! I really...
Calm down!
Now that we share a highly agreed goal,
you only need to do as I say.
Tomorrow morning.
We'll give a press conference to clarify this matter.
What you're gonna do is nothing.
During this period of time.
You two keep a distance and stay indoor
as possible as you can.
Then in a few days,
some other news come out.
This thing will be bygones.
You can leave now.
Today I call everyone here.
To discuss something with you.
I believe you all have known the Xiaodong thing.
I want to know your opinions.
War or peace?
Your majesty.
I have something that I don't know if I should tell you.
Your majesty, I think...
We should end them.
Your majesty, give me ten thousand elite soldiers.
I'll rush on a horse to kill all their family and their clan!
Your majesty, I think it's not a good idea.
Your majesty, who are they?
They're paparazzi.
Throughout history,
no one who has offended them end up well.
For example, that person.
And that person.
Especially, that person.
Which person? Minister Li, make it clear.
So abrasive.
Your majesty, I think I don't need ten thousand elite soldiers.
Give me two hundred average ones.
Once I see them following your majesty's car,
-Your majesty.
-I'll...
Although they're despicable and mean,
your majesty can't do the same thing as they did.
To be frank,
They're low.
But your majesty can't be lower than them, right?
Minister Li, why you always speak for those outsiders?
What did you mean by that?
I'm thinking for her majesty's dignity.
Her majesty's dignity?
You're just being cowardly!
Your majesty! I must risk my life to tell you this!
Shoot.
Even if I'll have my body smashed into pieces,
I must be loyal to your majesty
and tell you this.
Strong wind, high sky, miserable apes' crying.
Clean islets, white sands, above them birds flying.
Countless leaves keep falling off the trees.
Endless Yangtze River rises rolling torrents.
Remain to be a traveler far away from home.
Sick and alone, climbing stairs in a mirthless autumn.
Hardships, hatred and bitterness gray the hair.
Frustrated, put down this cup of turbid wine.
What you said,
has anything to do with what I'm suffering?
Your majesty, it doesn't.
I just want to show off my talent.
Behead him!
Your majesty, I just want to show off.
Not that serious!
-Shut up. Go.
-Fatuous ruler!
-So wise, your majesty.
Sorry, I didn't notice you.
Miss Xinyi!
I'm here!
Miss Xinyi.
I heard your calling hundreds of meters away.
Please let me handle such kind of trivia.
Go away. Go away.
Sorry.
Miss Xinyi, you can't be more careful.
It's okay if you hurt other people.
But what if you get yourself hurt?
I'll feel heart-broken. Right?
You gotta take good care of yourself, Miss Xinyi.
I've been keeping fit lately.
I'm really very, very tired.
Biceps, triceps, and chest muscles...
Xiaodong, have some water.
This press conference doesn't work out well.
Xiaodong.
To minimize the unfavorable influence,
you must have another press conference.
Again?
Of course.
But, before that,
our crisis PR will help you roll out a series of activities.
Among which,
you'll work with the rising popular star, youths' idol, Angel.
And produce quantities of news.
Angel? Is she much older...
Yes.
Nowadays, this kind of love is a hottest topic.
Besides, it helps further improve your fame in this trade.
It's the very that we want.
But how will my classmates judge me?
Don't worry about that.
I've discussed with your parents.
Later,
I'll handle the drop-out formalities for you.
What?
If you still want a campus life,
I can help you study abroad a few years later.
It's no problem.
Xiaodong, what I'm doing is for your good.
Drive, move on.
Let me take you to watch the sunset.
Why it blows out again?
You brats, stop right there!
Stop!
Guan Xinyi, sorry.
My classmates made you suffer this.
During this period of time.
You two keep a distance and stay indoor
as possible as you can.
Then in a few days,
some other news come out.
This thing will be bygones.
Keep practicing. Don't be distracted.
Xue Xiaodong is gonna drop out of school!
So, shall I stop him or not?
Your majesty.
I think, Xue Xiaodong's dropout might be his own will.
This thing might better help his future career.
Meanwhile, it'll save many troubles for your majesty.
Why not let it happen, your majesty?
Your majesty, I don't think it's a good idea.
As Xue Xiaodong's best friend, your majesty
must have felt that Xue Xiaodong is happy in our Class Ten.
So, is his own will to drop out?
If not,
as Xue Xiaodong's best friend,
shouldn't your majesty do something?
Which one of you shall I listen to?
Listen to your majesty yourself.
After all, you're the emperor.
Smile.
Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
Anyway, two popular new stars
will have a very deep cooperation in this movie.
Besides, they're very tacit already.
Next, questions time. You first.
Hi, Xue Xiaodong.
How do you think of Angel?
She's a very nice girl.
We're... Very good friends.
How good? Love at the first sight?
We're very tacit.
Not only at work.
But also in daily life.
Okay. This one.
Xue Xiaodong.
You're gonna drop out of school
because of that affair, right?
That's just a misunderstanding.
We're also considering about his dropout.
After all, Mr Xue Xiaodong's future
is what we value the most.
Thank you.
Since that affair proves to be a misunderstanding,
will you keep in touch with
your classmates, especially that girl?
Xue Xiaodong!
I have something to talk with you.
What's going on?
It's said that you're gonna drop out. Is it true?
Miss...
Shut up! Let him speak!
Are you afraid that we'll be defamed?
It's okay. We suffer that every day.
Yes! We're not afraid of that!
We have no fame anyway!
I've been defamed since childhood.
But I got over it.
But if you're really afraid of that,
I'll feel disappointed at you.
You're the strongest man I've ever known.
You even can beat your fat.
What else can't you beat?!
I want to hear what's really in your mind.
In fact, I don't want to leave this school at all.
I don't want to leave my classmates.
I also don't want to take part into this movie.
In fact, me and Angel...
Not familiar.
About work,
I want to fulfill it in my spare time after school.
I really love my classmates in Class Ten, Grade Ten.
I only want to stay in my Class Ten.
Together with you guys.
Because I really love my classmates.
Because I really love...
Study.
I also love study!
-I also love study!
I... I don't love study.
You must say it.
I love study!
Friends from media.
Actually we're not here for a launch event.
Let bygones be bygones.
In fact, we're here to clarify
Mr. Xue Xiaodong's affair problem.
As you see,
Xiaodong and his classmates are on good terms.
He cherishes this friendship.
So,
for those who try to defame Xiaodong,
we're responding with legal measures.
Xiaodong, we'll always stand on your side.
Sis Annie.
Okay. Let's call it a day now.
Go find them. Leave this to me.
I'm your broker!
Xue Xiaodong, say something more.
Don't leave.
Don't leave. Say something more.
Just stop right here!
Stop right here!
It's over now.
Haven't I given you bonus?!
Stop right here!
It's over already.
How many times have I told you that?!
Can we interview you more?
That hurts.
Buddha's Palm.
Name the move before you hit me.
Look at me. Look at me. Look.
What's up?
Am I losing weight?
Don't ask such a question.
Look, thanks to you,
I'm gaining weight lately.
Have lunch with Xue?
Don't read it aloud.
Can we have lunch together?
Okay.
He says okay.
It's your shampoo.
Yes, my shampoo.
The mutton should be done.
This tastes very good.
Which one?
You...
How could you eat hot pot at school?!
Is this against school rules?
You...
Liao Danyi, would you like to join us?
No need. I've got something else to do.
Excuse me.
-Hot pot.
-So delicious.
Liao Danyi.
You really don't want to know
what I'm gonna tell you?
Do you know it already?
You're pretending that you don't
or you really don't?
Sorry, I've got something else to do.
Liao Danyi.
I gotta tell you this even if you don't want to hear it.
I must say it today.
I don't care about the vibe and stuff.
I don't care whether I look nice or not today.
I gotta tell you, Liao Danyi.
Liao Danyi, I...
Shut up!
You, back off, keep steering the wheel.
Turn left. Keep steering.
Back off. Back off. Back off.
Move, that way.
Okay, stop.
And you, move on.
You, come here.
It seems that we have a worse vibe now.
But still I gotta tell you this.
Liao Danyi,
I love you.