# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 12
Lian Danyi.
You really don't want to know what I'm gonna tell you?
Did you already know?
Are you pretending you don't know or you really don't?
It's the first time someone expresses her love to me.
Can't fall asleep.
What should I do?
I love you.
So distressing.
[Once upon a time...]
The deadline is closing.
I haven't finished it.
So distressing.
How could this be helpful?!
[Hello, Word.doc. My head is full of complicated thoughts.]
[Can't sleep....]
[Once upon a time...]
[So I want to write it to you. I... A girl ... She...]
What am I doing here?!
No textbook has written anything about this.
Forget it. Just ignore it.
Welcome to come into the secret man's live room.
Today, your secret man is gonna show you...
Weight lifting.
Another side.
Friendly reminder:
Keep working out.
Because there's always someone
stronger than you in the world.
And they're also practicing hard.
Like me.
Don't give up.
Thank you for your gift.
Sister.
I...I...
It's live.
Look, look, so many fans.
They sent me so many things.
Here, allow me to introduce.
She is our wonder girl, Yezi.
My most beautiful, most lovely sister.
What're you looking at?
This...
Brother, do you know your deadline is in three days?
I know.
Don't say it.
It's live.
What if the producer saw this?
Sorry, every body.
This is your secret man.
Although my sister is very beautiful.
But lately, she is a little delusional.
How many have you written?
They will see this.
Of course I wrote some.
I'm working very hard.
You know what...
I'm your sister. You think I don't know you?
You haven't written any, right?
How is that possible?!
Last night, you don't know.
That speed is like flying.
Like a ghost hand.
No, no, don't touch it. Don't...
It's blank.
Well...
I've got to go now.
Have fun.
Live forever. More gifts.
Don't forget to send more gifts.
Now I'm running away from my delusional sister
And turning to a quiet place.
Let's continue.
Next is called sword swallowing.
Sword, okay?
Awesome, right?
Must be a long night yesterday.
Who...
Don't, don't...
Brother!
You've been watching SNH48's concert for a whole night?!
No, I...
It popped out. I don't know when.
Look... You have been watching it for a whole night!
Look, I...
I really did work last night.
I'll show you if you don't believe me.
Look.
[Once upon...]
Two words?
Yes, but.
You know it's hard right?
Once I started.
I will finish it right away.
Anyway, before I come back.
You must finish it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Don't worry. I promise.
Before you come back tonight.
I will finish it.
To create a beautiful tomorrow for myself.
I'm... I'm on it. Thinking.
Please, do me a favor.
Then don't forget to tell Wu Sir about
the first mysticism conference in our class.
Okay.
Deal.
Guan Xinyi.
You're waiting.
Yes.
No, no, I'm not waiting.
You're waiting for your destiny.
I saw fire in your eyes.
You must be a Virgo.
Yeah. How can you tell?
Virgos are all sensitive and sharp.
Very powerful among women.
I'm a Capricornus.
I know you Virgos the best!
Capricornus? Capricornus and Virgo are the best!
But...
Lately, Virgos are not quite lucky in love affairs.
What is that?
Follow me.
Lately, Venus is retrograding.
Venus retrograding?
Yes.
Once upon a time,
there's a restaurant.
They're very strict with the food material selecting.
Chef is quite skillful with his knife.
They way he performs his knife is amazing.
Right.
Yezi seems quite busy lately.
I should make something nice for her.
Make two big dishes.
Seems this won't be enough for any big dish.
No.
I must make something delicious for Yezi.
Need to go out shopping.
Hi, Guan Xinyi.
You...
You are too direct.
[I decline.]
No. Too official.
What am I writing here?!
Look, what's that?
What's that?
It's a mouse.
One more place to run into Guan Xinyi easily.
After this one, I will be safe today.
One more place to run into Director Yan easily.
What're you doing here?
We sold director Yan's bike by accident yesterday.
So we're hiding here.
You two are so bold.
What're you doing here?
Right.
I don't know why I am hiding here, either.
I'm home.
You're home.
Come, come on.
See what I have made for you.
Here, sit.
So many delicious things.
This is your favorite tomato chicken eggs.
A salad.
And fried chicken.
Hurry, eat.
You did these to celebrate your finished work?
Not yet.
But close.
Today, I'll watch you finish it.
No story, no sleep.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Go ahead.
Brother, how to cook this?
This one? Golden fried rice.
This is your brother's special dish.
First, rice.
Need to be the rice one night before.
Put two thirds egg into the rice and mingle it.
Then keep it in the fridge for fifteen minutes.
As for the one third egg,
leave it for the fried rice while you cook it.
Take it out, it will be
a wonderful golden fired rice.
Just like that,
Brother Ye and Yezi watched TV while eating snacks
and fell into asleep.
His story?
Not a single word.
The biggest problem since I was born.
Shall I discuss it with a girl? Will it help?
Speaking of that,
do I have any female friends?
Come here.
What for?
Shoot, what do you need me for?
I'm worrying about my brother.
He won't turn in his story on time. Shoot.
Shoot.
Begin.
I have to ask you something....
This thing...
Will you say it or not?
When did you become such a coward?
Shoot. Shoot.
You...
Has anyone told you they love you?
No.
Thanks.
Come back.
Tell me.
What's going on?
Tell me, what is that?
Nothing.
It's just...
I have a friend.
I have a friend, a girl told him she loves him.
Then he is quite distressing.
Didn't know what to do.
That friend.
He is a very good student.
Someone told you she loves you.
Usually that friend is yourself.
So, who confessed her love to you?
Hurry, no one is around, tell me.
I won't tell anyone.
Which blind girl told you she loves you?
The girl who confessed her love to my friend
is Guan Xinyi.
- Voice down!
- Guan!... Xinyi.
You?
And Guan Xinyi?
Well, Class One.
The most annoying one.
How did that happen?
Liao Danyi.
Let's date.
As from today,
I will do my homework with you.
I'll stop laughing.
It's okay.
My friend didn't know what to do.
It's okay. Girls, you know.
I can understand her feeling.
So I really can help you.
We're classmates.
We should help each other.
But, before that...
You must do something for me.
What is that?
Your brother...
Life is just a journey.
Let go of things.
Things start from your heart.
Laugh will heal all the worries.
Words
They will come when it's time.
Is he gonna be immortal?
He is seriously ill.
Two heroes are back.
Please sit.
I'll tell you what I've realized lately.
Writing.
It needs to wait for the Muse.
When Muse comes, you'll write swiftly.
But...
Brother Yihan. Your job, are you doing well?
Don't mention my job.
My Muse hasn't come,
I need to wait for the wind.
God has his plan on me.
I can't stand it.
What're you doing?
I'm waiting for the wind.
Let's go.
- God is on his way
- Come
I'm waiting for the wind.
Why're you dragging me here?
My Muse is on the way.
Brother, look at that.
What is that?
Look at there.
At last, here.
What did you see?
-This is your sister's room.
-Nothing.
This indicates her future.
This...
Understand?
What do you mean?
Look at this.
These garbage, means she can't live by herself.
Then there.
A bunch of toys.
She is playing toys still?
You can call her innocent.
But in a hard way,
It indicates she is a moron! Brother.
Right.
At last, here.
Those textbooks.
What did she draw on those textbooks!
Think about it.
When she enters into the society later,
when she has a meeting with her boss.
She still draws things on the book? Then...
So, brother.
You're not working just for yourself.
You did it for your sister.
You need to earn more money
to raise her up.
Otherwise, she will die!
Right , right
The worst possibility is that
she might smoke,
drink, fight.
Or even become a hooligan in the gang!
Do you understand? Brother?
Yes. I do
No, no!
Brother, calm down.
Right. calm down.
Right.
Danyi lad, you're very right.
I'm doing his for my sister.
Work hard.
For my sister.
I need to write.
I need to work hard.
Sister, brother was wrong!
I didn't think for you.
You're my stupid younger sister.
Don't say anything.
I'll go to work.
To fight for my sister.
Ye Muxi.
To fight for my sister. Ye Muxi.
For my sister. For my sister.
Ye Muxi.
What did you tell him?
He has been fixed.
Nothing.
Just some statement about facts.
Finally, done!
Lad Danyi, sister.
Thank you both.
Brother, you changed quite fast.
Why?
Life is fragile.
But sometimes
To protect something more fragile.
We'll become strong.
You two go on chatting.
I'll go back to sleep.
Thank you.
Bye.
It's normal that you don't understand.
I didn't overestimate you.
Don't underestimate me. Listen to me.
I'm very smart.
Your friend's thing is on me.
Why do I feel it quite unrealistic?
Mr. dinosaur.
Please call me Mr. Wolong.
A little respect, please.
Mr. Wolong.
Long time no see.
Your hands are still so cute.
What can I do?!
I don't like this, either.
Why can't you give me a pair of strong hands to work?
Mine, too.
I think it's quite cute.
Look. You both look so serious.
But with such cute hands.
I think that makes you quite friendly.
Wonder girl is quite good at quibbling.
What is the matter today?
I want to ask you that...
How to refuse someone you dislike very much?
That, you have to ask Zhu Zhiwu.
Dead Horse magic, summon Zhu Zhiwu!
I'm Zhu Zhiwu.
Shoot.
Although I'm old, I know,
Love is like a battle.
It's always like this.
Why?
One country goes attack another.
It's like one person goes chase another.
Not only needs to call their force
To show their strength.
To make the other surrender.
Of course, when one country is weak.
The other country will ignore them.
Then it will go make ally with another country.
It's always like this
But what if this country wants to make ally with another
which doesn't want the same.
Then what?
Allow me to explain it to you.
What're you gonna do?
You asked her here.
What're you gonna tell her?
You don't need to know.
Since you helped my brother.
Now I'll help you.
What you need to do is to be quiet,
cooperate with me, okay?
Hush. Come.
What're you doing here?
Guan Xinyi.
Do you love Liao Danyi?
It's none of your business.
Today, I called you here to tell you that.
You two are not possible.
Because, Liao Danyi...
He loves me!
- What?!
Since we were young, one year old.
Before my mom worked overtime,
she would send me to his home.
He fell in love with me at the first sight.
It's quite miserable.
Over these ten years.
He is always chasing me.
First thing in the morning,
he will come knock on my door.
To pick me up to school.
But I keep refusing him.
I said no, we're not possible. No.
I didn't expect that made him changed to another way.
He started to cook for me.
I mean. bento?!
So I said, fine. You do it.
I won't eat.
But he keeps making that.
Now the bento even has his figure in it.
The whole school will see it.
I really...
Tell her, you tell her, tell her.
How much do you love me. Say it
And he also said,
if I won't accept him,
he will never accept any other girls.
So I say,
you two are not possible.
Just give it up.
So gross.
You tell her, you explain it to her.
Tell her, tell her.
Tell her.
Tell Guan Xinyi
how much you love me. Say it.
Or do you want she to accept you?
I love you.
But, why do you love me?
Cute.
Nonsense.
It's because I'm pretty.
I love you.
Pretty.
Damn it!
Problem solved.
Why did I trust you?
It's right to trust me.
I solved your problem.
So it's right to let me handle it.
Now problem solved.