# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
The Big Boss
Episode 13
Why haven't you made any breakfast?
You've changed
I'll make it, I'll make it
I'm really scared of you
Little sister
I'm really sorry today
In order to live up to the expectations of folks
Pulled an all nighter accessing information
Fighting code word, ah
My vitality is injured
That is really no strength in me. I'll cook dinner for you.
Let go of brother today
Thank you
You starve me to death
All right, all right
Afraid of you, afraid of you
Go out for two miles
Turn left
A new gourmet city has been opened
Very, very good
It's lined with shops and food like clouds
The point is...
It also contains the one you like best
It is said that sister is like a cotton padded jacket
Brother lost to a pot
To eat hot pot, eat hot pot ah!
Eat hot pot, free drinks ah!
Free wine delivery
Come and have a look
Eat hot pot, free drinks
Which is the best choice out of so many hot pot restaurants?
Of course, I would recommend my souther Sichuan hot pot
In today's world Jiuzhousihai known Wurenbuxiao ah
No one knows, no one knows ah!
Xi also array too
It has Hot pot.
Of course, my northern pie is best known for its meat
It has a long history
Absorb all the essence of Chinese food
So we have become famous all over the world
You fart!
You talk nonsense!
You bounce
I cycle
Rebound
I recycle
Stop
I'll start another line
We are good in the south, we are better off in the South
We'll give a good North, give a good North
Southern
Northern brush meat
Pretty girl, would you like eating hot pot?
Does this pretty girl eat hot pot?
Sichuan hotpot is delicious, inexpensive and economical
Come to our shop
Please do not leave, customer
Especially cheap
Really, really, super cheap
It's delicious, not expensive. Our shop is free of charge
Go away!
Don't listen to him
Don't go to their shop
They use leftover cooking oil
I'm telling you huh
We have fish and shrimps that are delicious
Come on, let's go to our shop.
Come to our shop, customer
Absolutely tasty
Our family is authentic Sichuan hot pot
Enough is enough, enough
I have eaten already
Let's go to our shop
Don't go beauty, beauty...
No, I'm already done eating
Come to our shop
That's enough!!!
Come on...
Don't you have eyes?
You're blind
Come on, you make it clear, you make it clear
Every time it is like this
For any mistake little or big
You blame me all the way
What did I do, I, I?
What did I do?
Forget it, I won't tell you
I have other things to do
Wait, wait till you get it straight
What's the issue?
Say
All get out of my way.
Classmate Liao Danyi
Disperse from here
Classmate Ye Muxi
What were you arguing about?
It's none of your business. Go away
Sorry, I didn't think about your 'business'
Where are you going, Liao Danyi?
My driver is just around the corner
I'll give you a ride
No, thank you
I'll just cycle by myself
Oh, I see
Liao Danyi
You're in such a hurry to go out with me
Aren't you going to have hot pot with me?
What ..... hot pot?
Oh yeah
Let's hurry and eat
Let's go
Wait a minute
Where are you going? I'm going, too
Why?
Because the school said
In order to prevent students from adolescent rash love
Boys and girls can't go out and play together
So, wherever you are going,  I'm going too
Right here??
What's up
Not used to such places
If you're not used to food here, then do not eat
For the sake of work, well..
I can do it
Pretty girls, handsome boy
Welcome to our house
We are the most delicious shop on this street
Look at this! We have a new product recently
Take what you want, though
Meet all your requirements
Some meat, vegetables and wine
There's no need for wine
No problem, no problem
These are children of rich families
Really!
With what kind of person?
You can only come to this kind of place?
You're being too whiny
Don't eat if you do not want to
Actually, it's not just eating
This is true in life
What are the people around you in your life?
What will you become?
What do you mean?
Classmate Ye Muxi
No
Monitor Ye Muxi
Have you ever heard such a sentence?
Good and straight
White sands are black in Nirvana
I forgot. You are in class ten
Of course you won't understand that
Landlady, definitely
there is no meat left
We are hungry. Here, here!!
Liao Danyi classmate
I'll give you lamb piece
Here you are
No, thanks
I don't like mutton
Oh, I see
Good
Liao Danyi loves my words. Take this meat, eat till all is finished.
That's a good thing
It's been a day with you. I should be going
There must be a secret for such a hurry
Mr Driver,  we have to do what we often see on TV
Things that are not to be seen in reality
Just keep up with that car
Pearl nursing home
What's this guy doing here?
It is necessary to investigate
I beat and beat
I hit you, beat you
Where are you running to?
Beat you, beat you, I beat you, beat you
Where do run to?
Stop, I'll beat you
I hit you, I hit you, I beat you
Wait a minute
I don't know who you are
I don't know why you hit me
But you beat me again I will fight back
If I hadn't stopped you in time
Your conspiracy will have succeeded
You oppress people. Misgovernment makes people rebel
People have to turn their backs
Only Zorro, that's our hero
I cannot understand you
Why are you here?
I followed you
Are you sick?
You be careful
The old grandmother is as mad as a mad dog
running to bite
Shut your big mouth
Grandma, are you all right?
Grandma..
She hit me
Grandma began this kind of symptom a few years ago
She is sober sometimes
But most of the time
There is no difference between reality and fantasy
You come and see her every week
I never saw it in you
Deep filial piety
What's this?
Zorro, a very classic movie
You can't have never seen it
Is it nice?
You don't see him as a governor
Silly girl
In fact, he is a hero
He has deserted his beloved girl
Riding his horse Bordeaux
He's called Zorro everywhere
He took to chivalry
So touched!
So handsome!
Deeply touched!
So moving!
Who are you?
Spy at tower
No, grandma
Grandma
This technique
Dan Yi
Grandma recognized me
Dan Yi, why don't you talk to your dad
if he doesn't want to take
care of me?
Just leave him alone
You see, put me in this place
Join the gang every day
I'm not happy, you know?
I can rent out for myself
I can make money by myself
I can support myself
I won't give him any trouble
Do you know?
OK
Did you hear?
Grandma, please do not talk nonsense
How is what I have said, nonsense?
My great grandson
I'm sober now
How do you fold your clothes?
I'll teach you
Fold up
Why are you so stupid?
The first step is wrong
Do this
Then fold it up
Why are you so stupid?
You grew up together with Dan Yi, right?
You two are still classmates?
How many people are there in your family?
Are your parents well to do?
What kind of house do you live in?
Commercial housing or low-cost housing ah?
How about mom and dad's income?
What do they do?
Is it a civil servant or a business man?
You said just now
You grew up with our family, Dan Yi
And now with he's in school with you
as classmate?
Right
Nonsense
Really!
You're not afraid of me, are you?
Here's something for you to see
Do you fear me now?
Then tell me the truth
How's your family doing?
Especially good
That's good
Then what do your parents do?
Are they blue collar or white collar workers?
They are public servants of the state
Or the average wage earners?
Why do you want to ...
No, I don't think so
I told you to try my best
Saves you from talking nonsense
What kind of house do you live in?
Do you rent it or do you buy it?
Is this a bank mortgage?
Or a lump sum payment?
Can't tell it. Cheat.
I don't like you
You say you are doing well now?
Yeah
Can you pass?
Pass
You can't pass the exam
Where is light passing?
You know what?
Our family, Dan Yi, ever since he was small
He is the lord in school
From when he was small till now
He has been the class monitor, okay?
He is not the monitor
That's impossible
Who's the monitor then?
I am
You are the monitor?
Right
Honest confession -
How did you do at school?
Very good
Very good?
Especially good
Can you pass each grade exam?
Pass
Pass?
The light and the grid, and our family, Dan
The difference is not ten, eight Street
Do you know if our family is happy?
The leading lord in kindergarten
Now in the class or the largest department
Lord of the squad
I'm the monitor
Now it's me. I'm the monitor
You are the monitor
Yeah
Nonsense
No, I did not tell you much
How could you be?
Because I'm stronger than your grandson
Come in
Doctor, how's my grandmother doing now?
It's hard for us, too
You know, the old lady often has delusions
Our whole hospital is in general turmoil
She was bruised and scorched by flames
Doctor, I know the state of my grandmother too
Sometimes the brain doesn't work
but sometimes, she is sober too
Do you get it?
When is she sober?
Better not sober up
I said that Yang Yang
You run here every day
What does that mean?
Running around and around
You have to wear goggles
This ditch is like our home
That donkey grinds
Running round and round
How tiring!
Don't you just want to live a few more years?
What can you live and do?
It's not running around and around
Why don't you run around Yang?
Me too. I'll just tell you a few words
It's boring
You never joke
Lao Li!
You see that Huang
She doesn't know what to think
At her age
She bought a pink coat
Came a pink flower
After that?
She bought a green sweater
More soil and more soil
I wouldn't have done that anyway
Others just give me these
I'm not at home
I don't think you're so old
Zhao
Zhao Zhao Zhao
Sit, sit, sit
I know your brain doesn't work
But here's a letter
Zorro was important hero
He represents the safety of the people
Here you are, keep watch
Someone's coming to connect with you in a minute
I'm busy
Never go!
Yes, it's difficult for us, too
How could there be such a grandmother?
Do what you want
Regardless of other people's feeling
It's hard to make friends
Look at what I do
Have a face to say
Eat it
I'll eat first
Eat with your elders
You haven't moved your chopsticks yet, so you dare move your chopsticks
The elders are present
One who is hungry must endure
Where can you eat first?
No etiquette
Sit and sit. Straight waist
The honorable ones have honor
Eat to have the appearance of eating, do you understand or not?
Eat if you like
How do you use these chopsticks?
No one in your family taught you, did you?
Take it well
Such a big girl!
Eat vegetables first, know or do not know. Do not start with meat
You see, you see
You see what you eat like that
Are you a piggy?
Hang up
Don't be hungry like a hungry prisoner just released
Do you even know how to keep your body decent and dignified?
Where do you put your hands? Where do you put them?
The waist is falling again
Don't eat meat alone
Listen, these are vegetables
Vitamin C
Vitamin ABCDEFG, all up to W
What nutrients are there?
Little girl
How did they raise her at home?
Look at you
How you make sounds with mouth while eating
Like a pig
That's the sound of pigs eating
You're a girl
Who wants a girl like this?
No one is willing to accept such a daughter-in-law
I'm full
Finish eating
No waste of grain. Eat well
OK, look, you're eating well
Finish up all these vegetables
Dan Yi!
Yeah, grandma
Have you heard?
Uncle Wang, his family, Xiao Zi
That's only three months since he got married
Got depression
Jumped down from the sixth floor
I heard that it was because of his unfaithful wife
What else?
Uncle yuan, the eldest son of their family
University Graduate
As a result, the daughter-in-law failed to find a good one
He's not dead
His mother died of pesticide poisoning
You see what this is all about, really
What do you want to say, grandma?
I just wanted to talk to you
The wrong partner will ruin a man forever
I don't like it, Dan Yi
Grandma just wanted to caution you
Finding wrong partner means regret forever
What's this? No, I lost it.
How dare you throw my things?
Oh, I see
You just came to the baby in my box. Is it?
What's this?
Let me talk to you
You can't throw it out of my box, as long as I still have one last breath remaining
Grandma!
I don't have a grandmother. I don't have one.              Calm down
Calm down
I tell you
This is very painful, do you know?
You're stupid or normal, I don't know
I told you
If you hit me again, I will
Calm down Calm down
Good
How could you be with her?
You're on her side
You're facing her
Since you all said I was crazy, I'm crazy
You are all spies
Get out of here!
Get out of here, get out of here, get out of here
Grandma!
I really don't know why
I'm such a lovely girl
Why am I hated by your grandma?
I do not know either
My grandma is very friendly to young people
I  do not know why she hates you
Because she didn't see my lovely side
I'm going to see her now
Wait a minute
You should stop looking for her
I'm going to get some medicine for my grandmother now
Come back later, let's go back together
What's wrong with me?
I'm cute
Ye Muxi, are you lovely?
I think I'm cute
That's right
Doctor
Do you think I'm cute?
Yes, you're lovely
Yes!! Take it, take it
I'm going to find Liao Danyi now
Grandma
Dear
May the letters remind you of me
Although we are separated by the trials of a long journey
But I'm reading your letters all the time
March thirteen is our wedding anniversary
We were one of the few couples who held western style
weddings in those days
I will always remember
That day, you looked so beautiful in your wedding dress
March thirteen
Isn't that today?
How did the patient come here?
She came here so suddenly today
Hurry up and deal with it
Liao granny, you're dressed here
Lifted the bed sheets alone
Shall we go back for an injection?
An injection!
Don't play, don't play
It's okay, no problem
Go back to get the injection, okay?
I'm serious
An injection!
It's a small injection
Don't play, don't play
It's okay, no problem
Grandma
Sorry for being late.
What are you doing here?
These my flowers to her
But I didn't get to buy flowers
So use this pot instead
Today is my grandma's wedding anniversary
Give her some wedding photos
How did she come out dressed in bed sheets?
Great
No, it's a fashionable wedding dress
How can you call this just 'bed sheets'?
Nice!
Good looking!
It feels nice to look good
Nice!
Isn't something wrong with that?
No, I don't see anything
But the granny with the sheets on her face
Grandma
So beautiful
Look
Grandma, let's go
You're Zorro
Yes
I am Zorro
I'm sorry I kept myself hidden from you
Why do you lie to me every time?
What are you doing?
Deceive me less
You do it every time
You cheat me, cheat me, cheat me
You die, liar, liar!