[ Class is over in three minutes ]
The bell is about to ring in...
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
[ Class is over ]
Why?!!
Why the bell doesn't ring?
Time's up already.
Teacher didn't realize that?
Monitor, I hear the bell rings.
Leave with other classmates.
What did he say? I can't hear him.
My ears are bombed to deaf.
Monitor, the bell has rung!
I didn't hear that!
Did you hear that?
Did the bell ring?
I didn't hear that.
Anyone else heard that?
Monitor, we all listen to you all the time.
This time, please listen to me.
Leave with other brothers.
Or the next class will begin.
Speak louder.
Monitor, he said that the bell really had rung!
If you don't leave now, the next class will begin!
Liao Danyi
You're Commissary in charge of studies.
Tell me.
Did you hear the bell?
No, I didn't.
Liao Danyi, you bastard!
You're gonna kill us!
I didn't hear that, either.
How dare you!
Whoever acts recklessly, I'll kill him!
Xue Xiaodong!
Everyone here attend class like you do!
Don't act like some hero here!
Cheng Ling... Cheng Ling just wants to delay
a few minutes of our break.
Cheng Ling.
Take him away.
Leave a place for me beside him.
Whoever heard the bell may leave.
I won't stop you.
Those who didn't,
come with me.
Go carry bombs.
I felt that.
I felt that the next class is gonna begin.
The bell will not ring.
Shanqi...
Xiaodong...
Huang Nan, Huang Yi.
Shen Wei.
Cheng Ling.
My brothers left just like this.
And I'm gonna see them soon.
I think I can hear...
That bell rings silvery when class is over.
I can see our classmates' happy faces.
That moment is so wonderful, so pure.
Ye Muxi. Monitor.
Sorry.
I think I was wrong about you.
I always think you're a secondary high school student.
Once the teacher delays to dismiss,
you'll shout and make a fuss.
Or even run out of the classroom as a slacker.
But ever since you became the monitor,
you really have changed a lot.
I'm proud of you!
I'm the monitor.
I should stay here even if others don't.
It's been seven minutes.
Sorry, I didn't hear the bell.
So, now class is over.
But, no need to stand up.
Okay. Class is over.
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
Class is over!
We can go out now! We can go out!
Guys, that...
Let's begin the class three minutes earlier.
We...
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
Why?
Why?!!!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 03
Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong!
My god, why so many people?
Xue Xiaodong goes to a reality show in the weekend.
It's said on websites that he'll pass by here.
Then this happens.
Don't panic. Listen to me.
We have limited guards in our school.
And we can't play rough to drive them away.
But try our best to mediate.
As... As the new president of the Student Union,
I gotta try my best to solve this problem.
Make sure our students won't be stopped outside the school gate!
So sleepy.
I'm tired, too.
I can tell that.
Hurry. Hurry.
Pretend that I've told you a funny joke.
Why... Why?
That doesn't matter. Hurry, right now.
Hi.
He smiles to me. He smiles to me!
Can we take a picture?
Thank you. Okay.
A few days ago, on the honors day,
he's sung songs, super handsome!
Two days ago,
he didn't come to attend class because of the concert.
Today's his first day at school.
I see.
In fact, listen,
many people say, although our class is not some key class,
it's pretty lucky to be in the same class
with two princes charming.
Another prince charming, who's he?
Liao Danyi.
Wait.
Are you kidding me?
Liao Danyi?
Anything wrong with that?
Liao Danyi is handsome and good at studying.
The most important thing is,
he gives out an intellectual aura.
He's very popular among girls.
How could you guys think he's a prince charming?
Are you blind? Or I'm blind? Or the world is blind?
Who's blind?
This must be my spot.
Hi.
Hi, I'm Ye Muxi.
Hi, I'm Xue Xiaodong.
Hi, I'm Zhu Shanqi. We've met before.
Well, I've something to discuss with you.
About your fans...
Sorry, I've told them on Facebook.
They say they won't come again.
That's okay. I just...
Anything I can help you with, Ye Muxi?
Have I seen you on TV?
Recently I always show up on TV and websites.
You should have seen me a lot.
Not recently. Maybe in the past...
Your look and the way you talk...
You... Have you been on TV in your childhood?
No, I haven't.
I think you get a wrong person.
But I really feel that you look so familiar.
It has something to do with hula hoop and the stuff...
I said no. I haven't.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
Sister Annie, did you hear that?
Xiaodong, rest easy.
I've heard that.
We'll start the operation right now.
Get all people ready!
Release first-class red alarm!
Quiet. Attentive.
Most efficient.
This is the unique learning vibe of Class One.
Of course.
Class One is the best class in Maple Leaf Middle School.
Even between classes, we're preparing for study.
No one shouts or makes noise in the corridor.
As for other classrooms,
everyone has already run away.
Wait.
This attentive feel...
How could anyone who's not a student of Class One
give out such an attentive learning force between classes?
Who's this guy?
To sum it up.
Moonlight In The Lotus Pond, its main idea is...
Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong!
Its main idea is...
Brother Xiaodong! Brother Xiaodong! Xiaodong Oppa!
So, Xiaodong Oppa's main idea...
Xue Xiaodong's fans disturb classes.
Please go solve it.
Mr. Wu...
You can tell him yourself directly.
Me?
I'm your teacher!
I've lots of things to do every day.
Look, how busy I am!
Here, gimme.
Pass it to me.
Xue Xiaodong.
This is...
This is the theme song of my new album.
I sang it to you on impulse.
Do you like it?
On impulse?
What about the lamplight and dancing...
Those don't matter.
What matters is, please remember who I am,
as an idol, okay?
I must have seen you somewhere!
Not now. But in the past.
Something to do with hula hoop.
Stop dancing!
Where are you going? This...
Damn it. The plan didn't work out?
All staffs retreat right now.
Get ready for Plan B.
Excuse me, girls.
Xiaodong!
Xiaodong, I wanted to ask you this a long time ago?
Can I take a picture with you?
Can I friend you on Facebook and @ you?
Yes. Yes. You bet.
This is a snack I made by myself.
Hope you guys love it.
My first work.
Snack?
Xiaodong, you're really...
Really... Sweet.
I can make you more next time if you love it.
And, two tickets to my concert.
You can come with your friend.
Xiaodong, you're so nice!
Ye Muxi, I'm here for you.
Me?
Have time for an afternoon tea?
Yes.
I'll wait upstairs, then.
What's the matter?
I don't know, either.
You're sure that you don't know?
It's okay, then.
Tell me if there's anything coming out.
What... What were you gonna do with the scissors?
Eyebrow trimming.
Looks so delicious.
Tastes like happiness.
Shanqi, why are you also here?
I heard you called her.
I felt very happy, too.
So I came as well.
Sit.
Does it sound good, Ye Muxi?
Yes. Yes. Supper good!
Not bad.
So, have any impression on me now?
The impression was very profound in the first place.
So you haven't seen me on TV, get it?
I must have seen you!
I almost remember that!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
It must have something to do with hula hoop.
Can't you just forget that?!
Can't remember the way I look right now?
Or I don't look good enough right now?
Can you remember me?
For my entire life.
My entire life.
It... It still has something to do with hula hoop.
So handsome even he's mad.
Miss Xinyi, what are you looking at?
Transcripts of simulative high school entrance exams.
Look, in the three exams,
there's always one doing better than me.
But he's not in our class.
Look, this student.
Liao Danyi.
I know this idiot.
It's said that he missed an exam.
So, now he's in the worst Class Ten.
In this case, he can make up for the missed exam.
Why he didn't?
I don't know the details.
But isn't it good in this way, Miss Xinyi?
You'll always be number one in our class.
What do you know?
Only the most excellent ones get together,
can we be motivated to make progress.
Yes.
Liao Danyi...
Ye Muxi.
You're gonna sing and dance again?
You wanna know where you've seen me, right?
Come with me.
To where?
The auditorium.
Xue Xiaodong, why did you bring me here?
I've had enough of this feeling.
What feels worse than being shot is living at gunpoint.
You keep recalling where you've seen me, right?
Look this.
Three circles left. Three circles right.
Shake your neck. Shake your butt.
I got it!
You're that hula hoop fat boy!
Yes, I'm the hula hoop fat boy.
Now you're satisfied?
Go tell everyone.
Why should I tell everyone?
So you wanna threaten me with that?
Listen, you wish!
I have a company and many bodyguards.
Anyway, if you can't forget my black past,
you'll never leave this place.
I... How could I forget that?
They all say that I'm fat.
From now on, they'll never laugh at me.
Hurry.
Right.
That fat boy in the ad is Xiaodong.
No one knows how much little Xiaodong suffers
after that ad goes out.
He signs the contract with us on only one condition.
To erase the existence of that ad completely.
Lucky that the broadcast range of that ad isn't broad.
Now you can't see the ad on any platform.
But god knows,
in this big world,
there's someone
who can remember him as that fat boy!
You can't forget my black past, right?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna help you.
Help you forget it.
Don't worry. As long as this hammer...
This memory-erasing device hits you.
It'll end quick.
You... You said it's a hammer!
Calm down. Calm down.
-Very quick.
-Calm down!
Forget the trouble.
Don't...
Forget... Forget all of this.
Forget! Forget!
All departments, attention.
Make sure Plan B works out!
You won't talk or let me go.
What on earth do you want?
I don't know, either.
Why you care about such things so much?
Do you know how much I've suffered
to get rid of my fat?
Up to now, I seldom eat meat.
But do a lot of physical training every day.
Because I know,
my appearance is everything I have.
Once I lose it,
these fans around me
will leave me. No one will stay.
You don't know how hard it is to keep perfect.
You don't know.
Nor you can understand feelings of the one
being peculiar and mocked by the rest of people.
Well, to be an idol is not what you want?
I don't know.
My original plan is
to make them stop laughing at me.
So you want the whole world to like you?
How is that possible?
Yes, impossible.
One person not into you,
and one thousand people not into you,
what's the difference?
Listen,
there's someone who doesn't like me since childhood.
But, I don't care about him.
So,
you live for yourself, not for any other people.
So live up to it.
And, here's my little secret.
Actually I'm also your fans.
Really?
You like listening to my songs?
No! I mean, that ad!
I really like it!
Every time I practiced back in childhood,
I would swing back and forth like you did in the hula hoop.
Singing and dancing.
Sis Annie, Xue Xiaodong is in the auditorium.
Xiaodong, don't do any stupid things.
Hurry up!
Xiaodong, don't! Calm down!
Little girl, come and talk with me if you have any problem!
Your friend is a little weird.
I'm leaving first.
Sis Annie, let her go.
Sis Annie.
What's up?
So I really enjoy being an idol.
Liao Danyi.
You're...
I'm Guan Xinyi, the monitor of Class One.
Also the new president of the Student Union.
Maple Leaf Middle School divides classes by students' scores.
The more scores you get, the better class you have.
So, would you like to join Class One?
[ Maple Leaf High School Class Transfer Application ]