There's a bubble in the screen protector.
So annoying!
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze.
God. My god.
That...that...that...
How could he use such a phone! The screen is smashed!
God! What kind of person he is?!
He is so strange.
I'll follow him.
Followed him here.
This is...
This restaurant has only one star?
And he just walked in?
Didn't he check the comments first?
I'll go and see.
Must be awful.
One star restaurant.
Don't let anyone see me in here.
So humiliating.
I didn't order.
We only have this kind of noodles.
Why it tastes so delicious?
- I got soup on my skirt.
- May I ask, how can I get to Rd. Huaxin ?
Rd. Huaxin?
That direction.
And turn left.
Oh my god!
It's all over his shirt!
Cool shirt.
She thinks it's cool?
So awful!
What is he doing?
To correct the character?
Why he is so serious about this?
What the hell is he?!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 14
Okay.
Review your lessons.
How could they be like this?!
Students.
How could you be like this?!
You're so great!
You're awesome!
This essay is great!
It's so touching, I almost cried.
Yesterday, we learned the poem
Saying Good-bye to Cambridge Again.
It was written in 1928.
That year,
Senior Zhimo revisited that place.
Your question is very good.
Why Senior Zhimo?
To be honest, I really don't want to bring it up.
Your teacher, I graduated from Cambridge 99th session.
Majored in classical literature.
So at some point.
Senior Zhimo and I are schoolmates.
So I called him Shige (Senior Schoolmates).
But, me and him
we're different on one thing.
I got to Cambridge because I made the grade.
But Zhimo.
He just studied in there.
Do you know what does that mean?
He is an exchange student.
Exchange student!
No more of that.
Among all the essays I told you to write yesterday.
Xiong Tiancheng's essay is the best!
Xiong Tiancheng.
Xiong Tiancheng. Are you here?
Super bad luck.
Xiong Tiancheng.
Wu Sir.
Why... Why bother keep calling?
So that is the legendary....
Yes, he is the legendary junk King,
who is the source of all the pollution of Class Ten.
And no one has ever seen him.
No more Cambridge after Xu Zhimo left.
I step away softly,
just as I came here quietly .
I wave gently ,
sighing goodbye to the western sky.
Cambridge is still there.
The water is still running.
But after the poet left,
The Cambridge is lost.
No one can ever be like him
to read the sensitive Cambridge romantically.
Including every beautiful water grass in Cambridge.
Every silent summer insect.
That is the lost Cambridge.
Wu Sir.
He is one of the talented students in our class.
I believe you see it too.
He is indeed a talent.
But him,
He is always alone.
Doesn't like to talk to people.
In the ancient times, Liu Bei visited Zhuge Liang three times.
Today, Wonder Girl Ye will invite him for me.
To be the Chinese Representative.
Exactly!
They're Little Wilde and Little Maugham.
My pet.
Please don't hurt them.
Sorry.
Such a special place in the classroom.
I got the highest score of Chinese examination
back in junior high school.
The only condition to recruit me in this school
is to give me such a space to make a studio.
I'm quite satisfied.
Studio?
[Xiong Tiancheng Literature Studio]
Xiong Tiancheng,
I came to you today...
What kind of essay do you want?
No, no, no.
I'm not here to ask you to write anything.
I'm here to ask you
to be
our
Chinese representative!
Sorry, I'm very busy.
I have no time for idlers.
Leave.
O-kay.
So...
You two and Xiong Tiancheng were once
classmates in junior high school?
At that time,
he is the famous Dirty King in our school.
There's one time, during sweep-up.
We found a banana in his drawer
which has been there for a year!
Right. Right.
And you know what.
Let me tell you.
At the beginning day of Grade One in junior high school.
I saw Xiong Tiancheng holding a rice roll.
You know what?
They day we graduated from Grade Three
I found that rice roll in his drawer again!
My god!
How was he and your classmates getting along?
We didn't talk much with him.
Because he was always alone.
And there's one time,
In parents' meeting.
His father scolded him in front of everyone.
That was very harsh!
Since that, he talked even less.
Maybe he thinks it's too embarrassing.
Your essay has no sense of beauty.
Your pen.
I'll help you rewrite it.
Really?
Is that gonna be expensive?
I don't have much.
Don't worry, it's for free.
Okay, thank you.
You can leave now.
You've got all the best part.
So schemed.
Are we really gonna talk about this?
Look at yourself!
The meat is all on your side.
Can't believe it.
My little sister.
She is a good girl.
But just eats too much.
Look at you. I mean.
What? What? What?
Can't bear it?
So touching.
It's so nice.
Reminding me of the time when you were young.
You were just this little.
And I raised you up.
Do you know why you grow faster than the others?
Let me tell you.
Because you eat a lot. Quite a lot!
What is that smell?
Something smelled a bit off.
I must apologize to you.
I didn't create a perfect environment for your dinner.
My bad.
No, it's not.
I went to talk a weird student.
He is quite messy.
He has a strong smell.
Seems now my clothes has got that smell too.
How messy he is to get that smell?
Haven't showered for years?
Stay away from him.
Don't get some disease.
But although he is dirty, he is very talented.
So I wanna recruit him as one of our class committee.
I have an idea.
What is this?
Xiong Tiancheng?
Shadow stealer?
Look at his name. Look.
As a man who has the same job
I have to say.
It's not good enough.
He must be a writer online.
A newbie, right?
You knew what was my name back then?
Do you still remember?
A secret man.
Is that good?
A secret....
That's the point.
Why?
Cause it's unpredictable.
When it's unpredictable, they'll be curious.
Right?
You brat.
Always staying at home.
Xiong Tiancheng
Let me see what can you write?
The girl woke up in a wasted place.
There's a tavern in front of her.
The tenants are all some weirdos.
Like crazy scientist.
Gang boss.
Dead waitress.
Strange twins.
A girl who lost her memory.
And a lonely scriptwriter.
All kinds of clients they are seeing in the tavern.
All things begin in here.
And end in here.
This story is called Mozhan.
Do you like it?
Always surfing online.
You brat.
Dad, knock before you enter.
Do I need to knock? I'm your dad.
You don't need privacy in front of me.
Go, get me some beer.
Dad.
I had a fever.
Go now!
Wait a second.
Let me get a coat.
Sick leave?
What shall we do?
Same as usual. Home visit.
Come back, come back.
Although my teaching method is free-ranging,
I can be active sometimes.
How about this.
I'll do the home visit.
You go do your job. go.
Why're you looking at me like this?
-You, being serious.
-Is so weird.
Can't get used to it.
Am I that casual?
I don't care.
Who will fall in love with whom.
- Morning, Wu sir
- Morning.
Wu Sir, please sit.
This time, I also bring you a special gift.
What is that?
This is a novel wrote by Xiong Tiancheng.
I printed it out.
I hope you can read it sometime.
Okay.
I remember someone said.
In the history, nothing is real except the names.
While in the novel,
Everything is real except the names.
The protagonist in Xiong Tiancheng's novel
has a really bad relationship with his father.
In the novel it's like
it is the same whether his father exists or not.
Mr. Xiong. What I want to say is.
As his parent,
you're the first teacher he has.
Your personality, your habits.
Will play an important role in his life.
Xiong Tiancheng is a very talented boy.
I hope he can grow up healthily.
Mr. Xiong
I hope as his parent,
you can create a good environment for him.
I think you know better than us
about his needs.
Xiong Tiancheng.
Why do you hate cleaning?
Clean or not.
No one will care.
Then what's the meaning of it?
Why do you like to help others to write essays?
You can't get anything.
I...
I just want to be valued.
By you guys.
By everyone.
I'm done being invisible.
You know what?
The one I care the most
never cares about me.
But I do.
Really?
Xiong Tiancheng. I'll change you.
So let me make a plan to change you.
Dad.
Since you like Wuxia novels so much.
Let's play a game to find the hidden treasures.
About the clue.
You must check these places in proper order.
Remember the code.
I'm here to meet wonder girl Yezi.
I... I'm here....
This is...
Congrats.
You've finished the first pass of the game.
You must haven't cut your hair for a year.
It's easy to cause dandruff.
Please go to the next station.
I've been waiting for you.
Here, check out this one.
There're a lot of other kinds here.
This one is nice also.
Here, try this one.
Clear?
That's how do I look?
After we tried many times.
Finally we found a pair of glasses which suits you the best.
Contact lenses.
So I have wasted so much tries.
Next station.
Congrats. You've finished the second pass.
I heard you haven't changed your glasses for a long time.
Use your new glasses to see the world.
Please go to the next station.
Hello.
Hello, I...
[How is that?]
[Shadow Stealer]
[How do you feel about your new appearance?]
[Thank you for your game, mystery man]
[No, Big boss.]
Dad.
Hello, everyone. I'm Xiong Tiancheng.
There're all kinds of riddles in this world.
For example.
After death,
Is there another world?
Are humankind the only living creature in the universe?
Does the proton ever decay?
Silicon substrate creature, does it really exist?
Hello, everyone, I'm Huang Nan.
Hello, everyone, I'm Huang Yi.
There're many puzzles in the world waiting for us to solve them.
For example.
Why my bedroom is always so messy?
Why my partners always get themselves killed?
Why I can't hand in my homework in time?
What's the biological foundation of the sense?
How does our brain build the moral principles?
Ofo bike and Mobike, which one has more bikes?
Why the second eight weeks are always
faster than the first eight weeks?
Why the villain always has so many lines?
How many years can we extend the human life?
What really causes the loneliness disease?
We're losing hair everyday,
when will we become bold?
Why time is not like the other dimensionalties?
Political liberty and economic freedom are really related?
Why blow it first before you throw the paper plane?
Does it have scientific basis or it's just a custom?
What is the black hole?
When will we invent the medicine to cure HIV?
Why our Chemistry teacher Liang always makes so many mistakes?
Students?
Why there's always voices when I speak?
Please shut my mouth!
Do you believe I'll slap you out with my feet?
I strength so much took to teach you.
Now, everyone.
Turn your book to 120 Yuan.
We need to solve these puzzles.
These puzzles are the ones we need to solve.