# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 04
This class we do a one thousand meters in class practice.
The result won't be recorded.
But I want all of you to take it seriously as well.
Ready!
Why couldn't I defeat Sun Bin with Arthur yesterday?
You're a newbie.
Brothers will cover you.
Really?
Listen, I'll teach you some basic rules.
Arthur is a strong half flesh fighter.
How can you use the Hat skill?
You need to use the Time Wand!
Like Guan Yu, he needs to wear six pair of shoes.
Otherwise, he won't be fast enough!
Wait, wait, slow down.
I'll write it down.
You're eating snacks?
Thanks.
Shanqi, are you feeling better?
Teacher, I'm still a little dizzy.
Rest well.
Thank you, teacher.
Follow me, adjust your breath.
This is my strong point.
Just wait to eat the dirt behind me.
Come on, ready.
One. Two.
Xiaodong. Practicing?
No, Shanqi.
Xue Xiaodong!
I can't run any longer.
I'm that close to win you.
I'm a circle ahead of you.
I'm not myself today. Next time.
Do you hear me?
The heavenly god overpowers the tiger on the ground
The holy tower suffocates the ghost of the river.
Are you working alone before?
Why are you blushing?
My spirits soared.
Why turned yellow?
Why turned green?
I'm hungry!
Let's eat!
Wonder girl Yezi,
it's not your first time to eat this delicious hotpot.
Where's your table manners?
I don't know why.
Recently, I always feel so hungry.
Can't hear you.
Can't have enough.
No problem.
I finished my work early this afternoon.
I found this hotpot restaurant especially for you.
I hope you can be like this everyday.
Owner, five more dishes of meat.
Look. It's delicious.
I love spicy strip. Try one.
Give me one.
Not you.
Monitor.
Yes, anything?
Shoot or leave me alone.
You guys are unbelievable.
Firstly.
Efficiency values in everything.
We're here for the class committee meeting.
Not for a picnic.
Secondly?
Xue Xiaodong. What're you doing?
If you want to have a live concert.
Leave school.
Here's our classroom.
A live concert?
Flowers have told me...
Shut up.
Sit down.
We're at school.
Where we learn things.
Please show some respect.
Sorry.
Give me one more.
And Huang Nan, Huang yi.
You two, don't mess around.
Never seen you so positive when we hand over the homework.
-Delicious?
-And you two.
What're you two gossiping about?
We're eating.
Eating?
Those junk food you eat
decide your chatting must be boring.
Spicy strip is not junk food!
Shut up!
Cheng Ling. What're you doing?
Daydreaming.
You go on.
Sweet dreams. No one would miss it.
Finally we welcome....
Enough!
I'm gonna go home to review my lessons.
Bye.
What's wrong?
Our class committee is so casual, which means
I have done a good job as a monitor.
We have no problems.
Everything is just great.
Right!
Shut up!
Great?
You have no organization and discipline.
As a monitor,
You're still unbuttoned.
I like it that way.
Freestyle, you know?
I think you just got fat.
Are you kidding me?
Who? Who got fat?
I'll show you.
Are you feeling alright? Too tight?
Uncomfortable, right?
I...
Still can't button it.
See?
I can not only button it.
Also with chest out. Danyi.
Who did that?
It's her.
It's her big chest!
Lad Danyi, you're finally here.
Come, come. Sit, sit down.
Make yourself at home.
Danyi.
The reason I invite you to dinner
Cause I need to ask you a favor.
Shoot.
To be honest.
My sweet Yezi,
She is a sweet girl.
But she can be so careless sometime.
So please take good care of her at school.
Thank you a lot.
She is young. Still a kid.
Today.
I will use this tea to toast to you.
Take good care of Yezi.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Okay.
You...I...I...
Him? Take care of me?
He is always tag along.
So annoying.
Tag along?
I'm way ahead of you when I run.
And you've gain some weight recently.
You can tag along.
You....you...you...
You have only won me once.
Don't take it for granted.
I didn't run so hard that time.
And recently, you...
Me what? What?
Got fat.
Yezi, Yezi, Yezi. Have some meat.
Yezi is great! Have some meat.
Who got fat?
Say it again!
You got fat! Why can't you admit it?
Can't you face the reality?
I'm a lady. Fat?
- Are you afraid? Say it again!
- You got fat. You got fat. You got fat!
I really got fat.
I must lose some weight.
Three hundred sit-ups.
I can't...
Any good idea?
That's awesome.
Say it gently. Gently!
Well, I don't know if I should say it or not.
Shoot.
You're not a normal girl.
I know.
But I like it. Continue.
Menci said,
When Heaven is about to place a great responsibility on someone.
He will frustrate the one,
give him hard work.
make him starve.
but die in peace.
Makes perfect sense.
I ate it up!
Calm down.
We have more snacks in storage.
Spare me! Spare me!
First, be sharp and wise.
Just now, I found a secret master plan.
Here it is.
Look!
That man in the book is so strong!
This exercise is amazing!
It's true.
Here, here.
Looks great.
Look, it's invincible!
Look.
I ate it up again.
Wonder girl, relax.
We have more here.
Method of losing weight.
Can't find any.
Forget it.
Anyone I know?
Fat guy, who needs to lose some weight.
Who was once very fat.
Xiaodong.
Can you do me a favor?
What is that?
Can you help me to lose some weight?
I see.
Piece of cake. Piece of cake.
But monitor, didn't you say
you are gonna buy me some soda water?
Why are you still eating chips yourself?
Here's the thing.
We started to practice today.
We just ran a big circle.
Then I started to feel hungry.
I just wanted to replenish energy before we start.
We have run so far. So starving.
But I can only afford this.
Don't worry, I will treat you a big feast for helping me.
It's okay. I'm fine.
Chips have too much calorie.
I barely eat it.
A big feast is not necessary.
As an idol I must keep my figure looking good.
Don't worry. Monitor.
Your concern is my concern.
Since you kept my secret.
I will return this favor to you.
It's nothing.
Let's begin.
Then, will you do as what I say?
Repeat after me.
Lose weight or lose life!
Louder!
Good. How does that feel?
Good. Inspired.
Now throw your chips.
But... But I haven't eaten it up.
I'll throw it later.
Do you know how much calorie that has?
About 11.2 g Carbohydrate
About 24.1g Protein
About 30.8g Fat
So those add up
508cal.
A normal girl's daily calorie intake is 1014cal.
You have already got a half.
Are you sure you want to continue?
No.
Are you gonna eat this anymore?
I'm your calorimeter.
So if you want to lose some weight.
You must listen to me.
Say goodbye to junk food.
Junk food.
Goodbye.
Ye Muxi. What're you doing here?
Want some spicy strip?
Yes.
Are you ready? Ye Muxi?
I'm ready.
Okay.
First group.
Watch me.
One.
Two.
Three.
So easy!
You go.
Twenty.
Twenty?
A hundred!
Come on! Burn fat!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five.
Go down.
Ninety-five to go. Six.
Six.
Let's call it a day.
It has burnt.
Twenty at a time will only get it started.
No stop.
Seven!
Seven...
Stand up. Again.
Seven will do you no good.
Has to be twenty.
Think about the chips you had eaten.
Eight...
You haven't used up those calorie yet.
Go down.
I can't.
No, no I can't.
Your bottom will get fatter if you sit down.
Wanna lose weight or not?
Stand up.
Xiaodong.
Boss Xiaodong.
Can we start it easy?
Then...
This... This is too much for me.
That was just a warm-up.
We're about to begin now.
I'll teach you three moves.
Three times for each.
Stand up.
Finish your warm-up.
Up.
Nine.
Aren't you a nice sweet guy? Why...
The second you mention "weight"
Nice Xiaodong will become bad Xiaodong.
There's no nice way in this.
Nine.
Up!
Down!
Go on.
Come on.
I can't!
Come on. Go!
No!
Okay. Good.
Come on. Come on.
Imagine, I'm your fat.
Your body fat.
- No.
- Come on. You can do it.
I'm yours.
Stop.
Thanks.
I'll run by your side. Follow me.
Let's go.
Come on.
1.5 km to the endline.
That's easy to say. You drag this.
Okay. Move.
Watch me. let's go.
It's easy.
Ye Muxi.
You have to build some muscle while you lose your weight.
If you want to lose some weight.
Then you must gain your muscle.
You can't run from strength training.
You ring me up at 5 a.m.
to tell me this?
Look. We only have 1.5km left.
Hang in there!
Ye Muxi.
Make me a milk tea.
Sit down.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
It's because of Xiaodong's training.
He is a real monster.
I don't think so.
He is like an angel to me.
No.
Once you mention "weight" to him,
he will be completely changed!
So freaking!
Stop torturing yourself, why lose weight?
No.
I made an oath. I did.
It's so humiliating. No.
But when my Xiaodong gets serious.
That look on his face is so charming.
I'm thinking if I shall join your weight loss training?
But I never get fat!
Forget it.
I'm gonna make a milk tea.
What's wrong?
My hands and feet hurt. Can't move.
Let's go have dinner.
What dinner?
Water?
Oatmeal?
Cookie?
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes and come.
Where are we going?
Just keep going.
No peep.
Okay. Three. Two. One!
I prepared you this wholesome hotpot.
For me?
It's the most touching thing ever happened to me!
I miss you so much.
Where's mutton? Chicken?
100g lettuce. 30 cal.
100g day lily. 50 cal.
100g swamp cabbage. 80 cal.
This big feast is only 310 cal!
Feel free to eat!
Any sauce?
Right.
I made this especially for you.
No salt. No spice.
Relax. Zero fat.
Let's eat!
Here, have more.
Try that sauce.
Is that nice?
Ye Muxi.
I heard you're ill?
Is that serious?
Look.
Can't even speak now.
In fact, these days.
I feel quite sorry for you.
Am I too hard?
I know I shouldn't train you like a boy.
But you know.
I did it for your good.
Every time when it comes to weight.
I am always very serious.
Very stubborn.
I think.
We can start a new plan.
Which will not affect your healthy.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'll leave first.
There's one more thing.
Still need to keep diet.
Bye then.
Did you bring that?
Don't ask me to bring you snacks.
Didn't you say you want to lose some weight?
You don't know how terrible he is!
He wouldn't let me eat.
Not even a piece of chocolate.
So terrifying!
Aren't you ill?
Who is ill? I'm fine.
So you were lying?
It's not what you think!
- I...I can explain!
- Your conscience won't hurt?
- I didn't...
- Stop saying!
No.
How can you do this to me?!
Your conscience won't hurt?!
No. It's not what you think!
Now, go tell your chocolate.
You're gonna leave it. You hate it!
Come here. Tell it!
Tell it.
You don't like it. You hate it!
You will leave it for good. Say it!
Say it!
I love it.
You love it?
One hundred upward leg swinging!
No!
Chocolate!
Wonder girl. Get up. Get up.
Get up and wash your face.
Student Xue is here waiting for you.
Hurry up.
I will wait you downstairs.
It's for you.
It's my secret nutritious breakfast.
Has lots of vitamin, plant fiber.
and lots of protein.
It will wake up your energy for a whole day!
Brother, it's for you.
There's also one for me?
Such a good lad. Good lad.
He has a bright future.
Thank you. I'll drink first.
Fresh!
Just one sip.
I feel I'm filled with energy.
If you like it, I'll make you another cup.
I'm good. Xue.
I appreciate it.
I feel I'm filled with energy.
And there's so much possibility in my life.
I've made my mind.
I will do more things for my country.
To devote myself to my country.
Although it's weekend.
But I decide to go to work!
Take care of my sister.
- Brother.
- Thank.
-Brother.
- Bye.
Brother, take me with you.
Devote myself! It's okay. It's okay.
Devote myself. Devote myself!
Come back.
Drink this. We have more training today.
Come on.
Five more.
Hurry. Up.
Up.
Come on.
You can do it.
I can't.
You can.
Hurry. Come on.
One more set.
I can't. I can't.
One more set. You can.
You can.
Can't get up.
Up. Up. Up. Up.
That sofa will drag you down.
You wanna lose weight or not.
I can't.
Get up. Don't get comfy.
You wanna be fat?
Up. Up. Up. Up.
Hurry, now!
I can't.
Up. Up. Up.
Now!
Enough!
Do you wanna watch your concert?
Concert?
Where?
DVD.
But we're doing fitness.
But I have spent a long time finding it.
And I want to watch it so badly.
You really wanna watch it?
Fifteen minutes then.
Yes!
Here, here, here.
Look, right?
It's very hard to find this.
Right? It took me a long time.
What do you want to drink?
Cold water.
Okay.
In your fridge.
Here.
Thanks.
This.
Never mind. Never mind.
Look, look.
Look at you. So handsome.
The way you shake your hair. Cool!
This move.
Is it hard?
I tried several days but just can't get it.
It's hard.
It took me a long time to learn it.
Look. You really worked hard.
These days.
These days are quite hard.
Always training to late night.
Exhausted, right?
Look, that move.
I think it's time for you to relax.
Of course you won't be fat.
Recently, my company got me all fully booked.
Right?
I should relax a little.
Right, relax.
I will teach you how to relax.
You?
Follow me.
Ease your mind.
Close your eyes. Lay back, slowly.
Lay back.
Right.
Breathe in.
All things are disappearing.
Follow the sound.