Ye Muxi, goddess!
Isn't this Ye Muxi?
My goddess!
That's monitor of Class Ten, Ye Muxi.
Ye Muxi.
So beautiful.
Monitor of Class Ten.
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
A man calls you.
Hello?
Yes, I am.
My duty. It's okay. It's okay.
Monitor Ye Muxi, from now on,
safety of the Earth will be our common job.
I feel very honored to work jointly with you.
Okay. Okay. World peace.
Bye. Bye.
Hello, what do you like to have?
Where's the menu?
Right, how much is it here?
You're so humorous.
You're the monitor of Class Ten?
Yes.
Everything here is free for monitors.
Well, one portion each.
Baby. Baby, turn your head.
Look at this beautiful sister beside us.
You'll also be a monitor in school, okay?
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
Yes. Yes. It's me, Yezi. A monitor, yes.
Everybody here.
My sister!
Ye Muxi!
[ My idol, Yezi ]
Get up! Get up! Get up!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 07
Bye, teacher!
Ye Muxi, stop!
Today's great great great golden chicken steak must be mine!
You wish. Friends can give in to anything but not this!
Xiaodong, what a coincidence!
Are you also going to buy chicken steak?
No. I'm being chased by fans.
My idol! My idol!
Finally I'm the first one here!
My great chicken steak...
[ Sold out ]
Why is it takes him so long?
Is he lost?
Why so late?
Here, take it. Eat.
Get out.
Okay. Okay.
Come, eat. Chicken steaks.
After she failed in the chicken steak race,
she didn't have lunch.
But kept doing this after she came back.
Just a chicken steak. Why so exaggerated?
Just a chicken steak?
Look, what nonsense are you talking about?
Our school's number one master hand,
Chef Zhou uses his secret recipe,
only fries ten great golden chicken steaks every day!
That outstanding flavor.
That shocking fragrance!
Why?
Why let me eat so delicious chicken steaks?!
Why I can't eat one today? Why?
I want chicken steaks.
Great chicken steaks. Family Bucket.
Family Bucket...
Damn it. She's crazy.
No! Can't let this happen any more.
We must change the current situation!
The qualified score is fifty minutes and fourteen seconds.
School record, three minutes and eight seconds.
So my goal is within three minutes.
Chicken steak thief!
What?
You're Cheng Ling, right?
Yes.
You're our monitor, Ye Muxi, right?
Anything I can help with?
Today, I'm gonna tell you a story.
Called a dinosaur before pears.
Long long time ago, in the Jurassic Period,
there was a dinosaur family.
One day,
they found a pile of pears in the forest.
The considerate little dinosaur chose the smallest one.
But the smallest one was not a pear.
But a Fruit of Life passed down from ancient times.
So the little dinosaur turned into a tyrannosaurus in a second.
So, since then, it knew to share.
I'm done.
What do you learn from this story?
Ye Muxi.
Actually I've heard of this story.
But it seems a little different from yours.
Anyway, it's not right for you
to have so many chicken steaks!
But... But...
But what?!
Tonight we gotta review lessons.
So the canteen is still open.
So,
I expect your performance.
Xinyi!
What's up?
I'm a student of Class Ten, Shen Wei.
Class Ten? What can I do for you?
I know you're not only Class One's monitor,
but also the president of the Student Union,
in charge of societies and funding.
I want to apply for a society.
A society?
Astrology Society?
Yes.
It's about fortune telling, horoscope and dream interpreting.
No way!
Why?
Our school is a famous school.
How could we have such superstitions?
So, president, you only believe what you see, right?
Flip this onto this desk.
Haven three, Earth four.
It's about to happen soon.
What's about to happen?
Your love.
It shows that your true love will appear soon.
The way he appears is, on a colorful cloud.
Coming to you in a very impactive manner.
A colorful cloud?
So my true love is the Money King?
But it says so.
This is feudalistic superstition, totally nonsense.
I want one, too.
Come here.
Miss Xinyi, actually such a society of Shen Wei
doesn't go against school rules.
And it's very popular now.
Really?
Okay. Since that,
Shen Wei,
if what you said comes true,
I will agree you to build such a society.
President.
Believe it. It might happen soon.
Liao Danyi, you're so kind.
It's okay, teacher. My duty to do this.
Still, thank you.
It's lucky to have you in Class Ten.
Huang Nan
Who allows you to play with the curtain of our school?
So what?!
Stop there!
Don't come here!
Let me go!
Your true love will appear soon.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Are you alright?
Now I finally can eat my chicken steaks...
Sorry.
[ Sold Out ]
Let's go eat the chicken steaks.
That's to say,
you're buying chicken steaks for them?
Yes.
You won't eat a single one?
Never mind.
That goes too far! Are you being bullied?
If you are, tell me.
I can stand out for you, trust me!
No need, monitor.
They're not bullying me.
We are friends.
I'm willing to do that.
Mr Wu
Danyi
I have something to talk with you.
I'm going to talk with you, too.
Mr Wu, you first.
Danyi
I know you're very excellent in study.
And very famous back in secondary school.
Even you missed out on an exam,
you still made it into our Maple Leaf Middle School.
That's awesome.
I'm flattered.
That's the fact.
But I did better than you back then.
Danyi, although our Class Ten is not as excellent as Class One,
which fosters many top students,
yet I want you to know,
strong people adapt to circumstances;
stronger people create circumstances.
I believe you can create an assiduous learning milieu for Class Ten.
Mr Wu, I know that.
I'll try my best to do whatever I can for my class.
Go for it.
Bye.
Bye, Mr Wu.
President.
What can I do for you?
Nothing special.
It's just, that prediction you made for me...
It came true, right?
No, it didn't.
I just want to ask you,
did you put a curse and that kind of stuff on me?
President, you don't believe such things, do you?
But, anyway, it came true, right?
No, it didn't.
It was just a coincidence.
Well, how about another try?
Okay. I'm not afraid of that.
What are you doing?
Rituals are very important. Very important.
Here it is. Here it is.
It says,
your true love will walk on a fire wheel
and bump into you passionately.
Are you kidding me?
You're sure that you're using the Book of Changes,
not the Apotheosizing Tales?
It says so.
[ Exploration Lab (1) ]
Hi, Mr Yan.
Hi.
More.
Now okay?
Come on, more. More.
Come on! Still too little.
This time, we must blow Director Yan out.
Into ashes.
He's coming. He's coming.
Why monitor of Class One?
No idea.
No. She'll be blown out, too.
No. No. I gotta save her.
A hero saves a beauty.
I'm going.
Mine. Mine.
Gimme.
-Me save her...
-Me...
-You...
-Me!
Class Ten of Grade One!
your true love will walk on a fire wheel
and bump into you passionately.
Sorry.
I'll explain it to you later.
Fire wheel?
Cheng Ling, you look very tired.
Shanqi.
That... That chicken steak thing.
I've thought about it.
Next time, I'll run faster
to buy chicken steaks for you and monitor, too.
Never mind.
In fact, there's one thing that I haven't figured out.
What's that?
It's just...
It seems that whoever tells you to buy chicken steaks,
you'll do it.
You never refuse anyone.
Would you like to hear me out?
Of course.
In fact I...
I'm not someone good at communicating.
And... But when I was in secondary school,
I realized if I ran errands for the others,
they would talk to me,
made friends with me,
and took me as one of them.
So I like running errands for them.
In fact, I'm the opposite of you.
In the past, I didn't like making friends.
Nor communicating with other people.
Every day, I just sat before the computer.
I felt very happy looking at the screen.
But someone changed me.
Who?
Ye Muxi.
Big boss?
She showed up.
Made me feel the communication between people
seems a little different from facing the cold screen.
There's temperature.
So after I came to Class Ten.
being with everyone here,
and the one I admire the most,
I've been every happy every day.
I feel more comfortable than staying before the computer.
In fact, Cheng Ling,
making friends is not that complicated.
Besides, I think,
you don't need to be friends with every one.
With one or two bosom friends,
it's enough.
Spicy strips?
President, you scared me.
Why did you come in so suddenly?
I need another try.
It came true again, right?
No, it didn't.
Coincidence. All coincidences!
Coincidences. Coincidences.
How about another try?
The last one today.
There's no coins here.
How about we using this?
Do you have to be so casual?
Is my fate so cheap?
Tell me, what's it this time?
Is he with a red silk strip?
Or on a colorful magical cattle?
Neither.
It's very simple this time.
It says,
your true love will kiss you today.
Impossible!
It shows that your true love will appear soon.
Your true love will walk on a fire wheel
and bump into you passionately.
It says,
your true love will kiss you today.
Anyway,
it's still too early to be kissed now.
No, it's totally unacceptable.
I decided. I'll stay in class today.
So Liao Danyi won't...
Guan Xinyi.
Liao Danyi, why did you come here?
-I'm here for you.
-Stay where you are!
Let me explain it.
Stay where you are.
Stay away from me.
Let me explain it.
I've thought it through. If I can't defeat you,
you shall join us.
Cheng Ling
Join our class committee?
A committee member?
I can't.
You can!
You have an advantage over the others.
What's that?
Advantage? I have no advantages.
Come on. Let's go.
Why did it get locked?
Stay away from me!
Stay away from me.
I don't know why.
You're like a magnet today.
I bump into you every time I see you.
But I'm here only to apologize to you.
Why did you come for me?
Why did you approach me?
That's irresistible.
How could it be irresistible every time?
If it's not, then what is it?
Could be many reasons!
For example, kismet.
Fate...
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me!
Calm down.
Calm down!
Okay.
The door is opened.
How did you run yesterday?
No idea.
Well, which place did you get?
The first place.
The first place. How about you?
What can I do for you?
Race.
You're a girl. A race with me?
I find a very good sport man in our class.
But he's not in your team.
Who's that talented man?
Him. Cheng Ling.
Hi, everyone.
You're short. Can you really do this?
Believe me, you're gonna be shocked.
Give it a try, then. Come on.
Everybody.
Ready?
Go!
Where are you going?
Cheng Ling! Cheng Ling!
The canteen is right ahead!
Chicken steaks! Hurry!
Cheng Ling, you're so amazing!
Cheng Ling, I knew you can do this!
Boy, you run so fast.
Join our track and field team?
Yes, so amazing.
The relay race next week is counting on you.
Hey, Cheng Ling, what's wrong with you?
We've been waiting for a whole morning.
Where are our chicken steaks?
He's a member of our team now. What's the matter?
What's the matter?
Nothing. Just an acquaintance.
Just come to say hello.
So, Cheng Ling,
do you want to join our team?
Okay.
I like running.
Is it really so simple?
Gimme.
Sorry. I apologize for what I did.
Okay.
So simple?
Of course. You think I'm very narrow-minded?
But, to apologize,
you should offer me something like you do now.
I shall leave first if there's noting else.
Hey, come back.
I ordered the chocolate flavor.
Why did you buy me a plain one?
It's chocolate.
Have a taste.
I'm really sorry. I'll buy you another cup.
This guy doesn't seem that bad.
Well, is this an indirect kiss?
President, you scared me.
What's this?
Approval for foundation of your society.
Well.
You didn't know I would give you this
at such a moment?
So, president.
You also believe in kismet now?
What nonsense is that?
I never believe in anything like kismet.