# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 16
Are you guys looking for someone writing for you?
Sorry. I've already got a tight schedule this month.
Please come again next month.
Who are you?
Everyone calls me Language Master.
As for my full name,
too lazy to tell you.
So arrogant. Kill him!
It's not because I don't want to tell you my full name.
If I tell you that, it's gonna kill you.
Language Master, ten thousand people walk eastwards.
My full name is...
Alex· Black · Kristin·
Dior Depp ·San Diego ·
Francisco · Prometheus ·
Alexander · York Depp ·
Wellington · Alabama · Washington ·
Long Name Means Well-Educated ·
A Genius And Victor · Cheng
Of course, you may call me Cheng.
You can not run away this time!
All beings in this world.
So big so boundless, so small so measureless.
Everything lives in Nature's rules.
Sorry. I can't help if you want my signature.
My private time. No visitors.
Kill him!
Wait.
I'm a pacifist.
Don't like fight and killing.
But my fans...
We got visitors.
Gotta give them a remarkable reception.
I'll only use one fist.
It seems that we gotta use fifty percent of our strength.
It seems that we gotta use all our strength.
Stop. Stop.
[ Biology. History. Geography ]
I was wrong. Stop. Stop.
We were wrong. We were wrong.
Stop it.
I was wrong.
No. Stop it.
Now you know how powerful we are?
You're right, Master.
What you said is much more helpful than that on books.
We've committed grave crimes before.
As you sow, so shall you reap.
The crimes you committed before
can still be atoned in the rest of your life.
In next life, you'll have blessings in return.
Yes. Yes. Master is right. Makes sense.
I quit. I quit. I quit.
My wife is waiting for me downhill.
Gotta go back home to farm.
I shall go back to accompany my mom.
Bye.
What the hell is this?
I'm so mad.
I mailed my masterpiece to the publishing house.
Really?
Which idiot gave this to me?!
Me. Any problem?
Editor... Editor-in-chief.
I think this piece is so amazing!
My admiration for you goes like the surging river,
running endlessly.
Enough. Enough. Cut the crap.
This is the only one I can think highly of among so many works.
Review it quick. Then come back to me.
I'll tell you the content for our next issue.
Forget it. Must have some relations with her.
I better control myself and finish this as soon as possible.
Shen Luoluo, the Fortune-teller,
introduces everyone to this maiden.
Thus everyone knows,
this maiden comes from the spicy strip tribe.
And she's the chief's daughter.
-Lazio·July.
-I see.
I see.
The evil boss Rubbish · Liao hates junk food like spicy strips.
So he's imprisoned all the people of her tribe.
And every day, he makes them eat insipid green food
free of addictive and swill-cooked oil.
Makes every body live in a miserable hell.
So hateful!
They can't do that to you guys.
-Don't worry...
-But under the help of a mysterious man,
Lazio · July managed to escape from there.
But they found her trace all the way to here.
So it's a village.
-But this maiden Lazio · July...
-Shut up! My turn to speak!
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Yezi is here. I'll save everyone.
Don't worry.
Village Head, I have something to report.
Shoot.
The first thing is,
those remorseful soldiers told me just now,
because of Lazio · July's escape,
the evil boss feels being humiliated.
When they were about to surrender and packed up,
they sent a resignation letter to him by the way.
So the evil boss might come here in three days
by the address on the letter.
The second thing is,
when I bumped into Miss Lazio·July,
I had a prediction.
Although it's very vague,
it is in favor of us.
What should we do, then?
The evil boss will attack us in three days.
Sorry.
I make you suffer this.
Never mind. We can fight with them!
But didn't we lose to them miserably six years ago?
But it's been six years now.
So everyone has become stronger after six years?
Not at all!
And we haven't practiced since then.
I feel we've become much weaker.
Never mind! We have morale!
Yes! We have morale!
Do you still want to wait?
No!
Do you still want to hide?
Then we shall liberalize those being oppressed!
Okay!
Listen to my order!
Meal time!
Okay!
Eat this. Eat this.
Have more. Have more.
Yes, give some to her.
Yezi, that, that evil boss Liao is gonna attack us.
Is it appropriate for us just to eat like this?
Everyone, remember to do training.
Your unique skill.
Your unique skill must be mastered.
No problem.
Don't worry.
Go on.
Have some vegetables.
I think this sauce is very good.
That evil boss Liao, why is he so bad?
Why does he have to destroy our Fantasy Village?
So delicious.
Come here.
Miss July, you might not know this.
In fact, Rubbish?Liao is a member of our Fantasy Village.
Let me help you.
No, to be exact,
he and wonder girl Ye created this village with their own hands.
But later, he betrayed this place.
And claimed that he's gonna attack us.
And destroy this place.
Since then, wonder girl Ye started a long struggle against him.
But if we're really gonna fight,
Yezi must feel very sad.
In the past,
they're very, very close friends.
We live a happy life every day.
Hi.
They're our inventors here.
They're good at inventing things.
Twin Star Brothers.
This is the latest immortal water developed by us.
Drink it and your face will stay beautiful.
Want a try?
I'm beautiful enough.
Superstar · Xiaodong.
Today he's in charge of our dinner.
Hi.
Thank you.
Come here, Lazio.
This is the prophet in our Fantasy Village.
Fortune-teller · Wei.
Hi, would you like a prediction?
Animal sign, horoscope, marriage, very accurate.
Okay.
Give me your right hand.
Relationships.
Really?
What about me?
Let me see.
A lonely star.
What... What does that mean?
Pretty good. Pretty good.
To be exact.
It's also about relationships. Relationships.
Really?
We're the same.
We'll have relationships together.
Yes. We'll have relationships together.
What did I tell you? You can only eat it after it falls on the floor!
Don't you know the rules?
Wonder girl Ye, they are...
Them? They're beggars tramping to here.
One is Henchman · He.
The other is Stupid · Guan.
They do nothing but ask for food here.
Can't get rid of them.
Go away! Go. Go. Go.
Look, this is the fortune-teller stone.
As long as you put your hands on it,
clear your mind,
it can sense your talent level and attribute.
Come, let me try it.
So bright. She must be exceptionally talented.
But what attribute does the azure mean?
I've never seen this color.
Yes. What does azure mean?
Careful.
Azure means waiting for the rain.
And we're waiting for you.
So I think she's null attribute.
Null attribute?
For example.
My color is crimson. So my attribute is fire.
Language Master · Tiancheng's attribute is earth.
Monitor Yezi's attribute is water.
Xiaodong's is gold.
So we five have occupied
all attributes of the five elements.
So I think she's null attribute.
So I must be very awesome?
Great! I can help you now!
Well, what kind of magical ability shall I cultivate?
Null attribute is not suitable for any magic arts.
So you can't help us at all.
But you said I'm very awesome!
Because its color is pure and uncontaminated.
So it's very awesome!
Well, on which aspect the awesomeness lies?
It's my first time to see such a useless girl like you.
So you're highly worthy of appreciation and collection.
Why can't I master any skills?
If only I could master one single skill!
For example, Yezi,
how good it is if I can fly as you do!
Okay. It's very easy.
After eight or nine years learning, you can fly as well.
How is that possible? I have no wings.
Why do you have to have wings to fly?
I can fly because I use Money King art.
But this...
This...
Just an ornament. Want to wear it?
It's detachable?
Superstar · Xiaodong.
You alone here. Don't you feel very lonely every day?
What's called loneliness?
What's called solitude?
You can see me smiling every day.
But you can't see my helplessness,
my trouble,
my confusion.
How much I hope I can be like you guys!
To breathe air in the Nature.
To run on the beach.
Collect shells in the sea breeze.
But I can't get out of here.
I'm locked up in here like this every day.
Breathing my own breath.
Being sad at my own sadness.
Xiaodong...
Never mind. I've been used to this.
Xiaodong!
Meal time!
Okay. What are we gonna eat today?
Many your favorites.
It seems that there's hot-pot.
No. I want to eat pizza.
Why pizza? Hurry up.
The evil boss is about to arrive.
Fortune-teller · Wei, I need you to predict.
I need to know when they'll arrive.
More importantly, I need to know
how many people will come with them.
Yes, madam.
Superstar · Xiaodong,
I need you to arrange your fans to reach every corner.
I need to know in which direction they're gonna approach us.
But that will make me lose fans.
It's okay. I'll make up for the number through buying.
My fans are real people.
Doesn't matter.
Twin Star Brothers.
I need you to arrange for plenty of props.
To reduce their number as soon as possible.
No problem.
Power · Yao.
I need you to kill as possible as you can.
Okay.
Dark · Yuan and Cheng.
You'll take charge of shooting.
Okay.
And, the most important task.
Is yours.
Henchman · He and Stupid · Guan.
Tonight, you must get the needle mushrooms
and hot-pot condiment done. Thanks.
What about me? What about me?
Just stay behind me.
I'll protect you.
Won't do anything else?
Don't worry. You'll enter the stage sooner or later.
Okay. Everyone, get ready.
Okay! Okay!
Let's go!
Miss Xinyi.
Where are they?
All asleep.
Okay.
It's time to reveal our true identity.
Cast the spell.
Miss Xinyi, your face is stained.
Really?
Okay now?
Here. Here. Here.
My king, you come here alone.
It's dangerous.
My king, rest easy.
Everything is going smoothly.
[ Time flies. The duel day comes soon. ]
You're struggling in vain.
When we sneaked in here,
we poisoned every one of them.
Here.
More for you. More for you.
Okay. Okay.
I think this coffee must be good.
Where are you from, beggar?
Put it down.
Get our of here. Get out.
What are you doing?
So annoying! Why come here?
Put it down!
Unbelievable.
Gotta close the door next time.
What are you doing here?
Well, Master Xiong.
I have something to ask you.
What's that?
What book are you reading lately?
I've been reading many books lately.
What, you're interested into books?
If you want me to recommend some books to you,
that must be the books written by myself. Here.
Don't! Wait!
What's your book's name?
It's coming soon.
How could you hide those little tricks from me?
In fact, on the first day you came here,
I managed to know that you're spies.
But I faked being fooled by you.
To enjoy the game.
In fact, every time after you put poison,
I would put antidote as well.
So, none of us gets poisoned.
Yezi, let's fight!
Kill them!
And me!
Gosh.
My god.
Wait.
No. This feeling...
I...
No way. I've put antidote.
This doesn't feel like being poisoned.
Is it... Is it because...
Here. Let me recommend you
this sacred food of our Lazio tribe.
Feel it.
Close your eyes. Feel its flavor slowly.
Isn't it bouncy and spicy?
As if there are angels flying around you.
It is indeed a connotative food.
Isn't it delicious?
Have more.
Is it because those spicy strips?
Spicy strips?
Yezi, you're dead today!
Miss Xinyi, no...
It seems that we also...
Have a taste.
This is our Lazio tribe's specialty.
So delicious.
Am I right? Isn't it delicious?
We also ate spicy strips!
Now, only you and me left.
Give up. Before it's too late.
You're asking for this!
Stop!
Yezi!
The duel between Yezi and the evil boss Liao
lasts three days and three nights.
This is a duel that startles the world and makes gods cry.
Mountains and rivers are shocked.
And the ground gets moved.
Finally, the critical moment comes.
Give up. You're running out of strength.
You and your pals.
And the entire Fantasy Village.
Let me destroy it with my own hands!
Yezi, hang in there!
Useless thing, you won't make any different.
I'm useless.
I'm not good at anything.
I only bring trouble to everyone.
But as long as I can do a little help,
I'll contribute all my strength to this!
Don't worry. You're not fighting alone.
I'm here.
And me!
You guys are alright?
Just some spicy strips.
Already digested.
See? Liao Danyi.
You can never beat me.
Because you're always alone.
But I have my friends!
I have the entire world!
Impossible.
Who are you?
Do you remember your name?
And where you come from?
It's okay.
From now on,
you'll live with us.
Bear in mind your new name.
Baby · Liao.
Baby · Liao?
Come with me.
Welcome, Baby· Liao.
Welcome, Baby · Liao.
Welcome. Welcome.
Hi, everyone. I'm Baby · Liao.
I'm Huang Yi.
I'm Huang Nan.
I'm Lazio·July.
I'm Fortune-teller · Wei.
I'm Language Master · Cheng.
I'm Dark · Yuan.
Welcome, Baby · Liao.
Baby · Liao.
Welcome. Welcome.
Welcome to join this big family!
Let's eat hot-pot together.
Superstar · Xiaodong?
Where were you just now?
I saw everyone go to help you.
Felt that my help was unnecessary.
So I went to get the hot-pot condiment ready.
Come on, let's eat hot-pot together!
Eat hot-pot together!
Come on!
Hot-pot!
You sit here. I'll sit there.
In this way,
Fantasy Village embraces the long-lost peace.
The evil boss Liao loses his memory.
Now becomes Baby · Liao.
And lives happily with everyone else.
Eat it. It's very delicious.
Editor-in-chief, I've read this cartoon.
Rich in content.
Novel in theme.
So we'll issue this cartoon.
Go contact the author.
By the way, ask her,
has she ever thought to make The Big Boss into a series?
The Big Boss?
But... But this cartoon that I've read...
This one?
This one, I only read one page.
I put it on your desk to remind you,
in the future, keep this kind of work out of my vision.
The painting style, is really unbearable.
Okay.
Yezi, lunch is ready.
Stop working.
Let's have lunch downstairs.
Okay. In a minute.
Well, have you received my delivery?
What delivery?
Any call looking for me?
Well.
How could they call me looking for you?
Fine.
Then I shall wait here for my delivery.
Really?
I believe they'll contact me soon after they see that work.
Then I'll make a big money.
I'll take you to eat hot-pot all over the world.
Okay. Okay.
I'm already moved since you can think that way and say that.
So great. So great.
Yezi, seize the time to draw more.
Go downstairs after you're done.
Hurry. I'll wait for you.
When can we walk out of the forest?
Why I feel that we're back to here again?
I don't think so.
Master Stupid.
We'll walk out of the forest soon.
I'm so mad!
Unbelievable, those guys.
One day,
I'll help the evil boss restore his memory.
And kill them all.
So mad!
-So mad!
-Miss Xinyi, ease your anger.
Your inner injury is not recovered yet.
-Ease your anger...
-Speaking of that...
Gosh! Wait for me. Wait for me.
So mad!
Ye Muxi, what are you drawing?
A story that a hero defeats an evil boss.
Can I draw with you?
Okay.
Let's draw this story together.
And tell it to all kids.
what are you drawing? Go back to study!
Don't let me see you drawing any more!
Why is Liao Danyi still not here?
Well, I'll draw it by myself.
What shall I call the place where the heroes live?
Fantasy Village!