Gosh, how dare you turn on this?
Very brave.
Since it's on,
gotta play something.
Right?
So,
what do you want to see?
Comedy?
Costume?
Singing and dancing?
Fantasy?
Action movie?
Or, you just want to see something
while making instant noodles?
We can give you everything that you want.
Impossible is nothing.
But, if you want to see some soup drama,
Marry Sue,
or,
turn this off.
Because no matter how you define this,
this is not a...
Love story.
Class begins.
Stand up.
Hi, boys and girls.
Hi, teacher.
Sit.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 01
MC Nuggets chicken wings!
White crane spreads wings!
Dodge in front, Huskie behind!
Dragon by left, Tiger right!
Tomato, potato, can I take three with one yuan to my home?
Can't do it any more.
Wonder girl, hungry?
Yes!
Eat!
little sister, in a blink of eyes,
you've been such a big girl.
Thinking of this,
the feeling I have is so complicated!
Today is your first day to school.
I must see you off in a handsome way!
Make you dignified!
In future, whether you're in high school or college,
or postgraduate,
you'll always be my little sister!
Brother, I want radish!
Okay!
Brother, no need to see me off.
Are you kidding?
Today is my sweet Yezi's first day in school.
As your big brother,
I must send you there handsomely!
Don't you have scripts to finish?
Scripts?
Is it more important than my sweet Yezi?
Out of inspiration?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's go.
Today is a day worth remembering.
And going down in history.
And...
Killing spirit.
Stop. Stop, brother.
What's wrong with you?
You scared me.
This guy is my childhood sweet...
No, my arch enemy.
Lad Danyi!
Liao Danyi.
Ever since I could remember,
he's been around me.
Whether in kindergarten,
primary school, or secondary school,
this guy has been the monitor of my class.
Always goes against me.
He's a nightmare of my childhood.
Detritus in my shoes.
A plague that keeps me miserable.
Very unlucky.
The monitor stuff is most annoying.
You can't!
Study hard!
Lad Danyi.
No!
Lad Danyi,
this clothes makes you look really handsome!
Your first day to school?
What a coincidence! My sweet Yezi's first day to school, too.
What's wrong?
Bow tie loose.
Socks not balanced.
Shoelaces too loose.
I didn't notice these because we went out in a rush.
Sweet Yezi.
Brother Ye, she can do it.
Or she'll never learn it.
It's okay. My sweet Yezi is good in every way.
But sometimes she's a little careless.
The new semester just begins.
You'll leave a bad impression!
You think I'm not happy?
Because you've annoyed me?
Not at all.
Because as of today,
nine-year compulsory education ends.
As of today, I'm out of your control.
As of today, we're not in the same class.
Today, nothing is gonna ruin my good mood.
Brother, go to school.
Wait, bow tie.
Go.
Lad Danyi, see you later.
Wait for me.
Turn. Turn. Turn.
Why are you following me so closely?
Sticky candy?
At the next turning, go to another direction.
Turn! Turn!
Turn!
Brother, stop!
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Liao Danyi, stop!
What... What's wrong?
I appreciate your kindness.
But you can't see me off to the end.
Back to your own way.
I'm on my way to school.
I'm on my way to school as well.
Miss Xinyi, I've been waiting for a long time.
You also make it into Class One?
Must be hard for you.
To follow you, miss Xinyi,
It's worth it.
Today I'm the first one to get here.
I've chosen a best seat for you.
The fourth line by the window.
The third line from the front.
Neither too far nor too close to the blackboard.
Best day-lighting.
Ten o'clock a.m. Forty-five degrees of sunlight
slashes into the classroom to silhouette your perfect profile.
Besides, I've dealt with the one who sat in this seat.
I've closeted myself with all our classmates.
They all agree that you're the best candidate for our monitor.
That's unnecessary.
Isn't it a matter of course for me to the monitor?
Yes.
Get off, Yezi.
What are you watching? Stop it.
Stop it.
Listen,
Lad Danyi has been gone a few blocks before.
It's your first day to school. Do look beautiful.
Sister, I must stop here.
Your first day to school.
Hope everything goes well for you!
Brother, I'm going!
Okay. Sister, be careful.
My sister is really grown up.
So is her strength.
[ Maple Leaf Middle School ]
Everything is normal. Clear.
Copy.
You little troublemakers.
Do you know what gives you this punishment?
Cheating in the exam!
Being late!
Leaving early!
Cutting school!
Puppy love!
Smoking!
Leaving early!
Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong!
Hey, girls.
Don't push. Don't push.
Behave yourselves, girls.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Come on.
Bro, don't you feel a little dizzy?
Yes, all of a sudden.
Very quietly I take my leave.
as quietly as I came here;
Quietly I wave good-bye, to the rosy clouds in the western sky.
Liangchen, you're in a good state today.
You, too, Meijing, in a good state, too.
You saying that will make me shy.
It won't. Because I was telling the truth.
If you have a problem with me, spit it out!
I can handle it!
Why are you running away?
Where are the chicken drumsticks you bought?
Excuse me, senior. I'll go buy right now.
And cokes. Hurry.
The sun enters into Aries, Mercury retrogrades.
Disaster!
Miss Xinyi, basketball court is dangerous.
Leave this place now.
Can't even hold the ball, how could you play it?
This wall is so white.
No! I gotta control myself.
Right here.
Yes. Great.
Three years of high school life is gonna take place in here.
Hi, can you tell me where's Class Ten, Grade Ten?
This is the secondary high school.
Go across this playground, climb over the stairs
to the end. Go right ahead.
And the building in the deepest corner is the high school.
Okay.
Maple Leaf Middle School decides classes by scores.
Even if Liao Danyi is in this school,
he won't be in the same class with me,
unless he skipped an exam for one of the courses.
My happy, untrammeled, free
campus life without Liao Danyi
begins now!
What's wrong with your high school entrance exam?
Answering questions with your eyes closed?
Listening to videos with your ears stuffed?
How could you end up in my class?
One course missed.
What did you say?
Had a fever before exam. One course missed.
You really skipped an exam?
My word is so efficacious!
But this morning, you didn't wear school uniform.
I had a fever on the uniform day.
I picked up this uniform today.
Had a fever again and again. Why didn't it kill you?
Anyway, the last period of my youth,
the most wonderful three years,
can't be ruined by you.
Liao Danyi.
Hi, everyone. I'm your head teacher, Wu Heng.
We'll spend three years together from now on.
No more details about me.
'Cause in future, you'll get to know me thoroughly.
Now, everyone, please introduce yourself.
Hello, everyone, I'm Shen Wei.
I love horoscope and fortune-telling.
Constellation and Tarot cards.
I'm Yuan Ke'er.
My hobby is painting.
I love everything that is beautiful.
Hi, everyone. I'm Cheng Ling.
Nice to meet you guys.
Hope we can be friends.
Li Yao!
Hi, everyone, I'm Gao Fei.
My hobby is video games.
Hope we can be good friends.
Half of the first episode.
We're still not on camera yet.
You think it's good?
Such self-introductions sucks!
Don't you want something cooler?!
Want three-color dried fruit?
Gives you a special feeling in this special night.
Original price is three yuan. Now, only two yuan.
Are you lonely?
If you are, let this talking minion talk with you!
It's time to protect our country.
How about a gun?
To show your masculine side!
And regain your manhood!
Wanna be a hero?
Wanna get back your childhood?
Here's a chance.
For you to transform!
Do buy a soccer to build up your body.
For our country's sake, make yourself stronger.
So, if you're in any difficulty,
remember to contact us at any time.
I'm Huang Nan.
I'm Huang Yi.
This is Zhi'nan Xingyi Corporation Limited!
(To know is difficult, but to do is easy)
Hi, everyone. I'm Liao Danyi.
I hope I can work with you guys
to finish the three-year study orderly.
Hereby I request,
to work as monitor of our class.
Because ever since the primary school,
over the past nine years,
I've been serving as the monitor.
So I have enough self-confidence and faith
to completely live up to this position.
Don't make him our monitor.
I'm Ye Muxi.
Very well.
Everyone's self-introduction is very brilliant.
Now, let's enter into another session.
Class Committee election.
In this session,
I gotta make it clear to you guys.
Every committee member of Class Ten
should be elected by classmates through democratic election.
Just now, Liao Danyi recommended himself
as the monitor. Very good.
That means he's responsible and reliable.
So I hope you guys can follow his example.
And sign up for the election actively.
Well, let me see which one of you guys
also want to be the monitor?
What should I do?
Who can give me some good idea right now?
Now the entire world knows
that bastard Liao Danyi wants to be the monitor!
Who? Who can stop him? Stand out!
You're...
You guys are...
I'm Mr. Wolong.
You created me when you're seven.
I'm Sima Yi.
You created me three minutes after you
made this greenish stuff.
Sima Yi, Mr. Dinosaur...
Please call me Mr. Wolong.
That's my last dignity.
The class I'm in now is very chaotic.
But Liao Danyi wants to fight against me
for the monitor position.
But if he's the monitor,
this class will be totally over.
Currently, the world is divided with bad guys in the way.
This is really a very critical and fatal moment.
Wonder girl, why don't you rise in revolt for the people?
And replace him?
Replace him?
Replace him?!
Right.
Now let me announce,
monitor of Class Ten is...
Wait!
I, Ye Muxi, want to join the monitor election!
Ye Muxi? Okay.
Well, Liao Danyi, Ye Muxi.
Get your speech ready back home.
Tomorrow, see you both in the election site.
Thanks. Thanks. Thanks.
What are you doing?
Stopping you.
So early.
Yes, Miss Late.
A new bag?
What?
Let me have a look.
Come on, relax.
Relax.
That's right.
Let me see.
It's new.
I'll be earlier than you this time!
School is...
This way.
I didn't expect this.
Although you were riding in the wrong direction,
yet my car hit your...
Bike.
So I should compensate you and apologize to you.
Apologize.
Sorry.
I have no time taking you to the hospital.
Or checking your injury.
I'm in a hurry to school.
Me, too!
So we're alumnae.
But, why did you ride in this direction?
School is that way.
My mistake.
Is this enough?
Not enough.
How about this?
Gimme.
I want to do this thing for a long time.
Who cares about your money?!
What are you doing?
Boys and girls,
today is our monitor election day.
Candidates, please get your speech ready.
We'll start the election in ten minutes.
Hi, everyone, I'm Liao Danyi.
I want to join the monitor election.
So I've made a questionnaire.
Hope you guys can fill in it.
So, after I get the results,
I can accomplish my job more specifically.
Now I'm gonna start my election speech.
I don't know how you guys think about this monitor position.
First of all, I think, the monitor
should serve everyone in a better way.
And make considerate plans according to everyone's
academic performance.
No. I can't keep running in this way.
I must be late.
Girl, need help?
When you're in need,
Zhinan Xingyi is always around.
Any bike?
Kidding.
How could we have such an outdated stuff?
Then what?
Wait, girl.
Calm down.
Let's go!
I won't be late again!
That's all.
Thank you.
Now, welcome the next candidate.
The next candidate is still not here.
So we don't need to wait for her, right?
Last question,
any other classmates wants to the monitor?
If no,
let's officially appoint Liao Danyi as our...
Wait! Wait!
Mr. Wu, wait.
We have another candidate.
The candidate is her!
Sorry. Sorry.
Let us do it again.
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
The candidate is, her!
I...
Hi, I'm Ye Muxi.
I want to be your monitor.
I love hot pot.
And comics about Wonder Woman.
Well...
I don't know what I should say.
But I'll make you guys happy.
My academic performance sucks.
I have no experience on this aspect...
Ye Muxi, are you done?
I wanna be sworn brothers with you!
Yes, right, be sworn brothers with you.
My academic performance sucks all the time.
But because of this,
I understand the pressure that we students shoulder.
I'm not good-looking.
So no one has valued me.
But because of this, I know,
we students should respect and care about one another.
Besides, I have no prejudice against anyone.
I have neither experience nor plans.
But I can assure you,
if I'm your monitor,
my plan is to let you live in the moment.
I'll support everyone who has dream and unique ideas.
So, you'll be sworn brothers with me, right?
Do you want to let your youth shine?
Yes!
Do you want a totally unconventional monitor?
Do you want to vote for me?
Yes!
Then tell me, what's my name?
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
Stop!
Vote for me. Thank you.
Students, let me count the votes.
First of all,
Ye Muxi's votes.
Four.
Now, Liao Danyi's votes.
Three.
Mr. Wu, you gotta explain this.
To be honest, I understand your confusion.
Although it sounds ashamed,
I still gotta tell you the results.
During this voting,
only seven of you voted for your classmates.
Among the rest thirty-three votes,
twenty votes goes to Sunshine Girls.
Four or five votes goes to unknown Korean stars.
And some goes to the forth generation Naruto.
Ninja Turtles.
And on two votes it reads,
I'm Arthur. I'm durable.
Arthur is very durable.
I knew it's you guys!
What the hell?
So,
during this voting, only seven votes are valid.
Other classmates' waiver.
In future, the monitor of our class is
Ye Muxi.
Today shall be write down in history
and be remembered by the whole world.
Why?
Because as of today, I'm the big boss.
Not Liao Danyi!
And as of today, you guys follow me
to enjoy the life. What do you say?
Follow your leadership till the end!
Well, what should a monitor do?
What?
Anyway, it rocks!
It rocks!
Cheers!
Please give me a bottle of mineral water.
Isn't this our ordinary classmate Liao Danyi?
What are you doing here?
To comfort your penny soul?
We're both in the Class Committee now.
Try to get along well with each other.
Yes, we're...
Class... Class Committee?
That's to say, you're the monitor,
and I'm Commissary in charge of studies.
We're gonna manage Class Ten together.
Commissary in charge of studies...
After you're elected and went to celebrate,
we started to elect other committee members.
And I was elected as Commissary in charge of studies.
Commissary in charge of studies, what is your job?
Commissary in charge of studies is responsible for study progress.
If someone doesn't pay attention in class,
or draws little figures on books,
that should be managed by the Commissary in charge of studies.
But, Ye Muxi,
you won't be that bored, right?
After all, you're the monitor.
So, you'll still keep me under control?
You can think that.
Looking forward to work with you in this three years.
Big boss.
This is a world where light and darkness coexist.
Hope and despair interlock.
Evil forces are about to rise up
To devour my youth.
In this nervous vibe before the storm comes,
My three-year high school life as the monitor begins.