# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 18
Why they're all crowded in there?
What're they looking at?
Can't see it.
Make them go away then.
Isn't that the idol Xue Xiaodong?
Xue Xiaodong!
Let's go.
Campus singing competition.
Yes!
They finally decide to hold a nice competition.
This is made for my Xue Xiaodong.
Do you want to participate?
Rock and roll live forever!
I'd rather be a poet than a singer.
No, no. I can't sing.
To be honest, I'm interested.
But never mind.
It's okay.
In our class, there're a female and a male cavaliers.
Who is that female?
Like the one standing here.
Watch me.
Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
Ye Muxi.
Has anyone told you, you're a great singer?
No, never.
Don't sing it then.
Wait, I'll show you I'm the best.
Look, what's writing there?
English songs only.
All the Chinese songs you know won't be qualified.
What? What the hell?!
Who said that?
I feel so sorry about your singing career.
We're Chinese.
Why we must sing English songs?
Oh my lady Gaga.
What?
Don't you know that?
Let's go.
Anything I can help with, Ye Muxi?
You're a superstar.
So handsome, sings so beautiful.
You have so many fans.
I know you will win.
But this competition is also a chance for me to show myself.
So I wish you can help me.
What're you gonna sing?
I've prepared one song.
Okay.
# We will we will rock you #
Wait.
We've been to KTV together.
I know your style.
But can we try anther style this time?
A lyric song, a slow one.
Let me think.
I have one.
# Hey, I really miss you #
# Now it's raining outside #
# My eyes feel like to cry #
# I wonder where you are right now #
Bravo.
Then, I will sing this one.
But they said English songs.
Any English Song you can sing?
# You've built a love but that love falls apart #
# Your little piece of heaven turns too dark #
# Listen to your heart #
Wait, this ling, one more time.
One more time.
# Listen to your heart #
I know your problem now, Ye Muxi.
Your pronunciation and intonation are good.
But...
My opinion is,
if you want to win,
you need to go see someone.
To teach you English.
I'm not bragging.
If you want to learn English.
You made the right choice to turn to us.
Our Difficulty Easily Solved Corp. can do anything.
We can teach you anything.
Right.
Here.
Our special way to learn English is to write it down.
And turn it into Chinese.
What about this?
Here, for example.
This one, this line.
Well, look.
Sa Mu Wan(Someone)
La Ke You (Like you)
What does it mean?
Consider this as a kind of spicy oil.
It's so spicy, makes you thirsty.
Come on, read it.
Sa Mu Wan La Ke You.
Imagine a kind of very spicy oil.
very spicy oil.
-Okay.
-Now you remember it, right?
-Imagination, come on.
-Like you.
Right, right. next one.
Next one, this line.
This line is
Sa Mu Wan.
La Ke Mi.
Right, the word Mi is this all about.
Super spicy rice. Makes you thirsty.
I see. I see.
Sa Mu Wan. La Ke Mi. (Someone like me)
Spicy rice makes me thirsty.
Rice!
Yes, yes, rice.
La Ke You. La Ke Mi. (Like you. Like me.)
Sing it. Sing it.
# Sa Mu Wan. La Ke You. #(Someone like you)
# Sa Mu Wan. La Ke Mi. #(Someone like me)
Look, you've learned it.
Come on, let's continue.
Lad Danyi.
Can you do me a favor?
No.
You don't know what is that yet.
It's boring anyway.
You know what should a class committee member do?
To help people.
You're a class committee member as well.
How can you be like this, darling!
What're you doing?
Dear tree. I...
What do you want?
Aren't you my boyfriend?
Who is your boyfriend?!
Right, pretend.
Shall I tell the whole world
and Guan Xinyi as well.
So she will come after you again.
What a nice scene!
What the hell do you want?
Teach me English.
Let's go back to classroom.
No, I asked Liao Danyi
to teach me English.
Liao Danyi, teach me English.
This one.
Come on!
We
will start from the title.
Follow me.
Someone Like You.
Someone Like you.
Someone like you.
Some...some...someone Like you.
Don't sing it along.
Some...someone like you.
Someone Like you.
Someone like you.
Let's try another one.
You raise me up.
You rise me up.
I know this one.
Raise.
You rise me up.
Raise!
You rise me up!
Rise! Rise! Rise! Rise!
Not rise, raise!
You rise me up. Up. Up. Up!
One more time, follow me.
You raise me up.
Shit.
That pronunciation is right.
I'll teach you one last time. Raise.
Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Hi, Danyi.
Brother Yihan.
Yezi, come downstairs. Danyi is here.
Come in, sit.
How are you doing lately?
My study is not bad.
Not bad?
I see you both are so tired.
Come, come, Yezi. Danyi is here.
Danyi, you and Yezi chat here.
I'll get you some snacks.
Thank you, brother Yihan.
You're learning English lately?
Watch me raise!
What will you sing?
You can't sing Laugh in the Ocean.
Haven't figured out yet.
I've found you an easy one.
No, it's not challenging.
So the judge can't see my ability!
I mean which you can pronounce.
That never worries me.
Listen to me.
# Beat it! #
# Know you wanna be bad #
# Beat it, Beat it, Beat it, Beat it #
# Beat it! #
Stop! Stop!
Sorry.
What are you singing?
Beat it.
That's beat it.
Or maybe you can sing "Hello".
No, it's too old. No.
It's classic.
And the most important is there're two minutes
with no connected speech.
In that way, your English will sound better in one night.
Otherwise, I really can't give any compliment about your English.
Find something cooler.
# Hello from the other side #
Stop.
Wait, let me get a pen.
How do you pronounce it?
Other side.
Hello, right?
Stop.
Come here.
What're you doing?
You can't remember it like this.
How can you write it in Chinese?!
The palest ink is better than the best memory.
A De Sai De.
Now let's start to practice English.
Now, sing the song we learned today.
One more time.
# Tell me I want you #
# Tell me I need you #
# Tell me I laugh you #
Stop, stop.
The first two lines are good.
The last three words are "I love you".
I laugh you.
I love you.
Laugh.
Love.
Watch my mouth. I love you.
I Laugh you.
Love you.
I love you.
Love.
Laugh. Laugh.
I love you.
Laugh.
You two...
You're away too far!
Stop scrawling.
Let's read some books!
Let's not read this today. Take a break.
Three days fishing and two days resting is not gonna get you there.
I'm a very good singer.
I have ability and my way doing things.
Is there anything more important than learning singing?
Let's read this.
You try it.
Then we'll decide what we'll sing next.
Die.
Day.
You wanna die? Day.
Wait.
Die.
No, it's not gonna work. Too slow.
Class begin. Are you ready?
A B C D E F G
Repeat it.
Or how can I teach you?
It's international language.
But you didn't say a word.
This, this figure.
All the people in the world know it means OK.
Ye Muxi. Can you be serious?
I know what shall I sing now.
Okay. You sing it.
# Hello from the other side #
Only this one line, Ha?
That is not gonna help.
I will go meet Xue Xiaodong in his studio, they'll teach me.
More English practice?
Bravo!
Here, let's try it.
# Distance face all around me #
# With no place left to go #
# Just let me carry on #
# Immersed in dreaming my dream #
# Without you within me #
# I find the rest no home #
That's great. Ye Muxi.
I didn't know you can sing that well.
That's exaggerate.
Not at all, ask Liao Danyi.
Is that nice?
Ye Muxi.
It's time for the shower singer to raise.
But you should also practice your pronunciation.
Your special lyric is not professional.
You know nothing about art.
You get up so quick today.
Tomorrow is the mass-election. I must practice tonight.
That's great.
I like that.
I like your attitude.
Remember, give them a big shock tomorrow.
Watch me, I'll be famous.
And I'll make you the golden broker!
Yes!
You can. We can.
We can do it! Okay!
Golden broker.
I'm gonna be a broker!
I can!
[ Mass-election Day ]
Yuan Ke'er, Class Ten, Grade One.
I'm gonna sing the song "We will rock you".
# We will we will rock you! #
# Rock you! #
Go back. It's terrible. Leave!
Why ring the bell? Why ring the bell on me?
Because it's terrible.
Do you think Rock'n Roll is out of date?
Listen to me.
Rock'n Roll never dies! Rock'n Roll never dies!
Rock!
Hello, this is an English song competition.
# Rolling in the deep. #
This girl sings well. What's this boy doing here?
We're a band.
I'm the singer.
I will applause.
Hello, teacher.
We're Huang Brothers.
We'll gonna sing a Lala song.
One. Two. Three.
Teacher, why ring the bell?
You're too naughty.
We will not let you win.
We saw it coming.
So we've prepared this.
# Since the day you go away #
# Why did you leave me #
# leave me alone #
# with memory of solitude #
# I'm lonely #
# You're the only one #
# Love will bring us back #
# Back to you and me #
# Bring us back to you and me. #
Xiaodong, you sing so well.
I'll let you pass.
Xue Xiaodong. Xue Xiaodong. Xue Xiaodong.
Students.
Order, order please. Thank you.
# In the heart of the night #
# When it's dark in the lights #
# I looked my heart turning right #
# I see around #
# I miss you tonight #
# Your leap is on my leap #
# And your voice is in my ear #
# I looked my heart turning right #
# I see around #
# I miss you tonight #
# Hold me now, don't bother it makes me weak #
# Touch me now, don't bother I'll win this war alone #
# You can save me from what I become #
# I will try to be the one #
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
# I assume you never leave this town #
# You will always be here #
# But here I'm in this all alone and know that you're gone #
# I really missing you #
# If only I could be wherever you are #
# Really missing you #
# You'll always always stay in my dream #
My dear teachers, my dear classmates.
After this fierce competition,
we have selected the final five students.
They are...
Class Ten, Grade One. Xue Xiaodong.
What? Nervous?
Who? Me? No, not at all!
Class Three, Grade Two. Bo Bo.
Class Two, Grade Three. Li Qiang.
Class Six, Grade Two. Qi Nuo.
Congrats, you five.
Oh, and the last one.
Class One, Grade One. Miss Guan Xinyi.
Guan Xinyi.
Sorry, brother.
Can I have one minute?
Thank you.
I want to thank all the teachers and students for choosing me.
I'm glad I can make into the final competition.
As you can see it.
I have many chances in my life to stand on the stage.
So I want to give this chance to other students who need it.
So I choose to quit.
Thank you.
Why...why do you...
Well, if Xue Xiaodong quits.
According to the rankings.
The final one passed belongs to
Class Ten, Grade One. Ye Muxi.
I made it. I made it. I made it!
Congrats to these five students.
The finals will be held in three days.
Please find your singing partner.
Let's looking forward to it.
Partner?
Big boss, you're right to choose us!
Who are we?
We have many ideas!
We can sing a lot of interesting songs.
Like "As dance" in localism.
As dance!
It's perfect.
And this.
The Russian version of "Two butterflies"!
And English version of "My Skateboard Shoes" with rap.
That's awesome!
Yes.
Bravo!
We can add more things on our clothes.
Like we can wear some strange costumes!
Calabash Brothers! Calabash Brothers!
And Naruto!
Right, right.
And we can dress like be Matryoshka dolls.
With Bikini.
Right, right.
We can make fun of them.
Last time we threw smoke bombs to them.
And before that.
We can use many colorful smoke shells.
And cast it out. Cast it out.
Right, right, right.
We're so excited even just think of it.
Last time they suffered a lot!
My god, the smoke.
It's great! I love it!
You want some?
No.
Any problem happened to you lately?
None.
Any problem in study?
Ye Muxi.
I will not be your partner in the singing competition.
I didn't ask you to.
Do you need me to?
Yes.
You can go find someone else.
Xue Xiaodong is great.
I want to ask him as well.
But he has quit.
So he can't participate again.
I don't like singing in front of people.
Since you mentioned it.
Seems I have never heard you sing once since childhood.
How is your singing?
No problem.
Why you won't be my partner?!
I told you, I don't want to.
You should go find someone else.
Fine, I can sing it well without you.
Before the finals.
First I want to announce that,
One participant failed to find a singing partner.
Will be considered as disqualified.
But she insists to sing a song.
Now, may I present Ye Muxi, from Class Ten, Grade Ten.
# Empty space #
# Just fill me up with those holes #
# Distance face around me, with no place left to go #
# Just let me carry on #
# Immersed in dreaming my dream #
Before we realized,
Our Yezi has become such a great singer!
I'm so touched!
I wanna try. But I just can't.
Because the emotions is like the ocean.
# I try to carry on #
# My world is half asleep #
# I'm an ocean alone without you I'm incomplete #
Are we gonna lose like this?
No, we should be proud even we lose.
# I'm an ocean alone without you I'm incomplete #
# Incomplete #
Who is that?
It's Liao Danyi.
Liao Danyi.
Were we wrong about him?
She is not fighting alone?
He is about to sing now?
Let's find out if he has the potential to be an idol.
Come on, Liao Danyi.
Sing, lad!
# Empty space, fill me up with those holes #
# Distance face around me, with no place left to go #
# Just let me carry on #
# Immersed in dreaming my dream #
# Without you within me #
# I find the rest no home #
# I try to carry on #
# My world is half asleep #
# I'm an ocean alone without you I'm incomplete #
I didn't know Liao Danyi is such an awful singer!
It's like killing a pig!
I can't find a word to describe.
He...he...he is here to ruin it?
You sit here, I'll kill him.
You...you sit here.
I'll kill him first!
I'll kill him.
Our Xiaodong is the best.
I think it's good.
Quite different.
# Incomplete #
You're welcome.
The fifth are Liao Danyi, Ye Muxi from Class Ten, Grade One.
How is that possible ? We're the last?
They must have decided it earlier.
Have you finished your homework?
No, no, yeah...yeah...
How much have you finished?
Number one to five?
You haven't started right?
What do you want to eat tonight?
All good.
- How about...Hotpot?\ n- Hotpot?
Mercury is retrograde, it's bad luck!
What was your question before?
Date! My date!
Date?
You should conduct yourself well.
Big boss! Hello!
Don't forget.
2 p.m.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye
Listen to me, whatever you say. It's real.
The SpongeBob is not real.
Santa Claus is not real.
- Teletubbies are also....
- They're real!
They don't exist! Not real.
No, I must hold myself.
But the scrawl on the kindergarten wall is just terrible.
Maybe I'll just remould it a little.
Wu Sir.
What're you doing here?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Help me with the new textbooks.
Let's go.
Wu sir. I'm a young beautiful girl!
Well, I'm a young handsome boy!
- Hello, teacher!
- Wu Sir!
Come on, come on.
Where are we gonna shoot?
We're already here.
Sis, I wanna take a walk.
Okay.
Can you send someone to get us?
Listen to me.
No matter what you say.
It's real!
They're all fake!
Real!
Fake!
I'm ignoring you.
You're so childish!
I don't care!
You're so boring.
Your wrist must hold like this.
- Like this ?
- Yes, right.
Li Yao.
It's so good to have you to be the action designer of my novel!
Can you repeat it again?
Martial arts are not just words. It's like...
I'm running late. Running late.
Xiaodong. What a coincidence!
You're also here.
I have something to shoot in here.
I know. No, I don't know.
I'm just wandering around.
There's a coffee store. I'll show you.
Let's go. Let's go.
You two brats! Listen to me!
I can't catch you.
But don't let me see you at school.
If I see you in school,
I will make sure you two suffer a lot.
Seems we have met so many acquaintances today.
Right.
I still stick to my opinion.
I also stick to my opinion.
I do hate you.
Likewise.