# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 15
Stop.
Monitor, last time...
Li Yao took away my pressed powder.
My mom bought me that a few days ago.
I haven't used it yet.
That goes too far.
A gentleman takes things by fair means.
Yes.
This is the third compliant we've received this week.
All about that Li Yao.
Li Yao, female, sixteen years old.
A student in Class Ten, Grade One.
Also a famous bully in our school.
So she's the so called bully.
But she's gonna meet someone tougher.
But this kind of person looks so scaring.
We better let our teacher handle her.
No.
We can solve all the problems.
Why waste such an opportunity?
Yes.
Well, do you guys have any ideas?
Of course we should play tough against her directly!
Fight with her.
No. Violence can't solve any problem.
If we fight,
won't we be the same like her?
Well, monitor, do you have any ideas?
A duel face-to-face.
I've told you, violence can't solve any problem.
Besides, that's your textbook.
Don't scrawl on it.
Now the most important thing is,
to talk with her about what's really going on.
That's a very unique idea.
First of all,
we should send a mild yet mediocre student to her.
Why are you guys looking at me?
This is Li Yao?
She's indeed tall and burly.
Looks so scaring.
Where is she going?
God knows.
To do something scaring probably.
Zhu Shanqi, go.
Action speaks louder than heartbeats.
It's time for an afternoon tea.
Bye.
Zhu Shanqi, don't try to shrink back from this battle.
I'll go. Is she that scaring?
Hey!
What's up?
Do you like spicy strips?
Yes.
Have some, then.
What are you gonna eat if I eat it?
Wait.
I'll buy you more.
Girl, choose whatever you like.
Here. Come on, spicy strips...
How much?
Five Yuan each one.
All my allowance this month.
Here it is.
I want four.
Thank you, sir.
Okay.
Here, spicy strips. Spicy strips.
Here, spicy strips.
Why did you buy so many?
Why are you so fierce?
As expected, you were bullied.
Yes.
I've used up my allowance this month.
Still helps nothing.
She's gone too far!
How could she bully my friend like that?
Can't stand it any more.
What are you drawing?
It means nothing to defeat her in the cartoon world.
It seems that I should stand out now.
Don't worry. For this day,
we've been preparing for a long time.
I have at least ten ways to defeat her.
Between classes, we're invincible.
And I have ten thousand ways to make her die.
You're Li Yao, aren't you?
You can talk to me.
Don't point your finger at me.
My dad told me,
it's very impolite for boys to talk with girls like that!
Understand?
Yes. Yes.
Shoot. What's the matter?
It's said that you're beautiful.
So we came to check it out.
As we see,
it's worth coming here!
Beautiful!
Can't be more beautiful!
So great!
Lucky that she runs away.
-Or I'll beat her to death!
-All right, that's all.
Enough. Enough. Enough.
Guys.
Just now, I've talked with everyone
who claimed to have been bullied by Li Yao.
I think, we've worked
in a wrong direction since the very start.
It's not right?
We've been following her...
What solution does he have?
We can't even handle this.
How could Liao Danyi make it?
What's the matter?
Li Yao.
I'm Liao Danyi, commissary
in charge of studies of Class Ten.
I want to make friends with you.
Damn it. Damn it.
Liao Danyi, run!
Can't watch this.
Friends?
Yes.
Although he's my enemy,
I gotta help him out.
Come back.
You're sure you want to make friends with me?
Any problem?
No problem.
What's going on?
So Li Yao actually is a good student. Right?
Indeed she is.
I've seen her feed homeless cats between classes.
So I made such a guess.
You're mad at me because of spicy strips.
Only because you thought it's too wasteful?
Yes!
Oh, my god. Still feel a little scared.
It seems that Li Yao is from a military family.
Her mom is more amazing.
A national arm & fist boxing champion.
Arm & fist boxing?
A boxing technique to hit yourself first
before you hit the others.
I've been practicing it since childhood.
And I grow up in a martial arts school.
But dad thinks that I'm not like a girl at all.
He's afraid that no one will marry me.
So he sends me into Maple Leaf Middle School for a change.
So we're the same kind of people!
Let's be friends...
It seems that growth environment
makes you lack interpersonal communication.
Actually it also troubles me.
I also want to make friends.
But since the beginning of this semester,
no one talks to me, let alone makes friends with me.
But I've made some progress anyway.
When some students looked in my eyes,
they gave me snacks.
Isn't that called tributes?
Some other students are also very nice.
Although I broke their stuff,
they didn't blame me.
Isn't it because they dare not hold you responsible?
Actually I'm the same as you guys.
I also want a wonderful high school life.
And friends as good as you guys.
But...
No one wants to make friends with me.
That's no big deal.
Now you have us around you.
We'll help you become more like a girl.
A very adorable and very cute girl.
A girl everyone will fall for once they see you.
From now on,
a sparrow will turn into a phoenix.
Okay!
Weren't we gonna punish a monster?
What do you girls like normally?
Look, that toy.
How about you taking a picture with him?
No.
Come on.
Look, he's so round and he's dancing.
So cute!
You should be exposed to such things more.
How about you guys going there with me?
No, you should try such things by yourself.
Hurry. Hurry.
We'll support you right here.
Good luck.
Why are you running away?
Thief! Thief!
Stop! Thief!
Stop!
Stop right there!
-Why are you running away?
-Thief!
-Stop!
-Thief! Get him!
Don't let him run away! Stop!
Thief! Get him!
Thief! Stop!
Stop! He's there!
Get the thief!
Stop!
Thief! Thief!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Sis, I'm wrong. I'm wrong.
I didn't kill anyone!
Spare me, sis.
I'm wrong. It's yours now.
It's yours, okay?
I'm wrong. I'm wrong.
What's going on?
Thank you, sis.
For helping me get back my purse.
I'll send a silk banner to your school.
Never mind.
It's what we should do.
I'm Ye Muxi.
Ye Muxi.
Ye Muxi. Thank you. Thank you.
Well, what should we do next?
You caught a thief.
Class Ten has done another good deed.
But, Li Yao,
when you're chasing that thief,
you were so cool!
Not that exaggerated.
Li Yao, you're really good at Kungfu?
You bet.
My mom taught me.
But she won't let me use it normally.
Or I'll hurt other people.
Makes sense.
A toy store.
Li Yao.
Next, your task is to buy two fluffy toys.
Little girl.
How could you steal at such a young age?
Unbelievable. Where are your parents?
Only you alone here?
Xiaoshan.
Didn't I tell you that?
Don't run about.
After you choose a bear,
wait for me to pay for you.
Okay. Thirty Yuan it is.
Let's go.
Look. Look.
Easy. Easy.
Today you're not the leading actress, okay?
Okay.
Well, how can we help Li Yao be relaxed
and enjoy this to her heart's content?
Boss.
Actually we have an idea.
To help Li Yao be relaxed and pleasant,
we better give her a male partner.
You guys?
We'll pass.
I think this male partner must look totally harmless.
-Xue Xiaodong?
-No!
I'll pass.
No, you can't.
Actually we have a more suitable candidate.
And I've called him just now.
Monitor.
I...
Huang Yi called just now. Told me to come here.
So... So soon?
I've called just now!
Is there a distance between our school and here?
It seems only three miles.
Just needs a little running.
Li Yao, come here.
Let me introduce someone to you.
This is our classmate, Cheng Ling.
Leigong made a huge mistake.
When his opponent attacked,
he shouldn't back off.
He should stand firmly there.
So, there's no distinctive difference between
kickboxing and our traditional martial arts.
Understand?
Ye... Yes.
Hurry. Hurry. Follow them closely.
Li Yao.
Do you like this?
What do you think are they talking about?
Have they started talking?
We're pretty far away from them.
When could this run faster?
Can't get them now.
Hurry.
We're already in the amusement park.
How could we not try the most classic one?
That means...
Sky wheel!
Li Yao.
Have you tried the sky wheel?
No.
A boy and a girl in a room.
Sounds so exciting!
But...
How should we do the match?
Why it's you, brother?
This is different from my script!
I want a girl!
Why no girls for us?
Didn't we agree to draw lots?
This world is so dark.
Li Yao, it's your first time to be here.
How do you feel?
I think the view is so good.
Do you think so?
Li Yao, what's wrong with you?
I don't know.
It's my first time.
Are you... Are you acrophobia?
Does that mean I will feel dizzy,
and my heart beats fast?
Yes.
Well, I'm acrophobia.
Maybe because it's your first time here.
It's okay. It's okay.
Follow me. Calm down and breathe.
Make it stop. Make it stop!
Make it stop!
Anyone hear me?
-It's okay.
-Let me out!
-Li Yao, calm down.
Easy. I'm here.
Make it stop!
-Sit. Calm down.
-Stop this!
It's okay.
Let go!
My Kungfu won't help.
It's too high here!
I better let you hold my hands.
It's okay, Li Yao.
Breathe slowly.
What a beautiful view!
Such a rare opportunity. Still watching your phone?
Reference materials.
It's a rare opportunity to see such a beautiful view!
But you keep studying and studying.
You know nothing but studying!
Do you remember my brother took us out
to the amusement park when we were kids?
You enjoyed it much more than I did.
Since when did you become like this?
Because we've grown up.
If a grown-up have to be like this,
I wish I could be a kid forever.
Look, how beautiful the sunset is!
Do you know that?
Make a wish when the wheel reaches the peak.
It'll come true.
Really?
I should make a wish sincerely, then.
Let's do this together?
Okay.
But those clouds are really beautiful.
And such a beautiful sky wheel.
But I have to enjoy this with you...
No one made you stay in the same place with me.
But we always ended up together.
No matter when we were kids, or right now.
So despairing.
In fact, Li Yao, you know what?
You don't look fierce at all.
I think,
you're just a very cute girl.
What are you talking about?!
Better hold hands.
Isn't it pretty fun?
Ye Muxi, thank you for giving me
a most wonderful day in my life.
What's wrong with you guys?
Don't ask us. Don't want to answer that.
How are Cheng Ling and Li Yao doing now?
Come here. Come here.
How do you feel?
Not bad.
We make it anyway!
What?
That... That indescribable...
Flushing and heart beating.
Look. Look.
That's it.
All right.
Thank you.
You have fully proved yourself.
Come on, let's try another one! Let's go!
It's already dark. Ye Muxi!
Don't wanna play any more.
Li Yao, why are you still standing there?
Right. Come here.
Hurry, join us.
Let's go.
It's really fun.
Okay.
No.
-Okay.
-Not okay.
Li Yao, what brought you here?
Monitor.
I want to a member of our class committee.
Why did you suddenly have such a thought?
Here is the thing.
Since we came back from the amusement park,
I took your advice and always smiled at every student.
As a result...
Desirable results?
Some could understand that I wasn't bullying them.
But some...
Right.
If someone pops out and keeps smiling at you,
it's really creepy.
Never mind.
As long as some of them can understand me,
I feel very happy.
Besides, Liao Danyi has explained
to everyone who had misunderstanding about me.
Everyone starts to review me.
Liao Danyi?
Thank you very much.
And I admire you guys very much.
You can be together every day and you're happy.
So I want to further change myself.
If you don't look down upon me,
I'm willing to contribute all my bravery
and martial arts to you.
Why do I feel...
We've got a tough warrior?
May I?
Of course.
But you want to be...
I want a gentle position.
Commissary in charge of labor?
Okay, no problem.
Your ability goes beyond that.
But, before that...
You must teach me your arm & fist boxing.
Rise, please!
Monitor, don't worry.
I'll spare no effort.
Let me start it now.
Go to the playground first.
Here is our classroom.
A place for study.
My god.
You're so scaring.
Scaring?
Why?
I'm already not myself.
For you,
I've totally abandoned the old me.
Everything that I'm doing now,
is for you.
When your love for me blows hot and cold,
I'll lose my bearings.
I'm so useless.
I know you give up a lot for me.
I know you sacrifice your self-esteem
and pride to indulge me.
What a valuable thing it is!
This time, listen to me.
Next time, I'll listen to you.
If two people want to sustain their love,
they need to understand each other.
In this world,
how could someone like you ever exist?
there's someone like me
for someone like you in this world.
I'm not good at house chores.
I don't need a housekeeper.
I'm not good at cooking.
I don't need a chef.
I'm not good at social life.
I don't need a diplomatist.
What on earth do you want?
You.
I only want you.
I cry a lot.
You can lay in my arms.
Cry to your heart's content.
I'm very bad tempered and capricious.
I love your bad temper and your capriciousness.
No. No.
No!
Xinyi...
Did you get hurt?
What did you say just now?
Say it again?
I said, I'll give in to you in every way.
And dote on you.
Why do you have to push me?
Do I have to be a parrot with no self,
no ideas and thoughts of my own?
I won't make you a parrot!
I think there's something resonant between us.
Love might make me blind.
But it can't make me follow you blindly.
Do as I say is to follow me blindly?
Didn't expect you would judge our love like that!
You can't even fulfill the basic mutual understanding!
Let alone love!
Every time, it's me following your idea.
When have you followed mine?!
I got it.
I really want to be with you
through life and death together.
Whatever we do, we're on the same side.
But now, I think it's impossible.
Danyi!
How about this.
I'll buy you a new one.
Never mind. It's okay.
No. No.
I must buy you a new one as compensation.
I... I broke your mug. So I must compensate.
I... I probably have annoyed Li Yao.
This morning, she stopped next to my desk.
Raised my glass high in the air.
Next second, she broke it into pieces.
Now, I'm reflecting on myself seriously.
Hope I could find the reason why I annoyed her.
I didn't break it on purpose!
Who said I broke it on purpose?!
You?
Or you?