[ Are you there? ]
[ What's the matter? ]
[ Nothing special ]
[ A date? ]
[ Qianqing Palace ]
Guys.
I think you've already known that Liao Danyi
sent me a message today.
He says, a date?
I wanna know what that means.
Your majesty.
A date refers to all activities
that young people do when hanging out together.
To be specific, eat meals,
see movies,
walk on the street and other sensitive activities.
Liao Danyi... That's impossible.
Your majesty, Liao Danyi now is a rutting adolescent.
Won't let go of any girls around him.
Well, how should I reply?
Your majesty.
I think you may reply as ' a date about what' ?
Good idea.
Okay.
A date about what?
He replies.
He says, dining, XOXO.
XOXO?
Bad intentions! So obvious!
Shameless!
So, I reply as...
Of course no!
No.
Your majesty, if you give in right now,
it hurts your stateliness.
Your majesty, even if it's a trap,
you should go anyway!
Your majesty, say yes.
Then, okay is my reply.
Okay.
He says, looking forward to that.
Your majesty, I have an idea.
How about you send him ellipses as your reply?
Good.
E... Ellipses.
He sends me a smiling face.
This...
Your majesty.
You can send him a contemptuous look.
Saying you're going to take a shower.
This is the best way to end a talk.
He says, good night, hope I can dream of you.
This...
Damn it. Damn it.
This talk can't be ended.
What should I do?
Your majesty, I have an idea.
At such a moment, you only need to send him one word.
Then all problems will be solved.
What's that?
Interesting.
Smart.
Very smart, minister Li.
He's so smart.
What's wrong with you today? So weird.
Listen to me.
I won't be afraid of you at tonight's dinner!
Dinner? With whom?
Didn't you send messages to me that we'll dine together?
Messages? My account was hacked.
You don't know that?
He cheats people of money everywhere in my name.
I've told everyone.
Five hundred Yuan.
One thousand Yuan? This...
Scams are loathsome!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 05
I got this, Ye Muxi.
Just do it.
I feel sorry for what happened before.
So I always want a chance to apologize to you.
That thing, no big deal.
And it's a thing of the past. Don't take it seriously.
What's wrong, Ye Muxi?
Nothing. I suddenly feel my back...
How much sorrow do you have?
Just like a spring river running eastwards.
Good poem. Good poem.
I'm really good at reading poems!
[ Education Office, Director Yan ]
Now, class begins.
Class begins.
Good morning, class. Class begins.
Stand up.
Good morning, teacher.
What's wrong with you, monitor?
Don't know the rules for class?
Sorry, teacher.
I'm not the monitor.
I know you are not.
So tell me, where's your monitor?
That girl, are you the monitor?
So you just hide out there, mute, huh?
Come here.
What's your name?
Ye Muxi.
Ye Muxi?
Monitor.
Your brain must be mush, right?
Before class,
the monitor should lead the other students to say
good morning, teacher.
To show the basic respect for the teacher.
You know?
But you? Fugue?
Traveling in the Antarctic?!
Unbelievable! Stand outside!
Fine. I'm used to that.
What is this attitude?! Are you asking for trouble?
No.
I just... Hold this attitude to all the teachers.
Good. Very good.
Take your chair with you. Stand outside!
Don't believe I can't put you under control.
Take your chair with you.
Stand outside.
Hold it above your head!
Sorry, teacher.
I think it's not right to punish students in this way.
What a knight!
You've read too many tales of roving knights?
You stand outside, too!
Any other knights here?
Stand up if you're one.
If not, I'm gonna say more.
Since you all know what a cruel character I am,
I'm gonna restate a few requirements before class.
First, don't look around during the class!
Once found, outside.
Second,
during the class, don't whisper to each other.
Once found, outside!
Outside!
Outside! Outside! Outside!
Only you behave yourself.
Listen,
For anything,
no rules, no gains!
Okay. Let's start the class now.
Big boss, I need help.
Me, too. Big boss.
What?
Can't stand it any more.
I'm dying.
So what? I can't stand it for you.
Can't stand it any more. What should I do?
What are you looking at?
Are you guys in a PE class?
If not,
why you all stand outside?
Because...
They're being punished!
Monitor of Class Ten, you're such a good example!
Such a class is really not suitable for
a good student like Liao Danyi, huh?
Yes.
What did you mean?
You'll figure it out.
Let's go.
I hate students of Class One the most!
Why so arrogant?
Yes!
Back to your spot!
I was not angry.
Before you said that!
Emperor Yao wanted to give his empire to Xu You.
Xu You declined.
Emperor Shun wanted to give his throne to Zizhou Zhibo.
Zizhou Zhibo replied...
Mr. Wu, what a good mood!
Miss Luo, class is over?
Hurry, go check up on your class.
What's wrong with my class?
All your students are standing outside the classroom.
Don't you feel ashamed?
What?
Do I have to repeat that?
Put it down, all of you.
Which one of your dares to?
Director Yan.
Isn't it improper?
On which aspect?
The students in your class
don't know have to behave in class.
I tell them to reflect on themselves outside.
To think about their mistakes.
Director Yan.
Now it's not your class time.
The next class is mine.
I want my students to go back preparing for it.
Any problem?
See how your monitor behaves now?
Mr. Wu...
-You... You...
-Inside!
You're going against me in public.
What do you want?
Teach students according to their aptitude, you know?
Adopt different teaching methods before different students.
For students like them,
you should make them do some thinking outside!
To cherish our school.
And the wonderful time on campus.
Director Yan.
You've made they standing here for forty-five minutes.
I don't know what on earth have they got?
Wu,
mind your talking attitude to me.
Anyway,
I will never agree to any psychical punishment like this.
Fine.
Facts.
Talk to me again based on some facts!
-Teacher...
-You scared me.
Cool! So cool!
Am I?
Yes. Cool.
Call me Wu Sir, then.
Yes, Wu Sir!
Let's go.
Go. Yes.
Liao Danyi.
What's the matter?
Liao Danyi,
why are you eating alone here?
It seems that you haven't made any friends in this class.
I just like eating alone.
Really?
I think it's because
you've realized you're not the same with them.
Have you filled in the Class Transfer Application?
Liao Danyi.
I know you're good in study.
But what are you hesitating about?
Such a good chance.
I don't know what makes Miss Xinyi love...
You've said too much.
Got it.
Liao Danyi.
I still hope you can transfer into our class.
Hope you can think about that.
Where are you going?
Suddenly I feel that I have no appetite.
Want to eat in some other place.
Why are you here?
Where's your master?
Want to eat some?
I can feed you.
I'm Liao Danyi. What's your name?
Did you smell something?
Me, too.
What's going on?
Hot pot?
What are you doing here?
Having lunch.
Meat.
Who is this?
Seems to be someone's pet.
Speaking of that, in normal cases,
have you seen anyone taking a hot pot into school as lunch?
Any problem?
No.
I can't help it.
Hot pot is so delicious, isn't it?
Listen,
the hot pot inventor is so crime-ridden.
People can't stand any other food once they've eaten hot pot.
Don't you think so?
Xiaotian, you gotta take a shower anyway!
Runs away again.
Sorry!
My hot pot!
Xiaotian?
Yes, that's his name.
I'm so useless.
Let him run away again.
He's the protector at girls' dormitory!
Can we have dogs in school?
What are you doing?
Still have some water in my ear.
He's not just a dog.
In the past, he was a star's guide dog.
But he retired after his master died.
It's said that he's being taken care of by Mrs. dorm manager.
A guide dog? So awesome!
But you...
Trying to bathe him. He's too dirty!
Director Yan says, if not,
he'll be sent into the animal sanctuary.
How could he do that?!
Most dogs don't like bathing.
If only someone could help him with that.
How about this, I got this.
He's very agile.
It's not a easy job.
Me, monitor of Class Ten, will do.
Any direct connection to that?
Really? Thank you.
So, about this matter,
I will put it in a simple way.
You'll get some fruit and a brush.
To stop him running away,
you should hold him tight.
And stay with me like my follower.
Then watch me bathe him.
Okay?
Where are you going?
Review my lessons. Good luck to you.
He feels closer to you!
But I'm not the one who promised to bathe him.
You're always like this, ignoring your limits.
Since that, don't expect me to help you.
Why so stubborn?
I'll show you I can!
[ To bathe Xiaotian, Plan A ]
Xiaotian,
I don't think you won't fall into my hands.
Big boss!
What are you doing?
You... Why holding a water pipe?
Why eating my chicken nuggets?!
Yours?
They fell on the ground...
Belong to whoever found them first!
I prepared these for Xiaotian!
Who's Xiaotian?
[ To bathe Xiaotian, Plan B ]
Can you do yesterday's chemical experiment?
Barely.
I feel like that I haven't seen that equation.
In this way, you won't find me again.
As a dog, you're too acute!
[ To bathe Xiaotian, Plan C ]
In this way, you won't be afraid of any human.
I really can't catch you...
What happened?
Who are you?
Let's be friends?
Just because you students buy him dog food
and sausages,
and whatever is delicious.
Do you think you have some spare money?
You can barely afford your own food!
But buy food for that dog, that animal?
Unbelievable! So unbelievable!
What's going on, Miss Liu?
Girl.
The thing is getting worse.
What Director Yan stepped on was Xiaotian's...
Waste.
Shit!
How many times I've told you?!
It's a very dangerous, very insanitary thing!
Remove him right now!
Don't make me see him again!
Xiaotian is totally harmless.
Xiaotian?
Who's Xiaotian?
Miss Liu, who's Xiaotian?
He's just an animal!
Why give him a name?!
You know, it'll give many hidden troubles!
He doesn't bathe.
So dirty every day.
So many infectious diseases!
What if students get infected?
You gotta know,
he's never bathed again since his former master died!
No one disposes him?
No one can dispose him, right?
Fine, I decide to call the Animal Control right now.
Let professionals deal with him!
My shoe is so stained.
Animal Control? What's that?
People say it's a shelter for homeless animals.
If animals sent there haven't been adopted for a long time,
will receive mercy killing.
No, that's not good.
We gotta hurry and find a solution.
Can't let that happen!
No. I gotta find a way out.
Xiaotian!
I really have no time or other ways.
So, listen to me carefully.
I know you fear this.
But this is nothing. Look!
Not fearful at all!
What the hell are you doing here?!
Make room!
This animal again.
Director, he has a name. He's Xiaotian.
Aren't you  that student in Class Ten?
I'm Ye Muxi.
Monitor of Class Ten, Grade Ten.
Who stood outside?
He's bathed.
So, let him stay in our school.
How many times I've told you?
It's not about bathing or not.
No one watches him.
There will be many hidden troubles, you know?
I can take care of him!
Do you know...
Please. Here's the thing. Students like him a lot.
As a working dog, Xiaotian is very obedient.
Look, students volunteer to bathe him, which proves...
I don't wanna hear that. Shut up.
No. Stop. Shut up.
People of the Animal Control haven't come?
Where are they?
Director Yan.
They're here, Director Yan.
Hurry. Hurry. Catch him.
Take this dirty thing away from me!
How could you do this?!
What are you looking at here?
What are you doing?!
What am I doing?
Are you gonna bathe with him every day?
Ye Muxi, you gotta know.
This is the reality world.
Not those scribbles on your books.
Not a game that you can play with.
What nonsense are you talking about?!
I'm educating you.
None of your business!
I'm helping you get back on the right track of life.
Yezi, you're back.
What's wrong?
Class One, Grade Ten ]
[Where's the President of the Student Union?
Please give this back to her.
I've thought it through.
Forgive me for refusing the class transfer.
I have got to stay in Class Ten based on a reason.
It's still a long way to correct someone's conceptions.
[ Destined Encounter ]
So great!
Xue Xiaodong's new album,
My Valentine's Day Sweet Baby.
So amazing!
Makes people feel so delighted mentally.
He deserves to be the most handsome lad!
Come on, my fans!
Share it, come on!
Like it, come on!
I think, last year's
My Christmas Sweet Baby is better.
Wait. Wait.
I got it.
What?
This man thinks I haven't listened to last year's album
but listen to this year' album directly?
Why should he?
Besides,
Is there anyone on this planet
never listened to My Christmas Sweet baby?
If there is, caveman?
In fact, think about it,
if Xue Xiaodong often visits this website,
and checks his fans' messages,
it must be very interesting.
In fact, most fans are rational.
So those girls who make going to school a trouble for me,
their number is few after all.
Wait.
Why he says 'me'?
Why did you say 'me'?
What are you thinking about?
I'm just an ordinary fan surfing the internet in Wandering Cafe.
Wandering Cafe?
Right here?
This guy is in the same place with me?
Why does it feel like a destined encounter?
Is he...
Is he Xue...
Shanqi, hi.
Who're you? Shameless!
That girl running away seems to be...
Shanqi?