# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 06
Spicy strip?
You like this?
Super delicious.
What happened to you two?
Who?
Liao Danyi. Had some kind of spat?
What?
Get over with it.
We're all friends!
Who is his friend?!
Obviously. You know who.
Zhu Shanqi. Listen to me.
Since I was young,
I always wanted to get rid of him.
But I just couldn't.
He is like some shadow behind me.
I have nothing to do with him, like forever.
Do you hear me?!
So you two need to cooperate on this.
Wait.
It happened too fast.
Give me a minute.
Is there anything that I can't complete by myself?
Well...
Just tell me.
It's a job for two.
So you two need to finish it together.
Your classmates, Wang Liangchen and Xu Meijing.
They're very good friends.
It's a good thing to find a good friend at school.
But recently,
this pure relationship seems
to be heading for a bad direction.
So, to stop this pure friendship turning into
some dangerous thing for your age.
You two, please talk with those two students.
Tell them, at your age,
you should focus on study.
Wu sir.
I think you should talk with them. It'll be better.
I wish they could listen to me.
Besides, truth be told.
I have tried.
But they two laughed, very hard.
They told me they are just good friends.
And told me I was being paranoid.
In the end,
They gave me this sweater as a gift.
Nice handwork!
If they're really just pure friends like they said.
Then that will make me like that kind of rustic teacher!
No! I'm the coolest handsome Wu sir.
So I have to ask you two
to talk with Liangchen and Meijing nicely as their classmates.
To see if my concern is necessary
Or it was just in my head.
You're our Chinese teacher.
But, if they're really not that simple.
What shall we do?
Then in class committee's name,
save them out from this fruitless relationship.
So I will take Wang Liangchen.
And you handle Xu Meijing.
Do you hear me?
Did I just hear some sound of the wind?
When will you stop ignoring me?
I really felt there's something!
But I don't know where.
Ye Muxi. You're so mature.
I'm not mature.
The commissary in charge of studies is so mature.
Not like a human!
Xiaotian shouldn't just wander in school.
So what?
You'll let them take it, and kill it?
Whatever you think.
That's because you can't answer me.
I'm not doing this with you.
Then stay away from me.
Fine, stay away from Liangchen and Meijing.
Let me handle it alone.
You alone? Why?
I can do it as well.
I can handle it better than you.
Do you know what is love?
Do you have any experience?
Like you do.
At least I've watched many love movies.
Is there anything in those real?
Just some middle-aged men and women
stay at home and make it up!
It's art. You don't understand!
You said all of that to make your point.
Childish!
You're childish!
Say more and you're an idiot.
- I don't want...
- Idiot!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot!
Hello.
Hello Meijing.
Can I sit here?
You already did.
Anything I can help with? Ye Muxi.
I found we barely talked before.
So let's talk.
Okay, okay.
Let's talk about love.
Love?
I think the most beautiful
and magical thing in the world is love.
What about you?
I think it's okay.
I saw a movie the other day.
About love.
I'm so interested.
What movie?
Pleasant Goat.
Is there anything? Liao Danyi.
It's wrong.
Thank you. Liao Danyi.
I didn't think you're a man who likes to chat.
I didn't know you're so kind-hearted.
Look, we're having a great time.
Since that,
Then let's talk about...
Some secrets.
I think I'll pass.
It's okay. I'll go first.
Then you can tell me yours.
Okay.
My secret is
when no one is around
or when I am at home.
I'll sing and dance like a crazy person.
Especially when taking a shower.
I will take the shower caddy as my microphone.
And sing songs.
I'll make much noise.
Until my neighbor comes by to complain.
That is my secret.
Don't tell anyone.
What is yours?
[- Don't forget. Jinbao Street, 3p.m. tomorrow
- Okay, see you there.]
Well, Ye Muxi.
I've got to deal with something. I've to go now.
Wait, you...
Talk next time. Bye.
Wait, you can't let me talk in vain!
I just told you my secret!
Any other things I can help with?
Relationship.
Relationship... Sorry.
[- Don't forget. Jinbao Street, 3p.m. tomorrow
- Okay, see you there.]
What about relationship?
Nothing. I've gotta go now.
Wonder girl. Why summon us?
I do need to see you.
I want to ask you about love.
Love?
Mr. Wolong?
I'm a realistic man.
For a wife, virtuous is more important than good looking.
For a relationship, stable is more important than sweet.
So I don't know much about love.
Rumors say,
your wife looks...
Like a dinosaur.
You...
How could you say that about Mrs. Wolong?
What he said is true.
What about you?
His wife is quite beautiful.
But very fierce and tough.
How do you males talk like that?
If a girl is quite open,
you'll say she is fierce and tough right?
Tell me, you're based on what?
She has killed someone.
You men are really not helping.
Where's Hua Mulan?
Wait.
Dragon Shape Changing.
I'm Hua Mulan!
Are... Are you sure?
That's right.
This is my style.
Think about it.
If I'm not like this,
then how could I pretend to be a man in the army?
Fine.
I want to ask you about love.
Don't know.
Why?
What you heard are all made up!
You guys really can't help me.
Can you be quiet?
Why you didn't study?
It's boring.
Then what is not boring?
Games.
What can those help you?
Makes me happy.
Useless.
When do you think my brother will come to pick me?
Don't know.
Let's play for a while.
You've been reading for such a long time.
Just five minutes.
Let's play for a while, okay?
Let's play hide and seek, okay?
If you can find me, I'll...
I'll stop and read books with you.
Don't wanna play.
Just for a while.
Let's play hide and seek, okay?
Don't wanna play.
Just for a while.
Let's play.
Fine.
Then I'll go hide first.
You count to one hundred.
One. Two. Three...
Ninety-eight. Ninety-nine. One hundred.
She is finally gone.
I can do my Mathematical Olympiad again.
Normal friends watch movies at weekend together.
Liao Danyi.
Let me finish this well.
Wait and watch me.
But it's so far away.
I wish I had a telescope.
Thank you.
You... What're you doing here?
I was gonna ask you that.
How did you know they're gonna watch movies together?
I saw Meijing's ticket booking message on her phone.
Me too.
So what now?
Play it by ear.
Let's see how this relationship works.
A cup of hot milk tea. Hurry.
Right now. Now! I'm thirsty.
Okay, wait a second.
This, two for this one.
This and this.
This and this. Add.
They're in the shopping mall.
Okay, let's go in.
After they got in.
We followed them for a day.
But they didn't hug nor join hands.
No kiss either.
Does pure friendship really
exist between a boy and a girl?
Then why am I here?
Did I just waste a day?
Hello, you two.
I'm the owner here.
You two are very lucky.
You're the one thousandth couple in our store.
We have a prize for that!
Sir, we're not a couple.
We're not!
Not what you think.
We're not a couple.
Here, here. Super ice cream.
Dear, I'm so happy.
I'm so lucky to have you! God!
Ice cream! Can I have a spoon?
Okay. Okay.
A spoon!
Right, right. That's right.
Do you want one? No?
I want this. I'll eat. I'll eat.
They're just playing together.
What?
If I don't actually use it, they'll see us!
Then I want that tiger.
Okay.
No intimate moves.
Wu sir and us can relax now.
Luckily I didn't miss the opening.
Don't forget why we're doing this in here.
No talking in the movie theater.
Don't you know that?
They're in a flower shop.
Should have some moves.
They didn't do a thing for so long.
We should leave!
Wait!
Rose! Rose!
Proof of love!
Go out, now! now!
Calm down, calm down.
They changed it.
Why lily?!
I'm done! I'm exhausted!
I give up.
I'm so tired.
We can't just continue like this.
Congrats! You're the ninety-ninth couple in our store.
Here, a free bouquet for you two.
Why this is happening again?
Don't take it then.
70 Yuan for a salad?
Don't order it if you find it expensive.
You're kidding me.
Order whatever you want.
It's okay, I'll pay.
Okay.
Steak looks nice.
Lobster! Lobster!
Waitress, how big is the lobster?
Do you have hotpot?
You look a little nervous.
What?
It's not your first time to eat with a boy, right?
Are you kidding me?
I eat with boys every day!
Like wash my face and brush my teeth. Daily!
What does it feel to have dinner with a boy alone?
Just fine.
We're too far away.
What're they talking about?
How would I know?
Must be some other topic.
They look quite enjoying it.
You can't tell that.
Look.
Liangchen, don't you think our monitor is so beautiful?
She is so great.
I want to be her closest friend.
Not a good idea.
I heard she's gonna immigrate to Mars once she graduates.
Okay, Liangchen. I admit it.
In fact, I'm a robot.
I'm here to save the world.
Face the reality.
They're talking sweet things to each other.
Like...
I'm so happy today!
Can hang out with such an amazing person!
I'm also feel so happy
to eat and shop with such a charming girl.
Do you really think I'm charming?
I really do.
And what attracts me is your charisma.
Really?
Yeah.
It feels so strange.
As a man, I should hate to go to the shopping mall.
But when you're around.
I always find time flies.
Really?
Yes.
They're about to leave.
Are they really friends or a couple?
Maybe friends.
But does pure friendship really exist
between a boy and a girl?
How would I know?
I don't have any male friend.
You don't think we are....
We're just neighbors.
Grew up together.
That's all.
Anything else?
You're the person I hate the most in the world.
Then why did you always come
play with me when you were young?
Because I was blind.
But, you were so nice when you were young.
I didn't know since when
you became so so so annoying.
Always pointing fingers.
Won't let me draw pictures in class.
Won't let me do bla bla bla.
Won't let me play games, etc.
Of course I would hate you.
I just want you to be a little mature.
So you can take care of yourself.
It's my own business. Not yours!
They seem okay to me.
Let's call it a day.
Waiter.
Congrats, you two.
You're the one thousandth couple in our store.
You can get 70% off.
Hello, hello.
Liao Danyi, what brought you here?
Co..incidence?
Exhausted.
I wasted a whole day which I could study a lot.
Danyi, did you see Yezi?
I didn't.
Shouldn't be.
She should be home at this hour.
Besides, I made her favorite hotpot today.
Where could she go?
Right, Danyi.
Come,come.
Think about it.
Have you seen her?
Where could she go?
Okay, Danyi.
I'll go out to look for her.
If you hear anything about her,
Come to my house to tell me, okay?
Good kid.
Can't be it....
She wouldn't hide until now.
It has been five hours.
Ye Muxi.
Come out. You win.
God. Please.
Let me find Ye Muxi.
I promise. If I find her.
I'll take the responsibility to guide her.
Before she is able to undertake something alone.
I will always be by her side.
So please god.
Let me find her.
Ye Muxi. What're you doing here?
Liao Danyi, you found me!
Let's go home.
It's your turn to hide now.
Another day.
Let's go home to have some hotpot okay?
Okay
Liao Danyi. You really suck at this.
It took you such a long time.
Right. Ye Muxi.
Sorry.
Next time, wherever you hide,
I'll find you at once.
You promise?
I promise.
[Examination Room]
Teacher, I finished it.
I did the math. If I miss one exam.
Our scores should be close.
I'm just keeping my word.
Ye Muxi and Liao Danyi followed us today.
But they didn't find our relationship.
Right, they're too naive.
Our camouflage has no flaw.
Because we are...
Abracadabra
Meijing.
We've been hiding in this country for so long.
Waiting to find the soul of Chinese Kungfu.
Meijing, let's go.
Alright.
That's what they are?!