# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 10
Use this on director Yan.
Crumb it, put it in director Yan's mug.
Let's go.
Si Mayi is so handsome.
I couldn't quit it.
Wish I can stay at home to watch it everyday.
Monitor of Class Ten.
What're are you doing here?
I'm here as the president of the Student Union
to let you know that because
you've recovered your blackboard newspaper
and teacher Wu Heng pleaded with the headmaster.
So the headmaster decides to give you a chance
to participate in the blackboard newspaper competition.
Good luck.
But to be honest.
There's no much point.
After all, Class One will win the champion.
What... What do you mean?
We're also very good.
Nothing really.
It's just... You won't win.
What on heck?!
Ignore them.
We're awesome!
We have so many talented classmates.
Right.
Yes, they can get high scores.
It's not certain that will apply to the blackboard newspaper!
All the top art talent students are all in Class One.
Of course they're good.
It's nothing really.
Come with me later.
What for?
To spy on our enemy.
Class one wins the championship every year.
This year, I bet they're good also.
I don't believe they will win this time.
They're just some bookworms.
How good that can be?!
It's too professional.
It's a foul to be that professional.
Senior high school students are not like that!
I didn't know Class One is so good.
We can't underestimate them.
Look, let's settle a theme for our blackboard newspaper first.
Well, any ideas?
Boss, how about this?
We'll draw the Arena of Valor: 5v5 Arena Game.
Up-way, mid-way, down-way.
Red buff, blue buff, big and little dragons.
Draw them all.
We'll definitely defeat them!
[ Victory ]
Big boss, feel that? That's it!
So interesting. Okay?
Right, another idea.
Death, Naruto, One Piece.
Uzumaki Naruto with Monkey D Luffy. Blood boiling youth!
Monitor, understand?
I think... Music.
We use music elements blend with fashion elements.
We'll be surely outstanding!
I think the theme can be a fairy story about a prince and a princess.
My princess, me and my horse
come here to pick you up.
You're so beautiful.
My prince, have you noticed that
your horse is a little different from the other horses.
I'm a horse.
Don't say that.
When he was young.
The others laughed at him a lot because of that.
Actually, he is quite cute.
I'm a horse.
Cute. Look. See?
Cute.
I think we're students.
We should focus on study.
How about we draw an encyclopedia poster?
You're such a dull.
I think it's not enough.
Yuan Ke'er is much better than us together.
If Yuan Ke'er can draw something not so strange.
We'll win the first place.
I don't believe we adding up together won't beat Yuan Ke'er.
It's true.
Union is strength.
We must trust each other.
How about this, use this blackboard as an experiment.
Draw whatever in our thoughts.
I believe it will be wonderful, okay?
Okay, I agree.
Monitor, you know what?
I started to learn painting since I was four.
Don't underestimate me.
I know you didn't see that in me usually.
How should we put it?
It feels...
very fashionable.
Cool.
It's so ugly, gosh!
How could it be so terrible?!
Without Yuan Ke'er.
We're screwed, totally screwed you know?
Where're you going?
Monitor, it's late.
We're gonna go home to do our homework.
Go for it, monitor.
We'll definitely win!
Looking forward to the competition. Bye.
You're just gonna give up?
What shall we do?
It's a competition.
Since we're in.
We'll do our best.
What other choices do you have?
Do it on your own.
[Out Of Inspiration]
See through all the secrets in the world
See your next move in my hands.
The legend prophet in Maple Leaf Middle School
I'm Shen Wei.
Spokesman for Love and Justice.
Devil and angel's embodiment.
The strongest team in Maple Leaf Middle School.
Huang Yi.
Huang Nan.
I'm your big boss Ye Muxi.
Monitor.
You can count on me.
Hello, everyone. I'm Xue Xiaodong.
185cm, 66kg.
Like singing and dancing.
Today, we need to discuss about an important thing.
Recently, one of our classmates haven't showed up for days.
That student is Yuan Ke'er.
I believe she must be kidnapped by some mysterious organization.
Shen Wei did some research.
Please.
The blackboard newspaper competition is about to begin.
Ke'er is still missing.
I've done some research last night.
And listed all the suspicious persons and organizations on this paper.
Please pass around.
Shen Wei is right.
But the reason we need to find her
is not because of the competition.
It is because that she is our classmate.
What is Demon Dancing Group?
Sounds so scary!
Demon Dancing Group is the most famous organization nearby.
They occupy the square, public sitting area forcibly.
They make loud noise.
And dance in the square day and night.
You mean the square dancing ladies?
Kill& Punishment Duo?
What? Let me see.
Kill& Punishment Duo
are the cunning old fox Liu Laoliu
and the calm owl Wang Shisan.
A super intelligence combination.
They occupy the pavilions and benches on the streets
to play poker and chess.
And they always make people play with them.
You mean the old poker players?
What are those strange names?
Liberation Streets' Front
Those guys like to dance hip-hop
play music and skateboard etc.
Not some scary groups.
Any problem?
Don't you think this is the most suspicious one?
Welcome to our place. Anything we can help with?
We're students from Class Ten, Grade One.
I'm Ye Muxi.
I heard there's a student called Yuan Ke'er.
We're here to see her.
Yuan Ke'er?
Never met her.
Don't lie to us.
I know she is in here. Hand her out.
You mean I lied?
No.
But we know she is here.
So please cooperate.
It's not a place for kids. Leave now.
If you don't hand her out today,
this will not be over today.
This is your place but mine as well.
We are not leaving, neither can you.
We're young hooligans.
You want to take over this place?
Show me what have you gotten.
Come on, come on.
We don't want any trouble.
That's it? Right.
Boss, they're brothers, Huang Nan and Huang Yi.
I didn't know you two are quite famous.
Are you kidding me?
No one can beat me in this.
I didn't expect that truly.
But next,
I don't think you can handle it.
Black, you go.
What do you want?
What do you expect?
Ready?
Come on baby.
Wrapping head type.
Kicking type.
Waist type.
Waist circle type.
Marshmallow yepe.
Wrapping head type.
Three times left, three times right.
Dance battle.
Come on, come on.
Stage pose at last!
Scared?
How is that?
Black is our best hip-hop dancer here.
Xiaodong. Go.
So what? Hooligans are brave fighters.
This is nothing.
Let me show you what are true bros.
Hand!
What're you doing?
Do you trust me?
I don't!
Trust me!
Ye Muxi!
My hand. My hand!
Ye Muxi. No, no!
My hand.
My test papers.
My future. My future.
This is family.
I don't know you can trust each other with your future.
Anyone else?
No, right?
Ke'er. I know you're in there.
No matter what. We have something to tell you.
Right, Ke'er. Come out.
Come out. Ke'er.
So come out.
Come out, Ke'er.
Ke'er. I don't know why.
But I remember when you first came to our school.
You're such an innocent, cute and good girl.
But I don't know what happened to you.
to make you changed and stay in this place.
Tell me, did anyone do anything to you?
Who bullied you? I'll make him apologize to you.
Trust me. Tell us.
What do you know?
When she came to school,
she was a girl with a big dream.
But your classmate told her,
what she drew was nothing but garbage.
That makes her become like this.
Who is that? So bold!
Tell me.
Who? Who said that?
-Right.
-who's that? Tell us.
That classmate is your monitor.
Repeat that.
Give me a second.
Come.
Do you have something to tell us about that?
I don't know.
It's just...
I believe you. You can do it!
What the heck?
That's our blackboard newspaper!
I can't live with that. Wipe it off.
I quit!
That....about the blackboard newspaper...
Her picture doesn't fit it.
So I told her to wipe it.
It's easy, you go apologize to her.
I agree.
She is not that kind of type to apologize.
Why? Why I'm not that type?
You won't apologize to her.
I will apologize. Who said I won't?
Do you remember when you were young?
What? when?
When you were three, you did something wrong.
What? I apologized.
I apologized back then.
- Did you?
- Yes.
- You didn't
- I did.
- You never apologized
- I also apologized at five.
- In primary school
- I apologized for all of that.
In primary school you snatched my schoolbag.
What?
You scrawled on my book.
Right, but I apologized.
- In middle school
- I apologized.
You never apologized.
I did.
- I apologized at five
- No, you didn't.
Fine, fine, fine. I'll go apologize.
Let's go.
Yuan Ke'er.
Our monitor Ye Muxi has something to tell you.
Say it out.
Louder.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
Say it!
Turn around!
Stand still.
I'm sorry.
In Chinese.
Say it properly.
I'm sorry.
Can't hear you.
Hurry.
Wanna muddle through?
So...sorry.
Louder.
So...sorr...
Lost your voice? Hurry.
I'm sorry!
Why did you apologize to me?
Because I said your picture is not good.
So do you think it's beautiful now?
I always think it's beautiful.
It's just I don't know how to appreciate it.
Now you think Class Ten needs me?
We need you. So...
Come back to Class Ten.
Okay.
You think I'm just gonna let you take her away that easily?
Why don't you let her go?
Because she is only pretty girl in here.
What do you mean?
Sorry, just being honest.
What do you want?
What do we want?!
Stop it!
You bunch of kids.
You should be studying at school.
What're you doing here?
What're you doing with these wimpy kids?
Who is a wimpy kid?
You.
You think I'm afraid of a middle-aged man?
Who is middle-aged?!
Listen to me.
Middle-aged means people above thirty-five by law.
I'm thirty-four.
Wu Sir, what're you doing here?
Shanqi told me.
So I come to check.
This kind of thing,
I think we should let our teacher know it.
Get lost!
O...Original Boss?
Who are you?
It's me, Doggy.
The Doggy, your follower back then.
Doggy?
I remember you now.
You're not a kid anymore.
Don't touch our boss.
Do you know who is this?
My boss.
The hooligan of hooligans.
The strongest among the strongest.
Wu Heng.
What's going on?
I feel so dizzy.
What's happening?
Who can explain this for us?
Students, here's the thing.
It's just I'm also once young.
I'm the founder of this gang.
But when I built this,
it was not like this.
I built this to benefit the society.
To help people in need.
Like helping old grandma to cross the road.
Carrying goods for old grandpa.
But them?
What're you guys doing here?
Ignore all the rules and duties.
Since that,
I think it's time to dismiss this society.
Boss.
Don't call me Boss, he is our boss.
You heard him.
Dismiss then.
Why're you still standing here?
Don't you hear that?
Go.
Go home for dinner. Leave.
Bye, boss.
Don't stay in here.
Go home and do your homework.
Do hand it in tomorrow.
Ke'er.
So you came here today, for what?
Ke'er, about the blackboard newspaper.
I have so many things to tell you.
Yuan Ke'er.
Actually, I went to get you back
is not because of the blackboard newspaper.
It's because you're one of Class Ten.
But if you don't want to participate the competition.
We can totally understand.
No, I want in.
I caused too much trouble earlier.
Let me do something for Class Ten this time.
Okay.
It's great!
Now I'll announce the results of the blackboard newspaper.
The third prize, Class Five, Grade One.
The Second prize, Class Two, Grade One.
The First prize,
Class One, Grade One.
Not in the top three?
What? What did you say?
Class ten, Grade One? Top three?
Hilarious!
You know what?
We only care about the top three.
The others are not in the list.
Otherwise, you must be hanging at the last!
What is that thing on your blackboard?
Comics?
Any knowledge? Any useful content?
You want a prize by that?
Hilarious!
Well, the winners.
Send a representative to get the prize in Guidance office.
Congrats! Congrats!
Okay, dismiss. Dismiss.
Class Ten, calm down.
Don't be upset.
You're Class Ten.
It's normal to be defeated by us.
We'll win.
What did you say?
Listen to me.
We, Class ten will defeat your class at least once in this semester.
Keep dreaming.
Enough.
Don't argue with those boring guys.
Let's go.
Who is boring? Explain it.
Liao Danyi.
One day you'll realize.
You're nothing like your classmates there.
I'm so mad. So mad
Can't hear you.
I'll beat you to death.
Monitor.
Thank you for giving me the chance.
Sorry I let you down.
Why?
We should thank you for that.
You've done a lot.
It's so beautiful.
But we didn't win any prize.
No, you won.
You won the best painter prize in Class Ten.
Is there such a prize?
I'm the monitor,
I have the right to create a prize like that.
Create?
And most beautiful painter prize.
Most creative work prize.
Any prize for me?
I always want some prize.
Yes. The most handsome idol prize.
I'm flattered.
You earned it.
The trophy?
I'm the monitor of Class Ten.
So today, I'll hand the prize to you.
Let's go to that shop.
I'll buy ice cream for everyone!
Psychological victory?
Commissary in charge of studies.
We can't use the class fee for this.
So we'll go dutch.
No way.
How about we throw Ke'er up in the air?
Are we really gonna do that?
We didn't win any prize.
No, no.
We just want to...throw her!
Let go! Let go!