Damn it. That stupid driver hits another car.
Sir, I'm really sorry. Sorry.
It's all my fault!
I'll be responsible for all of this. Okay?
Miss Guan might be late because of this.
What could I do?
I'm about to be late!
I can only run to school.
Isn't that Liao Danyi?
He's also so late.
[ Maple Leaf Middle School ]
In this case,
am I gonna run into school
at the same time with him?
So other students will see us running together?
They will gossip, right?
They'll make guesses about our relationship.
If that happens,
we'll give it a try and date?
Then we'll stay together forever?
Annoying. Why are you thinking so much?
Now, one step at a time.
Since all people know it,
how about we...
First, run into school together.
As long as I catch up with him. Catch up with him.
Catch up with him.
He runs so fast!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 09
There's confusion in your eyes.
You must feel very confused deep down.
Spit it out.
Big Long.
I'm Wolong.
I'm already crouching here.
You still don't know my name?
Get me up.
Why?
I can't get up by myself.
Thank you.
What's the matter? Shoot.
I want you to do me a favor.
Just ask me for help.
I'll tell you everything I know.
Shut up, animal.
You empty big head. What idea do you have?
To help her out?
My head is big?
Do you remember that day...
I'm here! Coming.
Yezi is not calling you. But me.
Me. Me.
I've lived for hundreds of years.
That's my first time to see
someone being pulled down by his head.
You gotta be kidding me!
Wonder girl, you know?
That day, he was doping off.
I'm stuck.
He... He still pretended being calm.
You big headed giant baby!
You big headed mongolism!
You big headed loser!
You big headed idiot!
Think about it.
Aren't we both big headed?
It seems that you're useless.
Gotta erase you two.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Just tell us what's the matter.
Yes.
Today, I got a crime mystery.
Can't figure it out.
I really want to now who's the criminal!
Easy. Let me do some calculation.
Then I'll tell you the truth.
Those thick and short fingers can do calculation?
Don't judge everything by appearance.
Don't judge people by their looks.
The society really has changed.
All based on face value.
Okay. Okay. My fault.
Heroes, please get down to business.
What I'm gonna tell you is,
now the undercurrent is flowing.
Don't be panic.
Let reproduce the crime scene.
Look, this is almost a masterpiece!
Yes, a white wall changed overnight.
Awesome.
What are you guys doing here?
Class Ten of Grade Ten!
Don't you know the use of a blackboard newspaper?
To show your class's features and virtues.
And this is your class's features and virtues, right?
Who did this? Who painted this? Stand out.
We still don't know who did this.
Fine. You better not let me know who did this.
Erase it, right now, at once!
Because of someone's prank,
Our class's qualification for
the blackboard newspaper race gets canceled.
But, never mind.
If that one wants to admit his or her mistake,
please come to me.
But if you don't,
you may come to me privately.
I won't blame you for that.
I'm not strict with anyone.
I'm quite liberal.
Unlike someone.
Commissary in charge of studies,
although he's not our monitor...
This is obviously painted by monitor herself.
Ye Muxi.
I know you're very ambitious.
But to write a chapter of your life
is not to do graffiti art on school's white walls.
What?
Graffiti on our school's white walls, is not yours?
No. How could it be possible?
But that's your painting style.
No.
Many students tell me, that's definitely your work.
No. You really get me wrong.
Look, this is my painting style.
Totally different from those on the wall.
Indeed different.
Why on the Chinese textbook?
Ye Muxi.
When you're in my class,
Ye Muxi, what were you doing?
Why did you do this to me?
Anyway, I didn't paint that.
And, I'm the monitor.
I'll find the criminal. Rest easy.
Explain this to me.
Okay.
Come back!
I'm on it!
Come back. Come back.
Make it clear to me.
How does it go?
Still no one confesses to you?
I've been sitting there for a whole day.
Waiting and waiting.
No one comes to me.
I'm not surprised.
I really don't get it.
I'm so merciful, so cute.
And so nice.
Why no one confesses to me?
It seems that I can only take that one as a criminal,
rather than my fellow student.
I've read so many detective novels since I was a child.
Now it'll finally come  handy!
Watch me solve this problem perfectly.
You're not wearing glasses.
Why touch imaginary rims?
Let's start a brilliant deduction.
Now we're the suspect.
If we want to enter this crime scene,
we can only get in by the door.
But according to our deduction,
the door wasn't locked at that time.
Because once this kind of door gets locked,
it can only be opened by the key.
Well, what time is it now?
We can also know the crime time through deduction.
Either in daytime or at night.
And the criminal's gender...
Can also be known through deduction.
Either boy or girl.
There's also a third possibility.
Now, let's look at this crime fact.
It seems that there's only one
kind of handwriting on the blackboard.
So the criminal suspect is only one person?
Wait.
I have got a bold guess.
This is probably a gang crime.
One kind of handwriting is to confuse the others.
Right.
Is it possible that two people
worked together to finish this graffiti?
The first one finished the first half of it.
While the second one imitated the first one's handwriting
to finish the rest of it?
To my knowledge, in Class Ten,
the only gang whose members are close partners,
includes two people.
And you know their names.
Huang Nan, Huang Yi?
Yezi,
why do you have no appetite today?
Shouldn't be.
You never had resistance to hot pot.
No. I've been thinking about something.
But can't figure it out.
So I feel very upset.
That's not right.
Think.
Eat and then you have the strength
to solve the problem, right?
This is right.
This is our wonder girl Ye's character.
Have more. Here.
[ Astrology Society ]
Your true love will appear soon.
The way he appears is, on a colorful cloud.
A colorful cloud?
So my true love is the Money King?
Your true love will appear soon.
It's just an coincidence.
Well, how about another try?
Okay. I'm not afraid of that.
It says,
your true love will walk on a fire wheel
and bump into you passionately.
Your true love will walk on a fire wheel
Fire wheel?
Girl.
You're up so early. Wanna be a top student?
Not only a top student.
If I crack this case,
I'll be Maple Leaf's hero.
My story will be told for generations.
Are you still in a dream saying that?
Go back to sleep.
Huang Nan. Huang Yi.
What are you watching?
Let's go.
[ Man's Room ]
I know you're inside there!
Three.
Two.
One.
Boss. Boss.
We're here.
Why hiding from me?
No. We're not.
What's that?
Nothing.
Let me have a look.
This...
Take it out!
Gimme!
Isn't this just a comic book?
Yes. Yes.
Just a comic book.
Why hiding it from me?
This is a about a kid beating an alien.
Very interesting, then.
Wait!
Very bloody.
Very boring.
That's to say,
Huang Nan and Huang Yi can't be the criminal.
It seems that we should need a new deduction,
which should be more precise,
and entail mind mapping.
The criminal of the blackboard case comes out.
The four key leads that we get are,
Huang Nan, Huang Yi,
footprints on the site,
the crime tool,
and Mahatma Gandhi.
Plus the fact that we're a little hungry.
Everything here points to one single name.
Xue Xiaodong.
Why Xue Xiaodong?
Because, don't you find graffiti very fashionable?
In our class, the most fashionable one
can only be Xue Xiaodong.
This viewpoint and our four key leads,
support only one truth.
The criminal is Xue Xiaodong.
What's up, Ye Muxi?
Do you have anything hidden from me?
It's okay. Let me know.
You really want to know it?
In fact,
I... You...
Zhu Shanqi?
I had a very bad feeling just now.
So I came to join you.
Go on.
Shoot.
Okay. Shoot.
Okay. Okay.
If you really don't wanna tell me,
answer this question,
where were you after school last night?
Last night?
Xiaodong's meeting with fans last night.
He stayed there all the time.
So did I.
So happy.
So, what else are you gonna ask me?
No. Nothing. Nothing.
Nothing?
So, who on earth is the criminal?
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry that I hit you.
Never mind. It's okay.
Let me help you pick up this spray can.
Sorry. Thank you.
Take care.
Who on earth is the criminal?
What are you doing?
I've watched a movie before.
It's said if you've done something wrong,
you dare not look people into their eyes.
It's you! You're the criminal!
The most impossible one is always the criminal!
You're the criminal!
That's because you're stupid.
You can't find out the criminal.
Find out a criminal for me, then. Come on.
Come with me.
What?
Only two girls in our class love cartoon books.
Except for you, only into inspiring cartoons,
Another girl,
Yuan Ke'er, always sits in the corner,
only into dark cartoons.
If you know a little about every student in our class,
you'll know, she's the only student talented in art.
Only she can draw such an exquisite blackboard newspaper.
You know that again? You have no evidence.
What she's drawing now is
the same as what's on the blackboard.
Next to it, is the spray can for the graffiti.
It's been placed there for a few days.
Only some idiot can't notice that.
What did you mean?
Yuan Ke'er, did you really paint that?
Didn't expect you would find this.
Why?
What are you doing? She...
Obviously.
She doesn't wanna talk with us.
Even you go ask her, she won't tell you anything.
Liao Danyi.
Sooner or later,
you'll be one of our class.
What are you doing with your candid camera?
I'm the sanitation supervisor of our grade this week.
I'm commanded to record some labor work.
Look, your class.
How messy it is!
It seems that I should focus my patrol on your class.
Okay. Shoot your video.
I'll go clean it up. Camera on me.
No. No. No. I better shoot videos about Liao Danyi.
Where's Liao Danyi?
He must have finished this and go to the library.
Why him? Just put your camera on me!
Here. Look at this.
I'm good at cleaning work.
I'm really good at this.
I've practiced this.
One. Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
Two. Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six. Seven...
Working so hard? Have some water.
Dad.
Why did you come in without knocking?
What are you busy with lately? Looks so tiring.
The Student Union tells me to do
a figure investigation and study. Quite busy.
Okay. Keep going.
I should leave you alone here.
I need another try.
It came true again, right?
Your turn.
It says,
your true love will kiss you today.
Calm down.
Calm down!
Hey.
The door is opened.
I'm really sorry.
I apologize for what I did.
Okay.
I shall leave first if there's noting else.
Hey, come back.
I ordered the chocolate flavor.
Why did you buy me a plain one?
Well, is this an indirect kiss?
Since that,
I shall give you a chance to love me.
[ Cold Jokes ]
Meijing, have you heard of that joke?
There's an onion.
When it's walking, walking,
and walking,
it bursts into tears.
Well, how about that joke?
There's a male deer.
When it's running and running on the road,
it turns into an express male.
Well, have you heard of that joke?
A fatty falls off the stairs accidentally.
Then becomes a dead fatty.
Let's go to the library.
Okay.
Do you wanna hear jokes?
What a freak.