Monitor! Big boss! I was wrong.
Forgive me, big boss!
Forgive me, okay?
Forgive me.
I was blind. I was a fool.
I was wrong, big boss!
Big boss, forgive me.
Monitor. Look.
This is the traitor who
didn't believe you would be elected.
- Liao Danyi.
- No, no.
We must condemn him.
- Make sure he will never rise up.
- No, no!
-Tell him to go to hell!
-I didn't, monitor!
Forgive me, big boss.
I'm not a man. I'm not a man.
I'm not a man, I'm a beast.
Monitor, forgive me, okay?
We shall cast him aside.
We shall stone him to death!
- Stone him to death!
- Wait!
Yes. He is a sinner.
But you people,
throw a stone if you think you're innocent.
For example!
Me!
Stone him to death! Stone him!
Mo... Monitor.
I was wrong!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 02
What're you doing?
Aren't you the normal student Liao Danyi?
Do you need any help from your monitor?
No, thanks.
Good.
If there's anything, just tell your monitor.
Normal student.
Then please give me some room.
I'd like to study.
Is there anything making you upset?
Any worries?
Or any setbacks?
Ye muxi.
Just enjoy your moment of joy.
Because soon you'll realize
monitor is not an easy job that anyone can handle.
Yeah, yeah. Grapes are sour when you can't eat it.
Fifteen days.
What?
Fifteen days is your limit.
Then you'll run to me with tears
and beg me to take the burden.
Then everything will go back to normal.
I'm the monitor.
And you're my most troublesome problem student.
Like in primary school and junior middle school.
Everything back on track.
Liao Danyi, listen to me.
No matter it's fifteen days or a semester,
or a year,
I will be a better monitor than you.
I will despise you on this position.
As the big boss forever.
This is the roster.
Please remember each name quickly.
You shall arrange duty roster every day.
Later, go to the office on the 3rd floor
and get your textbooks for grade ten.
Remember, not one more
Not one less.
The blackboard newspaper needs new themes every week.
You can discuss this with
the Commissary in charge of entertainment.
Can't be too fashionable
nor too rigid, understand?
You shall make statistics about
all the course representatives' collections.
Supervise and help those students who
constantly fail to hand over their homeworks
You shall make budget for our class expenses.
When it's done, collect it from every students.
Our school pet, Green
eats bread and leaves.
Remember to feed it every day.
Mind its nutrition arrangement.
One more things,
there're two students of Class Ten
didn't come to register till now.
Go find out the reasons and report it back to me.
That's all I can recall now.
Questions?
That duty roster...
Right,
the most important thing.
Here, take this.
This is....
The key of our classroom.
And I need it for...
Aren't you the cutest student
who pretends to be confused?
You shall be entitled to
open and close our door from today.
I can't.
Students who arrive earlier will be locked outside.
What're you talking about?
I found you do have a sense of humor.
As the monitor of Class 10.
How could you not be the one
who enters the classroom first and leaves at last?
My advise is
just half an hour earlier than the others.
Just half an hour earlier.
Thank you.
As our commissary in charge of entertainment
I have many ideas of our blackboard newspaper.
I like the surrealism and abstractionism style.
Like Van Gogh, Picasso
Mondrian,
Dali.
Monitor, any opinions about
our blackboard newspaper this time?
We can settle our theme first.
Like crawfish?
Snail?
Starry sky?
Right, and sunflower!
Sunflower. Do you like sunflower?
You're our monitor.
I need your opinion, monitor!
Huang Nan, you..
You'll be the labor representative.
I'm Huang Yi, big boss.
Right, right, Huang....Huang Yi.
You help me arrange the duty roster.
I'm Huang Nan, big boss.
No.
Right, I know. I...
Well, Huang...
We're worked together for so long.
At least you can remember our names.
Don't mind, Huang Yi.
I'm Huang Yi, big boss.
I'm Huang Nan.
Huang Yi.
Huang Nan.
- Monitor.
- Do we have summer school uniform?
I don't....don't...
Monitor, who is on duty today?
Our duty roster is out yet?
Monitor, who shall I hand over my homework?
- Monitor!
[RESPONSIBILITY]
Why is this happening?
Nothing is like what I have imagined.
Like the contrast photo of
"before makeup" and "after makeup"?
First paragraph.
Tell me, what's your idea?
When I was in human form.
I had served a master.
Oh, Liu...
Don't mention his name.
Because I don't like to be considered
as a man who would talk behind people's back.
That master was once a merchant
who sold some DIY fashion things.
Straw sandals.
Not that specific.
That master...
how shall I put it...
He has no advantages over anyone else,
except his long arms.
Liu Bei.
Don't mention his name.
I didn't like him at first.
So although he came to visit me for several times.
But I didn't see him.
However, he was so persistent.
Even I pulled him into
my blacklist and turned off my phone.
None of those had stopped him.
He always came with his men.
Said they were gonna burn my house.
Anyway, carrot and stick
In the end, I had to give up.
And became the CEO of his group.
Then time flied.
He grew more rebellious.
Even left me a hot potato before he died.
But on the whole,
It was quite a satisfying cooperation.
Wolong.
Your memory.
Does that have anything to do with me?!
Wonder girl, easy. Easy! Easy!
What I mean is
a great leader doesn't need
to be so great in anything.
Like my former master.
You only need to remember one phrase.
What's that?
You can do it!
Monitor! I have a great idea
about our blackboard newspaper.
Shall I explain it for you?
No more word.
I believe in you.
You can do it!
I can do it!
Here, clean up our chemistry lab.
The chemistry lab.
In our hands.
I believe in you.
Believe yourself , just do it!
Monitor, where shall we get our textbooks?
Whatever you want.
Where shall I get it?
Trust your instinct.
- You can do it!
- Monitor.
You can do it.
You can do it!
Monitor.
Monitor,that...
Believe yourself, just do it!
Monitor, m...
Such an easy job.
Nothing complicated.
You're not that great.
Wait and see.
You're too careless.
It will become a mess.
What I did was great.
What's next?
Two students who didn't come to school.
Piece of cake!
You can't use your "you can do it" solution on it.
It's okay.
Students who didn't come.
Must be at home then.
If not.
I'll go find them.
It's not that easy.
Our school regulations say
no more than five days' absence in a semester.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
Dismissed.
They knew the regulations.
But they didn't show up for two days.
They must have their reasons.
It's nothing.
Big world. Nothing to be afraid.
And I will conquer all problems in a sec!
I wish I can say that.
Look. Look at you. Look at you.
Have some trust okay?
You think you're much better than me?
Wanna bet?
All ears.
Two students didn't show up, right?
One girl, one boy.
I'll take the girl, you take the boy.
Whoever can convince them to come first will win.
Not interested.
You're afraid, aren't you?
Can't afford to lose!
I am not interested.
Liao Danyi, afraid to lose.
Afraid to lose. Afraid to lose.
Do you hear him? Liao Danyi. Afraid to lose.
Give me his address.
Spicy strip. Spicy strip
5 yuan, 5 yuan.
Spicy strip, 5 yuan.
That overbearing aura.
After so many years,
it's my first time to see such a strong aura.
Is that from those two students?
[Zhu Shanqi]
Who is that?
Hello, I'm Ye Muxi. Monitor of Class Ten...
Is there anything?
I just want to ask why
you didn't go to school today.
I didn't want to.
Who is that?
Still me.
Your delivery.
You're finally here.
Are you nuts?
What's wrong with you?
Get out of my place.
Leave the food here and get out.
Do you really think
I'm here to deliver your take-out?
You'd rather work out your brain in school.
What're you looking at?
This is your room?
So dark?
None of your business, it's my home.
I like it dark.
Enough, no more peep.
Leave, leave now.
Out. Immediately.
[Xue Xiaodong]
Are you one of our dancers?
What're you wearing?
Go change it.
Hello, I'm here to see student Xue Xiaodong.
Another his fan.
Guards.
I'm not.
I'm his Commissary in charge of studies in class.
I'm here to talk with him.
You're Xiaodong's classmate?
From the Maple Leaf Middle School?
I'm Xiaodong's broker, Annie.
Nice to meet you, I'm Liao Danyi.
Okay. Good! Everybody, take a break!
Thank you, director!
Xiaodong, well done.
What are they doing?
Shooting a MV.
Xiaodong's latest Ep.
Ep?
Don't you know him?
Gosh.
He is the most popular idol now.
An idol?
How was I?
Super great.
Not that dramatic.
Xue Xiaodong.
You're...
Right, he said he is your classmate.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Liao Danyi, from Maple Leaf Middle School
Commissary in charge of studies of Class Ten.
I came to ask you why you didn't go to register.
I'm so sorry about that.
I did go to register on time yesterday.
But something came up.
So I'm here today.
What came up?
Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong! Xue Xiaodong!
So many long nights
made their hair greasy
So many days in waiting,
made them look pale,
with bloodshot eyes.
So many hours screaming,
made them voice hoarse.
In order to get the front row to see Xue Xiaodong.
Their clothes are in strips.
They're not afraid of pains.
They can think of one name
which is
Xue Xiaodong.
Xue Xiaodong!
No matter how strong our guards are.
we can never stop them.
When they see Xiaodong.
When they....when they...
Be tough, sis Annie.
They will not let go of anything.
Xiaodong's hair, clothes,
signature, and photo.
When they see Xiaodong.
They will never stop
until they get every bit of you.
Is that so?
Is that so? Is that so?!
Look!
These scratches were they left on me at school gate.
Okay, okay, okay. I see.
Now they know Xiaodong will
go to Maple Leaf Middle School.
And they know there won't be
too many guards in the school.
So they're all around at the school gate.
That's why I didn't go to school yesterday.
Since it's so troublesome to be an idol.
Why don't you just quit?
You...
No way, Liao.
To be an idol is my dream.
[Zhu Shanqi]
Mobile HDD.
2T
Hotpot soup.
Tomato flavor.
YSL lipstick.
Zhu Shanqi. Your poor memory.
If you keep doing this.
I'll keep out the real deliveries!
So what?
Come out and eat with me.
What do you want?
To make you go to school!
What's so good in school?
To make more friends.
I have lots of friends.
My QQ has exploded.
You can't be like this forever.
That is fine for me.
I can't let Liao Danyi win!
Zhu Shanqi. Just wait!
Zhu Shanqi won't let me in.
But I can force her out!
[ Plan A  Blackout ]
[ Plan B  Water break ]
Sis Annie.
I see them. There're so many of them!
Damn. Any idea?
I will go draw them away.
No. It's too dangerous!
It's my responsibility.
Xue Xiaodong's fans!
I have Xue Xiaodong's signed photos.
Anyone want this?
Signed photos! Signed photos! Signed photos!
Signed photos! Anyone want it?
Signed photos!
Give me one.
Love him so much!
Give me.
Gimme. Gimme.
Don't push.
It's all mine!
Gimme me.
Sorry, Xiaodong.
As your broker,
Of course I would choose your song as my ring.
It's okay. I can understand. Sis Annie.
It's not time for that.
Run!
Don't look back! Run!
Go!
Hurry!
There're ambushes everywhere.
We'll never make it to the classroom.
Xiaodong. Come back to our company.
So I can bring more men to protect you.
No, sis Annie.
I want to have a normal school life.
As an idol. I can't run away.
Since that.
You go. I'll stop them for a while.
Don't go.
I'm your broker, it's what I should do.
[Zhu Shanqi]
Who is that?
Delivery!
Do you really think I'm a fool?
Smells like the rice with mushroom chicken leg!
Forty Yuan.
Wait here, I'll get my purse.
I've paid it.
You want to buy me over with a meal?
Not that.
Well, I bought two sets of that.
Come in then.
What do you usually do at home?
Open my deliveries. Watch some American dramas
You like American dramas?
Not just that.
American movies, Japanese anime.
Japanese dramas, Korean dramas. I like them all.
My official account Throne Flower is quite famous.
I'm quite an American drama fan myself.
So you're that kind of critic?
But I'm quite picky.
Many dramas won't get a passing score by my standard.
Those are their hard work.
Easy on them.
You think you're good, you do it!
How can you say that?
If I'm commenting a refrigerator.
shall I learn to freeze things first?
They're made for their audiences.
They should allow any comments.
Make sense.
We can't stay here.
It's just a matter of time before they find you.
Seems I shouldn't come to school.
I was too naive.
Be an idol or a student.
Maybe I should go abroad to be a trainee.
No.
Why?
Yesterday, it was your choice
to go to school or not.
But now,
you must go report in Class Ten.
Why is that?
Because there's a student.
I don't want to be defeated by that one.
Never mind, you don't need to know the details.
I have an idea.
What is that?
My god. What...what is this?
Xue Xiaodong.
Xue Xiaodong?
Why that sounds so familiar?
So creepy.
So handsome.
He is in our class.
Should come to school today.
Wait, say it again?
Xue Xiaodong, wait for me.
I'm also your big fan!
Here I am to study as well!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Wait for me. wait for me.
Xue Xiaodong. Xue Xiaodong.
We're gonna meet right away!
Hello, classmate Xiaodong. I'm your fan...
I'm your classmate, Zhu Shanqi.
Nice to meet you.
Hello everyone, I'm Xue Xiaodong.
Hello everyone, I'm Zhu Shanqi.
Hope I can be friend with Xiao....
Be friends with all of you.
So it's a tie?
Liao Danyi. What are you wearing?
Don't ask.
You don't want to mess with an idol.
Although it's a tie.
But it's my first day as the monitor.
Yet you're so experienced.
How is that? Liao Dayi.
I'm a better monitor than you.
Say it. Say it. Say it out.
Say, say, say it.
About that...
Who gave the key to those two bandits!
Haven't you done any research?
Huang Nan and Huang Yi are the two
most famous imps in junior middle school.
Is that enough?
A little more.
You gave them the chemistry lab?
Many things in school have been bombed into ashes now.
Too exaggerated.
And the blackboard newspaper.
What is that?
You told our artist,
the Commissary in charge of entertainment. Just do it.
By the way.
Because our whole class all went to get the textbooks.
The way to the Education Office is all blocked.
Ye Muxi.
You've a long way to go on the road.
Liao Danyi.
You're the one I hate the most in the world.
I feel the same with you. Monitor.