# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
The Big Boss
Episode 17
The monitor will give you a funny show
Come now
Come on, come on
one two Three
O beauty
You dropped something
No, I didn't drop anything
You lost a boyfriend
Please pick him up
This is fun
This is our new study of tricks
Is there any effect?
How?
To know this kind of stuff
All right, all right
Everybody be quiet
I've called you all over
to discuss about the class committee
The problem of our distracting activities
Everybody knows that
We set up Class 10 committee
In order to help students to study better
But what have we been doing lately?
Someone went to look for the lost cat in the tree
Others helped the teacher find the missing wallet
And someone else
Goes and buys some snacks for girls
However
That girl is poor, too
How sad it is to not buy a snack!
Yes we have no way but to help her
If that's the case
We simply don't call it Class 10 committee
Call it society for good people and charitable acts
How's that?
So Ye Muqi
You act as a monitor
I need you to set an example
Refuse to delegate something that has nothing to do with learning
You have the courage to say no.
No
I didn't tell you to say no this time
Excuse me for interrupting
Monitor, Committee, hello
I have something to ask you for help
Sorry for interrupting you
Is this something to do with your study?
It doesn't seem to matter much
You see
This has nothing to do with learning
You can have the courage to say no.
No
Let's say it
What's your problem?
We can certainly help
Come on, tell us
It happened like this
Hey
I have something to discuss with you
What's up?
I'm playing game. Wait a minute
I just wanted to ask you
Wait a second!
Actually, I just wanted to ask you
If between the game and me you can only choose one
Who would you choose?
Let's break up
Finally opened a treasure box
Break up??
Why
Why not wait?
I
I haven't had time to open my chest
Why is the cell phone running out of battery?
There's one percent battery left...
Treasure
I really can't help it
Control myself, while playing the game
Just because
Just because of playing games
The most important person in my life left me
But the time when I play everyday
I can't control myself
No problem
It's good for you to realize the problem
We are sure to help
You don't know I'm sober now
You don't know, I'm sober now, but...
Once I start playing
I don't even know what I'm doing
No matter where, what occasion
I'll play with my cell phone
I don't even know when I was in my mind
thinking about something
So I beg you to help me
Be sure to help me quit this hard habit
I ask you to keep my cell phone
No matter what I say, no matter what I do
How can I ask you?
Never give it to me
Then I'll take care of it for you
Good
Come, for a change, a magic trick for everyone
Draw a card
This
See clearly?
I didn't see it. I couldn't see it
OK, I'll shuffle first
Six of hearts
Very good, very good
One more time, one more time
It sounds like I heard my cell phone ringing
No, your cell phone is mute
No sound!
Illusion, illusion, beat it
It's your turn
We'll do again
Draw another one
This
The magic deck gives optimistic vibes
Three of hearts
I really heard that
Something important must be up to me
Something important has come up to me
Maybe my mother called me
Or my friend was in a car accident
Hey classmate
You have to control yourself
Sit down
I hurry up!
Hurry up
Shall we change two?
Two, you come, you come
I heard it. I really heard it
It must be my cell phone ringtone
Don't move
You listen
That's from your mouth
Give back
Hey student
Give it back to me.
My cell phone
You control him
Give back
Control him!
I regained consciousness
Thank you, class leader. Thank you
That was nothing
Disperse, Disperse, Disperse
Wait
We'll hide one of your cell phones
Where you can never find it
Hello everyone
What's up, mate?
I've really figured it out
You're all for me
I know. I promise not to play with my cell phone
Really?
I am calm and serene
I think I can even move forward
A new step has taken place
That's good
Monitor
I don't know how to say. Can I be friends with you?
All right
Would you like to add a WeChat to your phone?
Yes, you can
You see, my cell phone isn't on me right now
You see, my cell phone is not on me now
I can use your mobile phone
Type in my cell phone number?
Ye Muqi, wait
You type too fast, I haven't said mine yet
Return my cell phone
run
I must stop him
Stop him quickly
Return my cell phone
Dry three Kun six fault
The vibration of the Yang and the interior of the Yang
Shake the back and leave the inner cavity empty
Today's purple micro-star red bull fighting
This is the location
Right at this moment
In my hand
Class leader
Next
Return my cell phone
Girls, have mercy
Sorry everyone, I was wrong
I couldn't control myself
What should we do then?
Let's play together
I think that's only our way to help him
He's in the game world
We need to recognize reality through his eyes
This is the best treatment
Tibetan mobile phone
We can hide for a while
But a temporary solution does not cure
Well, then, we
Download together
Surprise inspection
Hello, Ms. President
What are you doing here?
I'm president of the student union
It is compulsory to check all classes
I want to look at the dubious students
To see the students who are dubious
In what frivolous activities
they are wasting time
Nothing really
Here we are ready to play a game
Oh, what?
It's OK for us to have a rest and play games
It's also true that we can play games at break time
I tell you
Drama is the first big poison to affect learning
Playing is the first poison in learning
You are trying to sell this idea here
Does that suit you?
What about the game?
In fact, it is not a simple game
It's the process of playing games
To help this student quit his habit
So this game is not actually playing
It can promote friendship among students
I don't believe it
If you do not believe us,
you can play too
You dare not?
You fear that we'll win!
How could I possibly lose to you guys?
If you don't like it, let's have a try
Let's see who can make it in the shortest possible time
Rise to the highest rank
Let's see whoever comes here is afraid of whom
You're really afraid of chaos
This is pretty interesting
Let's get started.
Wait a minute
I don't have any interest in games
I won't play
The rest of the Zhu Xian Paladin.
Game on!
Daydreaming on the guest's bed again!
You have not grown up at all!
Crazy day
I don't know what to do
I
Quite true
And you are?
Don't you wake up like that?
Whatever good or bad you learnt
after months of studying with master carpenter
Does not mean you do your own repair
No, you can't do it yourself
I know some days you can cut wood knife  and wooden sword
Just like your father
Wooden knife or sword play
is no quality to boast about
Which girl wants to marry you?
Your mother, like your father
Ever since I entered our Li family's door
What did she ever do, huh
Just follow your dad
Yes
Spring comes
That is to go to chivalry
Leaving you as a nuisance
Gone for ever
Is not that I have lived frugally?
Opened such a small inn
I've brought you up till you're grown up
What's your name?
Ye muxi
I have put up with you throughout this life, Ye Muxi
Why have you become a slacker?
Not joking, but...
You kept me up so long
Why don't you know my name?
Daydreaming on the guest's bed again!
You have not grown up at all!!
Crazy day
I don't know what to do
Monitor
Don't control characters with non players
Dialogue are so long
Someone else will come in later
Daydreaming on the guest's bed again!
You have not grown up at all!
Crazy day
I don't know what to do
Daydreaming on the guest's bed again!
Everybody is here
That's not bad
Just the names of these martial art schools
How does it look like a game?
It's quite similar
The Shushan School of Shu characters
Is not a typo.
But I spent a lot of money
to get my hands off this job
It costs money to play this game
Isn't it free?
Yeah
Free. That's game time
Game props cost money
By the way
You should have chosen a school
Be sure to choose a neutral gamer
A diamond here
Equal to one yuan of RMB[Chinese currency]
But I spend very little
Basically depend on the task to save
Then the member of your head thirteen
What do you mean?
Don't worry about these details
You have stored so much money
Why don't you just buy one?
What about your favorite artifact?
You don't understand
Games are like life
Always aim a little ahead of your expectations
Forgot to tell you
Your game is bound for life
Unless you change your phone number and rebuild it
Otherwise, the characters cannot be deleted
You should have chosen the initial gear
Plain cloth, shoes, this equipment is simple enough
Simple wooden knife A attack power 1
Simple wooden knife B attack power two
The dragon and white knife
Attack power nine thousand nine hundred and ninety-nine
How can there be in the initial equipment?
This guards equipment.
And it wasn't bought with gold coins
Eight hundred and ninety-nine diamonds
Play first, charge 899 diamond, send Dragon Sword
There are five bottles of potions packs
That is the difference
between free players
and paid players
Actually, this game doesn't cost money
It's fun, too
That dragon wood knife can also be played with
That dragon wood knife can also be played out
Its drop rate is zero point seven per thousand
This is the driving force for me to move forward
Sounds like fun
Of course
I'm in the full-service top ten
Despite that's the poor wooden sword of the Dragon
I really stood at the peak of the king
Let's get the job done
Good good!
Imperial Sword of wind to the Demon between Heaven and Earth
There is lot of wine, happy music, but I'm alone
How good is a lonely man drinking?
Not as good as together
Good wine
How do heroes call you?
I walk rivers and lakes, with sword and wine
So people call me old white
White warrior.
How do they call you, young man?
As, Li Xiaodong
You have grown to be pretty handsome
Thanks a lot for your compliments
What is the use of being pretty?
Man can either be a scholar or warrior
What can you do?
A little bit of martial arts
With this physique of yours!
How about this
For the sake of your wine
Tomorrow
At the back of the restaurant. Let's meet there
To do what?
Come and you'll know
I'll take leave
That's your wine
This is to please you, young people
You can relax
We will do it well
Let's go first
You, just wait a minute
This lady, come here please
Take out
What?
What are you doing?
Don't make a fuss
I do it for my own reasons
Stand up
Take out
I really don't know
Shan Qi
Fight
Shan Qi can't bear it anymore
Yuan Ker
Fight!!
Calm down, everybody
Never get excited
This is even worse than the big devil
It's an invincible existence
Minutes are running out
What should we do then?
This is the first time I've ever been in this situation
Stand up
You
Shan Qi
I saw it
You're were in my closet
What did you take secretly?
Isn't it so?
Isn't that all for fun?
I see that we have no equipment
I have been looking around for any
At last I found the herb
That's true.
Now everyone is poor
But that's where you live
Is that your reason for stealing?
You are going to be in the rivers and lakes
Chivalric Knight
Does that suit your chivalry?
The lady
Now take it out
Here
Good
Although you have handed over the stolen goods
But the facts of crime have been established
The aunt has already reported herself
Official newspaper
Come with us, woman!
Don't leave me. I want to play games, too
Don't worry about it
It'll take three hours to get out of jail
Take fifty diamonds and get out of jail right away
Now you know the consequences of crime?
Are you all repentant?
Okay, that young man
Come up, please
Now that everyone has repented
Well, this herb is even appreciated by your aunt
Zhu Shanqi loses a herb
Aunt Lu gets a herb
Liao Danyi got a herb
I wish you a happy voyage
It seems that after the game is revised
It adds a lot of Education
Hey, friend
You'll have to wait a little longer
I can't move any more now
Why did I die at once?
You can resurrect automatically in five minutes
One minute left
There's another way
It is to spend five diamonds that can resurrect immediately
No, I don't want to recharge
50, 49, 48, 47, ...
First stage spike, level attack
Doesn't sting at the first level
What am I willing to do?
First stage spike, level attack
Who is the old gentleman in front of you?
I know how to get through this
Here I come
Old man, pardon me for interrupting
What a good mannered young man!
O sage like old man
you must be a famous figure in martial arts
Can you teach a few tricks?
It depends on whether you can stand the test
No matter what the test
I can handle it through my great versatility
Good
Then you'll try your best to hit me
I'm being polite
Somebody's hit me, somebody's hit me
I'm dying, come on, help!
My stomach hurts terribly
Why don't you let him accompany me to checkup?
Let him pay me two thousand and two hundred silver coins
Two thousand and two hundred silver
Are you a good man?
Violating law in broad daylight
No, no, No.
Follow me to the magistrate office
No
This, he
That's all right. He's picking me up
Follow me to the magistrate, sir
Good
Looks really good at Kung Fu
Huang Yi, you go up
One should learn from one's mistakes
Just fifty diamonds came out of it
I won't go. It's up to you.
Since it is so
Let's go ahead
No way!
We can't beat him at this level
What can we do?
All get out of my way.
But all of us are united
still we can't beat him
Why are you fighting alone?
The dragon and white knife
There's really such a thing?
Not the same like you guys
We gotta beat this guy quickly, pass the customs
Look at me
Oh, I see
This is the equipment of level fifty
Level fifty before you can wield it
Level fifty
Who says that?
What is written on the instruction?
Instructions
Who can see such a small word?
That's too much
Don't you think it's a little strange?
He kept hitting him with his eyes closed
That's where he is really powerful
Then we
Wait
Liao Danyi, be careful
Sir
Old gentleman
Is this is what you have been looking for?
It is found
I was afraid, really scared
I was looking for half a day
A lot of people are attacking me
Thank you
It is OK
Goodbye
What's the situation?
This
The game is like this
There are many wonderful ways to play
That's wonderful, too
This is really...
Wait
He's here to see me
White warrior
We have a lot of fate crossing paths with this kid
Surely the hero is waiting for me here
That is true
Although I seem to be an alcoholic
They all call me old white
So what?
Rivers and lakes say I have another title
I'm called the Wine Sword Fairy
I've heard so much about you
At first I met the latter
Found you to be great in bones
I want to teach you all my life's wisdom
Please master, accept your disciple's worship
But after meeting you
I met the man again
Could you tell me where I am?
May I ask where I am inferior to him?
You're mistaken
That's true
I met this young man later
Talked with him for a long time
Suddenly I realized the true meaning of life
Understood the harm of alcohol on the body
Alcohol really does harm to your health
So I've stopped drinking
But what?
There is a very sad news
Because my lifelong knowledge
Only after I finish drinking
can it exert true power
So
I've been here waiting for you a long time
Just to tell you
There's nothing I can teach you
Farewell
Listen
You think I'm not going to teach you anything?
Will I let you go?
I will pass you two words of wisdom
Remember
White wine, liver injury, beer, kidney injury
I love this game
jump
Jump for fun, jump, jump
Ye Muxi
Why are you jumping?
I like to dance, OK?
I just love jumping
Jump into the river and take a bath
Stop
Here is the main task of the game
Fairy Island
What, fairy island?
I would say this place is so familiar.
Imitation Legend of Sword and Fairy right
I know the background story
It's peeping a bath
I'll go first
Let's go
Good ridicule
What kind of thing are you?
I just didn't think anything had happened
My eyes
I will waste my eyes
Shouldn't there be a good spirit?
Why a grandma?
Game settings are like this
If it's not full of diamonds
The ratio of spirits and grandmother
It's one to ninety-nine
Wouldn't it be impossible to see the spirit?
They are all grandma
In fact, it is not possible to get herbs
'cause
It depends on the broadsword in my hand
It still seems we're going to have to fight
Fight
Calm down everyone
We shouldn't beat her at her level
There are two more options
What options?
Impress grandma, one is defeated
Then impress,
I suggest
Actually, you want to convince me
Nor is it not possible
But it depends on whether you are sincere or not
That boy, you look exceedingly handsome
Can we talk alone?
Then you can go
Give these two people some space and take a walk around the place
Ye Muxi
You
Me, I'm leaving too
What do they call you, young man?
What are you doing, young man?
Recharge
Five diamond can skip this task
Herbal medicine, I've got it
I'll take leave
Young man
Young man...
Don't leave, young man, please
Herb took us back to the Inn
The game's over
Yes
Let's go
I'm not going to let you pass
You're all gonna die here
Especially the ungrateful one
I have not spent money
Did you skip the task?
You can jump over this task
You can't jump my heart
Die!
Kill
Wait
If we go on like this, we'll be destroyed
Be careful!
You are no match for her
She took it with her hands
Add five dragon wood knives
God
That's level fifty equipment
Could it be..
She bought the equipment at the mall
Eat until you get to level 50
Now I'm in the game
The strongest being
This game really burns money
She really did this kind of injustice, big head!
That's a lot of money
What a pity!
It costs a lot of money
Really does
Where could I be so stupid?
It's embarrassing
Oh, my God, embarrassed, really
To say such a thing!
Embarrassed to speak out
What do you think?
It's embarrassing
I am embarrassed
Bring it on
Die!
Fell down, she fell down
Enemy fell down, but she's still fighting
Is she crazy?
Die!
Come on, let's go. Let's go
Let's go, walk, walk
That's the end of the game
Still, it's a really fun game
But it's not addictive, either
Hit it!
Cover up
In front
I wanted to ask you about the game and me
If you can only choose one
Who would you choose?
Let's break up
I figured it out
Crazy obsession game
In your eyes, it turned out to be so funny
You can understand that
Even if you can get the king
What about being a God?
That's all game developers
Let people get in the virtual world
Real life is not in vanity
and it's satisfaction
So it's not too late for you to wake up now
True
In this game, I am
wasting too much money
I forgot that adage
Good times never return
It's okay
You know
Maybe she's not far away
Maybe she's in some corner
Waiting for you to go back?
Really?
Dragon Sword
I got a new dragon knife. Do you want it?
No, no, no, I don't
I'm going, I'm to look for for what I lost
Strange
Finally, one thing was solved perfectly
Was it?
I always feel that more than one was addicted to online games
Cover up
It's getting late
Let's go to the snack bar
OK, OK
Let's take a walk
By the way, I know a shop
The shop is particularly good on.
It's delicious. I'll tell you
I have a clear mind now.
I repented. I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm playing games
Playing games
Didn't you want me to play the game?
I now find that
It's much more fun than you
# Looked up at the Ferris wheel around the Starlight #
# The moon is beside you with the breeze #
# Which cloud is crying, I don't know who's grieving #
# Tears are falling with rain you're blocking me #
# Another good soap opera plot plays in my head #
# There's no point in the story of his thousand-percent turns #
# That heavy rain encounter in your umbrella low #
# Or we never have met before, that would be a better plot here #
# I'm missing you #
# I'm thinking of the dew that quivering drips #
# Falling in the water beside the road to reflect your figure #
# On the blackboard in the corner dust has been reluctant to leave #
# You lost your ballpoint pen all the time here #
# That heavy rain encounter in your umbrella low #
# Or we have never met before, that would be better plot here #
# I'm missing you #