You're here.
I don't know why.
But it just happened.
That day after school
I saw Xiaodong sitting on his chair, alone.
So I was thinking.
Shall I go there and talk to him?
Pretend that it was quite normal.
And it has to be like I was just passing by.
Then I saw there's a mug
on the top right corner of his desk.
Then suddenly I sprained my ankle.
And accidentally knocked his mug down on the floor.
So I can pretend to apologize to him.
And acted like
I'm so sorry, Xiaodong.
Like I was very shocked.
And also, our hands touched accidentally.
My hand got cut by the mug pieces.
Xiaodong put this band-aid for me.
I want this on my finger forever.
Then I apologized to Xiaodong.
And asked him
if we can drink tea together later.
I would buy a new mug for him.
How about this, I'll buy you a new one.
No, no, it's okay.
No, no. I insist.
I broke this one, I must compensate for this.
What deep down, I was thinking.
So I can date Xiaodong.
In fact, Shaoqi was not quite a good actress.
Because I can see her motive before she came.
Sitting on her chair, she kept
looking at me with smile on her face.
If she wanted to talk with me,
she didn't need to break my mug.
Cause that is a limited edition.
It is quite expensive.
How about this, I'll buy you a new one.
No, no, It's okay.
No, no. I insist.
I broke it, I must buy you a new one.
But since she asked me
to have tea later, so sincere.
Then I'll go.
But all of those are not important.
So expensive!
I'm so screwed.
My heart was like a prairie with
ten thousand mythical creatures just ran over.
Why it has to be that expensive?!
It's like crazy.
It's just a counterfeit.
A counterfeit of a cup.
It's my allowance for a month.
I feel I was completely a psycho.
Gosh.
Why is that so expensive!
Xiaodong, you're away too far!
I'm the one who sold the counterfeit mug online.
When I saw it happen.
I knew Shaoqi will buy it.
Don't ask me why.
Heaven's secret must not be divulged.
And I defined it as relationship tragedy.
Once it's broken.
You'll get attention of the one you love
And win his/her heart.
I still have two more.
Not expensive.
Just around one thousand.
Do you want one?
It's quite a bargain.
Buy a mug, I'll give you a match bracelet.
Quite a bargain.
What mug accident?
I don't know.
I went to do my own business yesterday.
I was not there.
What did I do yesterday?
Can you cover me with mosaics?
I went to Director Yan's office to scrawl.
He doesn't know it yet.
About the mug accident.
We were there.
We saw the whole thing.
We saw business opportunity at once.
Can a mug make you rich?
Of course not.
So we decided to lead a mug fashion.
If you want to chat with the one you love.
Break his/her mug!
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Sorry, sorry.
What? Meijing. Want to chat with me?
Yes.
There's a very good movie on show.
This Is Not What I Expected. Have you watched it?
I have
I love the song in it.
Now all the mug sellers are our employees.
We'll spread the "mug chat" to every corner of our school.
of our country.
of our whole world.
Miss Xinyi.
I broke your mug accidently.
Why did you break mug?
I...I slipped.
You slipped?
As a man,
are you spineless?
You slipped?
I...I will buy you a new one.
No.
I like this very mug.
Pick it up.
But it's broken.
Stick it up.
So about mug.
This is mine.
If you're no more single.
Remember, come and break my mug.
If you're still single.
Remind me first.
So I can hide this to avoid misunderstandings.
And my mug is made of stainless steel.
You must do your best to throw it on the ground.
Smash it.
Otherwise, I won't know your motive.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 08
What're you doing?
I want you to stay by my side, okay?
Aren't you always so arrogant in front of me?
How many times have I told you?
Don't say anything happened at home in school!
Answer my question.
Stay with me, will you?
No.
You know what?
Now, with you by my side.
I feel so happy.
So stay with me, by my side.
Be closer to me.
No.
Just a little closer. Please.
Just a little closer, a tiny little closer.
So I can copy your answer.
Why won't you let me see it?!
I didn't review!
How is that?
Sorry, I failed.
Then what shall we do?
We'll fail English.
Xiaodong. What about you?
Completely blank.
Aren't you an all-around idol?
I devoted all my time to singing and dancing.
My study is my broker's job.
So we're on our own.
On our own?
Are you gonna start to study now?
There's not much time left.
We'll challenge the limit of tiny-mini cheat sheet.
Interesting. Never done that. I'll try that too.
Fine, seems it's my only way.
It's the smallest I can write.
Yes, it's quite small.
Then where shall we hide it?
What're you doing?
Nothing, monitor. Don't take us wrong.
Are you cheating?
I'm in.
Me too.
And me.
The most important thing is, how will you take it in?
Well, first, stuff it in the water tag.
Second, in the towel.
Third, in the pencil box.
Then I'll hide it between my arms.
Mine is on my fan.
Then I'll hide it in my clothes.
You know how important the English exam is, right?
Of course.
So, as the monitor.
I will not give up on anyone.
Until the last minute.
Hands.
Three. Two. One.
May the cheat win.
Okay, examination begins.
Put away your pencil box.
No food or drink.
Put away your drinks.
[ Blank sheet ]
Let's leave at once.
Stars waiting in the northern sky.
Northern sky.
[I don't know.]
All the sheets are here.
You can check which course you failed.
Now Commissary in charge of studies, distribute.
The number who failed in your class
is much more than any class in our school.
It's not just wrong answers.
Wrong answers
and beyond my imagination.
How can you face your textbooks?
If your textbooks can sue you,
you'll all be in the court
and sentenced to death, you know?
[Judge]
[Clerk]
[Prosecutor]
[Defendant]
Defendant Ye Muxi. Zhu Shanqi.
Huang Nan, Huang Yi, Shen Wei.
are accused of abusing and beating History, English,
Chinese, Math courses.
Silence. Silence.
Now, our prosecutor, Chinese representative Xu Zhimo
states the fact of the beating.
Thank you, judge.
Your honor, I'm Xu Zhimo.
Me and Yezi
have been nice friends since kindergarten.
The way I thought,
I thought we're good friends.
We've known each other for so long.
We share so many hobbies.
But this Yezi, she is too naughty.
She is away too far, your honor!
Here is what she did.
Who is the famous four in Tang Dynasty?
Her answer.
Harry Potter and Hermione.
Do you call it your answer?
Who is Du Fu, which kind of poetry did he write?
She wrote. Egg pie.
Are you kidding me?
You're crazy!
Sorry, honor.
I couldn't help it.
Your honor, justice!
You rock!
Silence! Silence!
You two, behave!
Defendants, show some respect to our court.
Next.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, your honor.
I'm Newton.
Who?
A hundred years.
You never succeed. Yet you're still trying!
Stop! No more apples.
Silence. Silence.
How many times shall I say it? silence!
You're in court.
Show some respect to the court.
To the judge, will you?
Back to the point.
I'm the Math, Physics and Chemistry representative.
I always the modern science is the greatest!
But since I met them,
Zhu Shanqi's answer of Biology.
What will happen when you put starch and iodine together?
Her answer, bread.
How hungry are you?!
Chemistry. Zhu Shanqi's answer.
How to tell nitrite from salt?
Try it. The nitrite is toxic.
Your honor. It's pure pseudoscience!
I want justice!
Silence. Silence.
Look, Newton is so pissed.
Any other prosecutors?
Hi, I'm Li Lei.
Hi, I'm Han Meimei.
We're not fine!
Yezi's translation for "Warm in winter and cool in summer"
is "East warm summer cool"
English question, what will happen in earthquake?
Huang Nan, Huang Yi's answer
You die, I die, Everybody die.
What?!
Your honor.
I'm always by Yezi's side.
I spent all my time on her.
Hope she can carry out my master's lifework.
To lead us through Jurassic Period and Cretaceous period.
I devoted my life to her.
But she...
History exam.
Which princess married to Srongtsen Gampo?
Snow White.
You've seen too many cartoons.
How could that be?
So miserable.
I couldn't stand it.
The statement part is so clear.
Anything else you want to say?
Defendants.
You will not get away today.
Now, I announce that...
Wait.
Your honor.
I'm the defense lawyer.
I know they are all sinned.
But I'd like to say something.
Although they acted so poorly,
they have their reasons.
That's my statement.
I beg your honor to give them
another chance to correct their wrongs.
A chance?
Why should we give you any chance?
Look at you, class ten.
How many students failed in the mid-term examination?
Look, in class one.
I'm the only one who failed.
Your honor.
Please give me another chance!
My belly didn't feel well in examination, so I failed.
Please give me another chance to make up for it!
Our school regulation.
Student who fails over four courses
will be suspended for surveillance.
Suspended for surveillance...
How many did I fail?
No need to ask.
You failed all seven courses.
But the headmaster have mercy on you all.
He gave you another chance.
There's a make-up examination in three days.
All the students who failed your examination.
Do cherish your last chance, okay?
Otherwise...
It's very hard to imagine.
You can get such a score.
Wu sir and me begged headmaster
so hard and got you one chance.
All of you, go to this moron's home tonight to study.
Who is that moron?
You think you're that indispensable?
We can study by ourselves!
Man up! Come with me!
God! We need you!
Help us!
If we fail again, we're to be dismissed!
You can't leave.
You can't leave us! You can't!
Master! You can't leave!
God. Don't leave!
Me and brother Yihan will help you
with this make-up examination.
I know you will, but why my brother?
You're his sister.
How could you not know
he was the top score in our city years ago?
The best among all the greatest students.
Danyi. Low profile. Low profile.
Let bygones be bygones.
That's all some rumors. Rumors.
Brother, I didn't know you're so good.
Of course.
Brother Yihan. Since they don't believe it.
Show them.
Since that,
I will not hide it anymore.
I'll show you some problem solving methods.
What's the most important thing?
Tell me.
Diligent!
Use your heart to feel every topic.
Of course. When you solve those problems
there're some secret methods.
Since you're all sitting here sincerely.
I'll show you a little.
Sorry, haven't done it for many years.
It became a little rusty.
Correct.
Last one.
All correct.
Brother, you're awesome!
Let us try it.
Use my heart. Yeah!
No.
Go.
Use my heart to feel.
You go.
Brother Yihan.
I don't think they can win by this.
Let's start from the foundation.
Am I right?
Students.
Danyi and I discussed a little.
That move is too complicated for you.
Not easy to perform.
But, now I have a simple version for you.
What's the secret about the examination?
Do it quick!
Attention, attention.
Before it turns pink.
You must pick it up, up, up!
Then add all the dishes in.
Here, here,here.
-Fill them all.
-Good.
Until you see all of them under the water.
Then stir it, stir, stir.
Use your sauce.
Stir it, stir, stir!
Speed, speed, speed.
Am I doing it right?
Yes, yes, yes.
What're you guys doing?
What do you see? What's in it?
There's sesame paste. Peanut oil.
My oyster sauce and lettuce.
All kinds of things.
Hurry, pick them up. Pick up.
Stir, stir.
Speed, speed, speed.
Okay, done.
Now it's time to feel your heart.
Begin.
How do you feel?
Why my tears are coming out?
Because I added onion in it.
Brother, you're the best.
I really feel I'm improving!
So delicious.
Shouldn't we be doing exercises?
Now let's begin to study.
Lad Danyi.
Actually, I can help them read the topics.
Brother, you've helped us a lot.
You can go back to rest now.
Page one.
I can help them...
Question one.
There're many questions...
Our state system is people's democratic dictatorship.
- People's
- Students
- its authenticity...
- Study hard, but also rest well.
What are our citizens' political rights and obligations?
The right to vote and to be voted,
political liberty, right of supervision.
The right to vote and to be voted
are citizens' democratic rights.
Look, M equals X, which is greater than minus one.
Then which is the right answer?
A. O contained in M.
B. O contained in M, but M doesn't contain in O.
C. Null set contained in M
D. O equals or contained in M
Which one will you choose?
M.
A. B. C. or D.?
Choose one from the four options.
So difficult. M.
Let's draw a number axis.
This is Zero, this is minus one, this is X.
You did it!
I didn't know which one shall I choose.
- You're great!
- Ye Muxi!
Listen to me.
Don't play with your pen, listen carefully.
M.
Choose A.
Zero is contained in this!
So the answer is three plus two equals X
Then this...
This is the final answer.
Got it?
Did you feel some cold air?
I felt it.
So gross.
I agree.
Let's back on this.
I've checked it.
The god of examination
will come to the third house at 3 p.m.
Good fortune!
Nice state today. I'm ready.
Full red, full blue, full benefit.
I'm ready, let's rock!
We're ready to become the superstar!
Doraemon with ten fingers.
After a whole night's special training.
We will definite score.
Because we have cheat sheet.
Wipe it now.
I'm not ready, what shall I do?
Anyway.
We all studied in my home.
And the results.
Let me put it this way.
The world is fair.
As you sow so shall you reap.
Actions speak louder than words.
Do the best if you're gonna do it.
And...
Whatever.
Me?
Do you think I will tell you
I got the lowest criterion of all seven examinations?
It's not luck.
It's my ability. Ability.
We were so happy.
We had no idea what kind of dangerous thing was waiting for us.