Where were you? I looked
everywhere for you.
The woman you just kissed.
Was it me?
Or...
your late first love?
The latter, I see.
- I...
- I'm...
not the shadow of
the one you seek.
So make up your mind
right here and now.
Either you cling on to your past
that's way past its expiration date,
or...
Or what?
See me clearly for who I am.
I know I'm not a
bad face to look at.
CHAPTER 6: FOUR
PILLARS OF DESTINY
Are you two dating?
What's his job? His age?
Where are you
right now? Tell me.
Tell me who that guy is!
She's not returning
any one of my texts.
Maybe he's a source of hers.
No way.
Just think of the gaze he held.
It'd easily melt your heart.
Ms. Kim, tell your heart...
to get a grip on itself.
I thought she was
a loser though.
- What?
- When it comes to men.
She's terrible at relationships.
The weather's hot, isn't it?
I like the summer.
So foxes withstand
the heat well.
It's the season when the
woods are the chattiest.
I don't have to ask...
to know that every
flower and tree...
get their fair share of
sunlight, rain, and wind.
They have a small
party all on their own.
That's not the case
in the city though.
The sunlight one
enjoys at home...
differs depending on
the floor they live on.
It's the same for
humans and plants.
Receiving more sunlight
leads us to being healthier.
You're quite
observant, aren't you?
Why have you been avoiding
eye-contact with me though?
- When?
- Even now, you're looking...
over my shoulder.
Look, I see carp in the water.
How adorable.
Right?
They're adorable.
Right.
What are you looking at?
You.
It's what you told me to do.
That's enough.
Stop looking at me.
It can only take so much gazing.
Darn it. I shouldn't
have said that earlier.
Wait for me.
But Ms. Kim,
doesn't that man
seem familiar to you?
- He does.
- Right? Where did we see him?
In my dreams.
He's a blend of those
who appear in them.
I was talking about
our show or...
No way.
There's no way I forgot
that pretty face.
But I'm sure I
saw him somewhere.
Are you still talking
about that guy?
Even if you chat away,
at least let it seem
like you're working.
You're embarrassing me.
Ms. Kim told me that
a true journalist...
always digs until
one hits a dead end.
- I can't believe you told on me.
- Unbelievable.
By the way...
What did she say about the
guy? Did she text you back?
Not yet. The curiosity
is killing us too.
If I'm being honest,
he looks like a gigolo.
That's what you want to believe.
You want to believe...
that life isn't that unfair.
- Hey!
- What the...
Get back to work!
Don't just pretend
to and actually work.
Who are you
searching for though?
- The governor.
- The governor?
He knows who took your parents.
Really?
And who's this governor?
He wears the skin of a
human, but isn't one inside.
He's one of the four
mountain spirits...
that once ruled over Korea.
A mountain spirit?
Please don't forget that
you're in the presence of one.
Oh, right. A former
mountain spirit.
You were ousted, right?
I gave up my title
of my own accord.
It may sound like
bragging coming from me,
but the other three
were minor spirits.
Me? I was the master
of Baekdudaegan.
Got it?
Okay.
Why is a mountain spirit at
the Korean Folk Village though?
All mystical creatures tend
to gather at this place.
It's a decent hiding spot.
Call it a retro
craze if you want.
It's nice to reminisce.
Are there non-humans
among us right now?
Could be.
Really?
Most lose their scent after
mingling with tourists.
Then how do we find
who you're looking for?
There's no need to.
We'll have a good time...
and he'll find us instead.
The fortune teller's
that way. Let's go.
Let's see.
My goodness.
- Hello.
- My goodness, hello.
Gosh, someone is finally here.
Let's see.
I can read your fate, physiognomy,
compatibility, and previous life.
Which one are you here for?
If you know all that,
why do you work here for
only 20 dollars per reading?
It's just for fun.
Here you go.
Can you tell us about
our previous lives?
Your previous lives?
Where's the one
for previous lives?
Okay, let's see.
Your previous lives.
Good choice. Young
people these days...
tend not to care too much
about their previous lives.
But it's actually very
important, you see.
Don't move.
- There we go.
- Are you using an app?
It's easy to tell.
Something seemed special about
you the moment you walked inside.
What was I?
In your previous life, you were
a member of the royal family.
You were a princess.
It tells you that?
Then what about me?
You were...
Let's see.
My goodness, you were
a laborer in the past.
You died while building
the Hangang Bridge.
If you were just going
to talk nonsense,
why couldn't you just tell
me something nice as well?
You should buy a talisman.
A talisman, my foot.
You guys shouldn't hang
around with each other.
If you do, one of you will die.
What?
You two never should've
met in the first place.
- Hello.
- My goodness, you're beautiful.
- I know I'm beautiful.
Welcome.
My goodness, you should come with
me and bathe with the fairies.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Hey, fairy.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Welcome.
- He's a mountain spirit.
- Hello.
- Where's the fortune teller?
- The fortune teller?
You need to walk that
way for quite some time.
For quite some
time? In this heat?
Aren't there any taxis here?
No, but we have that over there.
TAXI
Gosh, we just wasted money.
Was he talking gibberish or not?
I'm so bothered by what he said.
My team manager...
checked his compatibility with
his girlfriend before marriage,
and the fortune teller asked him
what took him so long to meet her.
They were told that
they were meant to be.
And then?
They were told that they'd
live happily ever after,
but it lasted less than a year.
- Did they get a divorce?
- Yes.
I don't believe in that
kind of stuff anyway.
If that kind of stuff is real, the
divorce rate in this country...
Who shot this arrow?
Who do you think would
use such a classic way...
to ask me out on a date?
Meet me at the
government office.
"The governor"?
Let's go.
One, two.
Go, go.
Nice.
Nice. That's what
I'm talking about.
Who are you?
- Are you here to read your fortune?
- No, I'm here for something else.
Do you need a talisman?
Enough of your nonsense.
I already know who you are.
Are the nine-tailed foxes
having a gathering here today?
- What?
- Forget it if I'm wrong.
Yeon was here.
Get to the point. A customer
might come any moment.
You have the item that helps us
see our past lives, don't you?
Let's see.
The eyebrows of a tiger.
My goodness. This is...
obviously not it.
Where is it?
My goodness. A goblin's cap.
Come on out gold
Let's see. Where is...
Ta-da.
Every single item that disappeared
from this world is all in this bag.
Give me that.
Not for free.
Here. What do you think?
My goodness.
My goodness, you fool.
- What?
- You can't buy this with money.
Why do you think these things
disappeared in the first place?
Look. It's gone again.
This place hasn't
changed at all.
Come on out, Governor.
Long time no see, Yeon.
You don't look as good
as you did before.
Why are you here?
I'm here to find someone.
Yeou Gogae falls under
your jurisdiction, right?
You do that kind of
stuff for humans?
I'm even willing to do more.
My fox sister died.
And apparently, the
guy who killed her...
right before her wedding was
a former mountain spirit.
And the guy who
helped her hide...
even after she ate all those livers
was also a former mountain spirit.
Living as a human being is
already difficult enough.
But you took away the lives
of all those pitiful...
All I did was...
hunt down those who brought
chaos to this world...
and did not deserve
to live among humans.
You and I are walking
different paths.
Then I have nothing to tell you.
I'm here to get what I want.
Right now, you should
focus on staying alive.
You can't put a
price on what I have.
What if I take it
from you by force?
Then you'll get
sucked into this bag.
If you're curious,
give it a shot.
Then what do you want?
Let's trade.
Give me something that means
the most to you in return.
Something...
that means the most to me?
Wait here for a moment.
Five minutes will do.
Don't get hurt.
It's too tiring keeping
this suitable for kids.
What do you say? Should
we make this rated-R?
I do not permit death.
I do not permit rude
punks like that.
Agreed.
Do not demean the fight.
Please go that way.
- Why...
- I'm not so weak...
that I need a hostage.
It's fine.
He lives for looking cool.
Make yourself comfortable.
It's called having pride.
TAX EVADERS
Do you have feelings
for the fox?
Or were you bewitched?
I...
What does Yeon mean to me?
I am using Yeon.
I entered into a contract
with him to find my family.
I pushed him into danger in order
to get information from you.
I like your honesty.
But I don't need
any of that now.
I want to kill them and
you quickly and go home.
He gets hurt wherever he goes...
because of me.
Looks like you won't have
such an easy life either.
I don't care.
If the path stinks, I'll
plant flowers along the way.
You're amusing.
It's as I've heard.
What?
However, you will
regret coming to me.
Who was it?
What moron brought a cell phone
into the Underworld of Darkness?
I'll leave your spicy
rice cakes here.
You twerp!
How could a grim
reaper say that?
Shut it! Find the
owner and torture him!
They've all gone soft.
This isn't spicy at all.
Sweetie!
Where did he go? We're so busy.
The mirror of the moon.
Are you trying to
kill a person...
with one of the four gems of
the four mountain spirits...
intended to protect
all creation?
So did your fox bead
protect all creation?
Or did it protect one person?
Why don't we drop all items and
skills and fight barehanded?
Fine.
Her heart seems to
break if you get hurt.
What is she to you?
Hey, that's the kind of thing you
ask after two bottles of soju.
Everyone knows that.
You're upset. You must
be sincere about her.
- Shut it.
- You are foolish, Yeon.
How could you love
a human again?
Stop speaking like
that. It's exhausting.
You have to see it through
like this, don't you?
This is how I have lived.
You're so inflexible.
Let me see. I told
you not to get hurt.
It's fine. It's just a scratch.
Hold on.
Hey, get up. Have
an iced Americano.
I do not drink iced Americanos.
What's with you two?
Let me formally introduce you.
He's a mountain spirit as I said,
and my best friend.
His true identity
is a moon bear.
GRANNY
Will you pick up already?
- I can't live like this anymore.
- That again?
I get startled and wake up
in the middle of the night.
My heart pounds really hard
when I think about my wife,
and I have to pee.
I don't want to hear about
an old man's incontinence.
It's natural for a couple
to fall into ennui...
after being together
for centuries.
- Ennui?
- Even Gyeonwu and Jiknyeo,
everyone's favorite couple,
are debating whether or
not to stay together.
No wonder.
That's why it hasn't been
raining on Chilseok lately.
Just be honest with her.
No. I'm scared.
What eternal luxury
did I want to enjoy...
that I married the
sister of King Hades?
Why must I eat this?
It's ginseng chicken soup. It's
good for you and delicious.
But why are you
buying this for me?
I think I've misjudged
you a little.
What if you didn't misjudge me?
Based on experience, no one evil
ever pitied helpless animals.
I don't like you.
Are you deaf? I don't like you.
Even if you don't, I'm sure
you'll like the soup. Try it.
Why are you smiling like an idiot
when I said I don't like you?
I was told it's fine
to be cruel to those..
who can't complain that it
hurts even if you bite them.
You're a lot like the
pets that I've met.
What?
Those who were abused
and abandoned...
bite even the hand
that feeds them.
It's because they don't
know how to be loved.
Shut your trap.
What is precious to me?
As if there could be anything.
LEE RANG
The person you have
reached is not available.
- You're ignoring my call?
- Please leave a message...
He even eats macarons.
They deliver both worlds...
of crispy rice puffs
and moist yakgwas.
Of course. So how
has it been lately?
You have a big family
to provide for.
The minimum wage
has been raised...
and I took out a
loan to buy a house.
Except for the characters
from fairy tales,
complaining about panic
disorders, it's been all right.
It all sounds like hard work.
I'll soon need to attend
my birthday party.
Have you perhaps
seen these people?
They disappeared 21 years ago.
I'll take even the smallest
lead, so if you know anything...
Was it March 3 on
the lunar calendar?
That's right. It's the exact
date of the car accident.
In the beginning of January,
a man in a navy blue
suit came to see me.
He told me about the accident
that would occur on that day...
at Yeou Gogae.
A navy blue suit?
Are you saying that he caused
the accident on purpose?
So?
I don't get involved in
events that could harm humans.
I didn't lend him
any of my men either.
Who was this man?
At first, I thought he was
just wearing human skin.
- But no.
- Then what?
He was a human.
- Are you sure?
- That's what I smelled.
Tell me everything you
remember about him.
His face is so vague
in my memory...
that I probably
wouldn't recognize him.
That's how
average-looking he was.
But his forehead.
- His forehead?
- Albeit faint,
signs of human
branding was present.
HUMAN BRANDING: A
TYPE OF PUNISHMENT
Human branding?
The one done to criminals?
- And the letters?
- "Seo" as in west...
and "Gyeong" as in Seoul.
Seogyeong.
Human branding indicates...
that he was born before the
Joseon Dynasty was found.
I wonder where he is right now.
Probably...
someplace close.
What do you mean by that?
Because the parents weren't
the targets of the accident.
What?
The daughter was
the initial target.
What are you going to do
if you hate every option?
GRANNY
Darn it!
Darling! Get back over here
and help me with the workload.
Yes, darling. I'm on
my way back right now.
I won't be long. See you soon.
- I want a divorce.
- What?
That's right.
I'm getting a divorce!
Hey, you!
You?
- Me?
- I couldn't care less...
about an old man
getting a divorce...
when he's old enough to
drop dead at any second,
so shut it.
What the...
Where are your manners?
She must want to experience
what death is like.
Just let her be.
She's from overseas.
What's the world coming to?
Where did he find
someone that obnoxious?
Don't even bother bowing!
But sir...
- Do you even know who he is?
- Why should I care?
He's the gatekeeper
of Samdo River...
and the brother-in-law
of King Hades.
Does being tight
with King Hades...
gives you the right to
be loud in restaurants?
Just eat your meal.
Darn, it's hot.
Here.
Let go of me.
The dog house and food for
the puppy you brought in...
I can't take it.
- Then what?
- You'll raise it instead.
Put it to sleep and I'll make
sure you receive the same fate.
Does your family hate dogs?
I don't have one.
But there's someone who
rescued me from the zoo though.
- So he's your savior.
- Of course.
He ripped the
zookeeper into pieces.
He killed someone?
Who is this savior of yours?
Someone you'll be
meeting pretty soon.
Don't keep the
girl by your side.
Why's that?
According to the man
who sought me out,
the girl...
has the scales of the King.
The spirit of the
King lies with her.
Long time no see, Yeon.
It's me. The person
you've been waiting for.
Our ill-fated relationship
would've ended...
if you hadn't
stopped the boat...
from crossing the Samdo River.
Could that have been a sign...
or...
Who could that man have been?
If he's lurking around me,
he could be someone I know.
A scar on his forehead?
I don't know such a person.
I'll look into it, so...
I just don't understand.
Why did he come after me...
and why did my parents have
to suffer because of it?
What am I anyway?
Yeon, why do you
keep protecting me...
without...
so much of an explanation?
Because...
I don't want you to get hurt.
I don't want you to
do anything for me.
I wish for your life...
to have a happy ending.
Also,
I'd like you to trust me.
Why don't we get
hold of that man?
How?
We have someone
that can serve...
as a link.
Why do you keep calling me?
Did you not see the 22
missed calls I left?
Do you think I'm
your girlfriend?
If I don't pick up, just
think that I'm busy.
We need to meet.
What are you scheming this time?
I just miss you. That's all.
You're obviously onto
something. I'm busy. Bye.
What are you so busy with?
Where are you right now?
Do you really think your brother
will tell you what he knows?
- No, of course not.
- Then what?
I'm going to make
Rang meet that guy.
How?
Hey, scribe.
Let me borrow this.
"Find"?
Find the man who has a criminal
branding on his forehead.
What did you just do?
It's like a talisman.
These shoes will take
Rang to that man.
We only have one shot.
Today, we must keep our eyes
on Rang no matter what happens.
Okay, I won't lose
him no matter what.
Go on inside.
You're here.
Why aren't you saying hello?
Did you forget the funeral?
Yeon came back a
mess because of you.
That's what you
call brotherly love.
By the way, that hanbok
looks nice on you.
That suit looks horrible on you.
You're really sensitive today.
It's starting to get me excited.
You're always so high
every time we meet.
It's like you're on drugs.
What are you doing at
Korean Folk Village?
I'm obviously not here to
do homework for school.
If you were, you
would've flunked.
Hey, old man.
I came to check something.
You're back.
What are you trying to do?
Did you come here knowing that
he's an actual fortune teller?
Anyone can tell that he's a fraud.
Just look at this fake mustache.
It's real?
He kept talking nonsense.
He does that on
purpose, you fool.
Go ahead and check.
There's no way he
means the most to me.
Yes, he's the most precious
thing in your life.
Your brother.
Darn it.
I'm off now.
What are you doing?
How should I put it? I'm
pretty much selling you away.
You're unbelievable.
He'll explain what's going on.
You'll be left with nothing
else but time anyway.
I'll see you next time.
- Where are my shoes?
- I don't know.
Is he a kid or what?
He always turns so immature in
the most unexpected moments.
Where do you think you're going?
- You can go first.
- Okay.
- Let me go.
- You're mine.
- Says who?
- A deal is a deal.
It's an unfair deal.
Yeon, hurry.
If you want to trick me,
you should at least...
Go on. Business is
closed for today.
Where is Yeon?
He joined my collection.
Will you be here
tomorrow as well?
I only do business
whenever I feel like it.
And the location
changes every time.
We only have one shot.
We must keep our eyes on
Rang no matter what happens.
In the beginning of January,
a man in a navy blue
suit came to see me.
These shoes will take
Rang to that man.
Do you have feelings
for the fox?
I wish for your life
to have a happy ending.
I'd like you to trust me.
- Let him go.
- No.
We have our rules.
- Please, sir.
- What's that?
- No, wait.
- Nothing can free him.
Tell me what I need to
do to get Yeon back.
The rules remain the same.
You can trade him with
your most precious item.
I'll do it.
I'll buy Yeon.
What will you give me in return?
If you don't come back
before 9pm, our deal...
will become invalid.
I have 1 hour and 40 minutes
before the clock strikes 9.
What is it?
What's the one thing that
means the most to me?
Think.
Let's think.
Once the sun goes down
People get off work
But why am I still here working?
Hello? Open up!
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Please open up! Hello?
Is anyone inside? Hello?
Sir!
Governor?
I heard a familiar voice.
It looks like it's urgent.
Thanks.
Thanks!
Wait a minute.
So? What is precious to you?
This.
A broken music box.
It still works though.
It's the last birthday present
that my parents gave me.
Is that all?
It has been exactly 21 years...
since they went missing.
To be honest, my memories
grow more faint every year.
I get confused...
whether what I experienced
really happened or was a dream.
There's blood on this.
That's why I hung on.
"What I saw that day
was not a dream."
"So..."
"they may be alive."
As in, it's like the last item
connecting you to your parents.
I'll appraise it.
What brings you
here at this hour?
You're right.
Why did I come here?
What do you mean?
Never mind. Apologies.
Don't tell me that jerk...
FIND
I will...
- not make the deal.
- What?
This isn't enough.
Why not? Why isn't it enough?
Because I'm not the one
that valuates items.
Please tell me.
What must I do? What...
can I do?
You are an annoying customer!
I'll repay you somehow.
- Please?
- Fine! Fine!
You were a princess in
your past life, not now.
You think whining will get
you everything you want.
Your hand.
Give me your hand.
- Left hand!
- Left hand.
You were born with
a very special fate.
Water and fire may fight,
and the earth may be dark,
but metal shall rule over it.
Thus, even if you are
surrounded by darkness,
a moon will shine from your sky.
What does that mean?
You possess the fox bead.
That is your moon.
Sorry?
Give me the bead.
Your life is overwhelmingly
blessed even without the moon.
- So...
- I'll give it to you.
I don't believe in fate.
I see.
The deal has been made.
Sorry? Already?
The lines on your hand.
The lines have changed.
The fox bead is gone.
How could you beat up an old
man as soon as you got out?
He deserved it. How dare that
young punk treat me like that?
I'm much older.
How did you do it?
How else? I bought you.
With what?
You didn't like, give him 10
years of your life, did you?
No. You were much
cheaper than I expected.
So you're mine from now on.
I'm very superficial,
so I won't grant you freedom
so easily like Aladdin.
You're a bigger
villain than Jafar.
Why didn't you go with Rang?
It was a precious opportunity
to find your parents.
To be honest, I was torn.
"This may be my last chance."
"Am I confident I
won't regret it?"
- So why did you choose me?
- Because I was confident.
Because I felt like
I could trust you.
Because I felt like you'd
give my life a happy ending.
What are you thinking about?
I realized...
there are more moments when a child
needs her parents than I thought.
For example, when the
child takes her first step.
Who else would be that
moved that you got up...
and took just a few
steps by yourself?
What about for you?
For me...
When I was the only one at a
picnic without a homemade lunch.
When the kid I fought
with in class said,
"I'm going to tell
my mom on you."
I couldn't beat kids with moms.
What a shame. I
would've beaten them up.
I resented them a lot too.
"Why did they leave
me all alone?"
"Why won't they come back?"
But they said it
was because of me.
The accident was because of me,
and my parents' lives
were ruined because of me.
You can cry if you want to.
No. I want to eat chicken feet.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
That's why I want to
eat spicy food and cry.
I want to be confused as
to whether it's my life...
or the spicy chicken feet
that's making me cry.
That's cool of you.
What?
I was worried that you'd
lie about being all right.
I'm glad.
I was worried about looking
cute instead of cool.
- Dig in.
- Is it good?
- It's not as spicy as it looks.
- I see.
Is this too spicy for you?
Of course not.
Something got stuck in my eye.
I see you don't have a
tolerance for spicy food.
As if.
I'm not some loser, you know.
No, just wait.
This is my battle to fight.
Where are you going
at this late hour?
Nowhere important.
I just have an errand to run.
Goodnight, then.
Yeon, wait.
Don't be so nice to me.
To be honest, it scares me.
Having a protector makes
me want to be dependent,
and I'm worried...
that it'll only make me weaker.
So that's how you've
lived your life.
Then I promise you this.
You'll reunite
with your family...
and live out the
rest of your life.
When the time comes,
you'll forget about...
your time with me and the
knowledge you have on my world.
You will live...
a normal human life.
You startled me.
Make your presence
known, you fool.
Granny, you know
everything, don't you?
Regarding what?
Imoogi.
It still lives.
Cause and effect is the
cardinal rule of our world.
Enough with the nonsense.
The girl was the one who
woke it up from its sleep.
And you were the one who sought
her out against my advice.
Then it's alive.
Yes, it is.
Then...
what was it that I fought for?
Why did A Eum have
to give her life?
It was the path you two chose.
Where is it right now?
I've warned you
time and time again.
Foxes and humans can
never end up together.
- Tell me.
- Your obsession...
- will be calamity.
- Tell me!
Hi.
What exited the well...
went into hiding immediately.
A piece of it was
found recently though.
What?
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
I made a promise.
I'll protect her even
if it ends my life.
That's the thing with love.
One wrong move and it
can swallow you whole.
Yeon is someone I
care about now too.
Imoogi and Rang are
connected somehow.
Harm her in any way and I will
end you for good this time.
Don't get swept up in this.
You don't want to see
the tragedy on replay.
But she'll be hurt
if I don't go.
You or the girl. One
must die in the end.