I guess you could say that
this was my golden days.
I was the master
of Baekdudaegan,
a mountain spirit who
controlled the wind and rain.
I was a nine-tailed fox who
was on a different level...
compared to the
lame creatures...
you see on horror shows.
Do you have a death wish?
That's odd.
My dog usually likes it
when I pat it this way.
What? How dare you! Do you
have any idea who I am?
You're a fox, aren't
you? Hi, I'm A Eum.
If I was given one
chance to change my past,
I'd choose this moment.
To make sure that
girl never finds me.
Lee Yeon!
How is it that you never
get lost and come every day?
Here.
Some call it...
the biggest scandal
of Baekdudaegan.
The story of a mountain
spirit that fell for a human.
In this day and age,
I'd be criticized.
But I couldn't care less.
I loved how she left
her trace in my woods.
You probably guessed already,
but this love story
has a tragic ending.
Someone stole her life.
Once she crosses Samdo River,
I'd never get to see her again.
I couldn't make her stay, but
I also couldn't let her go.
It's why I resorted
to abusing my powers.
How dare you!
Please be reincarnated.
I promise...
to find you.
Over the years, I came across
a few who did resemble her.
Excuse me.
What is it?
But none of them carried
the fox bead I gave her.
I apologize.
Are you A Eum?
You're not A Eum.
Forget everything you saw today.
If you don't,
I'll kill you.
I've been waiting for you.
Maybe I should've just
killed her then and there.
CHAPTER 2: I'VE
BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
Do you have a death wish?
I wouldn't be sipping tea here
if I was worried about that.
Would you like some?
Darn it.
After the stunt you pulled,
you're actually offering me tea?
Normally after that degree
of physical contact,
two people grab meals
and tea together.
The whole innocent act
doesn't go far these days.
Whether it does or not,
when you want something
from the other person,
it's only polite to
at least put down...
your pride or self-esteem.
Shouldn't you hear
me out first...
to know who's the
more desperate one?
If you don't manage
to change my mind,
you'll get what you
deserve for testing me.
It comes with a cost?
I'm going to take your eyes...
for having seen what you
never should've seen.
Deal.
EUNHA FUNERAL PARLOUR
Do you want everyone to
know that you're a fox?
What?
- Your tail.
- Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry.
Are you Director Ki Yu
Ri from Moze Corporation?
Oh, yes.
I'm here to meet the families of
those who died in the bus accident.
I can't believe you
came all the way here.
Come this way.
EUNHA FUNERAL PARLOUR
Sir, how much should a
conglomerate's daughter give...
to pay her condolences?
Why do you think we're here?
Because you killed them.
We came to enjoy their sadness.
We came to watch something nice,
so you should pay them enough.
Then I'll pay this much and
enjoy watching them all night.
You look exactly how
you looked 21 years ago.
I'm sure you're not going to ask
me how I manage to look so young.
- What are you?
- I'm a nine-tailed fox.
So you're a fox that's
pretending to be human.
What a lame reaction.
A normal human being...
- would scream...
- No.
I knew something like
you would exist...
somewhere out in this world.
I started directing a TV
show about urban legends...
so I could catch you myself.
You think you caught me, but it
might be the other way around.
First, let's hear
what you have to say.
21 years ago, we
met on Yeou Gogae.
What exactly
happened that night?
I followed the smell of blood, and
I ended up saving a little kid.
But I can see that
she's very ungrateful.
You saved me?
Why?
You just looked
like someone I knew.
But of course, I was mistaken.
What about my parents?
- They probably died.
- There were no bodies.
You're the only clue I have.
Please help.
I guess you lost your parents.
But I'm sorry to tell you
that I'm not interested...
in your memories of the past.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I'm sure you don't want
the world to know about you.
If things go as planned, the
show will air next Wednesday.
Your pretty face
won't get blurred out.
You sure held onto that flash
drive even while you were falling.
What are you trying to do?
You're more powerful than me,
and I obviously can't use the
law to make you cooperate.
But you see, I'm desperate.
I find this boring.
When you want to threaten someone,
you must be in a position of power.
Like this.
You're wrong.
I'm not threatening you.
I'm taking my chances.
When a fox is indebted to someone,
they must return the favour.
I don't care if
you're human or a fox.
I'll erase everything
I saw and heard.
But that is, only after
I find my parents.
REST IN PEACE
I'm sorry for your loss.
Come this way.
REST IN PEACE
What are you doing here?
- Who are you?
- Moze Department Store.
Don't you remember?
Oh, yes. I remember.
THE FOUNTAIN OF LUCK, MAKE
A WISH. IT WILL COME TRUE.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you.
- What did you wish for?
- What about you?
I have an older brother.
I want him to be miserable
for the rest of his life.
He's a real jerk.
I thought I might feel better
if I didn't see him around.
But I was wrong. I can't
seem to sleep at night.
I'm going to keep
bothering him...
until one of us dies.
What did you wish for?
I wished that I'd be able
to marry my girlfriend.
What a humble wish.
My parents won't ever
let me marry her.
Oh, dear. Do you
want me to help?
Who are you to help me?
I guess you could
say I'm a miracle.
Anyway, congratulations
on your wedding.
Your parents are no longer around
to disapprove of your girlfriend.
Was it you?
- Did you kill my mom and dad?
- Come on.
You have a crazy imagination.
Then what were
those coins about?
I guess you and I...
both got lucky.
She had this.
My goodness, an anesthetic?
She almost killed you!
Will you please sit
down? People are looking.
I'll make sure no one
takes anything again.
By the way, why do you think
her memory didn't get erased?
It's pretty rare, but our powers
don't work that well on some people.
For example, the female
shamans in the past.
But you just let her go?
And you even gave back her eye?
Rules are rules.
It's like we exist to repay
people for their kindness.
How long do we need to stick
to that old-fashioned custom?
We give back what we receive.
It's old-fashioned but romantic.
It shows a fox's dignity.
It's also a curse.
The bigger the debt,
the more we lose control
and become puppets.
Does she bother you...
because she looks like A Eum?
I've seen tons of people who looked
like her for hundreds of years.
I watched them
age and pass away.
And none of them were her.
How could the deities
be so indifferent?
Shin Ju, don't put on that face.
It makes you look really ugly.
Give her some.
Here.
Your dad is bored.
All done.
58 seconds. That was close.
That's enough. Now,
play with your dad.
I want to beat his record.
Okay, fine. Let's see if
you can beat my record.
Ready, go.
Do you think you can
beat me this time?
Do you think so?
Ta-Da.
Mom, Dad cheated.
I'm really sorry.
Here's my apology.
Will you please accept it?
It's my handmade gimbap.
Please take it
- There you go.
- It's good, right?
Let's give your mom one too.
Here's my handmade gimbap.
It's very obvious you're
acting for the camera.
Was it very obvious?
How embarrassing.
Okay, one for me.
It's delicious.
I want a gift.
Okay. Look here. Look here.
That's my pretty girl.
Mom?
Okay. All of you died...
in a bus accident on Yeou Gogae.
I'm sure the grim reapers
briefed you on that already,
so I'll skip that.
Now, you will face the
afterlife judges...
and have the sins you committed
when you were alive judged.
Don't be scared. You have no
need if you were a good person.
You know King Hades, right?
My wife standing there is
King Hades' older sister.
She isn't scary, is she?
I'm terrified.
- That old fart.
- Have you seen from movies?
I should plow his tongue.
- He...
- We need to chat.
set up the five layers of
the Underworld quite well.
The main point is...
- Hello, Director Nam.
- Hello.
I'm on the first floor.
Who wants coffee?
A Eum was reincarnated,
wasn't she?
I'm right.
Why do you want to find her now?
I want revenge.
I was sentenced to 600 years of
obligatory service because of...
Lying will land you
in the Underworld.
Do you want to be barbecued?
No. My hair is my life.
My red-brown hair.
You use to be on top of the world
as a mountain spirit. How did you...
Let's stop reminiscing
the old days.
- Where is she?
- How should I know?
You're clairvoyant. You see
everything that happens on earth.
Is it possible for
her to be reborn...
with the same face?
Hey. Reincarnation is random.
You should pray that
she isn't a boy.
Oh my gosh.
Boy or girl,
beautiful or ugly...
It doesn't matter.
As long as she isn't over 60.
Even if she is over 60, she's
still a baby compared to you.
No.
I don't want her
to die too soon...
after finally meeting her again.
Why do you look so exhausted?
I saw a dead body in my dream.
- It's an occupational hazard.
- You know,
I saw a woman in my dream...
wearing black mourning
garments and weeping so eerily.
- A virgin ghost?
- No.
It was you.
Hey. Don't jinx her.
- Was it really me?
- Yes.
I had a dream of losing a tooth.
Isn't that a bad dream?
You're so superstitious for someone
who doesn't believe in ghosts.
Don't mind him.
Losing a tooth in your dream also
means you may come into wealth.
Thank goodness.
Why you...
Excuse me. Will you
sell me that dream?
What?
I want to play the lottery.
Yeon.
- Don't look for her.
- What?
It may flip your destiny
upside down again.
I don't care.
Stop beating on your husband.
Cut back on delivery foods.
They're not good for your skin.
Here. I found this
on the way here.
I won't be here for a while.
Lipstick?
That's right. Resolve a
civil complaint for me.
Hey.
My parents' times
and dates of birth?
Okay. I'll text you.
DAD: NAM JONG SOO, MAY 3, 1958,
MOM: LEE YOUNG SUN, JUNE 26, 1960
It's neither good
news nor bad news.
Let's meet.
Meet me at the restaurant
The Snail Bride at 1pm.
THE SNAIL BRIDE
TRADITIONAL KOREAN
CUISINE: THE SNAIL BRIDE
Are you here to see Lee Yeon?
Yes.
This way.
Thank you.
You are blessed.
- Pardon?
- It's the first time...
he brought a person.
Hey.
About the times and dates of
birth that you asked for...
They're not on the list.
What does that mean?
As in, your parents aren't dead.
They're alive?
Where?
I don't know that much.
Why don't you eat?
You're the one paying.
It isn't the most
appetizing news, is it?
No, no. I'm very grateful.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll find them.
I said they may be alive,
but no one believed me.
No one.
Sorry about the
anesthetic. I mean it.
You know how to apologize.
I really was despicable.
I won't ask for you
to be understanding.
No. I can understand.
And I do.
So?
Why?
Right? She has enteritis, right?
Did you have
tteokbokki yesterday?
What?
- Yes.
- She ate the leftovers.
But that was level-five spicy.
Kong.
I'll prescribe a laxative.
Starve her today. Give her
only water and medicine.
Don't get sassy with me.
No snacks either, obviously.
Can you tell what she ate
just by looking at her?
I speak their language.
- I don't mean to be rude, but...
- No rude questions.
Especially something
that involves my privacy.
Okay. I'll change the question.
There are other foxes in the
world in addition to you, right?
Do they all look like people?
They live in this city...
just like you people.
They worry about real
estate and economic crises.
How do you want to pay?
Here you go.
Pay cash and I'll
give you a discount.
Then tell me about Shin Don.
Is it true that the monk of
Goryeo Dynasty was a fox?
My gosh.
- What else?
- Pay up.
Right.
Are there other creatures too?
Of course. And they mostly live
where humans would never guess.
How was today's meal?
Not bad.
Let's grab some lunch?
How about Korean cuisine
at The Snail Bride?
But I'm sick and
tired of samgyetang.
Can we eat something different?
Samgyetang and ginseng wine...
will rejuvenate us to get
through this hot summer.
Be honest with us, sir.
You just have the
hots for the owner.
What? That's
absolutely ridiculous!
Have you seen the chicken
they serve? Just come along.
Let's go.
Hello?
What is it?
My mom...
- passed away.
- What?
I had a dream of losing a tooth.
I saw a woman in my dream wearing
black mourning garments...
and weeping so eerily.
It was you.
This is where we part ways.
I hope that we never meet again.
What? You're just leaving me...
with the fact that my
parents are alive somewhere?
A. I'm a busy man.
B. We may currently be
living in the same world,
but there's a big difference
between where we come from.
I know that, but...
Those who got a
peek at my world...
ended up going crazy
or dying young.
I don't care and I'll
stay out of your way.
Just don't disappear.
What...
Can you get that call first?
Jae Hwan, I can't
talk right now...
Got it.
My coworker's
mother passed away.
She had a dream about
losing a tooth last night.
- A dream?
- She and I both had nightmares.
Contagious nightmares.
Do you really want to see...
the world I live in?
Studio Three, was it?
Yes. I left my equipment
there, but now it's gone.
Director Nam, is this
what you're looking for?
What on earth?
No...
When were you released?
I thought you said
you'd stay clean.
- I did nothing wrong.
- Really?
Then am I the jerk here?
Please don't kill me.
Give me one good
reason why I should.
- Well...
- There isn't one, right? Then die.
Just a second! Hold on.
Your brother told me...
that I could feed here.
Rang told you that?
What on earth is that thing?
A bulgasari.
A bulgasari?
The legendary creature
that feeds on nightmares?
Yes, they're especially fond
of broadcasting studios...
which are packed with people.
Eating metal reveals
their true identities.
Darn it.
Here's where I ask
you a question.
Don't come any closer!
I wasn't talking to you.
The hostage will answer.
At this very moment,
what can you do for me...
except get in my way?
I...
There's nothing you can do.
Go back to the
world you belong in.
Humans who grow accustomed
to the darkness...
will become beings that are
neither human nor anything else.
Hey, you. Get up. I
know you're not dead.
THE YELLOW SEA, JANGSAN POINT
- Heave-ho!
- Pull!
- My gosh.
My goodness.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
You're not even good
at doing your job.
But you never once skip a meal.
It's way past lunchtime.
I get seasick on
an empty stomach.
When will you ever learn
to do your job properly?
He's just like you
when you were young.
- Cut the nonsense!
- My gosh.
My goodness!
Is... Is that a human skull?
It's a dead body!
Watch what you say. Never
say that word on a boat.
Captain, we have
a Yain on board.
- Let's pay our respects.
- Got it.
We're going to
keep this on board?
Let's just throw it
back into the water.
When you meet a Yain, it's customary
to take him or her back to shore.
If you don't, they
haunt the boat.
That's just a superstition.
"Superstition"? The fishing
ground got destroyed...
when people didn't
follow the customs.
I'm sorry you had to
die in the southern sea.
This front tooth. The gold
tooth looks exactly like...
Is this Mr. Seo?
Hey.
Whose skull is it?
Do you have a name?
Can we eat first?
This is my first meal.
You're interested in every case
that occurs in this country.
This time, it's for
something personal.
Don't tell me...
you're still trying
to find your parents.
You need to get to
your senses, Ji A.
Let's stick to the subject.
Save the nagging for later.
This time, you'll have to
figure out for yourself.
We know who the guy is, but
the coast guard took the case.
- Do you know the cause of death?
- No, not yet.
But they identified the victim.
Who is it?
Let me see my dad.
Please let me see my dad!
Dad!
Please let me see him!
Are you still waiting
for your dead girlfriend?
I heard an interesting rumour.
Should I tell you what it is?
If you don't find it until
the end of the next month,
this woman will die.
Haven't you made
up your mind yet?
Please... Please let me live.
I'll let you live.
So just tell me where Rang is.
I don't know.
You're really inflexible.
How are you going to survive
in the 21st century like this?
I'll die even if I
tell you where he is.
Did he say that?
I'm way stronger than him.
Call him.
Let me know if you
change your mind.
No, wait.
Okay, fine. I'll call him.
Hello, it's me.
Things didn't exactly
go as planned.
I see you were drinking.
- Pour me a glass as well.
- Did you make him call me?
No wonder he sounded nervous.
You're all grown up now.
You used to hate raw fish.
Stop trying to look relaxed.
You must've been
pretty impatient...
seeing that you showed
up at this hour.
I was right, wasn't I?
She was reincarnated,
wasn't she?
Do you think she's
dead or alive?
She's alive.
If you wanted to kill her, you
would've brought her dead body.
And you love making bets,
so you'd never ruin the fun.
But what if I leave a dent
on our precious prize?
Don't even think of hurting her.
What will you do to
me if I do hurt her?
Tell me. I'm getting
really excited.
You're acting like this
because you lack affection.
Don't you get it? You
have a brother complex.
Shut it. It's all
because of you.
- Why is that?
- Just because of a woman,
you gave up your position
as a mountain spirit,
left the mountain,
and you even...
Yes, I know. I
even abandoned you.
Isn't that what
you wanted to hear?
Get out of my sight right now.
Did I upset you?
I'm done playing around.
The girl is in my hands.
Mind your manners.
Don't stay outside so late.
And don't drink too much.
It's not good for you.
You crazy fool. Do you
even know where she is?
Should I tell you or not?
I don't need to know.
You're here, and only one accident
occurred in this neighbourhood today.
No, I can go alone. I'm just
going to check things out.
Did you pack all the equipment?
Yes. Take good care of Ms. Kim.
Let me know once she
reserves a funeral hall.
Okay, bye.
Did you watch the
breaking news? The head.
She and I both had nightmares.
This can't be a coincidence.
I didn't notice this earlier.
But is that a Kimite patch?
Who are you looking
for? A human being?
Or a fox?
I'd like to keep it to myself.
Tell me. Thanks to my job,
I'm pretty good
at finding people.
No, thank you.
Why did you want to
come to this island?
I thought you wanted
to find your parents.
Let me ask you something.
Are all the dreams from bulgasaris,
the legendary creatures, true?
They cunningly mix
the truth with lies.
And they wait for
people to fall for that.
So that means part
of it is true.
If that's why you're
here, you should go back.
You need to be careful with
what you pay attention to.
Too bad. I'm already here.
The same boat. The same island.
A woman who looks just like her.
My guts keep telling me...
that this is a very
suspicious combination.
What in the world is waiting
for us on that island?
My gosh, why did you
only buy streusel bread?
I told you to buy
sweet red bean buns.
Just eat what I bought for you.
You darn brat.
If you keep acting that way, I
won't buy you anything anymore.
No, I take it back. Keep
buying me bread. It's good.
I waited for you.
Are you Mr. Seo Ki
Chang's daughter?
Excuse me.
I'm Director Nam Ji A,
the person who called.
Is he here with you?
- No, he's...
- Yes, I came with her.
- I'm a staff.
- What?
- Let's go to my house.
- Sure.
Come inside.
Do you want some barley tea?
I thought you didn't
want to be involved.
I changed my mind.
Don't let it bother you.
What is your problem?
What a shabby place. Do I
need to take off my shoes?
- I guess your father lived alone.
- Yes.
I worked at a semiconductor
factory and lived in Incheon.
My dad worked on a boat.
Don't be nervous. Make
yourself comfortable.
Did he go missing
because of an accident?
They said the storm
flipped over the boat.
Hey.
What did the police say?
They're not sure because of
the severe decomposition.
They say if a person...
gets caught in the propeller,
their body can get severed.
When was the last time you
heard from your father?
He called on the
morning of the accident.
I missed the call though.
VOICEMAIL
Pyung Hee?
Are you eating well?
Come by if you aren't too busy.
I packed up some
seafood for you.
I keep seeing your late
mom in my dream lately.
She tries to rush off
somewhere, holding your hand.
She must miss her daughter.
What happened to your mother?
She passed away from cancer.
Why did he have a
dream like that?
She came to get you.
If someone who died after living
out their allotted time shows up,
they're coming for someone.
I'm sure the person who was
supposed to die that day was you.
- Stop it.
- What?
Your father saved your life.
Is what some people may
say. That's what I mean.
There's no Americano, right?
Don't drink too much, and go.
Why do you think people from
a Seoul TV station came here?
I'm sure that brat Kyung
Hee snitched to them.
We should throw that
brat into the ocean...
- and make her fish bait.
- Lower your voice, man.
It really gives me a
bad feeling in my mouth.
Why did his head have to
get caught in our net?
No one has seen Jin Shik...
since he found the head, right?
It wasn't me. I didn't do it.
I had no choice.
Stay here in my house
rather than at a guesthouse.
Thank you.
You can use this room.
- I have to step out for a bit.
- Okay.
If you insist.
It's shabby as expected.
It's fine with me. I'm used to
it from travelling for work.
I'm not fine with it.
I'm sorry, but there's one room,
and I have to stick to the subject.
What about me?
There's a mountain right there.
I saw in a documentary that
burrowing is your specialty.
Sorry, but I'm a bit modern.
I can't sleep where
there's no boiler.
You can't go.
Borrowing is my specialty.
Hey.
- Who are you?
- I'm a customer.
Why don't you have mint
chocolate chip ice cream?
Just pick something that I have.
You have a terrible
service mentality.
Hello. I'm sorry to intrude,
but you're the one who found
that head recently, right?
Did someone report
it to the TV station?
No. I found out from the news.
May I join you?
Go ahead.
Were you close to
the late Mr. Seo?
We lived in the same
town, that's all.
We just saw each
other in passing.
We were neighbours.
No more, no less.
What? From what I hear, you worked
on the same fishing boat for years.
We can't talk for free.
I'd like to have a drink
poured by a young lady.
I haven't smelled the
scent of makeup in a while.
Hey. Why you little...
Oh, dear. I was
being too generous.
How dare a witch from
outside come here and...
If you're going to hit
me, would you please...
turn a little this way?
That angle doesn't
look too great.
- Darn it.
- Let's go.
Nice. You're tough.
That was nothing.
Why are you following me?
I'm not following you.
I'm investigating a story.
I'm doing something similar.
Then go ahead.
I plan to piggyback off of
you as much as possible.
So you do it.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Excuse me. May I
ask you something?
I just want to
ask you one thing.
It won't take long.
Excuse me. It won't take...
Ma'am.
Ma'am. I just need
a few minutes.
Why do you make it so hard?
It isn't easy to get elderly people
from the countryside to open up.
They always sing like
a bird when I ask.
Do you have a special method?
I break their fingers one
by one until they answer.
I doubt that will
be very productive.
You don't seem to be very
good at investigating.
- I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
People aren't the only
ones with eyes and mouths.
How does he walk so fast?
Do you hear something?
Hush.
It's a dead forest.
What?
All the spirits in
the forest left.
Why is that?
Because they were abandoned
and forgotten by people.
Who are you?
I greet the former
master of the forest.
- Do you know me?
- I saw you from far away once.
You're the spirit of
the guardian tree.
What misfortune happened here?
I do not know.
- You don't know?
- This island has changed.
The house spirits that
guarded the houses...
and the land spirits all left.
So there is nobody to fill me
in on what happens in the town.
Since when?
Since immediately after
the end of the Korean War.
Something evil came to the
island riding a typhoon...
But I couldn't see it and
I was too weak to stop it.
It must have been very
lonely being all by yourself.
I wanted to leave,
but I couldn't because my
feet are tied to the tree.
Is this why?
Will you cut that for her?
You're a soul!
You're a spirit.
Yes, yes. Dear deceased soul...
who left today.
Become a spirit. Become a soul.
Thank you.
I'm free now.
I don't quite get it,
but I'm glad I helped.
By the way, make sure
to wear some shoes.
Your pretty feet have
cuts all over them.
I see you have a history
with these woods.
But it's my first time here.
Travel north on this island. You'll
find your first answer there.
I see you have a history
with these woods.
But it's my first time here.
Travel north on this island.
You'll find your
first answer there.
She vanished.
You did well.
The rope was bound by the
prayers and wishes of humans,
so only a human could untie it.
Mighty King of the Yellow Sea!
Old madam of the
underwater kingdom.
- Please return my father's body.
- Old madam!
Please let him have his funeral.
Show mercy for this poor soul...
and return the body...
of her father to her.
Here I pray.
Here I pray for you.
Here I pray!
- What's wrong?
- He isn't here.
He isn't in the water.
His body returned to
shore before his head did!
Your father!
"Jangsansa Cave"?
I've never heard of it before.
JANGSANSA CAVE ENTRANCE, STAY
CLEAR DURING THE RISING TIDE
I'm going to grab a bite to eat.
Stop right there.
Don't move for a second.
What is it?
I feel like I've seen
this place before.
This was the place.
This is where this
photo was taken.
So you do have
ties to this place.
This was shortly
after I was conceived.
I was here too.
I came here with my parents
while in my mom's womb.
Why on earth were my parents...
on this island?
The duvet stinks. It must
not have been washed.
You're the one who was adamant
about not going to a nicer inn.
I have my reasons.
Just so you know,
I have a fatty liver.
- It's chronic.
- And why must I know this?
You're a nine-tailed fox.
Maybe you'll start
craving for liver...
We don't eat that crap!
- Really?
- Heard of the Chinese liver fluke?
Don't laugh especially
with that face you have.
What about my face? What?
You're ugly, that's why.
Oh my.
He went to the island to
find this reincarnated girl?
That's right. He's a romantic
although he seems otherwise.
They say that foxes only
mate once in their lives.
How romantic.
As if that's a good thing.
You know what that cost him.
At least once in our lives,
we come across that one person
we want to give our lives to.
I won't ever devote
myself to love.
My goal will be to
protect Mr. Lee.
That can also be love.
What was I expecting?
She was reincarnated,
wasn't she?
Do you think she's
dead or alive?
Is it possible for her to be
reborn with the same face?
Don't look for her.
If you don't find it until
the end of the next month,
this woman will die.
It may flip your destiny
upside down again.
What do you say?
I bet you want it.
My goodness. Wild ginseng
isn't easy to find.
How much can this be worth?
- Not yet.
- But...
Talk to her first.
Don't speak informally to her.
But she's only 74 which
is a baby by my standards.
What is it that
you want to know?
Go ahead.
Well,
why is everyone keeping
their silence about the head?
Well, that...
- You tell her.
- What?
You can't tell anyone...
that you heard it from us.
I promise.
Well, you see,
this isn't the first time.
That's right.
The human head...
- Jae Hwan, it's me.
- Ms. Nam, you won't believe it.
There really were similar cases?
- And the victims?
- Four Jane Does.
When?
The first incident
happened in 1954.
1954?
What on earth happened
on this island?
That man...
Excuse me. Weren't you on the
boat with Pyung Hee's father?
Excuse me!
Please hear me out!
Hold on!
Why are you running away?
Get lost, you ghost!
Don't kill him!
Yu Ri, there's something I want.
This place?
We just opened up.
The haunted house.
It's not that bad.
- What is that?
- It's a folk remedy.
- It's hot.
- Gosh, stop being a crybaby.
Your hand is so hot.
It's burning hot.
What...
What's this?
Long time no see, Yeon.
Who are you?
It's me. The person
you've been waiting for.
What?
But let me ask you something.
Why...
did you kill me?
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Something's coming.
So this is where it's buried?
A dragon with no feet.
What do you think that is?
You've gone head over
heels for a woman.
You also ruined your life
because you fell for a woman.
What did you say, you punk?
Something doesn't feel right.
I need to find out why my
parents came to this island.
She'll become a scapegoat.
You can't leave this place.
I want you to kill her.
That's how you can
keep your lady alive.