Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
When a fox turns 100,
it can transform into
a beautiful woman...
or become a man who
has relations with one.
However, a fox of 1,000 years
receives the sky's blessing...
and becomes a celestial fox.
Its abilities match that
of a powerful shaman...
which allows it to see
what are miles ahead.
I was going to wait
until we get home,
but here's your
birthday present.
Do you like your gift?
Yes, I love it.
1999, YEOU GOGAE
Ji A.
Help.
My princess, you're up.
Thank goodness. It was a dream.
President Kim Dae Jung...
- Here you go.
- Here's our fruit.
Mom, I love you. I
love you so much.
What's gotten into you?
Dad, I love you. I
love you so much.
My goodness. I also love
you very much, Ji A.
Did you have a bad dream?
I don't even want
to think about it.
- My goodness.
- They will be sticking to the plan.
Many people got injured due
to the fire that broke out...
at Seongjin Market this evening.
The fire broke out at 7pm...
and got extinguished after having
burned down three buildings.
The fire caused severe
damage to the market,
and a total of 22 people
ended up getting injured.
The fire broke out in a
cramped space in the market...
and spread throughout...
Mom, I'm hungry.
- Do you want some fruit?
- No.
I want walnut cookies.
Let's see. Where did I
put the walnut cookies?
I think we ate them all.
Can I get them for you tomorrow?
We never buy walnut cookies.
I had to go to the hospital
because it turned out...
I was allergic to nuts.
Oh, right. I forgot.
My mom never forgets that
because she's a doctor.
I just forgot about it because
I'm really tired today.
You're not my mom.
- Ji A.
- Where's my mom?
I am your mom.
Honey!
Come here!
Ji A, open the door.
Come outside. Let's talk.
Ji A, be a good girl.
You little brat.
A Eum.
Are you A Eum?
I guess not.
You're not A Eum.
Forget everything you saw today.
If you don't...
Road 144, Yeou Gogae.
A sedan rolled over.
I see bloodstains on the
driver's and passenger seat.
It looks like they
shed a lot of blood.
But I don't see any bodies.
Mom. Dad.
Yes, the only survivor
is a little girl.
Mom!
- Dad!
- Are you okay?
My parents are gone.
Will you help me find them?
I'll find them for
you. Don't worry.
Do you remember how
the accident happened?
Were you here by yourself?
CHAPTER 1: THE INCIDENT
THAT OCCURRED ON YEOU GOGAE
21 YEARS LATER
WEDDING, AUGUST 29, 2020
Please eat ice cream after
you eat your breakfast.
Why is it raining? I didn't see
this on the weather forecast.
Gosh, I know. I got
my hair done today.
- It's all wet.
- My goodness, you're right.
Your hair is all wet.
That's because a fox is
getting married today.
What was that?
He's handsome.
- Can you take a photo for us?
- Sure.
1, 2, 3.
- Let me see.
- It came out really nice.
- Does it look nice?
- You look beautiful.
You didn't send me a
wedding invitation.
Will you please excuse us?
- Who is he?
- Is he your ex?
- You should introduce him to us.
- Get out.
Lee Yeon, what are
you doing here?
I'm not here to
catch your bouquet.
How did you find me?
How did you manage
to hide so well?
Do you think you can get rid
of your bloodthirsty past...
just by changing your
looks and identity?
But you need to know that
changing your identity...
isn't as simple as you think.
- Please forgive me.
- It's too late for that.
I've changed. I don't
harm humans anymore.
Listen, you fox.
How could you dare dream
of having a happy ending...
after eating so many livers?
I'm in love now.
I want to live as a
human being. Please.
How romantic.
But you're still
going to die today.
You also once loved
a human being.
I'm sure you understand.
You must not know this.
But first of all, I hate it
when people bring up my past.
And second of all,
don't even dare...
to take out your claws.
- Goodbye.
- Just once.
Let me see him
just one last time.
Here's a piece of advice. It's
completely useless to do that.
Please. It's my last wish.
It's time for the wedding.
Oh, okay.
You need to go in now. Let's go.
Just until the ceremony ends.
There may be entities
living among us...
that we are unaware of.
Perhaps the many
urban legends...
are really about them.
- What do you think?
- Did you revise the script again?
The writer will faint.
- Will she be really mad?
- Of course.
Notwithstanding that, the
revision is much better, right?
Of course. What?
Then go with this.
A production director
needs to have guts.
It's really strange.
I don't believe in
monsters or ghosts,
but this scares me.
I'm not scared at all,
but I believe in them.
You do? Why?
Did you see one in real life?
Mom. Dad.
- Yes.
- Really?
You're just trying to scare me.
You can tell yourself that.
The weather stinks.
They say rain on your wedding day
means you'll have a happy marriage.
Congratulations!
- The meal tickets.
- We're good.
No, no. We'll take them.
All you get after giving
an expensive gift is food.
I can never digest wedding food.
Why do you think that is?
The air filled with forced
happiness suffocates me.
You should try to absorb the
forced happiness near you at times.
Who knows? You may meet the man
you're destined to be with here.
EMERGENCY. THE
INFORMANT FLAKED.
I need a story that
I'm destined to cover.
The informant flaked.
The pyebaek room is this way.
- Come this way.
- Please come with me.
Former master of Baekdudaegan.
By what authority
do you convict us?
Listen to this brat.
I'd be watching American TV shows
and having ice cream if not for you.
You're just a nine-tailed
fox stripped of...
your mountain spirit status
for breaking a taboo.
That's why I'm
paying for it now.
Help me!
Who are you?
Do you really think you
can hide dressed like that?
Who are you?
You really won't listen.
No.
- No.
- Don't look. Please.
How foolish.
You should've run away
when you had the time.
I wanted to be a bride.
Don't do something stupid like
falling in love in your next time.
I have one last favor to ask.
Please...
remove only the good memories
of me from his memory.
Sure.
Listen carefully.
Your bride...
Hey. She's not bad.
Hey. Keep it down.
You'll get me in trouble.
You look good.
Do I?
How could this happen?
Wait here.
What now?
- Hey, this is huge.
- What happened?
The wedding in the
next room was canceled.
Really?
Who was he again?
Who is he? Do you know him?
- No.
- Should I find out?
- What?
- How that peaceful wedding...
turned into Pandora's Box.
Who knows? That may be the story
you were destined to cover.
The bride ran away.
She ran away?
Sure, that's possible.
But what kind of an
enlightenment must you obtain...
to make such an expensive
about-face in life?
True love.
- Did she have a guy?
- Yes.
He said, "She's my woman."
Then the bride grabbed
his hand and said,
"I'm going with my love."
All the witnesses
said the same thing.
There's a sign of resistance.
- Isn't that blood?
- There was a scuffle.
No one mentioned that.
Most importantly,
why is this dress here?
Because she took it off...
You're right. What
did she leave in?
The witness statements and
the scene of the incident...
are telling different stories.
Were they mass
hypnotized or something?
I need to see what that woman
of this love story looks like.
Okay. I'll get a video.
It's fox fur.
- Fox?
- A red fox.
A native of Korea.
The native foxes are extinct.
Oh my.
There's something you
actually don't know.
In 2012, they started a
business reviving foxes.
Look.
EXTINCT FOX SPECIES
REVIVED AFTER 40 YEARS
How was a fox native
to Mount Sobaek...
found near here?
One was caught in an
apartment complex in Gyeongju,
and one even crossed the
DMZ into North Korea.
So showing up in a wedding
hall in Gangnam is nothing.
Hungry wild hogs rampage
through convenience stores.
All the foxes of Mount
Sobaek have GPS trackers.
None of them came to Seoul yet.
I was an assistant director for
an animal show for two years.
Okay. So where could
this have come from?
Please pick up.
I'm in love with someone.
I want to live as a
human being. Please.
A selfie? Now?
Nice.
Smile.
You loved a human once.
You understand
how I feel, right?
Here.
Thank you.
So Yoon!
Are you an alien?
- No.
- Then what are you?
- A nine-tailed fox.
- Are you over 100 years old?
Actually, I'm over 1,000.
What are you doing here though?
Nothing other than
waiting for someone.
- As in who?
- My first love.
Why?
Because a fox can only
love one person...
till death.
My mom waits for the
delivery man every day.
She only has to wait two days.
Not for me even after
100 or 1,000 nights.
- How are you coping with that?
- Not well.
Then what if I kept you company?
- No.
- Why not?
Just look at you. I hate
those with a runny nose.
Besides, humans die too early
to properly have a friendship.
I'm saying that life is short,
so try your best in life...
but know to let go when
something's too unbearable.
It extends to people, love,
and so on and so forth.
- Okay?
- Okay!
AFTERLIFE IMMIGRATION OFFICE
CRACKDOWN ON UNDOCUMENTED
SPIRITS ARE BEING ENFORCED.
AFTERLIFE IMMIGRATION OFFICE
How have you been, Granny?
You haven't been around much.
I've been busy, thanks to you.
Never did I imagine...
seeing the great Taluipa
struggle to operate a computer.
What can I do when
the world has changed?
The Afterlife should have
a five-day workweek too.
Did you get my text?
- About the female fox?
- Why was there no response?
Do I seem like someone who has
the time to listen to sob stories?
You're to obey the order and
capture whom you're sent after.
Until when must I carry this on?
Have you lost your mind?
Did they serve rat poison
at the wedding ceremony?
How can one not lose it...
after following orders as
a soldier for 600 years?
As a soldier?
Nobody forced you to give up...
being a mountain spirit
and live this way.
You're the one who
chose this life...
in return for that
girl's resurrection.
"I, Lee Yeon, former mountain
spirit of Baekdudaegan,"
"will punish those who
disrupt the order..."
"between the Living Realm
and the Afterlife..."
"in return for A
Eum's resurrection."
Foxes never stay in debt, right?
Darn it.
So tell me...
Do you want your freedom back?
You'll end up in the Underworld.
- What?
- I'll pray for it every day.
How dare you.
And stop munching on
glucosamine tablets.
Having a kind heart is
the key to healthy joints.
HYEONUIONG: GATEKEEPER
OF SAMDO RIVER
- Hey, Yeon.
- Hey.
MEASURES THE SIN
OF THE SPIRITS
What the... Is he
leaving already?
Darling!
Have some tteokbokki.
I've lost my appetite
because of that jerk.
Goodness, don't be so harsh.
Be more considerate of his
heart that awaits a dead woman.
This again? Stop
being such a sap.
You're absolutely clueless
when it comes to love.
I should have the
tteokbokki all by myself.
Mr. Lee, why haven't
you been picking up?
- What is it?
- It's a Code Red!
- Tell me what it is.
- Where are you right now?
"UNVEILING URBAN LEGENDS"
SHAMANISM AND SHAMANS
THE CURSED TREE
ALL 45 MEMBERS OF THE CREW
WERE FOUND AS SKELETONS.
Someone revised my script again.
Are you trying to
pick a fight with me?
I committed a mortal sin.
Your attitude says otherwise.
- Are they at it again?
- Should we fight it out?
- Yes, let's.
- No, don't.
Just stay out of it, sir.
I'm back!
- Did you find something?
- I'm not sure.
Is it about the runaway bride?
Bring it over so that
I can see the face.
A red umbrella with an
embroidered pattern?
He has weird taste.
I got the footage that
has the best angle of him.
This is him going in...
and this is him going out.
His face is completely
hidden under the umbrella.
Hold on a second. It didn't
rain after the wedding.
Then he's the intelligent type.
I get why he's alone
when he entered,
but why also on the way out?
- She can't be found.
- What?
I checked all the footage
from the wedding hall,
but I couldn't see
the bride leaving it.
Have you been listening to me?
- Regarding what?
- That...
That female director
brought over fox fur.
- Did you get caught?
- When I'm a seasoned veteran?
I'm now up to the point
where I'm wondering...
if I've turned into
an actual person.
You must be proud.
Anyway, I'm getting a bad vibe.
- Did you enjoy your meal?
- Somewhat.
- Installments?
- A single payment, please.
Mr. Lee, there... Over there!
What now?
"UNVEILING URBAN LEGENDS"
That's you, right? Oh, no!
Maybe you shouldn't carry around
that umbrella for the time being.
This? No.
Tell that human...
to catch me if you can.
- Are you serious?
- What...
TRADITIONAL KOREAN
CUISINE: THE SNAIL BRIDE
What did I tell you
about that bad vibe?
That show's actually
quite famous.
- Are you the one with the tip?
- Oh, yes.
I'm the director for
"Unveiling Urban Legends".
Could I get an autograph later?
I watch each episode
about 20 times, you see.
Please have a seat.
So you saw him?
- Of course.
- Who is he?
- A monster.
- A monster?
He never ages or dies.
Like goblins and aliens
you see in movies.
- I see you don't believe me.
- If I'm being honest, no.
You shouldn't
underestimate me though.
I don't lie.
May I ask what you
do for a living?
I'm studying for the state exam.
- And your hometown?
- Yeongam, South Jeolla Province.
My mother, who has always
been a farmer, has one wish...
which is to see me work
at a decent office.
Take care, then.
I have more to tell you.
Your backstory doesn't
match your shoes.
What kind of student can
afford customized shoes...
that are worth 4,000 dollars?
You don't have an accent from
Yeongam, South Jeolla Province.
That already tells me that I
shouldn't be wasting my time.
- Bye then.
- Yeou Gogae.
"Yeou Gogae"?
That's where I saw him.
How can I trust something
coming from an unidentified man?
You can check for yourself.
Hey, you're back.
Gosh, I picked the
wrong pair of shoes.
She noticed that right away.
But why are you smiling?
I like her.
What do you like about her?
I like her from head to toe.
Then should we eat her...
from head to toe?
No, not yet.
Which flavor do you want?
- Mint chocolate.
- That's all you ever eat.
I noticed that you're a
regular, so I gave you a lot.
Next time, just give
me the usual amount.
- Pardon?
- When I'm indebted to someone,
I'm obligated to
return the favor.
The number you've called
doesn't exist, you punk.
Long time no see.
- What do you want?
- I just missed you.
What are you doing?
I'm busy. Hang up.
You don't look very busy.
Let's meet.
I refuse.
I'll set your house on fire.
You're 600 years old.
Stop acting like a kid.
You'll regret it.
- No, I won't.
- Are you still waiting...
for your dead girlfriend?
I heard an interesting rumor.
Should I tell you what it is?
Don't try to mess with me.
If you want to
know, come meet me.
Tonight, go to the place I told
you about and get on a bus.
But I have one condition.
What's that?
You must come alone.
SEONGHAN-DONG COMMUNITY
SERVICE CENTER
"UNVEILING URBAN LEGENDS"
Hey, do you direct TV shows?
- Yes.
- My dream is to become a director.
You should become
something else.
I've been working today
for 22 hours straight.
- My goodness, you hurt me!
- Sir.
Are you okay?
Are you going to get
on the bus or not?
I'm coming. Just a second.
Get up. Let me take
you to a hospital.
Get off me!
Sir, I need to get on this bus.
- Hey, let's just go.
- My gosh.
- Are you not coming?
- I'm going. Just a second.
Don't go, you brat!
- Sir!
- Don't go, you brat!
It's him.
Don't go, you brat!
- Sir!
- Don't go, you brat!
It's him.
Wait!
YEOU GOGAE
Sir, where do you live again?
Just take me to that
tree over there.
Sir.
You're a lot heavier
than you seem.
How strange.
He's so heavy.
I can't even hear him breathing.
Sir.
It... It hurts.
Please... Your hand...
We're here.
You should cut down on alcohol.
Don't think I'll give
you credit for this.
I already paid you back.
What?
Sir, wait.
Where to?
Please follow the route
of bus number 1002.
Sir, did you see the old
man who was behind me?
Who are you talking about?
You're the only person I saw.
Hello? I'd like to
report an accident.
Road 144.
Yes, it's Yeou Gogae.
"Yeou Gogae"?
Road 144, Fox Ridge.
My parents are gone.
No.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Wake up.
Hey.
I said no pictures!
You need to stop
them. Seriously.
Hey, Ji A. What
are you doing here?
Detective Baek. You almost had
to process my corpse today.
What are you talking about?
- I almost got on that bus.
- What?
That was my bus. I was
supposed to be on it.
Are you serious?
- 5 are dead, and 1 survived.
- Really?
- There should be one more person.
- What?
There were seven
people on this bus.
Are you sure?
I saw with my own eyes.
He's the only one missing.
There's no body or anything.
He probably got off.
No. This bus didn't stop
before the accident.
There's no bus
stop in the tunnel.
I need to check
something. Get out.
Hurry it up.
"DEATH TRAP ROAD 144!
ONLY 1 OUT OF 6 SURVIVED"
"Only 1 out of 6 survived."
- Let's go.
- Too many people died.
- So?
- Just leave it.
I have to finish it by myself.
JUNG SOO YOUNG
Soo Young. Do you recognize me?
We met at the bus stop.
Do you remember how
the accident occurred?
You must be scared because you
were the only one who survived.
I was in a similar
accident a long time ago.
That's why I'm all alone.
If you put your mind to it,
a tragedy can become a
very convenient shield.
Because everyone fusses over you
and pours out their sympathy.
But I hope you'll become strong.
It's much more fun being a
production director than a victim.
Contact me if you need anything.
Did you see that young man
who sat by the window...
on the right side of the bus?
He had an umbrella like this.
You did see him.
What did you see? What
was it, that you're so...
He's coming.
What?
He's coming to kill me.
He'll come to kill me too.
Jae Hwan. Tell Detective Baek to
send some people to the hospital.
Yes. What about the
camera from the bus?
It's blank.
It's the same as
the wedding hall.
- What about on the road?
- There aren't any at all.
I'm looking for the teenage
girl who was admitted...
after the bus
accident yesterday.
Are you together?
What?
Found him.
WOOJIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Why does a TV station's production
director want to see me?
This voice. It couldn't be.
Why do you think?
Are you scouting me
to become an idol?
But sorry, I can't
sing or dance.
My only talent is my face.
Yes, I'm scouting
you, but not for that.
- Then?
- Fox Ridge.
Is it a horror movie?
It's an urban legend.
For example, 1 passenger on
the 1002 bus disappeared.
Like he evaporated
into thin air.
It doesn't sound like
it'll be very well-made.
Plus, I'm more into rom-com.
What about this?
That color photographs
really well.
I don't know if it's
a coincidence or fate,
but I saw you three
times already.
First, it was in a wedding hall
in which a bride disappeared.
Second, on the 1002 bus.
Third, at this hospital where
I came to meet the victim.
Let's say it was fate.
But sorry to disappoint.
I'm seeing someone.
Plus, I'm very devoted.
Did you kill them?
Or did you come to kill her?
I met someone that I
want to kill. Just now.
Where is he? He said he'd
be back in 10 minutes.
Don't people usually have
evidence to back them up...
when they ask rude
questions like that?
Like physical
proof or witnesses.
Or at least a police badge.
You're right. I was very
rude, wasn't I? I'm sorry.
I don't need your empty apology.
You didn't touch your coffee.
Have some.
I don't eat or drink
anything from strangers.
It's such a dangerous world.
One more thing.
What now?
- What's your name?
- Who knows?
Why don't you try to find out?
Wait.
At least take my business card.
It's inside.
What is this, a blind date?
I don't want a second date.
Hey, Jae Hwan. Ask Detective
Baek to run a fingerprint for me.
Yes.
A leather bag.
This is totally fate.
The little girl whose life you
saved 20-plus years ago showed up.
She must not even remember.
I don't like it.
She really does look like her.
I get surprised every
time I see her too.
You should quit consulting
for that TV station.
No. That's directly
related to my livelihood.
It's just a B-rated program.
It's the only show you enjoy.
"Unveiling Urban Legends".
You even posted a comment
on their website...
that the Grim Reaper's
outfit was all wrong.
I know Grim Reapers well...
Concentrate on driving.
Soo Young, are you all right?
I told you to keep
an eye on her.
I only left the room
for about five minutes.
- Did you catch the guy?
- No one saw even a shadow.
Maybe she's just dreaming.
I'm not!
Ji A, I don't want to stay here.
I must leave.
Soo Young.
If I stay,
I'll die.
MISSING PARENTS
"MYSTERY ACCIDENT
ON YEOU GOGAE"
I don't if my clothes will fit.
I'm sorry for putting
you out like this.
It's only for the night.
What about your family?
I live alone, so make
yourself at home.
She's all alone.
When did she get discharged?
It hasn't been long.
She asked me to
give this to you.
- Who...
- The lady who took the patient.
Soo Young?
Why aren't you in bed?
I suddenly remembered...
what happened in
the tunnel that day.
The bus entered the tunnel.
I took out my earphones...
only to be met with silence.
Do you want...
Everyone was dead.
From the darkness,
he began to approach me.
He?
The man with the umbrella.
What did that man do?
He tried to kill me!
I was terrified.
It's all right.
It'll be all fine.
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
- Lift up your feet.
- I'm good.
Soo Young, where were you headed
in the middle of the night?
What? Home, of course...
I checked your address
and in order to do so,
you had to be going
the other way.
You see, that night...
Stop blabbering
whatever comes to mind.
Ji A...
When did you figure it out?
Humans...
instinctively move to
protect themselves...
when involved in car accidents.
However, the sole survivor
of that bus crash...
had no defensive wounds.
I don't believe in
miracles, you see.
Who are you?
I'm someone you know...
and also someone you don't.
How...
Where's the real Soo Young?
I ate her.
As if something like
this could hurt me.
I know.
I only offered myself as bait.
Bait?
Hey, you. Didn't I reject
your proposal earlier?
What you're looking for
will be at my house.
Shouldn't you get busy?
- Did you miss me?
- As if, brother.
- Brother?
- It's a long story,
but the family has a dirty past.
This is why kids
must be disciplined.
How many people have you killed?
Are you worried I'll be
sucked into the Underworld?
No, it's because
you embarrass me.
This is because I don't want
a pathetic life like yours.
What's more pathetic is
a grown man who whines.
Time out. How about
a bet instead?
Old habits really do die hard.
If you don't find it until
the end of the next month,
this woman will die.
- What?
- You know I'm not joking.
I'll see you around.
You... Who on earth
are you people?
Forget everything about me.
DETECTIVE BAEK
I got the result back on the
fingerprint you wanted an ID on.
As if something like
this could hurt me.
I only offered myself as bait.
Bait?
Shin Ju, is that you?
Why are all the doors open?
Did you miss me?
- As if, brother.
- Brother?
It's a long story, but the
family has a dirty past.
What's going on?
This is why kids
must be disciplined.
How many people have you killed?
Are you worried I'll be
sucked into the Underworld?
No, it's because
you embarrass me.
This is because I don't want
a pathetic life like yours.
What's more pathetic is
a grown man who whines.
Do you like it?
How did you come here?
Name. Lee Yeon.
Age. 36 years old.
It's pretty obvious that you
live with a fake identity.
Now, I can proudly
say that it's fate.
You remember what happened?
I don't know what it is, but
I guess it didn't work on me.
What do you want?
The original copy is in here.
If you want it,
come and take it.
I knew it. You're not human.
Did you just test me?
Forget everything you saw today.
If you don't,
I'll kill you.
I've been waiting for you.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
It comes with a cost?
I'm going to take your eyes...
for having seen what you
never should've seen.
I'm going to keep
bothering them...
until one of them dies.
Go back to your world.
I'm desperate.
Is that a Kimite patch?
So this is where it's buried?
Do not look for it. It will
change your fate again.
A Eum was reborn, wasn't she?
Just don't disappear.
Do you really want to
see the world I live in?