Does it not hurt anymore?
Look at me.
Long time no see, Yeon.
She's mine.
How does it feel?
After a whole 600 years,
you face your enemy through
the body of the woman you love.
Ji A...
Where is she?
Right here. She lies inside me.
She screams in agony...
while resenting her
inevitable fate.
Let me ask you this, then.
Who was the other guy...
and what exactly are you?
This is all your doing.
If you had let her be
sacrificed in the island's well,
we would've stayed as one,
not be split into two.
Though when the times
comes, we'll unite.
And when exactly
will that happen?
When we jump into
your body instead.
What's with your
obsession over my body?
Why can't you unite in another's
and live happily ever after?
Are you not aware of
the speed it grows?
Could it be...
that you not only grow,
but also age as fast?
That's the curse laid on you.
I came across one opportunity
to change my fate.
By becoming a dragon?
If I had,
I'd have been the spirit
of Baekdudaegan, not you.
So what you want is revenge.
That's why out of all
the immortal bodies,
you're after mine.
Just so you know, now
that I'm finally dominant,
she'll soon fade away.
- I'll kill you.
- If you do,
she'll die too.
And saving her will
lead to your death.
Will you save her
or save yourself?
I hate to tell you this,
but none of the above
is what we want.
Yap all you want.
I won't let you touch this body.
You're weak.
What?
Does it weaken you to
be dominant in her body?
Most of the Imoogi's strength
and abilities lie with him.
You're only the
heart, so to speak.
That's why you need
Ji A as your shield...
to prevent me from
knowing how weak you are.
You two can't change
the inevitable.
With you gone, it'll
be over. Just you.
And you're the only
one I need, Ji A.
Please.
Just give up that
body of yours and die.
Ji A,
I know you can hear me.
I know you're there.
Shut it.
Come back to me.
I'll always be waiting for you,
so come back to me.
I'll always be waiting for you.
I've been waiting for you too.
When it comes to waiting,
no one can do it better.
24 hours? I could sit
there even for 24 years.
I had a feeling that
I could meet you here.
I'll always be by your side.
I'm yours till death do us part.
Yeon...
Yes, it's me. I'm right here.
Help me, Yeon.
Just kill me instead.
So that I never hurt you.
Ji A, it's all right.
It'll all be all right.
CHAPTER 13: THE OTHER IMOOGI
Dr. Koo, thank you for
today. You saved us.
Thank Mr. Lee Yeon, not me.
Take care then, guys.
Mr. Lee!
I'll be right there.
Yeon or the Imoogi, none
of them matter to me.
All I need are the
ground cherries.
Just the ground cherries!
Hey, there.
One shouldn't be so rough
in the driver's seat.
- Who are you?
- The name's Hyeonuiong.
I'm here to retrieve
the ground cherries.
Who sent you? Imoogi? Lee Yeon?
How's that of importance?
What matters is that this
doesn't belong to you.
Stop talking nonsense.
The ground cherries
are mine. They're mine!
Gosh, that hurt so much.
I hate the smell of gunpowder.
Listen to me. You shouldn't
fight against fate.
What? Are you also a monster?
My goodness.
It looks like we'll
meet again pretty soon.
Mr. Lee.
SHIN JU'S ANIMAL HOSPITAL
So right now, she's
Director Nam, right?
But who knows when she might turn
into Imoogi and attack you again?
I let him hurt me.
What?
I wanted to check.
The fact that Imoogi split
into two could be his strength,
but it could also
be a fatal weakness.
What do you mean?
The Imoogi inside Ji A's body...
is a little different from
the one I've seen until now.
They're both the same Imoogi
but a little different?
This one is a lot more similar
to the Imoogi from my past life.
What can I do to help?
Go meet the Snail Bride and ask
her about the fortune teller.
The guy who took the fox bead?
Should I turn them
back into humans?
Check the list and turn only those
who still have lives left to live.
It'll be tiring to turn them
all into humans at once.
Okay, got it. But
let's eat first.
Honey, should I
buy you tteokbokki?
How about I add some
fritters and sundae as well?
I also want extra cheese.
Okay, I'll add extra
mozzarella cheese.
And as for spiciness, I'll
order level three for you,
and I'll get myself a level one.
THE LIST: A RECORD OF
EACH PERSON'S LIFESPAN
There will be chaos...
if I don't stop him now.
NAME: NAM JI A, DATE
OF BIRTH: MARCH 3, 1991
DATE OF DEATH: 2020...
Even so,
I'd still choose her.
NAME: NAM JI A, DATE
OF BIRTH: MARCH 3, 1991
DATE OF DEATH: 2020...
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
With my own hands...
I stabbed you with
my own hands...
and hurt you.
I know better than anyone
that it wasn't you.
Look at me.
How do you feel? Are you okay?
How could you possibly
be worried about me...
when you were the
one who got hurt?
Want some coffee?
Or how about chicken feet?
No.
Do you want me to take you home?
I don't think I can go home.
What if I change
like I did earlier...
and hurt my parents?
Then I might really go crazy.
Then should we go
somewhere instead?
Yes, let's go somewhere.
Let's go to a place where
it'll just be the two of us.
Don't worry too much
about your parents.
I told Shin Ju to
keep an eye on them.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
Wherever.
Do you remember
when we first met?
When you were a little kid?
No.
Of course, I remember.
All my life, my job was
to chase after people.
You were the first person
to chase after me instead.
I should've just
asked you out then.
Then we would've been able
to enjoy our time together...
for a lot longer.
Darn it!
Were you going somewhere?
Forgive me. I
must've been crazy.
I was blinded by the ground
cherries. I was out of my mind!
Look at me.
You were born as a servant
in a filthy thatched house.
And you've come a
long way since then.
It's... It's all thanks to you.
I saved you right before you were
about to get executed for treason.
Yes, how will I ever forget?
Then...
why did you help Lee Yeon?
I heard you told
him a lot of stuff.
Please... Please show me mercy
and give me another chance.
No, there's no need.
I no longer need...
anything or anyone.
There's been a change of plans.
Pardon?
I want you to become miserable.
And I mean, every single
person who's alive right now.
Go and turn yourself in.
You're better off
living as a criminal.
Should we play a game?
What game?
Like you said earlier, let's
pretend like we don't know anything.
How exactly?
You're just an average person
who's bored of your dull...
and ordinary life.
And as for me,
let's say I'm not
a nine-tailed fox.
Do we know each other?
We're...
married. We're a married couple.
We're just an average couple.
Let's say you went
to work as usual,
and I'm waiting for you to
come home as I cook dinner.
- What do you think?
- So I'm the breadwinner?
I own tons of buildings
and have a lot of cash.
I just want to be a house husband
who gets paid rent every month.
Don't laugh. Try being serious.
What do you want me to do?
Just a second.
Wait here for a moment.
Okay, now come home from work.
Go on. Come home from work.
Gosh, this feels stupid.
I'm home.
Honey.
"Honey, I'm home"?
Is my little puppy mad?
Why are you mad?
Look at the time.
You always say it's normal for
a woman to come home late...
because you're
out there working.
Did you or did you not promise
to be home by midnight?
Did you promise me or not?
- Do I have a curfew?
- Yes.
You broke curfew
twice last month too.
Are promises to me unimportant?
I did, didn't I? Can you
forgive me just this once?
This just won't do. Take a seat.
Sit. Let's talk.
Honey. You finally got
sober not long ago.
Me?
You're creating the
background story too.
Darling, you've changed.
Do you even love me?
I love you.
Me too.
Are we making up now?
Of course. Our
fights never last...
more than five minutes.
It's not fair.
Why can't we even have an
ordinary life like this?
It's so unfair.
It would've been so nice...
if you were human...
and we were really married...
If Imoogi never existed...
If we lived in a
world like that...
If I had met you like that...
I'll protect you.
No matter what happens...
when this fight ends,
you must stay alive.
That's good enough for me.
Regardless of how many
times I am reborn,
the world is filled
with darkness.
Yeon, I'll show you...
what the world I live in
looks like at the end.
TERRY
Hello?
A party will begin.
I don't plan to be
nice to you anymore.
Just wait.
I pity you.
You've never learned how
to give or receive love.
All you know how to do is
threaten people like this.
As you say, I am
threatening you.
Because your body will
be a ticking time bomb.
Look at yourself.
Soon, that will take full
control over your body.
When that time comes, you will
kill Yeon with your own hands.
Have you lost your mind?
Why are you going
through my computer?
What are you thinking? Why are
you messing with when she dies?
She's the real thing.
The real Imoogi.
What do you mean?
The real Imoogi is
within her body.
We must get rid of that in order to
get rid of the one running rampant.
You plan to sacrifice an
innocent child to catch Imoogi?
Knowing what she means to Yeon?
I do. I know better than anyone.
- So how could you?
- That's why I'm doing it.
Yeon can never let her die.
Imoogi knows that as well.
What do you think will happen...
if it takes over Yeon's body?
You'll kill a person because of
something that didn't happen yet?
What are you trying to
protect by doing that?
This is my job!
Because of that same reason,
our son lost his wife,
and we lost our son.
You added her name to the
list of the dead then too.
Thanks to that,
our son took his own life,
and we couldn't
save his soul yet.
Thanks to that, we
prevented a pandemic.
Bok Gil can't even
be reincarnated!
That was...
his fate.
You know, I thought you
had changed a little...
after losing your
child like that.
But I was wrong. You
haven't changed at all.
A much greater
calamity will come.
- If we don't stop it now...
- Fine.
You stop the calamity.
I'll stop you.
What are you trying to do?
The moment you change
the date that she dies,
it's over between us.
I write this as I
watch you sleep.
I've decided to return to Seoul.
The conclusion I made after
spending a night here is this.
No matter how far we run,
we can't escape.
I'm on the beach.
Let's walk together.
Let's walk to the end of the
beach and go back together.
I'm small and powerless.
The weight of my destiny
is too much to bear.
I feel like I'll sink to
the bottom of that ocean.
But Yeon, you push
me up like a buoy.
You make me float.
You make sure I don't sink.
I vowed to give her...
the gift of a boring...
and warm life...
that normal people live,
but down by the beach,
this is how she replied.
"Not alone."
She wishes to die together...
and live together.
However,
that seems to be a promise...
I can't make.
Save Mr. Lee.
I tried everything,
but to no avail.
Why should I?
Why must I help you?
Because I stabbed
him on your command.
This is your responsibility too.
What do you think I even am?
The owner of the
ground cherry tree.
You don't scare me.
And you mean that.
Still, shouldn't a deal
be beneficial to me too?
You don't seem to have
anything to offer,
and this half-breed
is useless to me now.
Take my life in
exchange for his.
Are you sure?
Just a second.
Mr. Lee, I'll no
longer be with you now,
but I wish you a long life.
Don't skip your meals
and put on some weight.
Stop chasing after
your brother too.
Just a little.
I hope you find a
little more happiness.
Kill me.
Don't stall. That's
even more annoying!
Open your eyes.
Consider your request granted.
However,
you're coming with me.
When the Imoogi in
her calls for you,
you will become my soldier.
Stay in places like
that for too long...
and the darkness will
swallow you whole.
How may I help you?
I'm here to turn myself in.
Sorry?
I killed her.
Killed whom?
The mummified victim you found.
Are you for real?
There are four more.
Search my car's GPS history,
and you'll find the burial
sites for all victims.
- Check it out.
- Sure.
What's your motive?
Why would the head of a
broadcasting station...
All I wanted was longevity.
If you had been in my shoes,
you would've made
the same choice.
Want me to go in with you?
No.
I want to properly draw a picture
of my parents' faces inside my head.
- If anything happens to me...
- That'll never happen.
Still, go ahead, if
that's how you feel.
Don't worry though.
It only surfaces when
it senses danger.
Or when it detects blood.
Come to think of it...
Long time no see, Yeon.
The scales are slowly
replacing my skin.
It might not be long before...
I lose myself completely.
Well, I'm off to
see the Snail Bride.
Bring my part-timers
over to my place later.
Sae Rom and Jae Hwan?
Yu Ri... Where's Yu Ri?
She left with that scary man.
She won't ever be back.
What did the fortune teller
say? Did you look into it?
I've been asking my contacts.
He didn't seem like
some lowly spirit.
Who is this geezer?
Well,
this seems to be a
groundless rumor,
but one of the
Afterlife judges...
is said to leave his
post once in a while.
That's interesting.
Anyway, let me know if you
find out anything about him.
- Here.
- What is this?
What is all this?
I was never able to buy you
anything with the money I earned.
It's been eating away at me.
When did you find the time...
out of your busy
schedule to buy this?
Gosh, it's pretty.
How nice.
Try it on.
I don't want to wear it out.
Our daughter bought this...
with the money she
worked hard to earn.
Wearing it out is
how we thank her.
Go ahead and try it on.
Should I?
This isn't the way home.
Give me five minutes.
Is it that good? Is it?
Yu Ri!
What brings you by at this hour?
That was unexpected.
It's my goodbye.
We're breaking up.
- What do you mean?
- Shin Ju, you were just dumped.
So don't wait for
me any longer...
and don't come looking for me.
Did I do something wrong?
No, I'm just tired of you.
- I get bored easily, you see.
- No.
That's not who you are.
Though it takes a while,
you offer up your heart
once the road to it opens.
Though you act cold, you
are the kindest of them all.
- As if you know me well.
- I do.
- How you treat Rang and the dog...
- Enough with Mr. Nice Guy.
I hate how you patronize me...
about needing
friends and family.
Your dowdy looks and
that constant smile?
I hate them all.
I won't patronize you.
I'll buy and wear whatever
you tell me to wear.
I won't smile if you
don't want me to.
Will you please stop?
I hate you, okay?
I don't like you!
You're lying.
I don't want you
clinging onto me either.
I'll be off now.
I can't break up with you.
- Let me go.
- No, I'll never let go.
I won't let go until you
take back what you just said.
Shin Ju.
You're making me get sick
of you by acting like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for whatever it is
that made you feel this way...
Don't follow me.
Will you please just
disappear from my life?
She told me I act too nice.
She doesn't like how I
look or the way I dress.
I think I kind of
understand what she means.
The ground cherry
thief is a real brat.
Why would she play with
your heart like this?
Don't speak ill of Yu Ri!
Please.
Stop crying.
She's my first and last love.
I was even going
to propose to her.
Yesterday, I went to Jongno
and bought her a gold ring.
But I can't believe...
There must be a reason why she
suddenly broke up with you.
I don't know why.
It's Imoogi. Imoogi took her.
Mr. Lee.
Rang.
What are you doing?
You're awake. You're back.
Stop acting so unusual. You're
making me want to die again.
- How did you wake up?
- What do you mean by that?
What do you mean
Imoogi took her?
He saved my life, and she
went with him in return.
Soo Ho saw them leave together.
No, we need to find her.
- Not like this.
- What if he kills her?
Let me go.
Are you dumb or what? Are
you trying to die with her?
I figured you wouldn't be able to
punch him, so I did it instead.
I promise you this.
I'll save your girlfriend
and bring her back.
I'll kill Imoogi.
Leave that to me.
He tried to kill me twice.
What about Soo Ho?
Is he home all by himself?
Yes, of course.
You can't leave
a kid home alone!
He won't leave the house even
if you try to drag him out.
You're all here.
Although, I can't say
I'm glad to see everyone.
Who are they?
They're my part-timers.
- What are you looking at?
- You also look like a sculpture,
so I can already tell.
You're not human, are you?
Don't talk to me
or I'll bite you.
No wonder.
So there are 3
humans and 2 foxes.
What are you, Dr. Koo?
There are 3 humans and 3 foxes.
Now that we're done introducing
ourselves, let's begin.
We're here to discuss our
plan, so why are you here?
Because I've dealt with
Imoogi a lot more than you.
And you also have
one inside your body.
Leave her out. What if he hears
everything from inside her body?
No, we need her for this.
Whoever disagrees
with that can leave.
We've all encountered
Imoogi at least once.
And we almost got killed
by him one way or another.
He's even holding
someone hostage.
On top of that, he lives
in two bodies, not one.
We need to catch them both in
order for this fight to end.
And what's even worse...
What's even worse is...
that the main spirit
lives inside my body.
Hey, Imoogi's friend.
Why don't you just kill yourself
and make this easy for all of us?
You should've just
stayed in bed.
Living as Sleeping Beauty
suits you a lot better.
We can't kill Imoogi by
hurting him physically.
He can even manipulate
people's thoughts,
and Ji A and I are the only ones
who are free from his powers.
It won't be easy,
but try your best...
not to face him one on one.
But how can we fight him
without encountering him?
You won't be able to do much
even if you do encounter him.
You'd probably
just call for help.
- I'm warning you.
- "I'm warning you."
What does Terry eventually
want by doing all this?
He told me he's going
to kill everyone.
And then...
Soon after, a virus will spread.
No one will ever be happy again.
"A virus"?
Will you stop playing games?
I'm listening. Just
get to the point.
Up until now, I was worried
Ji A might get hurt.
So I kept trying to fight
the Imoogi we all know.
But now,
we're going to
change our target.
How are you going to kill
what's inside her body?
You've found a way, right?
Yes, I have.
TRADITIONAL KOREAN
CUISINE: THE SNAIL BRIDE
Do you remember the fortune teller
we met at the Korean Folk Village?
Yes, of course.
Thanks to someone,
I lost my fox bead.
I heard he's actually pretty
powerful. Is that true?
He's one of the
afterlife judges.
- What?
- He even has...
the Sin Slayer.
No way.
What's a Sin Slayer?
It's a dagger that slays sins.
It slays sins?
I heard King Hades made it himself
a long time ago with the branch...
of the tree that
weighs our sins.
But didn't it disappear
thousands of years ago?
Snail Bride just picked it up.
But wouldn't that dagger
hurt Director Nam?
No, she won't get hurt.
The Sin Slayer is
a wooden dagger.
It slays things that
cannot be slain.
In other words, it'll
only slay Imoogi's spirit.
Thank goodness, Ji A.
When are we going to do this?
Tomorrow.
How does it feel
to be born again?
I don't know if it's because
I came back from the dead,
but this coffee tastes amazing.
You should live a long life.
If you die early, you won't be
able to drink coffee anymore.
It'd be no fun.
Were you scared I might die?
Yes, I was scared.
What's yours? Let me have a sip.
It's good.
Why are you so nice to me?
We've never really been to
a cafe like this together.
All I needed to do
was just reach out.
I don't get why I never
thought of doing that.
What's with you? You're acting
like you're about to die soon.
It's really delicious.
It is, isn't it? Let me
try a sip of yours too.
- No, you can't have mine.
- You ungrateful punk.
Hey, don't drink mine.
What happened?
Nothing.
Was it her?
It wasn't like that.
You're defending her,
so I guess I'm right.
Will that sin-slaying dagger
really work on Imoogi?
It has been over 600 years.
I plan to end this
fight once and for all.
What if you fail?
What happens to me then?
Rang.
That's why I need you.
I worked so hard all my life.
I was so close to becoming the
most powerful man in the nation.
Darn it.
But I'm stuck in this tiny cell.
At least I'm alive.
I'm alive.
TWO MEALS
This too.
How could you want
tteokbokki right now?
Even if the world ends
tomorrow, I'd want tteokbokki.
Give me that. Fill that up.
- You want a cheese ball, right?
- Yes.
- One cheeseball, please.
- Okay.
This is so good.
- This is really good.
- This?
How does this taste good even
in the midst of everything?
Right?
Don't come to me
for the time being.
Your lives may be in
danger if you're with me.
That's up to me.
You guys almost died.
Do you remember...
when my mom came to Seoul
to get back surgery?
She cried because she couldn't go
to the hospital because of her show.
You went to the
hospital in my place.
You were there for my mom.
If she were all alone that day,
I would've blamed myself
forever after she died.
- Let us help too.
- She's right.
We're ordinary humans,
so we're powerless,
but I want to do anything I
can if it will save your life.
Right now, going back to work...
is how you can help me.
Mr. Choi will throw a hissy
fit if all three of us are out.
He isn't in.
What?
He turned himself in?
Imoogi wouldn't just
let him live like that.
Find out what's happening
at the police station.
Okay.
The person you have reached...
Mr. Choi isn't
answering his phone.
- Call an ambulance!
- Okay.
This is Geumran Police Station.
- We need...
- Let... Let me. I'll help.
- Please hold his head up.
- Okay.
Snail Bride, we have
to pull up our plan.
TRADITIONAL KOREAN
CUISINE: THE SNAIL BRIDE
He's making his move.
We don't have much time.
We'll catch the Imoogi
in Ji A's body today.
Everything must go
exactly as planned.
We get it, so say it.
It's simple.
Ji A will draw her blood...
and lure Imoogi out.
Once he comes out, I'll stab
him with the Sin Slayer.
Shin Ju. Once Ji A and I go in,
lock the door from the outside.
No one can come near us
until I give the signal.
Why not?
By chance if he
escapes from Ji A,
you guys will be in danger.
He may enter one of your bodies.
That's why I made a
border with horse blood.
He's different from the
Imoogi we've known until now.
We don't know what he looks
like or how and where he'd move.
We don't know
anything right now.
We cannot make a single mistake.
What if he goes into you?
That won't happen as
long as I'm conscious.
Shin Ju.
It's a snake. I got one that
is a perfect fit for him.
So, the best is if you
can slay it in one go.
Even if he gets away,
that snake is the only
body he can go into.
Let's go. I want to get rid
of it as soon as possible.
Here's the dagger.
Thank you. You should go.
Please be careful.
Okay, then.
Shall we begin?
But first,
tie me to the chair with this.
What if I hurt you again?
That's unncessary.
Do as I say. Okay?
Why do you keep
trying to protect me?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Don't say that. You'll jinx it.
Okay, then. I'll tie you up.
Okay. Yeon.
Will you give me a hug?
Don't hesitate
because of me, okay?
There's nothing to
be nervous about.
It's only a blunt wooden dagger.
I'm prepared for any
unwanted injuries.
As if I'd let you get hurt.
Besides, this dagger can
only slay the unslayable,
like Imoogi's soul.
Does that mean, it
can also slay...
your soul too?
Don't hesitate
because of me, okay?
There's nothing to
be nervous about.
It's only a blunt wooden dagger.
I'm prepared for any
unwanted injuries.
As if I'd let you get hurt.
Besides, this dagger can
only slay the unslayable,
like Imoogi's soul.
Does that mean, it
can also slay...
your soul too?
Of course, it can.
- But...
- Yes?
I've been meaning to ask.
Who are you?
What's dying...
is your soul.
- You can't.
- Move.
I'll kill her if
anything happens to Yeon.
Do so, but only
over my dead body.
You think that can stop me?
How pathetic.
Who knew you'd actually come in
possession of the Sin Slayer?
Hey. Are you pretending
to be asleep?
Wait.
Did that really kill his soul?
This was inevitable anyway.
So how about it? An
old home for a new one.
Don't you know how pricey
houses are these days?
You little thief.
- What on earth?
- Isn't it obvious?
This is what I
needed to confirm.
So this is how you
jump from body to body.
The fortune teller has been
untraceable since the folk village.
Even the Gatekeeper of Samdo River
hasn't been able to spot him.
Darn it.
What now?
Go out and find me a
random wooden dagger.
A wooden dagger?
What use do you have
for a blunt dagger?
To slay the unslayable.
How about we change
the game a bit?
Stop the car.
So this dagger was never...
It cost 10 dollars
at a flea market.
The fortune teller
only pops up...
wherever it wants to
whenever it wants to.
Darn rat.
Right back at you.
What was with the
silly Ji A act?
Did you know it was me?
I could smell the
metallic scent of blood.
As you know, I have a
heightened sense of smell.
Anyway, I thank you
for the donation.
Knowing my secret...
doesn't automatically
give you the upper hand.
Even if you bury it elsewhere,
I'll still find a way back to her.
I will keep doing so until
you hand over your body.
So what you're saying is that I
can plant your soul elsewhere...
by burying this.
For instance... How
about that rat snake?
I dare you to try.
Don't tell me...
you're expecting me...
to be gently dragged
out of this body.
Right. If I'm being honest,
I like this piece of Imoogi
better than the other one.
A villain should at
least be this crazy.
Romance, my foot.
This woman is and will
always be my hostage.
The other piece of Imoogi is
more interested in Ji A...
than being united with you.
He is nothing but a
bunch of fragments.
Not according to him though.
You think you can pit
us against each other?
Dream on.
Do you even know what
he's up to right now?
You see, he's...
Irritating imbeciles.
NAME: NAM JI A, DATE
OF BIRTH: MARCH 3, 1991
DATE OF DEATH:
DATE OF DEATH: TODAY
Innocent lives are
being sacrificed.
It won't be long before
chaos sweeps the world.
No, you're wrong.
All along, you're the one
who's been chaos itself.
- Honey.
- Don't call me that.
For I...
just decided to
give up that title.
Don't be ridiculous.
On whose authority?
Stop right there.
You heard me!
The moment you step
past those doors,
you'll lose everything.
I'll make sure of it!
Are you okay?
Yeon.
Yes, it's me.
Let's hurry.
At least so I can be myself...
right before it all ends.
I want to be there beside you.
Let's end this.
Let's put an end...
to this exhausting fight.
THE LIST
NAME: NAM JI A, DATE
OF BIRTH: MARCH 3, 1991
DATE OF DEATH: TODAY
NAME: NAM JI A
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Just give me three more days.
I can catch him! I
can catch Imoogi!
It's too late.
You'll regret this.
If it weren't for me,
Yeon would still be...
living as a mountain spirit.
Yeon will never
forgive me for this.
Don't make me regret
liking you, Yu Ri.
I have the power to destroy
everything you care for.
Let's join hands and kill the
gatekeeper of Samdo River.
And what's the condition?
Give me Ji A.