Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Hi.
What exited the well...
went into hiding immediately.
A piece of it was
found recently though.
A piece of it?
It can't be.
On her body.
She has lost the fox
bead you gave her.
In consequence, something
within her awoke.
What?
Why there...
of all places...
when it took her 600 years...
to finally be reborn?
All she wants...
is to live her life out...
as normally as possible
with her family.
So why...
Why is it within her?
That's her destiny.
Her destiny?
Says who?
What did she do to deserve this?
Do you dare to question
the higher powers...
at a place of the Almighty?
You already knew, didn't you?
It's why you constantly
told me to forget about her.
Right now,
I feel like I've
been betrayed...
by a bank I trusted
my money with.
So?
I'll need a compensation.
I took you in and helped you
when you had absolutely nothing.
How dare you have the guts to
think that I owe you something?
Enough!
Relax, Yeon.
You too, honey.
Listen to me carefully.
If I find out that Ji A
will end up dying early,
I'll make a mess of the
Living Realm and Afterlife.
I don't even want to
look at you. Leave.
Did you see it?
I'm curious to
know how you feel.
I feel like I might cry.
I had to wait such
a long time...
to finally meet that person.
You have a lot on your mind.
- Pardon?
- You think I'm peculiar.
Am I no longer the
Imoogi you once knew?
If I've changed, that's
because the world has changed.
Imoogis and nine-tailed foxes
exist in a rapidly changing world.
There's no need to see the
world in an old-fashioned way.
Now, they will start
looking for us.
That's what I've
been waiting for.
I really can't wait
to meet that person.
She was pretty harsh, but
I'm sure she didn't mean it.
She's very cold-hearted,
but she cared for you...
like her own son.
Don't console me.
I'm already pretty
close to crying.
Yeon, don't get
swept up in this.
Just act like you
don't know anything.
Don't jump into fire when
you know it's dangerous.
But she'll be hurt
if I don't go.
You don't want...
to see the tragedy on replay.
If you get involved,
either one of you...
must die in the end.
That's become fate for
both you and her...
the moment that
thing was born again.
No, Ji A won't die. Never.
I made a promise.
I promised to help her live
a proper life this time.
I'll protect her even
if it ends my life.
CHAPTER 7: THE TRAP OF SAMSARA
There are more moments when a child
needs her parents than I thought.
For example, when the
child takes her first step.
Who else would be that
moved that you got up...
and took just a few
steps by yourself?
When I was the only one at a
picnic without a homemade lunch.
When the kid I fought
with in class said,
"I'm going to tell
my mom on you."
I couldn't beat kids with moms.
If only they were mean though.
If they were, I
might've been able...
to forget about them and
move on with my life.
Why have you been searching
for your parents all this time?
It's simple.
I miss them, that's all.
The fox bead?
I didn't know it
was that important.
You gave it to that
fortune-teller, didn't you?
He suddenly started talking
to me about my fate...
and promised to let you
go if I gave him that.
But still, how could you...
give it to him so easily
like a piece of candy?
Because I couldn't
afford to lose you.
I'm going to stay
here for a while.
You're going to stay?
At my house?
- You're going to live here?
- Yes.
I've never seen a nine-tailed
fox with such an open-mind.
Then do you want to
come to my place?
That's not what I meant.
Why all of a sudden?
It's the least I can
do for your safety.
Don't make me risk
my life to save you.
I was going to ask if you're
okay sleeping on the sofa.
You're using your
life to negotiate,
so it's hard to refuse.
Why are you up? I left
after I saw you fall asleep.
I had a bad dream.
- You had a dream?
- I saw a little boy.
And he said "Hi" to me.
- And then?
- That's it.
At first, it totally
creeped me out.
But after I woke up,
I felt pleasant to have
met him for some reason.
It felt like I knew
him or something.
Yes, he's the most precious
thing in your life.
Your brother.
I'll have a cola.
Why cola?
Last time, I got drunk and ate
the pigeons in my neighborhood.
I've been trying not
to drink after that.
I had enteritis.
Were you the one who
left a dead pigeon...
in front of my front door?
I went all the way there?
I don't remember.
What are you? A stray cat?
Did you fail to find what
you were looking for?
These glasses are the
eyebrows of a tiger?
So if I wear this, I can
see people's past lives?
Why do you look so sad?
- I'm not sad. I'm angry.
- Why?
I'm angry that I still have
the emotions of a human being.
Maybe it's because
I'm a half-blood.
Yes, you told me your
mother was human.
Did she hold you and
carry you on her back?
Did she catch chickens for you
and feed you all the nice parts?
You're making the
alcohol taste bad.
I just want to know how
it feels to be loved.
"Love"?
Mom.
Wait here for a moment.
No, I'm scared.
I'll be right back after
I gather hazelnuts.
Let me go with you. I
want to go with you.
Why do you give me
such a hard time?
I haven't given up on my
life just because of you.
Do you want the both
of us to just die?
Mom?
Love...
can get you killed.
The one who loves the other
person more becomes the prey.
I don't want that. I'd
rather be the predator.
Is it Shin Ju?
What has he done to sway you?
I'm surprised to hear
you talk about love.
I won't get swayed.
No matter what happens,
your enemies will
always be my enemies.
You should go.
I want to be alone.
KI, KOO, YU, SHIN, RI, JU
We got a 99.
Mr. Lee and Ms.
Nam only got a 25.
See that?
According to the scientific
law of probabilities,
there is definitely
something there. Yes.
Even if she is from another country
that doesn't know Confucianism,
she kissed me on the cheek
when we first met, and...
What are you saying?
Why should I get neutered?
What, do you mean, I'm in
heat? Watch your mouth.
Anyway, your mom...
pretended she didn't like it, but
she finished the chicken soup.
She speaks meanly, but
she isn't a bad person.
You know that, right?
What? You want chicken soup?
You had your dog food
just half an hour ago.
You don't remember?
You're driving me crazy.
Hey!
How long will you stand there?
- All night long.
- All night?
Don't mind me.
You're standing right
there, staring at me.
How could I not mind you?
Should I watch
from outside then?
That's out of a horror film.
You don't like this, you don't like
that. How can I protect you then?
Sleep on the couch.
No. It's outside of
the monitoring radius.
- Then sleep here.
- Okay.
I meant in the
room, not in my bed.
As I told you before, I'm modern.
I need a bed in order to sleep.
You can sleep on the
floor if you're afraid.
I'm not afraid.
Aren't you going to sleep?
I can't fall asleep.
My dad taught me
this a long time ago.
If you can't fall asleep,
imagine something that makes you
happy just thinking about it.
Like mint chocolate
chip ice cream?
For me, it's the smell
of freshly cooked rice.
The sound of a pencil
being sharpened.
New sneakers.
Pro baseball season.
A complete set of
world literature.
A puppy's toe beans.
Dad's handmade gimbap.
Something no one writes anymore.
A letter.
Your turn.
Are you asleep?
What? For me...
Red umbrella.
No!
What was that about?
Why are you smiling?
Wasn't I cool just now?
I moved quickly like
Spiderman, and...
The type I hate the most.
And his nose is running.
Mister. Do you like Spiderman?
- No.
- Why not?
- I just don't.
- I like him.
I don't care at all.
Stop talking to me.
I'm in a bad mood already
without your help.
I woke up at 4:30...
It's almost done. Almost done.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
- Dried pollack soup?
- That's right.
Did you burn this?
You are impressive.
It's not burned. It's...
What do you call it?
I'm making dried
pollack soup, but...
Go buy more pollack.
I used it all up.
All of it?
I added sugar by mistake.
I'll do it. Step aside.
Hi.
Hey. Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Let's have breakfast.
Dried pollack soup is
the best for hangovers.
Did you make all of
this by yourself?
That isn't important.
- It's the thought that counts.
- That's awesome.
- Good morning, Ms. Nam!
- Oh, my gosh.
Why are you coming from there?
I heard you moved in together.
I had to bring Mr. Lee
fresh clothes anyway, so...
Where's the bleach?
Bleach? Why?
The hard water stains on
the sink are terrible.
I scrubbed the tiles with
baking soda and vinegar.
I have to clear the drain
of all the hair too. Also!
Don't let delivery food pile up
in the fridge. They're all germs.
- She's like a mother-in-law.
- Gosh.
I don't want to meddle
with someone else's home,
but Mr. Lee has never done
a chore in his entire life.
And he has OCD to boot.
- What was that, you punk?
- Enjoy your breakfast.
Where's the bleach?
It's in the bathroom.
Under the sink.
He should just keep looking.
Why did he come out and...
Hold on.
- Did you burn this?
- Well, not "burn" per se.
It's more like I failed at
controlling the temperature.
Why are you cute in the
midst of all of this?
The dried pollack is
dominating my body.
Cute? I'm over 1,000 years old.
- Let's eat.
- Yes, let's eat.
It's soft-boiled.
Eat up.
Yes?
Ma'am.
Come in.
Here.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
So... Ms. Nam.
I know it's not my place
to say this, but...
Please be safe.
If you get hurt, Mr. Lee...
He'll be hurt 2, 3...
No, 10 times worse.
Yeon's so lucky.
He has a friend who
worries so much about him.
He's very precious to me.
I promise.
I'll do my best to be safe.
Yeon has become...
precious to me as well.
Let's go.
- We'll be late.
- Okay.
Coming!
Where are you off to today?
Me? To work.
This place of work you implied.
Is it perhaps my place of work?
Yes, of course.
You need a pass to enter
a broadcasting station.
I'm a nine-tailed fox.
Who could get in my way?
I'll take care of it.
What's with the suit though?
It's so that I can
blend in at the office.
- Don't you like it?
- That's not why I mentioned it.
Only the executives
wear neckties, you see.
Really?
Can you at least discard that?
No, I'll pretend to be
an executive instead.
- Good morning, sir.
- Keep up the good work, everyone.
What on earth? Did you
just hypnotize them?
Yes.
Why take on a role
as a director though?
In TV shows,
that's the position held by
those handsome and wealthy.
So? What will you do
next as a director?
I'll wait for you right here.
Here? All day?
When it comes to waiting,
no one can do it better.
24 hours? I could sit
there even for 24 years.
- Here.
- Right.
Have a good day.
Call me if anything happens.
Got it.
Thanks, Yeon, for
being here for me.
If you get involved,
either one of you...
must die in the end.
That's become fate for
both you and her...
the moment that
thing was born again.
This could very well be
the last life I live.
I guess it could be worse.
Darn, I forgot to
remove the nails.
Hello, I'm the babysitter
who starts today.
All I ask you is
to feed him well.
Today is the day.
Today, the Imoogi
will be fully grown...
with a new face and body.
A man in a navy blue
suit came to see me.
He told me about the accident
that would occur on that day...
at Yeou Gogae.
Albeit faint,
signs of human branding was
present on his forehead.
"Seo" as in west and
"Gyeong" as in Seoul.
Branding the face
of a criminal...
was the most brutal punishment
that involved bodily harm.
A branded criminal was
hated and looked down on...
and couldn't live
among others anymore.
And "Seogyeong" is the
old word for Pyongyang.
SEOGYEONG
Why Seogyeong though?
SEOGYEONG, HUMAN BRANDING
"Those who lead the
Revolt of Myocheong,"
"the uprising
which aimed for..."
"the transfer of the
capital to Seogyeong,"
"were sent into exile
after being branded."
"Revolt of Myocheong."
"Those who destroyed..."
"the order of the land
with their prophecies..."
"had these words branded
on their foreheads."
"Seogyeong or
Seogyeong Traitor."
Darn it. You committed treason.
Because the parents weren't
the targets of the accident.
The daughter was
the initial target.
Where are you?
Right on his tail.
It seems he has
someplace urgent to be.
- On his own?
- Yes, he's alone.
Keep an eye on
what Rang is up to.
I'm to look for a man...
with his crime branded
on his forehead.
He's in league with Imoogi.
That's right. I'm sure that
Rang is connected to it too.
Darn it!
Did he drop his
wallet or something?
Find the glasses.
Do whatever you need
to do to find them.
Glasses?
Who is he on the phone with?
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- She's here.
- Begin the interrogation.
Time out. Jae Hwan, let
me see your forehead.
What? Why?
It's nothing.
Who's that guy?
- Who is he?
- Your boyfriend?
- I bet he's a source.
- How much did you each bet?
- 50 dollars.
- Now tell us what he is to you.
What could he be to me?
I'm just as curious too.
- What do you mean?
- Whenever that's the case,
feel that person's pulse.
- What?
- The body's reaction never lies.
Why is his heart
beating so fast?
Maybe his body's reaction
isn't always honest.
Have you two held hands?
Not the hands but...
You didn't hold hands, but
you did something else?
What part of him
did you grab then?
Do we have a story
for the next show?
My gosh, it's as if I came across
a rare item in a video game.
What? What is it?
I just want a good
look at your forehead.
I know who took your glasses.
- Who is it?
- Some kid.
A kid?
I guess you were
pretty drunk yesterday.
I don't have a family.
But there's someone who
rescued me from the zoo though.
So he's your savior.
Of course. He ripped the
zookeeper into pieces.
He's someone you'll be
meeting pretty soon.
I'll be off now.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Make sure you're all
free for dinner tonight.
The president
invited us to dinner.
What is he going to buy for us?
We got invited to his house.
His house? That's going
to be so uncomfortable.
Why would you think
of it that way?
He normally only invites
his close acquaintances.
But this time, he invited us.
You know what this means, right?
You know, right?
Anyway... Forget it. Let's
just all eat chicken soup.
What's all this?
What... I think
there's been a mistake.
We were just about to
order chicken soup.
Eat up. It's on the house.
- On the house?
Why are you suddenly
giving us free food?
I was told that a very
special guest is here.
I did bring 80 percent
of all the employees...
at our broadcasting company
if you think about it.
I may be a VIP customer,
but this is way too much.
You could go broke, you know.
Do you lack magnesium?
Why do you keep
twitching your eye?
Enjoy.
Every ingredient that's used
to cook traditional food...
has a special story behind them.
Yes, just like the chef here.
Doesn't she speak so eloquently?
Let's eat.
You're able to receive this
kind of special treatment...
because I'm your boss.
You little minions.
What do you keep staring at?
What?
It's nothing.
That guy...
It's him, isn't he?
Yes, it's him. You sneaky brat.
Come here and join us.
Me?
Seoul is a small city, isn't it?
We all met here by coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
Then why were you here?
Because of Ms. Nam.
What's going on
between you guys?
Jae Hwan.
I have feelings for her
although she doesn't.
A one-sided love?
What a waste of
that handsome face.
He has feelings for
me, and so do I.
Why did you follow me?
Why did Yeon have you follow me?
Listen.
Do you still think I'm a little
kid who used to follow Yeon around?
I know you're not.
I also know that
you can kill me...
without leaving a single trace.
Then tell me why
you followed me.
You...
should know that
better than anyone.
Do you think we're
playing 20 questions?
All my life, I've
lived for Yeon.
And I was able to
live thanks to him.
That means I can't
do anything...
to cause him any harm even if
that could cost me my life.
Are you being loyal
or sympathetic?
Or are you just dumb?
It's the same reason...
why you're so obsessed about
hurting your older brother.
It's because we both like him.
I'm sorry if this is out of
line, but what do you do?
- What's your job?
- I don't have a job.
I knew it.
You have lots of time
but no job experience.
That's explains why
you've fallen for Ji A.
Can I break his ribs?
No, you can't. Hold your anger.
But seriously, do you
really not have a job?
- He gets paid rent.
- You own a building?
He owns 30 million dollars'
worth of real estate.
I do?
By any chance, do you
have any brothers?
- I do have a little brother.
- Then we can be in-laws.
How old are you?
I'm not that young.
- I'm a thousand...
- He's older than he looks.
- Have you done it once?
- Done what once?
He's asking if you're also
divorced just like him.
Is he the guy who got divorced
in less than a year...
Yes.
I guess you know him.
He's never been married before.
He's like a guy you'd
see in a fantasy drama.
What's up with him?
That's his ritual.
He always does that.
Is it good?
Look. This is nice.
- Just eat it.
- By the way...
I need to go somewhere.
Hey, kid. Are you okay?
You're pretty.
You think I'm pretty?
Kids these days
have bad eyesight...
because they're always
on their smartphones.
- A eunuch.
- What?
What's a eunuch?
- It's really sad to explain...
- I'm not a eunuch.
- Do you want me to prove it?
- What are you doing with a kid?
He called me a eunuch.
Kids don't know how to lie.
Hey, kid. Are you okay?
I'm scared.
- What?
- Your face...
It's so scary.
Does that mean I have a
really bad first impression?
Yes. I heard kids
don't know how to lie.
Hey, you're here.
- Where is Shin Ju?
- He's still alive.
Don't take it out on him.
If you have something to say,
just talk to me directly.
You must care for him a lot.
I care for him a lot more
than my little brother...
who's still going through puberty
ever since the Joseon Dynasty.
Why did you put a tail on me?
I guess we're both not the
type to beat around the bush.
Why did it have to be an Imoogi?
You finally found out?
There are many other
ways to harm me.
So why did it have to be that?
I figured it'd be interesting
to reenact your past.
As you know, I'm an aesthete.
Does he have something on you?
I guess he does.
We both give and take, so
I'd call it a contract.
Listen to me carefully.
Sometimes, there are people you
should never make deals with.
I need to make a living.
It's not too late to stop.
If you don't stop now,
it'll come at a price.
Let me ask you something.
What if I was the one in danger?
What if my life was at stake?
Would you have
come to rescue me?
Save yourself.
You seem to be enjoying
yourself with your first love.
But if she knew everything...
that happened in her past life,
would she still stay with you?
If you touch her,
I'll really kill you this time.
Mr. Lee. I've located the kid.
Fine,
I'll let you kill me.
Give me Shin Ju.
You owe me for his life.
Mr. Lee.
Give me the glasses.
No. They're my magic glasses.
I won't go easy on you
just because you're a kid.
Stop it. I hate
hearing people cry.
If it were in the past,
I would've killed you.
I'm only going easy on you
because of the low birth rate.
No.
It can't be.
Geomdoong?
Yay! I'm so excited!
Faster!
Geomdoong...
I won't give my heart to
something like that again.
Never again...
Why did you follow me?
Are you Spiderman?
You moved all quickly
and stuff like Spiderman.
You're annoying to look at.
Then why did you buy me
yummy chocolate pastries?
I'm just paying a debt.
I'm saying, "Eat
this, and get lost."
A pet?
To brush their hair?
He looks dumb too.
Why did he have to be born as
a human being of all things?
Let's enter the castle.
Ms. Nam. Come quickly.
Hurry.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
There's a second floor too.
I wonder what something
like this costs.
Why? So you can buy one?
It's not bad, but it's too
far from the train station.
Whatever.
I've never seen ground
cherries in Seoul before.
Are these ground cherries?
They look like lanterns.
I used to scoop out the inside
and blow on it like a recorder.
- Does this make sounds too?
- Of course.
My mom said it was bad luck,
that it would bring out a snake.
My gosh.
Don't touch that.
- It holds a special meaning for me.
- I see. I'm sorry.
I have only two
rules in this house.
One. Don't touch
the ground cherries.
- You can't blow on it either.
- It'll bring out a snake.
Second. You cannot go
up to the second floor.
Is someone there?
No, I live alone.
And the caterer.
Anyway, he says not to
go up there, so don't.
You must be hungry.
- Mr. Lee.
- Yes?
Water.
What?
- Water.
Here.
- The cap.
You want me to feed you?
I'm injured.
Okay, fine.
- Where's Ms. Nam?
- She has dinner plans.
You don't need to go?
She went with colleagues.
She said she'll see me later.
Where's the chicken?
That's right. Chicken.
It's on its way.
- One whole chicken.
- Garlic drumsticks.
- Did you order original?
- Yes.
Seriously...
I'll let it slide since
that tastes good too.
Feed the dog before
the chicken comes.
Okay.
Anyway...
Are you really in pain?
Are you overreacting so that
you can order me around?
I'm hurt physically...
and emotionally.
See? What did I tell you?
I said that necklace
thief was suspicious.
Stop calling her a thief.
She has a nice name. Yu Ri.
Whatever her name is, she used
you because Rang put her up to it.
We had a bad start,
that's all. We're a 99.
What? What's 99?
Look.
It's a marital compatibility
test using names.
KI, KOO, YU, SHIN, RI, JU
NAM, LEE, JI, YEON, A
"Nam Ji A and Lee
Yeon." What? 25?
My back. My head.
My legs. My heart.
I'm going to redo
this. You did it wrong.
Okay, let's make a toast.
"Unveiling Urban Legends".
I hope you'll continue
to dominate in ratings...
and stay on air
for years to come.
We can do it.
- We can do it.
- Tell me...
- When we went for the shoot,
I packed a cross, a rosary, a
talisman, everything there is.
And a case of medicine
to calm his nerves.
I'm sure he was prepared.
Although he was prepared,
the camera was
rattling in his hands.
Ji A almost murdered him.
That's when I realized...
that people can be
scarier than ghosts.
Ji A has guts.
I recognized it during her interview
and made sure she stayed with us.
I remember. You said,
"You have to join
us no matter what."
I remember something too.
When we went to the workshop,
we were in the retreat
center, and the mic broke.
- So...
- Did you go to a workshop with me?
Yes, sir.
Anyway, do you believe in
ghosts and the supernatural?
A long time ago, I almost died.
It was a miracle
that I survived.
What I met that
day wasn't human.
Then what was it?
I said it was a miracle.
Gosh.
- Where's the bathroom?
- Go straight down the hall.
I'll be right back.
Sir. So...
You went with me to
the awards ceremony...
Is there someone upstairs?
Maybe I heard wrong.
I shouldn't be snooping
around someone else's home.
An artificial nail?
I must've been born
to drink champagne.
- Gosh.
- Stop him.
- Sir, I think you had enough.
- How dare you.
Champagne doesn't even
qualify as alcohol.
Shouldn't Ji A be back by now?
- Why don't I look for her?
- No, the guest should stay seated.
We'll be here waiting, sir.
Welcome.
- Hey.
- What time will the dinner be over?
In about 30 minutes, I think.
- Are you still at the vet?
- Yes.
Tell me the address
and I'll pick you up.
It's fine. The others and
I will take a cab together.
All right. I'll see
you at home then.
See you in a bit.
Sir...
I told you that the second
floor was off limits.
Sorry about that.
Is there someone
in the room though?
I hear sounds coming from it.
It must be the wind. The
window was left open.
Let's grab some dessert then.
Sure.
Why are you crying?
Because it's been so long
since you've looked this happy.
Right.
Well, enjoy it while it lasts...
and have this be the
look you remember me by.
You're talking like
someone who's leaving.
As if that would happen.
Please live a long life...
and enjoy the happiest of
times while Ms. Nam lives hers.
Ji A, I'm glad you're
here. Are ghosts evil?
Is that why you hunt after them?
If that's the case,
they should be arrested.
Sir, let me tell you this.
I believe we are a community.
It doesn't matter if they
are supernatural beings.
When we actually encounter them,
we should thank them...
for helping us earn a
living and beg for them...
to keep the antics up.
You found this at his house?
- Yes.
- It gives me the creeps.
It's a glue-on artificial nail
with cheap embellishments.
Who could it belong to?
It's neither yours or mine...
and none of the catering
staff had fake nails either.
Also, his wife passed
away over a decade ago.
Why don't you ask if
he's dating anyone?
Directly?
How can you get by in life
with a mindset like that?
It'll make more sense to
think that he has a hobby.
Doing nail art?
As if that would make sense.
Your rice is ready.
You're home.
Did you make dinner?
I already ate.
I know that, but you said
you like freshly cooked rice.
I may not be a good cook,
but I can make the
best steamed rice.
So this is how it feels
to come home after work...
to the smell of
freshly cooked rice.
I'll make sure you do
every day I'm here.
Here.
What's this?
I picked it up on the street.
- Mint chocolate flavor?
- I'll go and change.
For a second, I thought
she was handing me trash.
What do you normally
do at night?
Watching American
TV shows, was it?
I also read and watch the news.
I usually watch movies.
Should we watch one?
Shall we?
- What's this?
- What...
Hey. Did you see that just now?
I can't believe it.
What I read online was true.
Let me see.
- My gosh.
- Is it on?
Try this.
What's wrong? Are you
not enjoying the movie?
I'm enjoying it.
I'm enjoying it so much
that I wish time would stop.
Me too.
For me, it's the smell
of freshly cooked rice.
New sneakers.
Put them on, and look at
yourself in the mirror.
It'll give you the
answer to your question.
New sneakers.
What kind of shoes
do women like?
Excuse me, can you...
My gosh.
My goodness.
- What do you want?
- I sent a gift to your lady.
Have you heard of the
eyebrows of a tiger?
LEE YEON
PUT THEM ON, AND LOOK AT
YOURSELF IN THE MIRROR.
IT'LL GIVE YOU THE
ANSWER TO YOUR QUESTION.
Gosh, how lame.
My gosh.
She means nothing to me.
Don't you get it? I used
her as bait to get to you.
Yeon.
Did you see it?
Tell me. Did you see it?
Please look at me.
What...
did you see?
I was...
murdered in my past life.
You...
killed me.
Your sole purpose...
was to find the Imoogi.
Yeon.
You used me...
to offer as sacrifice.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
If I ever get to be born again,
I want to live as a human being.
I'm not going to be
easy on you anymore.
Where is the Imoogi?
You were born to be
offered to me as sacrifice.
She's going to be my wife.
What do you fear the most?
Yeou Gogae.
I'm willing to do anything now.
Mom!
Please hang in there
just a bit longer.