Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
I told you to sit
tight, didn't I?
And so we meet again. How
long has it been exactly?
I didn't have to torture the
traitor to get my answers.
I wanted him to tell you
where and when to meet me.
I see the blade won't kill you.
Back then, I wore
the skin of a mortal.
Not this time though.
You have some cute tricks.
I wanted a chance to
measure our powers.
Sounds good to me.
Not bad.
You know nothing
about me, Lee Yeon.
I've lived far longer
than you think I have.
I existed long
before you were born.
The past is just a past.
And I'll outlive you.
Don't dream of an
unrealistic future.
In order to become a deity...
and finally be free of
this world's darkness,
you endured 1,000 years
beneath the black water.
This world would've been mine...
had I not been spotted by a human
while ascending as a dragon.
I feel bad for you. It's like...
getting kicked out of an exam...
because you got caught
with your phone.
How sad.
But that's how your fate
has been designed, Imoogi.
You really should
get a proper name.
You haven't changed at all.
You're still very arrogant.
You must think you have
the world at your feet.
I don't know about anything else,
but I do think that way about you.
You make me want
to trample on you.
Your brother, your woman,
and the life of her parents.
I have control over them all.
What do you have?
Let me make a reasonable offer.
Lee Yeon, if you give up your body,
I will let everyone else live.
What do I look like to you?
Seogyeong Traitor.
You're the one who
took my parents!
This is the carnation
I folded for them.
Flip it over.
JI A, WHY WON'T YOU SAVE US?
Ji A, why won't you save us?
Are they alive?
- Where?
- Bring me the mountain spirit,
and I'll return
your parents to you.
- Tell me where they are!
- You saw them,
but failed to recognize them.
What do you mean by that?
You'll soon find out.
I won't let you
get away with this.
Call the cops then or
perhaps your boyfriend.
Any option will do,
but you won't ever see
your parents again.
Why? Why my parents?
Because I knew this
day would come.
You would do anything
to save your parents.
Just like how you saved your
father in your past life,
I hope that you'll once
again make a wise choice.
You'll let everyone go
if I give up my body?
Ji A, her parents,
and even Rang?
I'd like the entire package,
but just the heart will also do.
Are you serious?
I am.
So what will it be? Yes or no?
I...
I don't want to.
- Why not?
- Because you seem like the type...
to go back on a deal.
I don't do business
with those kinds.
I'll personally free
them all from your grip.
Then enjoy...
trampling on those you treasure.
I know this isn't
appropriate to ask,
but why did you come back?
As if anyone would welcome...
the symbol of calamity,
plague, and war.
If you're asking me my view of
the world, I don't have one.
All I want is one thing.
I want that woman.
The woman who was supposed to be
offered to me as a sacrifice...
but ended up saving
you and killing me.
I like her.
How dare you?
That's enough. I just
wanted to test your power.
For me, this is
just the beginning.
"I want to die. Now."
Do you feel it?
I knew it. You're
connected to him.
- What?
- You are his shell.
Why are you doing this?
You're also human.
I'm human, so I don't want to
die, and I have so many desires.
Was committing treason
not enough for you?
All I did was dream
of a new world...
after having been
born as a lowlife.
My kids, wife, and mother.
All I wanted to do was make
sure they could eat proper food.
But they called it treason
and threatened to behead me.
And that's when I met him.
I'm sure it wasn't for free.
What did you have to give in return
for being able to stay alive?
My kids, wife, and mother.
I offered my family to Imoogi
and was able live in return.
You're crazy.
You must lose something in
order to gain something.
So you want me to sell Yeon out?
You want me to become
someone like you?
The choice is yours, Ji A.
Because of you, your parents
were gone for half their lives.
You can either see them
at their funeral or...
One drop of this
will be enough...
to make him fall
into a deep sleep.
Put Yeon to sleep.
Then you can get the life
you've always dreamed of.
CHAPTER 11: GROUND CHERRIES
I told you we should've
gotten a massage chair.
We'll only end up using
it as a clothing rack.
It's a waste of money.
I'm old now, so my body
isn't as healthy as...
Will you put some
strength into your hands?
Got it.
Bok Gil used to
give great massages.
He was also worried that you were
always working day and night,
so he'd gather the bark of hardy
rubber trees and Siberian ginseng...
and boil them for your joints...
I don't want to hear you
talking about that unfilial son.
Don't call my son unfilial.
Get out.
Why do you keep acting
like you're the only one...
who's heartbroken because
of our son's death?
I said get out!
It was because of you.
He wouldn't have
committed suicide...
if you hadn't killed his wife.
She was possessed with a
ghost that causes plagues.
I couldn't just sit back and
watch the entire nation...
suffer from a plague
because of her.
Exactly.
That's who you are.
You're neither Bok Gil's
mother nor my wife.
You're just the gatekeeper
of the Samdo River.
Meanwhile, I've been
trying so hard...
to understand you for so long, but
I guess that was foolish of me.
I don't even want to
look at you. Just leave!
132 PEOPLE COMMITTED
SUICIDE IN GEUMRAN-GU.
GRIM REAPERS ARE REQUIRED TO
GATHER AT THE TEMPLE OF DEATH.
It's Imoogi, isn't it?
You have two days to
bring me Lee Yeon.
It's his body I need.
Rather than thinking
about breaking the deal,
think of a way to
untangle the mess.
Imoogi, that scumbag.
What in the world has he done?
"UNPRECEDENTED MASS
SUICIDE, CITIZENS IN SHOCK"
Can you believe this?
It's like a horror movie.
How could 132 people
in the same district...
all commit suicide
at the same time?
Do you think they were some
kind of a suicide group?
There wasn't a
single will found.
People who commit suicide
normally feel the urge...
to let people know
why they chose to die.
Or maybe it was a cult.
In the 1970s, a group of cult
believers in Jonestown...
committed mass suicide.
They all drank poison,
but this time, the causes
of death are all different.
This is so weird.
I'm back.
Hey, Terry. You're back.
Hey, wait. You were at
Geumran-gu. Hey, are you...
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
- Pardon?
- Didn't you see the news?
An hour ago, a group
of people died there.
- Really?
- Where is Ji A?
Didn't she come with you?
She left early saying
something urgent came up.
- Isn't she at the office?
- Really?
I didn't see her come back.
- Here's the footage I took.
- Thank you.
How was it today?
Did Ji A give you a hard time?
No, not at all.
She's really kind.
NAM JI A
Bring me the mountain spirit,
and I'll return
your parents to you.
LEE YEON
JI A, WHY WON'T YOU SAVE US?
Come in.
My goodness.
This place is nice.
The living room is spacious,
but there aren't a lot of rooms.
I guess vets make
a lot of money.
Come this way.
Have a seat.
This is...
It's borscht, a
traditional Russian dish.
I know you probably didn't
grow up eating this.
But I thought you might miss
the smell of where you're from.
Don't you like it?
I sometimes miss the forest
where I was born and grew up in.
Right now, it's turned
into an apartment complex.
I know this smell.
I also like it.
On top of that, it's delicious.
Eat up.
I'm sorry.
Geomdoong?
Mister.
You brat. Get back here.
Don't annoy me. I will kill you.
Who's this?
My stepdad.
Come out. Get over here.
You choose.
You ask me for help,
I'll make sure you never
have to see him again.
Or I'll just go my way.
Hey you. Do you know him?
Why are you butting
into our family matter?
Quiet. I'm waiting
to hear his response.
What are you? Are you a cop?
So...
I...
Soo Ho. Answer wisely. Got it?
I have to go home.
Okay.
Yu Ri, who has no
friends or family.
- What?
- I can't live without chicken,
but if you want to eat
Russian food at every meal,
I'm willing to change
my preferences.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying I want to become...
your family and your friend.
Family... Well,
I have something
similar to that.
Your fake mom and dad
that Lee Rang gave you?
The department store owner?
Yes.
I'm their dead daughter's
fill-in and just an empty shell,
but they can't live without me.
People say...
they'd like to throw away their
family if no one was watching.
Because they make life
hard on each other.
But then again, you
end up going back...
and taking them back.
Like Lee Yeon and Mr. Lee?
Right.
So...
Let the department owners
have their lives back,
and become a true
family with me and...
What are you guys doing here?
- Mr. Lee!
- Yeon?
What are you doing here?
I live here.
Hey. Have you seen Ji A?
She wasn't here. Why?
She isn't at the office
either. Where is she?
Anyway, keep doing whatever it
was with the necklace thief.
This is Yeon's house?
It's okay. His
house is my house.
Did you just laugh?
Sorry. Let's eat.
Mr. Lee?
What?
What are you doing here?
I felt like I could see
you if I hung around here.
You weren't answering your phone
all day long. Did something happen?
Yes.
Me too.
What happened?
But first...
Ta-da.
Open it.
Something that makes you happy
just by thinking about it.
You remembered.
Of course.
The smell of freshly cooked rice,
a complete set of world literature,
Dad's handmade
gimbap, new sneakers,
and me.
Buy one, get one free.
They say if you buy your girlfriend
sneakers, she'll run away.
Even if you run away, I want
you to wear new sneakers...
and only go on nice paths.
Why are you smiling so sadly?
Do you not like them?
I do.
I never knew that the
word "sneakers"...
had such a sweet meaning.
I like you.
So much that I wouldn't regret
exchanging my life for you.
Should we take a walk?
On a nice path.
Together.
What's this?
What else? A fresh human.
Who is he?
None of your concern.
Turn him into a ground
cherry for emergency food.
Much obliged.
He moved the ground
cherry pot somewhere else?
Do you want to watch?
Are you allowed to show me?
There's nothing to
hide between us.
It looks like an ordinary
seed, doesn't it?
It traps the body and soul,
so I call it a latch
for the body and soul.
Only Imoogi can create it.
What an evil soul.
He was in and out of prison...
Did you save a little kid?
I need at least one good deed...
to defend myself with when
I enter the Afterlife.
- Do you want more milk?
- Yes.
Eat up.
Stop eating already.
That milk is mine.
Why doesn't that lady go home?
You go home.
Or I'll eat your liver.
I don't have a home anymore.
Stop acting all pathetic.
Thousands of people in
Seoul don't have a home.
- Are you homeless too?
- Not me.
Stop fighting.
Soo Ho, right? Where's your mom?
My mom got beat up
every single day...
and ran away with
some guy I don't know.
That's why my stepdad
was so mad at me.
So you must have nowhere to go.
Oh, my gosh.
Mr. Lee, why are you
doing this to me?
Eat up.
What are you thinking about?
You know the story "The
Little Mermaid", right?
Andersen?
Yes.
Ever since I was a child,
I hated the ending.
She could've lived if she
had killed the prince.
So why did she
turn into sea foam?
What about you? What would
you do if it were you?
A long time ago, I thought I'd
definitely kill the prince...
and save myself.
But? Have you changed your mind?
Now that I've met the prince,
I grew to like him much
more than I imagined.
Although if the
prince were gone,
the fairy tale could
end with a happy ending.
If I were the little mermaid,
I'd kill the sea witch.
I'd rather not be her plaything.
I've been cursed.
I could have my parents
back if I sell you out.
I've heard their wish,
so tell me yours.
I want my voice back...
and find my prince.
All while not turning
into sea foam.
So come witch-hunting with me.
Are you sure you
can spare such time?
Our deal expires in 24 hours.
It may very well be
my last living day,
so what's it to you
whether or not...
I let it go to waste?
You'll just throw
your life away?
For the brother you loathe?
Imoogi met with Lee Yeon today.
He let your brother know
of our three hostages.
Ji A, her parents, and you.
Where do you think
he is right now?
Has he even called
you in concern?
Liar.
You've been
abandoned once again.
You're right. I did abandon you.
I'm sorry...
for saving you after your
human mother abandoned you.
Yeon...
I never abandoned you.
He said he never
once abandoned me.
You of all people
know that it's a lie.
- Hey, kid!
- Yeon?
He saved me from the
Forest of the Starved.
He had to in order to save Ji A.
You're nothing but disposable.
Shut it!
Lee Yeon will do
anything for Ji A...
even if that
involves killing you.
If you go after her,
I'll kill you for
real this time.
Will you give up your life...
for a brother who only
cares for his girl?
Yes, Mr. Lee.
What? Shin Ju?
He wants to talk to you.
This is Shin Ju.
You know, right? Where's Yeon?
He went to see Ms. Nam.
So where?
I'll call you back
with an answer.
It's 132 people.
The number of dead people
who aren't on the list is...
There will be more.
- What?
- He is chaos itself.
We're only getting started.
Then let's bring him in. Tell
me how, and I'll do it myself.
It's beyond your capacity.
In order to bring him in,
you'll have to do what
you hate with passion.
And what may that be?
Hey, Yeon. You're here.
What? My gosh, you...
Hello, sir and ma'am.
I'm Nam Ji A.
Well, Yeon told us
a lot about you.
It's nice to meet you.
You!
How dare you bring a
living person here?
I know she's a living person,
but she's also at the center of
the argument you were having.
You have stepped in here
far too early. Go back.
I'm well aware that you highly
value rules and principles.
I came here knowing
the risks because...
Do I look like your
fairy godmother?
- What the...
- Hold it.
Or maybe...
you'd like to know when you die.
No. I stay away from fortune
tellers since I hate spoilers...
even about my own life.
- Then what?
- I lost my parents at nine.
This isn't a place
for your sob story.
I hear that I possess something
that belongs to Imoogi.
That's also the fate
you were handed.
I plan to defy that fate
until my last breath.
It is why I came here knowing
that it wasn't a place...
for living people.
- She's just like you.
- Yes, we were made for each other.
I admire you not being
intimidated by me.
So tell me why you're here.
Let me borrow Clairvoyance.
I wish to know where
my parents are.
- What?
- It won't be for free.
As if you have anything
to offer in return.
I'd let you overcharge
me knowingly,
but I don't have much to spare.
Then with what will
you strike a deal?
We'll bring you Imoogi.
Yeon and I.
Gosh, I made it out alive.
Didn't you see me
trembling in there?
It hardly seemed like the case.
I thought that past lives
and the Afterlife...
only existed in comic books,
but they're real.
Sinners only have
better lives...
until they take
their last breaths.
Do you help the dead cross
Samdo River from here?
I give a presentation about
what to expect in the Afterlife,
catch those who refuse
to cross the river,
and keep my wife happy.
I'm glad...
that someone as considerate
as you is the first person...
people meet after passing.
You grew up well even though...
you lost your parents
at a young age.
They'll be incredibly
proud of you.
Will I ever get
to see them again?
Let's trust Yeon and
believe that he'll deliver.
This isn't like you, Granny.
Why do you say that?
Because you would've
turned Imoogi into stone...
way before he became a problem.
I remember how you turned...
the northern mountain
spirit into one...
just for getting
on your wrong side.
So why...
is Imoogi an exception?
Because I don't want
to see you go crazy.
- What do you mean by that?
- A piece of him lies with her.
The Imoogi.
Is there a way...
to free her from it?
No.
Either she dies...
or the Imoogi leaves
her voluntarily.
I don't believe that. How can
a piece of it be with her?
You must've heard
something about it.
Despite your best efforts,
Imoogi was awoken.
The girl will be sacrificed,
and the rest of your life
will be nothing but painful.
That...
is your fate.
Now I get why you didn't
want me to find her.
From the start, you
said we shouldn't meet.
You didn't want me
to get hurt again.
You didn't want me dragged
into that fate again.
Thanks, Granny.
But still, I choose her.
My only purpose in life
was to meet her again.
It looks like...
you'll always end up
making the same choice.
The ground cherries.
That's where her parents are.
Let's go.
- We'll be off now.
- Oh, okay.
If anything happens,
come here and repeat
my name three times.
I don't know if you'll win or
lose the fight against fate,
but I still want
to bet on you guys.
Thank you.
You should go now.
Did you find out?
The ground cherries.
"Ground cherries"?
I've never seen ground
cherries in Seoul before.
Are these ground cherries?
That's where my mom and dad are?
How?
That plant can trap the body
and soul of a living person.
And he used that to lengthen
the lives of his followers.
Let's go. It was
in the living room.
It was in the center
of the living room.
He probably moved
it somewhere else.
It wasn't there
when I last went.
Our deal expires in 24 hours.
You drove a wedge
between the two brothers.
Do you think Rang
will fall for it?
Yes, he will.
Rang has a deep-rooted
obsession for his brother.
It's a lot more
twisted than you think.
You think he can kill
him because he loves him?
Leave this to me.
I'll bring you Yeon's heart.
Don't look down on him.
The reason I got defeated
by him long ago...
was because I
underestimated him.
That's why I set up three traps.
We just need one of
them to fall for it.
Once this is over,
I'll go into politics.
I'm sick of pretending to be the
CEO of a broadcasting company.
- And I deserve a reward.
- Whatever you want.
You little monster.
Where do you think
he is right now?
Has he even called
you in concern?
You've been
abandoned once again.
Will you give up your life...
for a brother who only
cares for his girl?
- Yeon.
- Were there ground cherries...
at Imoogi's house?
Ji A's parents are
trapped inside there.
Do you know anything about that?
Is that all you
have to say to me?
Did you see the cherries or not?
I did.
Where did he hide the cherries?
I don't know that much.
- Bye.
- I can find out.
The CEO values it as
much as his own life.
- Really?
- Let's meet tomorrow.
Let's talk about it then.
Rang told me he'll look into it.
I'm going to meet him tomorrow.
Where? What time?
Should I go with you?
Leave it to me.
I need you to do the thing
that only you can do.
What are you guys doing here?
We got too worried about her...
after knowing her boyfriend
is a nine-tailed fox.
- Ji A.
- What?
How did you know where I live?
Director Nam once did a
background check on you.
Why did you come
all the way here?
We came to see if you're safe.
I won't ever approve
of a nine-tailed fox...
Actually, I take that back.
How big is this living room?
I didn't think it was right
to visit empty-handedly.
- What is it?
- It's just a snack.
Mealworms?
I asked a friend who
directs an animal show,
and he told me foxes love it.
I had trouble choosing between
mealworms and crickets.
You can go ahead and enjoy it.
Did you guys eat dinner?
- No.
- I'll order.
Only the fox's death can
break a deal made by a fox.
GOBOON'S TRIPE RESTAURANT
They wrap it in a bundle?
Let me eat with them first.
The CEO was the accomplice
of the mummy case?
I asked him about the nail I
found, and he admitted everything.
Why don't you call the cops?
And say what?
That our CEO is from Goryeo?
And that he's a follower of Imoogi
and goes around killing people?
You think they'll believe that?
You're right.
Then why not let Detective
Baek put on those glasses...
that show you
people's past lives?
Once he sees
people's past lives,
he might believe that
there's a guy from Goryeo.
Are you sure he graduated from
the best university in Korea?
He's a nice guy.
Why aren't you eating anything?
You didn't eat the mealworms,
and you're not eating any tripe.
Do you eat people's livers?
You're making me
crave it a little.
It's pretty good.
I know this is rude,
but do you have a tail?
Why would you ask if
you know it's rude?
I still can't believe that
you're a nine-tailed fox.
Yes, he has one. I saw it.
Unbelievable. Then do you also
put a leaf on your forehead...
and transform yourself?
That's a raccoon.
And I do know how to transform, but
I don't because it's not classy.
Show us! Show us!
You punk.
- My gosh, just eat.
- Just eat the food.
I'll do it.
What made you change your mind?
I want to live.
Do you really think you can
take out your brother's heart?
You can take out his heart.
I'll lure him to you.
You have such a tender heart.
Take this.
And lure Yeon to the
location I tell you to.
From now on, we'll
be moving together.
You can sleep here tonight.
He's so fit to work at
a broadcasting company.
- You should keep working here.
- You're too kind.
Did you buy everything
this morning?
Yes.
- Eat up.
- It looks good. Let's eat.
When did you get so close?
Hey. He's a real piece of work.
He knows history, literature,
arts, religion, everything.
He's a walking encyclopedia.
He was useful on the field too.
Remember the foreign language
papers on past lives?
He translated the English,
French, and Chinese papers...
all last night.
What's your secret?
I never left home when I was
young because of my health.
I was alone other than
for my babysitter.
So all I did was read.
Good morning. So this
was where you all were.
Nice. Who picked up sandwiches?
- It's mine.
- Just one. Don't be cheap.
Urban Legends team, we
have a team dinner tonight.
- I'm out.
- Me too.
No, no, no. No
investigations, no editing,
no excuses will
work today. Why not?
Because it's Terry's
welcome dinner.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Making coffee.
What's with these flowers
that don't suit you at all?
So that you can enjoy the
scent of our old home.
Pick one that you like.
Women love this stuff.
That was thoughtful of you.
So? Where are the ground
cherries? Did you find out?
What's the rush?
I don't have time to chit chat.
- What?
- I don't have time either.
But still, listen to
what I have to say.
What is it?
What am I to you?
Where did things
get twisted again?
I've done all I could.
What's the problem this time?
Answer me.
What am I to you?
You're family.
Sickening family that thinks
just because we had the same dad,
you had the right to do all
sorts of wicked things to me.
Don't think I'll feed
you flowery words...
just because you
surrounded me with flowers.
I'm sick of your
whining at your age!
You're so mean to me...
when you're endlessly
magnanimous to her.
Yes. Because she's
much tougher than you.
She doesn't cling onto her
family tragedy like a loser...
and whine like somebody.
Isn't it odd?
You were never once
a nice brother,
but shone in my
eyes as if you were.
You seemed perfect.
I wanted...
to become like you.
Drink it.
What if you spiked it?
Calm down. I'm just kidding.
So? Where are the
ground cherries?
Wait. We'll find them soon.
Don't you dare try
anything funny.
After you saved me from
the Forest of the Starved,
I thought...
I should die for you someday...
in order to save you.
But you know, I
realized I couldn't.
I want to live.
That's why...
I need you to die, big brother.
Do you want to fight?
I can't beat you if we
fight fair and square.
The coffee.
If you cared for me even a fraction
of how much you worry about her,
I wouldn't have done this.
I could never.
You idiot.
We got Lee Yeon.
Wait until I get there.
Don't call me on
this phone again.
Darn it. Does he think I'm
his lackey or something?
Hey. Here. Come here.
Sit down. Sit. Okay.
Okay, then. Fill your
glasses everyone.
I'll fill yours, Terry.
Okay. Here you go.
- Thank you.
- I'll pour my own.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- Drink up.
Gosh. I wish I had
a son like him.
He's handsome,
smart... He's so...
My gosh. He's so
fit. He's solid.
He's totally... Sure.
You're a good kid.
I'm starting to
respect Mr. Choi now.
How is he so unchanging?
I'm going to get some air.
Terry, where are you going?
I need to meet
someone for a bit.
I'll be right back.
Where did you
learn such manners?
- Sorry?
- Who leaves a dinner...
without saying anything?
Especially the guest of honor.
- I'm sorry.
- I have a lot of questions for you.
Like what, for instance?
What's your favorite book?
- "A Lover's Discourse: Fragments".
- By Roland Barthes?
Have you read it?
I got baited by the title.
I thought it'd
teach me about love,
but to understand
his language of love,
one needs at least
a master's degree.
He wrote many beautiful phrases.
"He praises her perfection..."
"and praises himself..."
"for choosing pure perfection."
Meanwhile, I praise cocktails.
Come on.
I have five minutes
left. End our deal.
Our deal ends when I
have Lee Yeon's heart.
I brought him to
you as promised.
Now announce the
end of our deal.
Can't you see I'm
waiting for Imoogi?
Being rude, are we?
I bet it drives you crazy.
You can't kill the one
who you owe a favor.
Once a slave, always a slave.
You can't do anything without
your master's approval.
Watch what you say.
You're still bound to
me by the favor you owe.
You serve a creature that
sucked the blood of your family.
Shut it.
How did it feel...
to watch your parents,
wife, and children die?
Did you cry?
- I told you to shut it.
- Then say it!
Say that our deal is over.
Fine. I'll end our deal...
in my own way.
You've lost your mind.
No can do, I'm afraid.
I may be a worthless
piece of trash,
but I can't sacrifice my
family to get what I want.
You... Then you'll die.
I won't.
Foxes die when they
go back on a deal.
And foxes...
can change their appearances.
Although, I find it distasteful.
You and your desire
to seem graceful.
I thought you said
you'd only take a sip?
What's going on?
Since when...
Since your place last night.
What are you...
doing here?
I'm sorry.
I only thought you were
one of the hostages.
I didn't think
he'd kill everyone.
So how about you keep
living by my side?
No matter what I do,
I can't be free of my deal.
There's a way.
How?
Swap places with me...
and bring me to him
just like he wants.
I'll do it.
Take this.
You can sleep here tonight.
Darn you. How dare you!
You. Kill Lee Yeon right now...
Stop harassing my brother...
or I'll have to snap your neck.
So, the choice is yours.
Kill Rang and have your
life ended by me. Or...
change his deal.
Save me and our
deal will be over.
The ground cherries...
Take me to where they are.
- Here.
- We drink to get drunk.
- Darn it.
- But you're wasted, sir.
- But...
- Please drive safely. Bye!
I'll get going then!
Take my car instead. I called
for a designated driver.
- It's fine.
- But I'm not.
Sorry about that.
You can get going.
Ms. Nam.
- Yes?
- Are you seeing someone?
Yes, I am.
What's your boyfriend like?
Like someone from a fairy tale.
Break up with him.
- What?
- Fairy tales for grown-ups...
tend to have savage endings.
So long. Thank you
for everything.
What a blabbermouth.
I no longer am bound.
Nice acting, by the way.
You were good enough
to be an actor.
Maybe I'll give it a shot.
Terry.
Don't pretend with
the romantic feelings.
Because to me,
you're nothing...
but the thing that took
my parents from me.
I see you've known all along.
Is that why you've
been keeping me here?
I need you to do the thing
that only you can do.
What only I can do?
While I search for
the ground cherries,
keep Imoogi occupied.
Imoogi?
Where is he?
Someplace...
much closer to you
than you think.
Much closer to me?
No way...
You seem unprotected...
for someone who knows
my true identity.
Yeon told me...
that you can't kill me.
He's right.
I'm quite fond of you.
Mom.
Dad.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
You probably wanted to warn me.
I'll save your life
no matter what.
You're going to attack
Imoogi directly?
I'm going to find his weakness.
I'll kill those who
are precious to you.
A bigger disaster is on its way.
Don't touch them.
Look carefully. I am you.
Where is Ji A? Where is she?
A plague will hit this world.
No one will be happy.
Why does it have
to be Ji A? Why?
Turn everything back
to where it belongs.