Mom.
Dad.
Is this for real?
Are you really my parents?
Mom,
don't you recognize me?
Dad, it's Ji A,
your daughter.
I get it though.
It's been over 20 years.
Our daughter...
is all grown up.
And you're still...
a weeper.
Do you...
recognize me?
As if a parent wouldn't
recognize their child.
Mom!
We're sorry for making
you wait so long.
I'm so sorry.
I missed you.
I missed you so much.
You and your brother
did a great deed.
For the first time in 20 years,
Ms. Nam will sleep in peace.
I deliver when I
put my mind to it.
- And your brother's deal?
- Over and done.
That's so cool.
Praise me more.
Life is so unfair.
How can you be handsome and
good at solving problems too?
You blind me!
Have you made up
with Lee Yeon then?
It's more like I let it pass.
But I don't like the guy.
Why not?
He's been hurting you
since like forever!
Don't tell me you'll
be living with him now.
I'm not insane, you know.
Just don't ignore me now that
you have your brother back.
What if I do?
I'll bite you.
I did a bad job
raising you then.
5 YEARS AGO
This is what you do.
If someone bites you, you
should bite them back.
The world is cruel to those who
can't even scream when bitten.
I never asked you to save me!
I know.
Those who take others
in against their will...
and feed and care for them only
to discard them later on...
are the worst in
my book as well.
Which is why you're to leave
once you finish eating.
What?
I told you not to follow me.
Attack me.
Again. Right here and here.
This is the jugular.
Remember that.
Again.
Again. Again.
Mr. Lee,
I managed to hit the
jugular in one strike.
Good job.
How about I buy you some jokbal?
No way! Jokbal reminds
me of my sick past.
How about bossam instead?
No. Tonight's a
night for jokbal.
Darn it.
Gosh, don't do that!
How about half and half?
Sounds good.
MISSING PARENTS
Goodness.
What is all this?
I passed out flyers at first,
but no one would believe me.
That's why I became a TV
show director instead...
to find you myself.
And I have now.
Ji A.
We couldn't be prouder.
How do you feel? Does
it hurt anywhere?
We're both all right,
so don't worry.
It's better to be safe, so
let's see a doctor soon.
It's that music box.
The accident at Yeou
Gogae seemed to have...
only happened yesterday.
Our world seems the same, but
20 years have already passed.
- My gosh.
- Where were you...
all this time?
I'm not sure.
I feel like I awoke
from years of sleep.
- You too?
- Yes.
Then...
What about this? Isn't
this your handwriting?
"Ji A, why won't you save us"?
I woke up just this one time...
and was approached by a
man with fair complexion.
He told me that we'll be able to
see you if I wrote that message.
He must've helped you.
No, it wasn't him.
It was Lee Yeon.
Yeon was the one
who saved you guys.
- Is he the guy we saw earlier?
- Yes.
What kind of person is he?
I'm all he ever cares about.
He waited to meet me
for a really long time.
And he even sacrificed
his life for me.
Is he your boyfriend?
- I guess you really are grown up.
- My goodness.
I must say, I'm very upset.
I always wanted to be the first
to know about your boyfriend...
and was looking forward
to nagging at you.
Go ahead and do it. I really
want to hear you guys nag.
There were so many things
I wanted to do for you.
Now that you're back, you
can do them for me now.
Okay, I will.
I'm so proud of you, sweetheart.
You grew up so well and
became a hotshot director.
JI A
What's with the video chat?
I thought you might be
scared to sleep alone, Puppy.
- "Puppy"?
- Let's do everything...
other couples do.
Let's come up with
nicknames for each other...
and get matching rings.
And let's even do corny
stuff on the phone.
Like what?
Something like this.
You must be really happy today.
Yes, I'm happy. So happy
that I feel like I can fly.
Don't fly away.
Your puppy is going to cry.
Thank you, Yeon.
Thank you for keeping your promise
about finding my parents for me.
I wish all your nights will
be as happy as tonight.
I'll make sure that happens.
Ji A, let's sleep.
I need to go.
Good night.
Good night. I hope
you dream of me.
CHAPTER 12: CATCHING TAILS
I almost died! Those
crazy nine-tailed foxes!
I was just about to call you.
I almost had him, but it
turned out they tricked me.
Yes, I made a small mistake.
You lost the ground
cherries and hostage.
Thanks to you, I don't have
that many options left.
I can turn everything
back. Trust me.
So tell me.
Where are you right now?
I'm just outside.
I can hear everything.
I can hear how troubled
you feel right now.
Come inside. Then
you'll find out...
if it's life or death...
that's waiting for you.
I'm not going to die. No way. I
sacrificed so much to stay alive.
I'm not going to die. No. Never.
Why am I here?
Welcome.
Imoogi.
I prefer being called
Terry than Imoogi.
It was the first name
you ever called me by.
So this was your doing?
How did you bring me here?
I didn't bring you
here. You called me.
- What?
- This is your dream.
And it means we're
communing with each other.
Cut the nonsense. I'm not
interested in communing with you.
We're bound to
each other by fate.
Go away. Just get lost!
Look carefully. I am you.
I need to catch Imoogi.
But I must do it in a way
that Ji A won't get hurt.
Then...
where should I start?
It's me, Yeon.
I don't find it fancy
talking to you either.
I called thinking you'd need
something like ground cherries,
but forget it if
you're not interested.
Really?
Then let's meet.
Yes, forget everything else.
I just need those
ground cherries.
Forget about Imoogi and Lee Yeon.
I don't care about them anymore.
WE CAME RUNNING TO YOU.
Ta-da.
What's this?
It's a new cell phone.
I didn't have to go
to a cell phone store,
so someone ordered it for me.
Someone ordered it?
They even deliver
cell phones now?
They deliver it to you within
an hour upon your order.
- That's so interesting.
- Here.
If you press this, it'll
start calling my number.
MY LOVELY DAUGHTER,
MY LOVELY MOM
Don't answer anyone
else's calls.
Don't open the door
for strangers either.
Don't worry and go to work.
I know it'll take some time for
us to get used to living in 2020.
But your dad and I aren't kids.
You can lean on me. It's okay.
Ji A, we should
eat with that guy.
Who?
Yeon?
"Fate and connection"?
He showed up in your dream
and said that stuff to you?
I don't think it
was a normal dream.
My face was covered in
snakeskin. It was horrible.
What if something deep inside me
is calling for him continuously?
What if that's it?
Why me of all people?
I'll catch him no matter what.
You trust me, right?
I trust you.
Oh, by the way,
Are you free for dinner tonight?
Dinner?
My mom and dad want to meet...
my boyfriend.
That's me.
Yes.
Would you take a
look at the kitty?
I'm sorry, but
I'm on my way out.
- Is it hurt?
- It was a stray cat.
I think it got caught in a trap.
I'll pay for the
treatment. Please.
What a good young man.
Bring him over.
Here.
Did that hurt?
It's okay.
Luckily, the wound isn't deep.
It isn't?
You poor baby. Who
did that to you?
What?
Who? Who did it?
What is it? Can the
cat speak or something?
Where did you find him?
On the hiking trail nearby.
It's Imoogi.
He is...
Imoogi.
These are lotus leaf
short rib patties.
They're on me since this
is a happy occasion.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Eat.
What's the job?
Tell us our rate first.
We're quite expensive.
I'll add a zero to the
current minimum wage.
As in, 86 dollars?
What should we do first?
What you do best as
people in broadcasting.
Get information on someone.
On whom...
Imoogi.
Fables, legends, folktales,
children's stories,
even comics are fine.
Bring me everything
there is about Imoogi.
- Why?
- Weakness.
I plan to find his weakness.
You're trembling.
A vet shouldn't be like that.
My apologies. Excuse me.
Touch that, and you die today.
You know who I am, don't you?
Koo Shin Ju, Yeon's
right-hand man.
So you can understand animals.
What do you want?
Yeon and I are playing
"catch the tail".
"Catch the tail"?
Which gets me to my point.
Are you a good hostage?
Just kill me instead.
I'd rather die than
become a weakness...
for Mr. Lee.
So that's the type you are.
I'm not afraid. Kill me.
I guess this could
be a suggestion.
One day,
when the Imoogi inside
of her calls for you,
you will...
Imoogi killed us
in our past lives?
And that Imoogi is our intern?
That's not right.
Why are all the hot guys either
a nine-tailed fox or an Imoogi?
Sorry about that.
Okay, I'll let you guys talk.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to submit my edits...
and go home.
I'm going grocery
shopping with Dad.
Should I drive you?
It's okay. See you at
home. Make yourself pretty.
- Okay, then. We'll go too...
- Sit.
Now.
I'll tell you something
much more important now.
I need know-how...
on how to impress her parents...
Here. Right here.
- Okay.
- They're so pretty.
- Thank you.
- Give me a taste.
- Here.
- Is it okay?
- Good?
- No, go in.
You seem to be doing
that on purpose.
What if I undo another button?
Seriously. Go back in.
- Is it okay? This?
- Yes.
So this is what they like.
Thanks, my part-timers.
Hey.
- Hello.
- You met him yesterday.
Let me formally introduce
myself. I'm Lee Yeon.
Nice to meet you. We figured we'd
eat and get to know each other.
- Let's go inside.
- Wait.
Remember.
"Thank you for inviting
me. This is a small gift."
At least red ginseng.
Or expensive cosmetics.
As in, show them
how wealthy I am.
Thank you very much
for inviting me.
This is a small gift.
A lighter? I don't
smoke though...
It's the model that
I drive as well.
Please enjoy.
He's a very generous person.
Let's go.
Please come in.
- Yes.
- Go inside.
It's been a while since
I've cooked with Ji A.
I hope you like it.
To be completely honest, it
isn't really my favorite.
The bulgogi marinade
is a bit strong.
It's delicious.
Everything is delicious.
You're a very honest fellow.
Don't ramble when they
ask you a question.
- Always be honest and brief.
- Be honest.
How old are you?
You'll be shocked if I tell you.
Why? How old are you?
I may look young,
but I'm much...
So... He's 36 in Korean age.
He lived sort of abroad
for a while. Right?
Did you study abroad?
We met when we were
studying abroad too.
So? Did you go to
college abroad?
I didn't go to college.
Well... It's not like you
have to go to college.
I didn't go to
high school either.
I never went to school at all.
Then what do you
do for a living?
I don't have a job.
Well... You're quite
the free spirit.
But I'm rich. I gave
you a car and...
Stop it.
They said they were
going to break up.
- Right.
- But they're still together.
- Really?
- I was so dumbfounded.
Gosh, what if the guy
was being too clingy?
- Exactly.
- What options do we have?
- Isn't he pretty reticent?
- Right. I told her not to...
What would you like?
Before I order... It's so loud.
Pardon?
I'm so sleepy.
I want to sleep.
You're the Snail Bride, right?
- Why are you here?
- To eat.
Take my order.
Fine. What do you want?
What does Yeon usually eat here?
I'll have whatever Yeon likes.
So you're a college professor,
and you're a doctor, right?
And Ji A is a production director
who graduated from the best college.
I see I have nothing
to offer in comparison.
Still, I like your
daughter a great deal.
What about her do you like?
I've experienced a lot
of things in my life...
than you think I may have.
The years were cruel to me.
But funnily enough,
eating beside Ji A like this...
makes me feel like I'm
a member of this family.
And it warms up my heart.
Me too.
With my parents gone,
I tried desperately hard to
be all right in this house.
But Yeon made me realize...
that we're supposed to
live in the shadows...
of the people we can rely on.
I wanted to be that
kind of person too.
You grew up well. Both of you.
The food's on the saltier
side, but I hope you enjoy it.
I will.
You're not a bad cook.
Why on earth are
you after Mr. Lee?
He's been drowning
in loneliness...
and he only recently found
happiness again. Why...
There are many variations...
regarding the story
of the snail bride.
But every one of them...
ends tragically.
It's the same for
me and Lee Yeon.
One of us has to die
for this story to end.
Listen to my words carefully.
You...
Look at this one. My gosh.
- This is Ji A at 100 days.
- How adorable.
How can her hands and
feet be this tiny?
Even at this size, she
had quite the temper.
- Who does she take after?
- Not me.
As if. That was your
guilty conscience talking.
Ji A has her mom's
temper but my looks.
Oh, what was that for?
Should you be showing
my photos this easily?
You don't have any
bad photos at all.
Of course not.
Unbelievable. Is that so?
- Ta-da.
- What?
What's this? Dad,
are you kidding me?
Why not? You look adorable!
- You're pretty in that one too.
- Stick to the nicer ones.
Darn it.
I want him dead.
You're home.
You always drink Americano,
so what's with the latte?
It's to help me remember this
day that will be a one of a kind.
Who knew that such
a gentle moment...
could ever encase
my bitter life?
Was it that nice?
My mind wandered off when
watching your family photos.
I thought of marriage...
and having a baby
that takes after us.
I also imagined eating
gimbap at Han River...
and getting into an argument...
which I'd probably lose.
I never age,
but there I was
with gray hair...
with you by my side.
If I were human...
If only I were an ordinary human,
things would've been perfect.
Does life taste
bitter again now?
- Why don't I add some sweetness?
- Sure.
- What's this?
- Ta-da!
Matching rings!
I've always wanted one.
- Really?
- I was going to buy it for you.
You've given me enough.
All you do is give.
Do you like it?
Why...
Why would you?
No way. I couldn't have.
It couldn't have been me.
What happened?
I did it.
I... With my own
hands, I hurt Mr. Lee.
- I must've been insane.
- Why would you though?
I don't know.
Why did I do such a thing?
I honestly don't know.
Yu Ri, calm down and think.
I was on my way over after
receiving Mr. Lee's call.
Out front, I bumped
shoulders with some guy.
He said,
"I want him dead."
The rest is a blur.
- What guy?
- Imoogi.
It was probably Imoogi.
The guy you saw.
He controlled your mind
by planting a suggestion.
It wasn't a coincidence.
He approached you on purpose.
But why would he
do that to Yu Ri?
So he could send a warning...
to me.
"In every gain, there's a loss."
Rang rarely trusts anyone.
Imoogi used the one person
he feels comfortable around.
That's how...
a young and weak fox like you
were able to hurt him like this.
What a cowardly jerk. I should
go and teach him a lesson.
You're no match for him.
How is his condition?
Can he live?
I stopped the bleeding, but
he has shallow breathing.
He also has a weak pulse.
So what does that mean?
He's too weak right now, so
all we can do is watch...
Will you please do
something to save him?
What about the ground cherries?
We have the ground cherries.
I promised to give it to
Granny at Samdo River.
Can't we just use a few of them?
In every ground cherry,
someone's life is trapped inside.
You want me to kill people
so I could save Rang?
So what if they die?
Then let me do it. I'll do it.
Mr. Lee.
Your brother's life
is on the line.
You're forbidden to kill people.
However,
if you don't break that rule,
you won't be able to save Rang.
I wonder what your choice is
going to be this time, Yeon.
Where are they? Where
are the ground cherries?
At my place.
Really? Then let's go.
No, you can't go.
What?
I was always curious.
Why didn't anyone else
come back as humans...
other than Ji A's parents?
It's as if he wants me to
use the ground cherries.
Do you think he's testing you?
If I break the rule and kill humans,
I'll get dragged to the Underworld.
It could last days or weeks.
Then I won't be around
to protect Ji A.
What he wants...
is my absence.
We're not going to use
the ground cherries.
I'm going to catch Imoogi first.
And I'll save my brother's
life in my own way.
Give them to me!
- Yu Ri.
- Give me the ground cherries!
Stop it.
What's this?
Hey, Mr. Nine-tailed fox.
Do you want me to
be your friend?
- No.
- Why not?
Your nose. I don't like you
because you have a runny nose.
Hey, you're the boy
with the runny nose.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Choi, do you
think I'm a joke?
No, of course not. I
don't think you're a joke.
Then why would you...
buy me flowers and drinks?
When you do that for a widow who
runs a restaurant by herself,
it just means you want to
spend the night with me.
It's sad to hear you say that.
To me, flowers and alcohol...
make me feel happy...
and give me positive energy.
I had no idea those two
things could end up...
hurting you like this.
I mean...
Why me?
You have a pretty
nice background...
I want to be with
you. No one else.
I don't think of you as a widow
who runs a restaurant on her own.
You seem very special to me.
I really mean it.
I feel like you're
hiding a lot of things...
behind those miraculous eyes.
Yu Ri, get some sleep.
Can you go ask him for
some ground cherries?
I'm sure he'll listen to you.
Let's have faith in him
and give him some time.
I'm sure he'll find a way.
He's a jerk.
He's so cold-hearted
and ruthless.
Rang is in this
state because of him.
To be exact, Mr. Lee didn't
cause this to happen.
He warned Rang many times that
getting involved with Imoogi...
will only bring him misfortunes.
Whose side are you on?
Rang.
Rang!
Yu Ri.
Yu Ri, get up.
Is he sick?
Get out!
Soo Ho, we should go.
Is he also a nine-tailed fox?
Who told you that?
He's the little brother of
that guy who was here earlier.
The guy who came earlier
is a nine-tailed fox.
Your brother's life
is on the line.
Can't we just use a few of them?
Give them to me!
Give me the ground cherries!
What's the disinfectant?
It's this one.
Don't put on airs.
That's not how you do it.
What do you know?
How do you know all this?
My mom got hurt every
time my stepdad hit her.
So I used to do this for her.
Really? Then I'll
leave you to it.
If anything happens
to him, I'll kill you.
Where are you going?
Rang, I'll save you.
Gosh, no!
Rang!
Forgive me. I should've
stopped Yu Ri.
She managed to steal them
but they all withered?
- Yes.
- How is Rang?
He hasn't gotten any better.
Look after that
ground cherry thief.
She may cause trouble.
I'm sorry.
Should I bring the
tree to Madam Taluipa?
- No.
- Then?
Not yet.
I'm playing catch the
tail right now as well.
You look like you spent
12 years in 1 night.
I don't know where to
go to hide from him.
I'm dead.
You deserve it.
I'd kill you too,
if my right-hand man
caused trouble and hid.
Please save me. I'll
do anything you say.
Please give me the
ground cherries...
My ground cherries.
Don't you dare.
- Tell me what you want.
- Help me catch Imoogi.
The number of ground cherries will
vary based on the information.
Anything. I'll
tell you anything.
But how can I trust you?
From what I saw that day
when I was disguised as Rang,
everything about you was a lie.
I understand why
you can't trust me.
I wouldn't either.
But I didn't do it
because I wanted to.
Now, you say that?
I wanted to live.
I just wanted to live.
I know I'm staying alive
pathetically, but I'm still human.
I was an ordinary human
being at one point.
After losing my family to him,
I wanted to get
revenge if I could.
If I could get another chance,
I want to start over
as a new person.
Okay, okay.
Lift up your head.
If you cry while carrying this,
would you or would
you not seem sincere?
You even rubbed evening
primroses on it.
How did you know?
People don't change that easily.
You're smarter than you seem.
But do you think you
could kill me with this?
It's not loaded.
I just wanted to see...
whether the former
mountain spirit...
is stupid enough to
fall for my tears.
I can't bet my life on an idiot.
Now, we're talking.
Records about Imoogi are similar to
the tales by the most famous one,
the Jeju Island's
Kim Young Suk tale.
The regions are different,
as well as the time periods,
but all the endings make
me a bit uncomfortable.
Right? If a beautiful woman
is offered as a sacrifice,
a hero appears out of nowhere and
defeats Imoogi after a battle.
But it's never a happy ending.
The protagonist in Kim
Young Suk's story...
stabs and kills
Imoogi with a sword.
But it says he was murdered
by the dead Imoogi.
He killed him,
but he didn't die.
Maybe there's more than one.
Maybe there were two
Imoogis from the start.
You'll strike Imoogi directly?
What do you think?
If I like your answer,
I'll give you the whole thing.
This is something
that only I know.
The shaman on the island
said he can never die.
He simply sleeps.
I know that too.
The question is, how
do I put him to sleep?
It's the same as
how you woke him.
Don't you remember? The
well from which he awoke.
You're not making sense.
Do I have to throw him
back into the well?
It doesn't matter, as
long as there is water.
What matters are
the ingredients.
"Ingredients"?
The bodies of living people,
the blood of the sacrifice,
and the power of one
close to a divinity.
A mountain spirit. My power.
You were the final
ingredient to wake him.
There are so many records
about fighting Imoogi,
but there's nothing about what
weapon they used against him.
- I found something.
- What?
Look. A serpent
that lives in water.
The protagonist fights the
Imoogi living in the swamp,
and he covered himself
in horse blood first.
Imoogi must hate horse blood.
Nice. Send that to him now.
Should I include
an emoticon or not?
What do you think?
IMOOGI HATES HORSE BLOOD.
That's simple.
We just need those three
ingredients and water, right?
The problem is, he
wouldn't just sit back...
and wait for you to
put him to sleep.
IMOOGI HATES HORSE BLOOD.
THE STRONG YOUNG MAN COVERED
HIMSELF IN HORSE BLOOD.
TRADITIONAL MONSTERS: IMOOGI
I'll make him just
sit back and wait.
So I was thinking...
What? What are you doing?
I need the body of
a living person.
Hello, sir.
You want us to pick up
the ground cherry tree?
Okay. Leave it to me.
Really? Do you mean it?
Okay, okay. Take
care of yourself.
What did he say?
That he can catch Imoogi.
He got something out of his lackey
by pretending to give him...
ground cherries.
I'll go and confiscate the tree.
No.
What do you mean? Let him
have the ground cherries?
No. Yeon.
Yeon can't catch Imoogi.
What do you mean?
Because he's Yeon.
Because he's the Yeon that we
know, he can never ever do it.
Stay strong and think of
what you fear the most.
What I fear the most?
Being abandoned.
Mom abandoned me...
and so did you.
I will never abandon you.
I promise I'll save you.
I will catch...
Imoogi.
Jae Hwan! Sae Rom!
- Can't you hear me?
- It's no use.
They're under my spell.
Don't you dare touch them.
I'll kill you.
Go on a date with me.
Then I may let them live.
What?
Wear what I picked out.
Hello? Hey, you!
Ji A. These were by the
door. They have your name...
on them.
What do I do?
Sae Rom and Jae Hwan are
in trouble because of me.
Maybe I should call the police.
They will be fine.
I'll find them.
I already asked Shin Ju
to track their scent.
There's no need for
you to meet with him.
No,
I will.
I'm going to meet him.
Today's the day we catch him.
They all suit you.
The dress, necklace,
and everything else.
From now on, write down...
"puppeteer" as what you
do in your free time.
I love the expression you
hold when you talk like that.
Let's just eat.
I missed you, you know.
Can't a person eat in peace?
Shouldn't you be nicer to me?
One word from me and
they'll go flying.
Why me?
Because...
I think you could lead
me to what I truly seek.
What you truly seek?
The thing only I don't have.
The thing I may have
lost since my birth.
A long, long time ago,
a ninth son was born into...
a prestigious half-blood
family in Silla.
The baby didn't let out a cry,
but the mother sobbed.
The baby's limbs were
sunken like a snake's.
Its eyes, ears,
and even the voice
were deformed.
What happened to the baby?
His father who was a noble...
tried to kill the boy,
but the midwife stopped him.
She said it could curse him.
Instead, the boy grew
up locked up in a chest.
Other than the midwife who fed him,
not even his parents or brothers...
came to see him.
A baby that doesn't
cry will be forgotten.
It was a human being.
You were human before
turning into a monster.
The boy was thrown to a
cave of plague victims...
and was...
eaten.
This is horse blood?
Yes.
Time flew and that cave became
a tomb for plague victims.
And one day, a white
snake slid out from there.
Those who saw it called it "imoogi"
and regarded it as ominous.
That's how the story goes.
I figured it out.
The thing you truly want.
It's being loved by someone.
Will you help me get it?
And if I decline?
I'll kill you.
After I kill Lee Yeon,
I'll kill those you love...
and then you.
Soon after, a virus will spread.
No one will ever be happy again.
"UNVEILING URBAN LEGENDS"
Isn't the air nice and fresh?
Sure.
Are you waiting for someone?
- No.
- You know,
I don't think I
ever got my answer.
How do you feel about me?
I'm sorry, but my
love's been depleted.
A whole 15 years'
worth of my love...
is now Yeon's to keep.
What does he mean to you anyway?
Tell me.
How dare you lay a hand on
her? I should cut that off.
I'm afraid you're
the third wheel.
We're actually on a date.
Let me take you out instead.
I hate those who go
back on their words.
I wish to fly.
Got you!
I guess they didn't fly.
Not dry land but water is
the right place for Imoogi.
This is horse blood.
Figuring out your weakness
wasn't cheap, you know.
And this is my blood. I
guess our date ends here.
No, Yeon. You've
got it all wrong.
What's going on?
What went wrong?
You went after the wrong one.
What?
That Imoogi you're
desperately seeking.
The main piece of it
doesn't lie with me.
Then...
I'm burning up.
- What's wrong?
- My body is burning hot.
Does it hurt?
It's so hot.
It's okay. You'll
be fine. Please.
Does it not hurt anymore?
Look at me.
Long time no see, Yeon.
She's mine.
Get out of that body right now!
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
I might not have a lot of
time until I lose control...
of myself.
Take my life, and
use it to save Rang.
I plan to put an end to
this exhausting fight.
This sword only kills evil.
It'll only kill Imoogi's spirit.
You must stay alive until
the end of this fight.
- No.
- Move.
You messed with the
list of the dead?
I won't let anyone take Ji A.
Come at me.