Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
It's hot.
Gosh, stop being a crybaby.
Your hand is so hot.
It's burning hot.
Long time no see, Yeon.
Thirsty...
12 HOURS AGO
Water!
Water.
Water...
Water. Water!
DEATH
CHAPTER 3: THE SECRET
OF THE DRAGON KING
Being at sea wasn't enough and
he drowned himself to death.
He drowned?
In that toilet?
I fished his head out myself.
Look at how bloated
his stomach is.
That's all due to him
chugging down water.
Please call the police, Captain,
and close off this restroom.
Talk about it being
all for nothing.
This is what he gets after
throwing himself at his life.
What do you mean by that?
He was on The Galaxy,
the fishing boat...
that flipped over.
Then he was on that boat
with Pyung Hee's father.
Yes, there were four
of them in total.
Is this the police?
I see someone threw a party.
- What's wrong?
- It stinks.
What do you mean?
He smells like a stinky fish.
The body hasn't had time
to decompose yet though.
Hair?
But his is Gray.
I smell the sea...
and a faint scent of the
duvet from that house.
That house? You mean,
Pyung Hee's house?
DEATH
"MISSING FISHERMEN OF THE GALAXY
RETURN HOME AFTER 28 DAYS"
- Take a look at this.
- What?
That man. It's the same guy.
Four men were on board
The Galaxy that sunk.
Three returned
home in one piece,
- but one...
- Only his head came back to shore.
Please let me see my dad!
Dad!
By the looks of it,
he won't be the last.
Are you saying more
people could die?
Then we should get going.
Why?
To stop it, of course.
- I don't want to.
- What?
It's not my job.
Besides, they're not
good looking enough.
Come on!
I'm picky when it
comes to looks!
THE SECOND SURVIVOR
OF THE GALAXY
Who's there?
Jin Shik.
It's me.
Mr. Seo?
Mr. Seo, is that you?
Jin Shik.
Jin Shik!
I'm hungry. Food. I need food.
THE THIRD SURVIVOR
OF THE GALAXY
I'm starving!
More food. I need more food.
Who's there?
- Who are you?
- Come on. We've met before.
This house is a mess.
I heard you were with the guy
who lost his head that day.
Get out of my house. Get lost.
I'll leave when I want to.
You punk.
You need to learn how to behave.
I want you to answer
my questions politely.
If you don't, I'll start breaking
each one of your fingers.
What happened on the boat?
We met an unexpected
storm that day.
The weather forecast was wrong.
Then why did only
three of you survive?
Mr. Seo got swept
away by the waves.
And we were lost out in the sea.
- And then?
- That's all I remember.
I swear!
- When I woke up, I was onshore.
- Okay. I'll start with your pinkie.
Wait.
I bet you were scared.
You spent 28 days on that lifeboat
without any food or water.
It's just the right condition
for you to lose your mind.
The strong sunlight would've
caused your skin to burn.
And even with an empty stomach, I
bet you were constantly seasick.
You were probably sick of waiting
for someone to come save you,
and I bet you got angry the
more you thought about it.
"Why me? Why?"
Shut it!
The fifth day was
probably the worst...
because it hadn't rained at all.
First, you would've
gotten dehydrated.
Please help us.
Are you crazy?
Are you trying to die?
We're all going to die anyway.
I don't want to die.
- I don't want to die.
- My goodness.
I'm thirsty.
I bet my daughter
is worried sick.
Pyung Hee.
I'm thirsty.
I'm hungry.
But it's strange.
You say you starved for 28 days,
but you didn't lose much weight.
You didn't have Wi-Fi, so you
couldn't have ordered delivery food.
- What did you eat?
- Stop!
I... I didn't do it.
It wasn't me. I didn't do it.
I...
refuse to die out here.
What's the matter with you
guys? What are you doing?
Don't do this. Please.
I'm not going to die!
It wasn't me.
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
It's meat.
It's meat. I see meat.
Give me my meat.
Meat. My meat.
Give me my...
Hey, wake up.
Sir.
Is this hair?
He's dead.
SEO PYUNG HEE: SEO
KI CHANG'S DAUGHTER
Dad.
Stop crying. Your
wish came true.
There's only one
more person left.
But what will you
give me in return?
Who keeps messing with the list?
Honey!
What's the matter?
It happened again.
WARNING
Oh, dear. There's an error.
Someone who wasn't on
the list just died again.
Honey, don't be so
hysterical about it.
"Hysterical"?
No, I mean, don't
get too stressed.
I mispronounced it.
You're just stressed
due to work.
What were you doing
while I was busy working?
You were watching a
drama, weren't you?
No.
I was watering the
Euiryeong Tree.
You watered a tree
for three hours?
Honey, my diligence isn't
important. The list is a mess.
I'll hurry up and fix the
regional mortality statistics.
Wait here for a moment.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I wonder what kind of
trouble is waiting to happen.
I've seen lots of paintings...
as I gathered information
for my TV show.
But I've never seen a painting
that gives me the chills like this.
I wonder why.
There's something
missing in this drawing.
THE PAINTING OF
THE DRAGON KING
You startled me.
Oh, sorry.
Do you seriously have an
appetite for that right now?
Why? It's my favourite snack.
Two people died.
So what?
Why can't you give me a
more reasonable reaction?
Do you know how many
people in Joseon died...
during the 50 years of war?
3.5 million.
I've seen more deaths...
than all the funeral
companies in this country.
I'm sure there was
at least one death...
that made your heart ache
among those 3.5 million people.
Take a look at this.
The same painting was also
in that house earlier.
Isn't this a portrait
of the Dragon King?
Yes, but it looks
nothing like him.
- You saw him?
- Back when I was a mountain spirit.
We were in the same
leadership program.
People glamorized him too much.
He's not this good-looking.
This painting is a little different
from the ones I've seen before.
Look. This is the
usual painting.
Do you notice what's different?
This is just like
"Where's Wally?"
This has no feet.
Feet?
You're right.
A dragon that has no feet.
Do you get what this is?
This isn't a dragon.
It's a snake.
It's an Imoogi.
Are you Lee Rang?
I've been waiting.
Is that really asleep in here?
Yes. The spirit of immorality.
The king of the corrupt.
Lee Ryong.
Oh, my goodness.
That was so cringy.
Adding a title from the afterlife
in front of their name...
doesn't change who they were.
He died while facing
off against Yeon, right?
Along with that human woman.
Prior to entering
the wench's body,
he entrusted our family of
shamans a portion of his body.
I guess he never goes all in.
He's the opposite of me.
Anyway, are you ready?
A woman born in the year of
the sheep. A living sacrifice.
- And...
- Leave Yeon to me.
Go to the cemetery and pick
some evening primroses...
that grew on the flesh
and blood of corpses.
Let me ask you something.
Are you not brothers
with Lee Yeon?
We are brothers.
Half-brothers, to be exact.
If he awakes,
Lee Yeon will not survive.
- So?
- Why are you...
aiding your brother's enemy?
Come here.
- What is it?
- Pack your things and leave.
As soon as possible. Leave
this wretched island.
What?
I have a bad feeling about this.
What do you mean?
I'm saying you may
die if you stay here.
You said you weren't here to save
anyone. Why am I an exception?
That's none of your business.
I won't go home for a
reason I don't know.
So you can find the
person you came to meet.
I need to find out why
my mom and dad came here.
Why am I aiding the enemy
of my own blood relative?
It's a good practice not to fully
trust your business partner.
That's not what I meant.
Did you see Yeon while
he was a mountain spirit?
I heard about him
only through rumours.
What was the rumour?
The most merciless of the four
mountain spirits that rule the land.
No one could dare
exploit his woods,
and thus the Baekdudaegan
Mountain Range was always lush.
My brother was a mountain
spirit in name only.
He had no sense of altruism.
But you know,
even when we shared an apple,
he always gave me
the bigger half.
I still remember how
sweet that apple tasted.
Then why...
He used that tender hand with
which he sliced the apple...
to slice my stomach.
Obviously, it scarred me emotionally
much more than it did physically.
- Is that why...
- I'm a fox after all.
I need to return the favour.
I'm determined to go
to the Underworld...
together with Yeon.
Ms. Nam, I came to the
library as you asked.
But what am I looking
for? Dead bodies?
So... You mean chopped
up bodies, right?
Run a search for "Eohwa Island" and
find every incident or accident.
Call me if you find anything.
What are you looking for?
I'm bothered by something
the old ladies here said.
You can't tell anyone...
that you heard it from us.
This isn't the first time.
The human head...
Granny.
Did you hear anything about
that punk from before?
What punk?
Imoogi.
Didn't you...
end his life with
your own hands?
- I did.
- Then?
Just because. I'm just worried.
If by chance A Eum was
born again into this world,
I can't let that thing
coexist with her.
Such devotion.
- How would I not know if that...
- Okay, bye.
Look at this rude punk.
- Hi, Pyung Hee.
- Hello.
What are you reading?
What's wrong?
You're not Pyung Hee, are you?
How are you...
This is the best place to read.
Anyway. You're all alone.
He's nearby.
No, he isn't.
I can smell him
better than anyone.
Anyway. You're all alone.
He's nearby.
No, he isn't.
I can smell him
better than anyone.
You're the one who
killed the fishermen.
You shouldn't go around accusing
people. Do you have proof?
That book.
This? I like the classics.
"Moby Dick" is a novel
based on true events.
A whaling ship that sank
in the 19th century.
What happened to it?
It ate and was eaten.
Just like Pyung Hee's father.
Oh, my gosh. You scared
me half to death.
Look at this.
It's here too.
What are you doing?
I'll ask the questions.
I asked, what are you doing?
I said only I ask the questions.
If you don't answer my questions,
you'll never cast a net again.
Explain this painting.
But you know, if I were the
killer, I'd need a motive.
What was my motive? For justice?
I wasn't sure until a
moment ago, but I am now.
The fishermen's deaths
are like a fireworks show.
A fireworks show.
You're drawing attention
with outrageous incidents...
to distract us.
That's your motive.
- Why?
- Probably...
to hide the real reason
you're on this island.
Awesome. You're quite
smart for a human woman.
Since you got the answer right,
I should reward you.
You're looking for
your parents, right?
- Give me that.
- Why?
You saw them in your dream.
How do you know?
Just say the word.
Who knows?
I may have the answer.
Can you really find them?
That's right. Should
I grant you...
that wish?
I asked what this painting was.
It... It's the Dragon King.
He calms the storms...
and sends fish to fishermen.
There are big
rituals for him too.
- Liar.
- Fishing isn't like farming.
It isn't within human control.
- I'll just cut it.
- I'm telling the truth!
Where did you get this painting?
One of the village ladies
bought them from mainland...
for each and every household.
Just ask anyone!
Forget everything you just saw.
- How much is it?
- Goodness. When did you get here?
That'll be a dollar.
How many of you came as
part of the production team?
A pretty boy came by and
asked for directions...
to Pyung Hee's house.
Pretty boy?
I only need to hear one word.
"Yes."
I decline.
Why is that?
Foxes never stay in debt, right?
In other words, you
always collect on favours.
Loosen up, will you?
Why be so stiff when
it's just good old me?
Let me give you some advice
since that's how you feel.
Don't gamble with another's
tragedy just for kicks.
There's a word for people
like you, you know.
A colossal jerk.
You have no idea how much
I hate vulgar speech.
Call me that again
and I'll kill you.
Why me? Why are
you messing with...
I'm done talking to you.
Here's some advice in return.
Don't put too much
trust in Lee Yeon.
What do you mean?
When he finds what he wants,
you'll be begging for mercy.
He left.
You're still in one piece.
What did he say?
He said he could find
my parents for me.
And?
Even when I order pizza, I
never go for a half-and-half.
I always choose just one.
What are you getting at?
I turned him down...
because you're the
fox I'm betting on.
Smart lady.
Is that all?
Don't put too much
trust in Lee Yeon.
Yes, that's all.
Well, I'm famished.
How about you take your own
advice and leave the island?
- What?
- Your brother.
He's cooking up
some sort of event.
And that's what I'm waiting for.
Seriously?
Not a familiar face, right?
She's not domestic.
- Then?
- She's probably from abroad.
That explains her
sophisticated look.
How much in jewellery
is she wearing?
Who booked the table?
Ki Yu Ri. She's the director
of Moze Department Store.
She doesn't seem like
a self-made woman.
Maybe she won the lottery.
Foxes who reek of
money and power...
fall into one of
these two categories.
They either come from a prestigious
bloodline like Mr. Lee Yeon...
or they broke taboo
and stole a human life.
Sitting here like this
makes me wonder...
if all that happened
this morning was a dream.
If only life could be just
as uneventful every day.
Then settle in the countryside.
Don't you miss the nature?
Not really. There aren't
any department stores.
Also, I can't live
without black coffee...
and mint chocolate
ice cream anymore.
Some fox you are.
Life's the same for everyone.
Just because these ladies wear
baggy pants in floral prints...
doesn't mean they
have kind hearts.
Get digging, and you'll find
all sorts of dirty secrets.
Is that the case for you too?
I'm just curious as to
how your life has been...
for all those centuries.
What about you then?
Why have you been searching
for your parents all this time?
It's simple.
I miss them, that's all.
I miss my mom and dad.
Same here.
I'm waiting for the one I miss.
Your first love? Was it human...
or a fox?
Why did you part ways when
you still miss her this much?
I see you won't tell me.
The first being I loved was a
human girl who ended up dying.
It's why I'm still hung
up on her. Happy now?
But you said you're
waiting for her.
You're waiting for
someone who's dead?
She promised...
to be reborn.
Here. Clean up for me too.
Only the staff can enter.
Gosh, my bad.
I don't think it was a mistake.
Do I look like someone who
resorts to petty theft?
How about we exchange names?
We are of the same
species, after all.
I'm Yu Ri.
Technically, we're
not the same species.
I take it you're from Russia.
- Sharp, aren't you?
- How did you come to Korea?
- Were you...
- Yes, I was smuggled.
Have you been on a
nine-hour flight...
squeezed between
Makarov pistols before?
The moment we landed,
I wanted to blow the
smuggler's face off.
It doesn't sound so pleasant.
Which is why you can understand
how frustrating it is for me...
to hear people say...
that I'm not the self-made type.
Well, you see...
It's my duty to
confirm these facts.
You wish to know my
secret to success.
- Exactly.
- It's nothing big.
Get closer. Come on.
I'm sweet...
but also deadly.
- How could you let her take it?
- I'm doomed.
Without the necklace,
I can't understand what
animals are saying.
Serves you right for claiming
to be the greatest veterinarian.
A deadly thief?
There's nothing more pathetic...
than being blinded by
a woman's beauty...
But you also ruined your life by
falling for a beautiful woman.
What?
So what do I do?
What else? You know who
she is, so get it back.
I can't.
She carries a gun.
You're a fox, darn it.
How can a gun scare you?
You know I've been traumatized
after being shot in the tail...
by a hunter.
Just please get back here soon.
Stop whining and get
it back yourself!
Why is that branch broken?
It must've hurt.
I hope you grow well.
The wind is blowing
from the Northwest.
Something's coming.
Hey, Jae Hwan.
You found similar cases?
Who were the victims?
All four of them were
unidentified women.
When did it happen?
The very first case
occurred in 1954.
August 13.
In 1954?
Since immediately after
the end of the Korean War.
Something evil came to the
island riding a typhoon...
Tell me all the dates in order.
August 25, 1961.
September 6, 1979.
September 7, 1987.
The dates are really far apart,
but this is pretty much
a serial murder case.
- Which days of the week?
- I'll tell you in order.
Friday, Friday,
Thursday, and Monday.
It has nothing to
do with the days.
Between August and September...
Wait.
LUNAR CALENDAR: JULY 15, 1961
Year 1979...
LUNAR CALENDAR: JULY 15, 1979
Year 1987...
LUNAR CALENDAR: JULY 15, 1987
The lunar calendar.
They all happened on July 15
based on the lunar calendar.
If I'm correct, they all
happened on the same date.
What?
And today is that day.
Director Nam, you should
get out of that island.
What in the world
happened on this island?
Excuse me.
Weren't you on the boat
with Pyung Hee's father?
Two of the survivors
passed away.
Your life is in danger.
Excuse me!
Please hear me out!
Hold on!
Why are you running away?
Get lost, you ghost!
Don't kill him!
It's not that bad.
- What is that?
- It's a folk remedy.
It's hot.
Gosh, stop being a crybaby.
Your hand is so hot.
- It's burning hot.
- What...
What's this?
Long time no see, Yeon.
Who are you?
It's me. The person
you've been waiting for.
What?
But let me ask you something.
Why...
did you kill me?
Who are you?
You should've let me go.
What are you?
Our ill-fated relationship
would've ended...
if you hadn't
stopped the boat...
from crossing the Samdo River.
No.
That woman is born with a face
that only I can recognize.
And I don't see it in you.
You really...
don't know anything, Yeon.
It's hot.
What did you do to me?
It was really hot.
The scar is gone.
Who are you?
What kind of question is that?
Answer me.
- What's with you?
- Who are you?
It's me, Ji A. I'm Ji A.
Don't you remember anything?
You just...
Aren't we too old to play catch?
We hate each other too
much to play catch.
I actually meant to kill you.
The photo.
Run away.
What's going on?
Are you guys dating?
Hurry.
Hurry up and run.
- Get out of my way.
- No, just play with me.
This is domestic
violence, you know.
When a child doesn't behave,
it's best to give them a beating.
But because I failed to do that,
you ended up becoming a jerk.
You keep blaming it on me...
when you were the one who
turned me into an orphan.
I should get you a mouth
guard for Christmas this year.
Where's my cell phone?
Who are you?
I've never seen you here before.
I came from a broadcasting
station in Seoul.
Do you live here?
Yes.
Which way do I need to go
to go back to the village?
That path over
there is a shortcut.
Thank you.
By the way,
how long did you live here?
A very long time. I've
lived here a lot longer...
than what you might imagine.
Then by any chance,
have you ever...
seen these people?
This was taken here
many years ago.
Wait. Wasn't this
woman pregnant?
Yes, she was. Do you remember?
Did you talk to them?
Why did they come here?
Drink before it gets cold.
Okay.
The baby in her womb
was upside-down,
or the umbilical cord was
wrapped around its neck.
Anyway. They prayed to the
Dragon King in the cave...
for an easy labour and delivery.
The Dragon King?
He really answers prayers.
Even when Typhoon Sarah hit,
only our island was safe.
We used to hold huge rituals
for him back in the day.
Like the ritual for a big catch
before fishermen went out?
How does someone so young
know things like that?
When was the ritual?
During the Ghost Festival.
The Ghost Festival?
That's July 15th on
the lunar calendar.
And you performed
the ritual yourself.
This was the only
house on this island...
with a five-coloured flag.
SYMBOLIZING LIFE, DEATH,
DISEASE, WEALTH, AND ANCESTORS.
It means the owner is a shaman.
I do this for a living, you see.
And ma'am.
This pregnant woman in
the photo is a doctor.
She would've gone
to the hospital,
not a cave, if something
was wrong with the baby.
Sit back down. I'll
tell you everything.
You can tell it to the police.
Look, miss.
You can't leave
this place anyway.
I didn't drink your tea.
I don't eat or drink
things from strangers.
What's wrong with me?
It wasn't the tea,
but the incense.
Are you laughing?
That was plenty of time.
Do you still not get it?
Don't you know why she
ended up on this island?
- What?
- She's going to be a sacrifice.
You don't have much time.
Just so you know, she can't
take your call right now.
What happened?
Her scent is completely gone.
The sun will be setting soon.
Please hang in there just
a little while longer.
Just like you, your mom...
came voluntarily to this island.
Ever since she became pregnant,
she had the same
dream every night.
You tricked your mom...
while you were in her womb.
I am the original
mountain spirit,
the master of the
mountains and streams.
Lift this darkness
and lead me to her!
Maybe it has been too long.
It isn't working at all.
Let's go.
There's no point.
It was you.
The bodies of the dead
women found on this island.
They were all
precious sacrifices.
Give me a break.
Hey, lady. That was just murder.
Be a sacrifice.
You are a very special child.
You have no idea how
long I've been waiting.
Die. You must die.
You have to die.
No.
Die. You must die.
You have to die.
Halt!
Yeon.
Don't touch her.
I will tear out your limbs.
This has nothing to do with
the old master of the mountain.
Why don't you keep walking?
Says the living corpse.
Who was it...
that provided you with
longevity you don't deserve?
Tell me who you serve.
You can't stop me anyway.
The evening primrose
will keep you out.
Die!
Die.
Return to the earth.
How dare he!
What is it, my darling?
Yeon took a human life.
Can you walk?
If you lend me an arm.
What was that woman?
A human being.
One who wished to live longer.
I badly wanted to
clock her in the mouth.
So you say. You nearly
died just now, you know.
But I didn't.
Mr. Lee, I know it was
a desperate situation,
but what about the consequences?
Just hang up if you're going to nag.
I'll have to receive the punishment.
This is why you should never
get involved with a human girl.
This one in particular knows
about A Eum's past life.
What? The director lady?
I don't know what she is, but
I'll be keeping my eye on her.
Your love story is more
than just famous among us.
It's probably your
brother playing tricks.
The fruit corner will
begin its closing sale.
A special discount price.
It'll never be this price again.
Where are you? The supermarket?
SPECIAL DISCOUNT,
NECTARINE, 2.152 DOLLARS
I needed a pick-me-up
after what had happened...
and this is my
very own paradise.
Did you take my
credit card again?
Hello? Mr. Lee? You're
breaking up. Mr. Lee!
Is this organic?
Alcohol?
I'm too much of a human...
to easily fall asleep
after such an event.
Join me.
I never said anything since it
could make me seem old-fashioned,
but you're too informal with me
when you don't even know my age.
Those over 60 are universally
considered as grandpas.
Be as informal as you like.
Why do you keep saving me?
3.5 million deaths
don't faze you at all,
so why?
Do I have something...
that you're looking for?
I have countless
questions on my mind,
but I'll leave them be for now.
I'll say this though.
Thanks, Yeon.
The 9-year-old me and
the 30-year-old me...
both lived thanks to you.
You see,
I may not be able to kick
butt and control the weather,
but I'll return
the favour someday.
You can count on
me to protect you.
Do you perhaps
have the ability...
to duplicate this
bottle of soju?
Like the Miracle of
the Loaves and Fishes?
Yes.
I'm not Jesus, you know.
Just drink what you have.
Are you leaving on
the first boat out?
I see you're limping.
You sacrificed your leg
to avenge your father.
How did you...
You were lucky enough to
live to tell the tale.
Don't ever resort to
cursing people again.
Karma can sting.
It's empty.
- What?
- Everyone's gone.
What do mean?
It's as if the entire
village vanished.
Not even a human
shadow is in sight.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
It's the place where
evil spirits come and go.
How dare you! What
were you thinking?
Why do you hate your
older brother so much?
If you want to live,
you'd better not
fall asleep tonight.
What do you want from me?
Your lady won't get to live
a long life this time either.
The Underworld of Knives. Then
I'll be able to leave today.
Or you might never
be able to leave.