LEE DONG WOOK
CHO BO AH
KIM BEOM
KIM JUNG NAN, AHN GIL GANG
HWANG HEE, KIM YONG JI
THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES VIRTUAL
AND INDIRECT ADVERTISEMENTS.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
PLEASE HIT THE SLATE!
CLAPPING
- Do I need to clap again?
- That's fine.
- Okay.
- Let's begin.
We'll begin now.
YU RI IS WAITING FOR SOMEONE.
WHY IS HE TAKING SO LONG?
WHO IS THE OWNER OF THIS CHAIR?
HER PATIENCE WEARS THIN.
Darn it. What time is it?
Why isn't he here yet?
I'm sorry. Did you wait long?
Do you want to die?
I'm sorry.
A wounded cat came to my hospital,
so I was treating its leg.
The cat was a bit chatty,
so I was hearing it out.
Turn on the TV already.
Lee Rang will appear
at any moment now.
I almost missed the premiere.
Tale of the Nine Tailed
has the highest ratings these days.
I can't miss any of it.
Applaud.
IT'S THE MOST POPULAR
WEDNESDAY-THURSDAY DRAMA.
Tale of the Nine Tailed
is a 600-year-old epic of fate.
Come join us.
That was random.
A 600-year-old legend awakens.
15-minute summary
of the Tale of the Nine Tailed.
Once a fox turns 100,
it can become a beautiful woman,
or it can become a man
to have relations with a woman.
A fox that lived for 1,000 years
makes a connection with the sky,
becoming a "chunho".
Its extraordinary abilities
equal that of a shaman.
They can see things many miles away.
Nine-tailed foxes
are legendary creatures.
NINE-TAILED FOXES
ARE LEGENDARY CREATURES.
However, they have adapted
to the human world now.
- Exactly. I got my hair done today.
- It's all wet.
WHY DID HE VISIT A WEDDING HALL?
After consuming so many livers
of your foster parents' and men's,
you don't deserve to have
a happy ending.
HE MUST PUNISH A FOX
FOR HER EVIL DEEDS.
Lee Yeon, a former mountain spirit,
has been using his skills...
to punish the wicked
who have tainted this world.
Have you heard this saying before?
"A fox's misbehavior
eventually catches up to them."
Of course he went in by himself,
but why is he walking out alone?
Ji A runs into him by coincidence.
Being a producer, she smells
something fishy about him.
Then one man visits her.
Yeou Gogae.
That's where I saw him.
How can I believe you?
SHOULD SHE BELIEVE HIM?
TO FIND OUT WHO LEE YEON IS,
JI A GOES TO A BUS STOP.
A condition?
WILL LEE YEON APPEAR?
Half doubting,
she goes to the address.
It's him.
Ji A sees Lee Yeon again.
SHE MISSES THE BUS,
AND THEY FAIL TO MEET.
Unfortunately, the bus he was on
gets in an accident.
Hey. Can you hear me?
There was only one survivor.
What did he do?
HOW DOES THE ONLY SURVIVOR
REMEMBER THE INCIDENT?
He tried to kill me.
The bus to your house
was on the opposite side.
SHE SEEMS SUSPICIOUS!
I'm someone you know...
THE SURVIVOR SHOWS HIS TRUE FACE.
THIS WAS ALL LEE RANG'S TRAP.
- Do you think you can...
- Ji A was willing to...
put herself in danger
to meet Lee Yeon again.
JI A RISKS HER LIFE
IN ORDER TO MEET LEE YEON.
"Bait"?
- Did you miss me?
- Do you want to die, brother?
What did she want to ask Lee Yeon?
JI A MEETS LEE YEON AGAIN
WITH THE VIDEO SHE TOOK SECRETLY.
Why did she chase Lee Yeon
so persistently?
WHY DID JI A CHASE LEE YEON
SO PERSISTENTLY?
Did you test me?
I've been waiting for you.
21 YEARS AGO, YEOU GOGAE
21 years ago, Ji A was spending
a happy birthday with her parents.
However...
Due to an accident at Yeou Gogae,
she lost both of her parents.
And she experiences...
something very bizarre after that.
SOMETHING VERY FRIGHTENING
AND BIZARRE HAPPENS.
Forget everything you saw today.
LEE YEON SAVES JI A'S LIFE
AND TRIES TO ERASE HER MEMORY.
If you don't...
You mean they are alive?
HER PARENTS ARE ALIVE SOMEWHERE?
I don't know about that.
Ji A wants to use Lee Yeon
to find her missing parents.
Meanwhile, the scull of a fisherman
is discovered at a remote island.
The shape of the gold casing...
Could it be Mr. Seo?
Ji A heads to the island...
to find clues about
her parents' disappearance.
And Lee Yeon goes to
the same island...
to find clues about Ah Eum,
who has been reincarnated.
This was where they took this photo.
WHY DID JI A'S PARENTS
COME TO THIS ISLAND?
This wasn't the first time.
I'm talking about human heads.
It seems like they are trying
to hide something.
- And...
- I didn't do it. It wasn't me.
The sailors act suspiciously.
THE SAILORS ACT SUSPICIOUSLY.
Excuse me.
WHAT HAPPENED ON THIS ISLAND?
Hey!
JI A GETS INJURED
WHILE CHASING AFTER THE TRUTH.
Was it because of something
inside her?
- Something strange happens to Ji A.
- What is this?
It's been a while, Lee Yeon.
Who are you?
WHY DID JI A SUDDENLY CHANGE?
You really...
don't know anything.
SHE SAYS SOMETHING STRANGE
AND RETURNS TO NORMAL.
What have you done to me?
The scar disappeared.
The islanders begin to die
as if they've been cursed.
THE ISLANDERS BEGIN TO DIE
AS IF THEY'VE BEEN CURSED.
They were all on the same boat
with the dead sailor.
THEY WERE ALL ON THE SAME BOAT
WITH THE DEAD SAILOR.
And they all served the Dragon King.
WHAT DID THE DRAWING OF
THE DRAGON KING MEAN?
The sailors were shipwrecked.
THIS IS WHAT REALLY HAPPENED!
I'm hungry.
THE TRAGEDY STARTED AS THEY
BEGAN TO LOSE THEIR MINDS.
- No.
- I won't die here!
The shadow of misfortune
from the island...
was slowly approaching them.
DID THE DEAD SAILORS
WORSHIP IMOOGI?
This is a snake, not a dragon.
Imoogi.
I have a bad feeling.
LEE YEON SENSES A BAD FEELING
ON THE ISLAND.
I mean, this is the perfect place
to die.
You have to die.
Stop!
Do you know that a bad feeling
is hardly ever wrong?
HIS BAD FEELING EVENTUALLY
BECOMES TRUE.
Don't touch her.
I will rip you apart.
You can't stop me anyway.
We're surrounded
by evening primroses.
All of this was a plan
to offer Ji A as a sacrifice...
to bring back Imoogi.
LEE YEON USES HIS ABILITY AS
A MOUNTAIN SPIRIT TO SAVE HER.
- Die!
- Return to the earth.
Lee Yeon saves Ji A's life again
just like 21 years ago.
LEE YEON SAVES HER LIFE AGAIN.
Yeon killed a human.
However, there was something
they didn't know.
That something evil was born
on the island that day.
Your obsession will bring
a huge disaster.
To you...
LEE YEON AND JI A WERE NOT FATED
TO MEET AGAIN.
Is this what you call fate?
Despite the frightening warning,
they find themselves
attracted to each other.
THEY FIND THEMSELVES
ATTRACTED TO EACH OTHER.
Lee Yeon received punishment
for killing a human...
and left Ji A for a while.
- Give us your body.
At that moment,
Ji A falls in danger once again.
JI A IS ATTACKED BY YOUNG GHOSTS.
Lee Yeon senses
that she's in danger,
and risks his life
in order to return sooner...
by heading to
The Underworld of Knives.
It's that her death...
will pierce deeper into my flesh...
than these blades cutting me now.
I'll make sure to protect you.
- Give us your body.
LEE YEON THROWS HIMSELF
TO SAVE JI A AND FALLS.
Don't die...
because of me.
Ji A cries after Lee Yeon
sacrifices himself to save her.
JI A BEGINS TO CRY.
At that moment,
something unbelievable happens.
THE FOX MARBLE INSIDE JI A
IS AWAKENED.
I found you.
Meanwhile, who is this boy...
sitting in this ominous room?
The babysitter turns into a mummy
as soon as Imoogi touches her.
IMOOGI KILLS HUMANS
TO GROW BIGGER.
Lee Yeon gazes romantically
at Ji A...
as if he doesn't know anything.
Actually, they were soulmates
who were fated 600 years ago.
THEY WERE SOULMATES
FROM 600 YEARS AGO.
In order to find out the truth
about Yeou Gogae,
they go to meet
the district magistrate.
WHAT KIND OF SURPRISING TRUTH
DO THEY FIND HERE?
Your parents weren't the target.
- What?
- The real target was the daughter.
WHO WAS THE ONE
THAT THREATENED JI A'S LIFE?
MEANWHILE, LEE RANG GOES TO
A SHAMAN...
TO FIND THE TIGER'S EYEBROWS.
What are you...
LEE YEON IS SUDDENLY SUCKED INTO
THE POUCH.
Lee Rang wanted the tiger's eyebrows
that showed one's previous life...
and sells Lee Yeon to the shaman.
Give me the fox marble.
JI A SELLS THE FOX MARBLE
TO SAVE LEE YEON.
The deal...
is done.
What?
Was it because the fox marble
was gone?
Imoogi shows itself to Ji A
that night.
IMOOGI SHOWS ITSELF TO JI A.
Hello.
Something strange begins to happen
to Ji A's body.
JI A HAS SCALES ON HER BODY AGAIN!
Hello.
A NEW BABYSITTER ARRIVES
AT THE PRESIDENT'S HOUSE.
BUT SHE WAS MERELY AN OFFERING
FOR IMOOGI TO GROW STRONGER.
Imoogi grows up quickly
by eating human beings...
and finally becomes
a fully grown man.
IMOOGI FINALLY BECOMES
A FULLY GROWN MAN.
And second, never go upstairs.
Is someone up there?
Despite the president's warning,
Ji A walks toward Imoogi
as if she is bewitched.
A nail?
Imoogi isn't the only thing
that deludes her.
Wear them and look in the mirror.
WHAT IS JI A'S PREVIOUS LIFE...
SHE SEES THROUGH
THE TIGER'S EYEBROWS?
This woman means nothing to me.
Did you not think
that I could've used her as bait...
to wake you up?
Lee Yeon.
600 YEARS AGO, AH EUM WAS KILLED
BY YEON, THE MAN SHE LOVED.
I was only...
a sacrifice.
WHO'S THE JUICE LADY
THAT CAME TO SEE LEE RANG?
Imoogi uses Ouduksini...
to lure Lee Rang
into the world of subconsciousness.
It's a starving ghost.
LEE RANG WAS TRAPPED IN
THE FOREST OF STARVING GHOSTS...
WHICH IS WHERE HE WAS TRAUMATIZED
AS A LITTLE KID.
JI A COULDN'T AVOID
OUDUKSINI EITHER.
I guess it must be Yeou Gogae.
Dad, can't you hear me?
I said, stop the car.
The woman he loved
was trapped in Yeou Gogae.
And his little brother was trapped
in the Forest of Starving Ghosts.
One leads you to your brother,
and the other to your girlfriend.
IMOOGI TESTS LEE YEON BY
PUTTING HIS LOVED ONES IN DANGER.
Which one will you choose?
Neither of them has much time.
WHOM WILL LEE YEON CHOOSE TO SAVE?
Whom do you think he'll choose?
Hey, kid!
Lee Yeon heads to the Forest
of Starving Ghosts to save Lee Rang.
Yeon?
Ji A?
Meanwhile, Ji A was caught...
- in a sweet illusion.
- Ji A.
If this is just a dream,
please don't wake up.
This is good.
Whose face was that?
This is bad.
If she doesn't get out on time,
she'll be trapped in there forever.
MEANWHILE, YEON AND RANG ARE
FIGHTING THE STARVING GHOSTS.
No!
Lee Yeon rescues his brother
but fails to escape himself.
You must.
Be aware of your surroundings
and why you're there.
Thanks, Lee Yeon.
JI A REMEMBERS LEE YEON AND ESCAPES
FROM HER SUBCONSCIOUSNESS.
Lee Yeon.
It was so hard
to get you to come here.
IMOOGI AND YEON'S FIGHT
GOES BACK TO 600 YEARS AGO.
- What do you want?
- Not the likes of you.
This was actually a trap
set up by Lee Yeon to catch Imoogi.
I found him.
I'll come and get you soon.
You better wait.
- Repay me, Yeon.
- 600 years ago,
Ah Eum sacrificed her life
to save Lee Yeon.
AH EUM CHOSE DEATH BY MAKING YEON
REPAY HER IN ORDER TO SAVE HIM.
I promised...
that I would protect you.
After centuries,
they finally met each other again.
And their tragic past
doesn't stop them...
from falling in love again.
LEE YEON AND JI A PROMISE
TO LOVE EACH OTHER ETERNALLY.
Say hi. He's our new intern.
I look forward to working with you.
Meanwhile, Imoogi hides his identity
and approaches Ji A.
What?
And Ji A finds out about the enemy
who's always been nearby.
JI A FINDS OUT WHO THE ENEMY IS.
Do you know who
this nail belongs to?
Did you see her too?
WHO IS THIS MAN WHO'S BEEN
KEEPING HIS EYES ON HER ALL ALONG?
What do I look like to you?
A west capital traitor.
You took my parents, didn't you?
HE WAS THE GUY WHO CAUSED
THE ACCIDENT AT YEOU GOGAE.
Offer me the mountain spirit,
and I'll give you your parents.
We'll catch Imoogi.
Yeon and I will do it together.
Lee Yeon and Ji A decide to fight
against fate one more time.
THEY DECIDE TO FIGHT AGAINST
THEIR FATE ONCE MORE.
HOW CAN THEY CATCH IMOOGI?
LEE YEON STRIKES BACK
TO CATCH IMOOGI.
Imoogi befits water...
more than land.
The Imoogi you're looking for...
I'm not the main one.
IMOOGI'S MAIN BODY
WAS INSIDE JI A.
It's been a long time, Yeon.
Will they be able to turn things
back to normal?
She's mine.
Get out of there!
Imoogi is really tenacious.
He still can't let go of his greed
even after 600 years.
Should I go and take care of him?
What do you say?
No, he's unbelievably cruel.
You'll get hurt. It's too dangerous.
I'm sure Lee Rang and Lee Yeon...
will do what they can
to destroy Imoogi.
After all, they've made up.
They're on good terms these days.
They hated each other for 600 years.
That's because Lee Yeon
was blinded by love...
and ignored his little brother.
- Wait.
- You know that.
- You think he was blinded by love?
- Yes.
Lee Yeon and Ms. Nam are
destined to be together.
Don't talk about
their relationship so lightly.
Do you actually believe in fate?
I feel like you and I are also
destined to be together.
I don't think that applies to us.
Let's see which couples
were meant to be together.
Beware.
This could make your heart stop.
Let's take a look
at the love stories in this drama.
The couple who were destined
to meet after 600 years.
Lee Yeon and Ji A.
A fox never lets down the partner
they got together with.
Not until they die.
LEE YEON TRIES TO USE
HIS OLD POWERS...
IN ORDER TO FIND JI A.
- I really loved this scene.
- Me too.
I thought they'd lead him to her.
- But nothing happened.
- I guess it's been too long.
IT TOOK A WHILE, BUT HE FINALLY
GETS BACK HIS POWERS BACK.
Was this the first time
he showed himself...
- as a nine-tailed fox?
- He was so cool here.
- The CG was amazing.
- I know.
I didn't know they'd express
the nine tails that way.
- The CG team is...
- Hey, it's Sin Ju.
- What?
- I was really nervous back then.
It was my first scene with Lee Yeon.
- And Snail Bride?
- Yes.
IS SOMEONE LOOKING FOR LEE YEON,
THE NINE-TAILED FOX?
- Is this where Ji A comes in?
- I knew it. You're not a human.
JI A WAS DESPERATE
TO FIND LEE YEON.
- I've been waiting for you.
- "I've been waiting for you."
Isn't she gorgeous?
Be born again.
AH EUM AND LEE YEON'S LOVE
ENDS TRAGICALLY.
I'll make sure to find you.
- Isn't it so sad?
- It's really sad.
This scene was really sad.
And as I watched this scene,
I could see how Lee Yeon...
ended up with
such a complicated fate.
600 YEARS LATER, LEE YEON MEETS
JI A, WHO LOOKS JUST LIKE AH EUM.
- Please don't die.
- Isn't this when they realize...
that they both love each other?
Yes, it is.
It's also a very important scene...
because it's when Lee Yeon
realizes that Ms. Nam...
- is Ah Eum.
- Yes, that's right.
- He confirms it.
- Right.
I found you.
LEE YEON AND JI A SLOWLY START
EXPRESSING THEIR AFFECTION.
- That was so cute.
- I know.
You got me a mugwort bouquet.
It's just my taste.
Oh, that's it.
It's what he remembers
from 600 years ago.
- It's what Ah Eun did to him.
- I personally love...
how this drama
doesn't miss out on...
even the smallest details.
Before we found out that Ji A
was actually Ah Eum,
Ji A was shown...
as fearless and outspoken.
She was very brave.
But after Ah Eum overlaps with her,
she also showed how feminine
she could be, and that was nice.
Yes, she really does have
a lot of sides to her.
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
She looked beautiful here
at the folk village.
From what I know,
this was the first kissing scene...
between Ji A and Lee Yeon.
- This scene?
- Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
AUGUST 2020, THE SHOOT
OF LEE YEON AND JI A'S FIRST KISS
AFFECTIONATE
DO THEY FEEL HAPPY
JUST BY LOOKING AT EACH OTHER?
I bet it was really hot that day.
THE TWO FOXES ARE
EXTREMELY FOCUSED.
You look nice.
- Nice. I look handsome.
- Okay.
Did you hear that?
"Nice. I look handsome."
"Nice. Look at my broad shoulders."
It's the first time Ah Eum saves
the nine-tailed fox...
as a human being.
Do you remember what Lee Yeon said?
He doubted she could help him
since she was only human.
Action.
AH EUM, A HUMAN BEING,
HELPS A MOUNTAIN SPIRIT IN NEED.
- Great.
- Thank you.
Okay.
I have good eyesight,
so I'll watch from here.
I'll be honest. I can't see a thing.
As you watch them shoot,
you can see
that they look great together.
- They look really close.
- They do.
That melts into the scenes.
Otherwise, all those scenes
wouldn't come out so great.
This is weird too.
It feels like you don't even care.
It's all dry now.
- It's okay now.
- I was just kidding.
LEE YEON WAS ABLE TO ESCAPE
THANKS TO AH EUM'S HELP.
HE RUNS FOR HIS LIFE.
LEE YEON ALWAYS MAKES
THE STAFF LAUGH.
Let's try that again.
I was scared.
People might chase after me.
Okay.
LEE YEON AND JI A
SLOWLY GROW CLOSER TO EACH OTHER.
The man letting
his shoulder get drenched.
Talk about a cliche, right?
He's saying that
he'll always wait for her.
- Thanks, Yeon.
- And that he'll protect her.
His love couldn't be more innocent.
I'll stay here.
NOT WANTING TO LOSE HER AGAIN,
YEON DECIDES TO NEVER LEAVE HER.
Call it a minimum safety net.
SIN JU AND YU RI
LOSE THEMSELVES IN THE LOVE STORY.
LAUGHING
- When one can't sleep...
- "Ji A..."
- Think of the things you like.
- Gosh.
Like mint chocolate ice cream?
I...
Didn't this seem like
a scene from a fairy tale?
Yes.
They fall asleep while making
a list of what they like.
One sheep, two sheep...
Before I go to bed,
I keep picturing...
your face as well.
Did you cook?
As you can see,
Lee Yeon will do practically
anything for her.
And like this,
I'll check to see if she's alive.
Hey, she's breathing.
- Also...
- You know,
Dong Wook teases others and
plays pranks every chance he gets.
I know.
He loves to have fun.
Anyway, you said that you like...
the smell of freshly cooked rice.
That started with an "anyway".
We'll go again.
LAUGHING
- Don't you love Ji A's laughter?
- Yes.
It's boisterous.
And here...
ARE THEY DEBATING OVER
HORROR FILMS?
What kind of people
are unfazed by horror films?
It's a stress-reliever.
They must be opposites
when it comes to horror movies.
We're complete opposites.
That's a pretty scene.
- Right?
- Their size difference...
LEE YEON AND JI A'S LOVE DEEPENS.
That's what I thought.
I like you.
SIN JU'S TOUCHED.
When do you find Lee Yeon's gaze
to be most romantic?
I'm on Lee Rang's side,
so I've never thought
of Lee Yeon to be nice.
But if I have to choose a moment...
Don't. I'm the only one
you should see.
Your eyes should be for Sin Ju.
I've known Lee Yeon for 600 years...
which is why I know
his coolest gaze.
He sometimes gazes down
with his chin tilted upwards.
You'll see that his red lips
are slightly parted.
Could you try it on camera?
SAME EXPRESSION, DIFFERENT FEELING
That's the gaze.
LAUGHING
I like her.
It's Imoogi!
How dare you?
LEE YEON AND IMOOGI DUEL
TO SEAL JI A'S FATE.
- How cool.
- Ms. Nam.
Yes?
IMOOGI APPROACHES JI A
WHILE HIDING HIS IDENTITY.
Don't act like a man in front of me.
To me, you're
just my parents' enemy.
DOES JI A ALREADY KNOW EVERYTHING?
I just got goosebumps!
Let me see.
THE SCENE SENT CHILLS DOWN
THE RUSSIAN FOX'S SPINE.
He speaks in a completely
different way now.
You look defenseless.
You can't kill me.
It's true.
No!
Lee Yeon should've seen this.
Him kissing the back of her hand.
He wouldn't have let it slide.
Ji A...
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO THE COUPLE
NOW THAT IMOOGI'S IN THE PICTURE?
What did you think
of their best scenes?
My favorite scene is the one
with Lee Yeon at the crosswalk.
Me too!
Jinx?
- With the red umbrella?
- Yes.
He lifts up the umbrella
to see her in front of her.
He's about to approach her
when she tells him not to.
- She goes to him instead.
- I'll come to you.
"I've been waiting for you too."
This is the expression
that Lee Yeon held.
And don't forget the rain.
- Cool, right?
- He's the Master of Romance.
Their chemistry explodes on screen.
Lee Yeon and Lee Rang show
an unorthodox brotherly love.
Nice.
It's Lee Yeon and Lee Rang.
- It's Lee Rang. I mean, Mr. Lee.
- They're indeed brothers.
LEE YEON AND LEE RANG ARE KNOWN
TO BE AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
"Tell me. I'm so eager to know."
You're acting
like you lack affection.
This conversation doesn't
seem important, but it is.
"You're acting
like you lack affection."
Just because of a girl,
you gave up on being a spirit and
turned your back on the mountain.
Yes.
- " I gave up on you."
- I gave up on you.
THEY'RE ALWAYS AT
EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
THE TWO BROTHERS
FIGHT OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
- Nice.
- Check out the action.
Their action scenes
were my favorite.
I love when they duel...
and when they fight
on the same side.
How long has it been?
- Baby fox, Lee Rang.
- You were alive?
I didn't hear from you since
you left for the Styx.
I'm on the verge of tears too.
THE EVENT THAT PULLED
THE BROTHERS APART
Raise your sword.
What are you talking about?
In my opinion, this is the scene...
that's most important
in the brothers' saga.
- Yes, I agree.
- Lee Rang was a sinner...
who had to be punished
by a mountain spirit...
that was Lee Yeon.
But he was also a big brother
who cared for his sibling.
He's someone he wished to protect.
He must've been torn
between those two roles.
The rift between them
that lasted 600 years...
was caused by this event.
I think I spotted a tear.
Please add a drop
with computer graphics.
SEPTEMBER 2020,
FILMING FLASHBACK SCENE
They look cute on set though.
Baby fox.
I'm sure you know that people
call Lee Rang as the baby fox.
Of course.
Do I fall to my knees
after his sword goes through me?
Yes, please.
He needs to get on his knees.
- How considerate of Dong Wook.
- It might hurt.
Action!
THANKS TO YEON,
RANG'S KNEES DON'T GET HURT.
MY BROTHER'S THE BEST!
RANG IS TRAPPED
IN THE FOREST OF STARVING GHOSTS.
- The Forest of Starving Ghosts.
Hey, kid!
Gosh, this moment.
The first full moon of
the lunar new year. Jwibulnori.
Wasn't this scene incredible?
- They worked really hard.
- With their backs to each other's.
And you wet the bed that night.
For three years after that,
- Be quiet.
- I called you a bed wetter!
"Be quiet."
- Action!
- They sure had it rough.
I heard that it took
three weeks to film...
all the scenes needed in the woods.
THEY SPENT 3 WEEKS
FILMING IN THE WOODS.
It must've been difficult
due to the summer heat.
Yeon and Rang.
It was possible
because it was those two.
RANG WAS INJURED AFTER
THE ATTACK OF THE STARVING GHOSTS.
HE ANNOUNCES THAT HE'S GIVING UP!
I'm tired of dragging this leg along
with me.
- So?
- Go to your woman.
- This scene...
- It's a great one.
Personally, it's my favorite scene.
You still give up easily...
- and whine like a baby.
- My favorite.
How could life and death be
so simple to you?
I shouldn't have come.
That's the expression of his
that I love.
- I see.
- Right?
Didn't I mimic it perfectly?
ONCE AGAIN,
THEY LOOK COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
YEON'S LINE THAT BROUGHT YU RI
AND THE VIEWERS TO TEARS.
"I have never missed a target."
Think carefully about
how you survived...
with that stupid head of yours.
- Will you keep it down?
- Gosh.
WHAT DOES RANG THINK
IS THE BROTHERS' BEST SCENE?
Every scene to me
seemed like the best...
which is why I'm finding it hard
to choose just one.
But the scene in
the Forest of Starving Ghosts...
where Lee Yeon...
told Rang the ultimate truth...
is most memorable to me.
"I have never missed a target."
The emotions I felt when I heard...
that he had never missed a target...
and the way we interacted...
make that particular scene
my favorite.
You see, foxes...
They can change form!
- We can change forms.
- "We can change forms."
Leave my brother alone...
or I might just actually kill you.
Lee Yeon and Lee Rang
look great together, don't they?
Yes, they look like actual brothers.
Even though they're
arguing once again,
they look good together.
That's how they are
in real life too.
Exactly.
This is so cool,
but what about me? What about us?
- Let's take a look!
- Here we go.
The sweet but scary,
Sin Ju and Yu Ri.
If a fox has money and power,
it's one or the other.
THEIR THRILLING FIRST ENCOUNTER
HAPPENS AT SNAIL BRIDE.
Someone who stole a human's life.
I must be a fox who
falls in love at first sight.
I remember falling for you
at the Korean restaurant that day...
while eating my lunch.
- I like those who are handsome.
- Really?
That must be why you like me.
- I guess.
- Thanks for saying so.
You owe me now.
LOVE IS IN THE AIR.
Shall we introduce each other
since we're the same species?
Why are you laughing?
I can't help it
when I think of this moment.
This was before
we got to know each other.
Exactly. We were
practically strangers.
I'm sweet like this.
We had to smooch
on the first day we met.
Right, we smooched.
- Here?
- Yes, you smooched me.
SIN JU AND YU RI'S FIRST ENCOUNTER
IS INTENSE.
YU RI APPROACHES HIM
INTENTIONALLY.
We met for the first time
at the vet.
What we love so much...
is this background music
whenever we appear.
I agree.
THEY'RE MESMERIZED BY THE MUSIC.
HE SYMPATHIZES WITH HER PAIN.
So this was when you first gazed
at me so melancholically.
Many comments were
about your melancholic gaze.
Here's the gaze.
BECOME ENCHANTED BY HIS GAZE.
YU RI BRINGS A WOUNDED DOG
TO SIN JU.
This was when we met...
- for the second time.
- A dog thief?
I realize that not only are you
beautiful on the outside...
but also on the inside.
This was when...
I also realized that you were...
a nice fox.
- What are you doing here?
- I have something to discuss.
I was shocked because I thought
Anastasia had died.
- Were you?
- Yes.
Check out that sweet music.
- Do you hear it?
- I do.
I'll look forward to it.
This was my first time
smooching you,
and I was so nervous.
What? I'm going to kill you!
See you later.
We rarely made bloopers,
don't you think?
We did shoot the same scenes
over and over again.
- Weren't those bloopers?
- Not at all.
Then what's a blooper?
When the director says, "Cut"?
NG!
That rarely happened.
See? I'm right.
- Yes.
- We were the best partners.
Let's continue.
What brings you here, Yu Ri?
Tell us the truth now.
Why were you craving a drink?
Me? I was thirsty.
Okay.
What? Where is this zoo?
SIN JU BECOMES ENRAGED
AFTER HEARING ABOUT YU RI'S ABUSE.
How could he beat you up?
You're so manly.
- What? I'm sorry.
- Do you want to sleep with me?
- What?
- Sleep with me.
There are different stages
to say "I like you".
It's the same music again.
ARE THESE TWO FOXES FLIRTING?
You could ask me to date you.
Perhaps we can say that today
will be our first day as a couple.
Let's skip what's unnecessary.
That was an amazing line.
This must be behind the scenes.
Am I too dark-skinned to be seen?
I can only see my yellow shirt.
I can see your teeth, though.
You're so harsh. You are!
We weren't that close back then.
Yes, we were.
You could ask me to date you.
THEY IMPROVISED THIS SCENE.
Let's skip what's unnecessary.
THEY'RE EMBARRASSED.
Why didn't they air this part?
- It was funny.
- Why didn't they?
THIS COUPLE MAKES US SMILE.
They're all embarrassed.
You're good at cooking too.
I thought you'd be homesick.
I'm good at it.
I know this smell.
- In real life?
- Yes.
I'm good at cooking ramyeon.
I mean...
IS SIN JU PROPOSING TO HER?
I'm furious again.
You always get mad.
To be honest,
you diss me a lot.
- When?
- In that scene as well.
You say that I have
no family or friends.
You call me a necklace thief.
This is my first time
in a relationship.
Do you think
our love will come true?
I'm not sure.
I really want that to happen,
but it's really not up to me.
It depends on how you go about this.
She always plays so hard to get.
But then again, this is her charm.
Our drama isn't only filled
with lovey-dovey scenes.
- There are...
- What else is there?
- many scary scenes as well.
- I'm really terrified.
- There are various goblins.
- Native ones?
Yes.
- I'm so terrified.
- Me too.
- I can't watch those scenes alone.
- Me neither.
Can you watch them with me?
Let's watch them separately.
A BRIDE IN A SNOW-WHITE DRESS
She's the first goblin to appear.
- Gosh.
- Gosh, that scene.
I'm really scared.
Those young ghosts terrified me.
Seriously.
What's the name of that goblin...
- that ate coins?
- Bulgasalyi.
Bulgasalyi.
Starving ghosts.
- Grandpa Jangseung.
Ouduksini.
Don't be bewitched.
List of native goblins on the drama.
Which goblin scares you the most?
The young ghosts.
- I...
- The one that goes...
- like this?
- Don't mimic them.
Stop it.
Don't.
Stop.
HE'S SULKY.
I am the sole emcee
of Tale of the Nine Tailed...
LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT THE NATIVE GOBLINS.
A MYSTERIOUS-LOOKING
OLD MAN APPEARS.
Are you coming or not?
I am. Just a minute.
What scared me the most...
was that he was on Ji A's back.
He's extremely heavy.
He slowly choked her
and weighed her down.
He was a kind ghost.
- He saved her life.
- He did.
In exchange for some makgeolli.
SHE'S FIXATED ON THE MONITOR.
That's so terrifying.
CHILLS RUN DOWN HER SPINE.
THE OLD MAN STANDS UP AS SOON
AS THEY ARRIVE AT THE VILLAGE.
We're here.
You should cut down on drinking.
How cute.
- She doesn't seem to be acting.
- Right.
She's exhausted.
WHO IS THIS OLD MAN
WHO SAVED JI A'S LIFE?
AFTER DROPPING HIM OFF,
JI A HURRIEDLY LOOKS FOR A TAXI.
LOOKING AROUND
- Sir, there was a man behind me.
- Who?
I only saw you.
These scenes are scary.
IN THE PLACE
WHERE HE HAS DISAPPEARED...
- That's a jangseung.
- It's fun to learn...
about our native goblins.
I think it's one of the factors
that makes our drama great.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
IS FULL OF EXTRAORDINARY CHARMS.
GRANDPA JANGSEUNG
IS THE VILLAGE'S GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- This scene was...
- This scene.
How do I put it? It was bizarre.
He gobbled up those coins.
THIS BULGASALYI GOBBLED UP IRON.
He's good.
THIS BULGASALYI IS DOING
A COIN MUKBANG.
Bulgasalyi.
Lee Yeon saves her again.
He beats the goblin to a pulp.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN
TO THIS EVER-HUNGRY GOBLIN?
This scene was full of action.
BULGASALYI IS A KILLER
WHO EATS COINS.
THIS FUNERAL HALL FEELS SPOOKY.
I hate this. It's so terrifying.
Guys, I'm sorry.
You're both so beautiful,
but this scene is too scary.
I was terrified here
when they showed...
the children's portraits.
THIS FAMOUS SCENE GIVES THEM
GOOSEBUMPS EVEN TO THIS DAY.
This scene gave me goosebumps.
This scene.
Those innocent children were smiling
while doing that.
It was really terrifying.
It must've been difficult
to go to bed that night.
HE APOLOGIZES TO THE VIEWERS.
We're sorry.
Give us your body.
We want this body.
"Give us your body.
We want this body."
"Give us your body."
That scene.
- Give us your body.
WHY ARE THEY STILL ON EARTH?
You molested them, didn't you?
THE SISTERS DIED INNOCENT DEATHS
BECAUSE OF THEIR UNCLE.
- Goodness.
- I was so drunk that day.
- I didn't mean...
- You...
- filthy animal!
- The police are on their way.
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
Gosh.
- They...
- Their grudge was relieved.
Right.
AT TIMES, HUMANS ARE THE SCARIEST.
THESE CHILDREN HAD A GRUDGE.
There's a reason.
WHICH NATIVE GOBLIN IS NEXT?
- The Forest of Starving Ghosts.
- It's the starving ghosts.
It's a starving ghost.
How did you feel
when you saw them...
- I was terrified.
- for the first time?
They were so fast.
THE STARVING GHOSTS CHASE
AFTER LEE RANG.
- There are two of them.
- Aren't they so fast?
HE RUNS FOR HIS LIFE.
They keep on coming back to life.
Were starving ghosts always strong?
You should never set foot in there
to begin with.
It's either that,
or you should be
the number-one starving ghost.
SHE BLURTS OUT NONSENSE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DREAM ABOUT THEM!
THESE STARVING GHOSTS NEVER DIE.
Vegetable juice lady ghost story?
THIS NATIVE GOBLIN
WAS THE MOST SEARCHED.
Personally, she was
the second scariest goblin.
IF YOU GET BEWITCHED BY HER,
YOU CAN HEAR MUSIC.
This is the song.
GATEKEEPER, OPEN THE GATE
I DON'T HAVE A KEY
LISTEN TO THE LYRICS CAREFULLY.
Right.
One side doesn't have the key...
while the other side
can't find the door.
Jae Hwan explains...
What are you doing?
What are you... Don't!
- Sin Ju.
- What?
What is your biggest fear?
- Mine?
- Let's see.
WHAT IS HE THE MOST AFRAID OF?
- Could it be pistols?
- Pistols?
HE WAS COMPLETELY SUBDUED
BY YU RI'S SWEET AND SCARY CHARMS.
THEY SHARE A FRIGHTENING MEMORY
ABOUT PISTOLS.
- Gatekeeper, open the gate
- Stop that. I'm scared.
Excuse me.
THIS VEGETABLE JUICE LADY
HAS A FRIENDLY SMILE.
Come on.
BUT SHE SEEMS SUSPICIOUS.
Miss.
THIS OUDUKSINI IN DISGUISE
HAS A SIGNATURE LINE.
WHAT IS YOUR BIGGEST FEAR?
She was the most-searched word
on the internet.
Do you remember?
SHE MADE A HUGE IMPACT
WITH HER CHARISMA.
She was so scary.
OUDUKSINI USED PEOPLE'S FEAR.
That song sounds so creepy.
You're a nine-tailed fox
who loved a human.
You'll end up...
making that woman die
with your hands.
SHE CURSES HIM
UNTIL THE LAST MOMENT.
Hey, lady. You should worry about
your own destiny.
Do you know how much I waited
to see this?
I bet all the viewers were tricked
by Lee Yeon.
You probably thought...
Come here!
LEE YEON TRAPPED HIMSELF ON PURPOSE
TO CATCH OUDUKSINI.
he was lost in
the Forest of Starving Ghosts.
That was his plan to lure her.
He was just pretending to be lost.
The more goblins there are,
the more Lee Yeon suffers.
I really hate that!
A NATIVE GOBLIN THAT USES
ONE'S DARKEST FEAR, OUDUKSINI
THE STRONGEST GOBLIN
IS FINALLY COMING!
This is so scary.
- It's Imoogi.
- His acting is awesome.
He's so scary.
He eats human beings.
And the door opens right here...
Gosh, it's the first time
Imoogi shows itself as an adult.
It had a strong impact.
It was I who should've been...
FOCUSED
WHY DID IMOOGI COME BACK
AFTER 600 YEARS?
- Does that mean...
- I'll become a mountain spirit...
and take her as my bride.
Gosh, Imoogi's greed is endless.
He and his ambition.
IMOOGI CAN CONTROL PEOPLE'S MINDS.
We're fated to be together.
Disappear. Get lost!
Look closely.
THE GOBLIN THAT'S ILL-FATED
WITH LEE YEON AND JI A
I'll make a reasonable offer.
THE MOST POWERFUL
NATIVE GOBLIN, IMOOGI!
DO NOT LET THEM DECEIVE YOU!
Imoogi isn't frightening...
because he's a ghost or something.
It feels like he could be
really around us somewhere.
He feels like an actual criminal
who could be around us.
- Really?
- Yes, to me.
You're right. He's so hard to read.
Most goblins usually say
they're goblins...
and make it obvious.
But Imoogi is different.
SMILING
Why are you so pretty?
YU RI IS ALWAYS PRETTY.
But it would be so hard
for Lee Yeon...
if he kills all the goblins
on his own.
So there are people who help him.
- Ji A.
- There's Ji A.
- And Lee Rang.
- There's Lee Rang.
- There's also Hyuneuiong.
- Oh, the deities!
- The deities.
- That's right.
We have some reliable deities
on our side.
- Shall we see them?
- It's time to meet them.
Let's see them now.
Let's meet the deities that protect
Lee Yeon.
THE COUPLE THAT PROTECTS
THE AFTERLIFE IMMIGRATION OFFICE
TALEUIPA AND HYUNEUIONG
- Don't make a fuss.
- Taleuipa and Hyuneuiong.
Lee Yeon must never hear of this.
Taleuipa is so scary.
She's very powerful too.
She's suppressing her power.
- She can do anything.
- I don't even want to...
go near the
Afterlife Immigration Office.
Because I've committed so many sins.
I'll be thrown into The Underworld
no matter what.
I never want to go near there.
How dare you!
TALEUIPA WITNESSED LEE YEON'S
TRAGIC LOVE 600 YEARS AGO.
Have you ever worked with
actress Kim Jung Nan?
- No, never.
- Never?
I'll go straight to the fiery pit
as soon as I meet her.
STRAIGHT TO THE FIERY PIT?
- You committed many sins?
- Yes. I'm a sinner.
- She's usually very kind though.
- Really?
She's so sweet, like this.
SHE'S AN ANGEL THAT SHARES SNACKS
WITH THE STAFF.
Now it's time to meet
the deities of The Underworld...
HYUNEUIONG IS
TALEUIPA'S HUSBAND...
WHO MEASURES THE WEIGHT
OF THE DEAD'S SINS.
Come on, no need to be afraid.
HE KINDLY SHOWS THE WAY
TO THE UNDERWORLD...
FOR THOSE WHO HAVE DIED.
Do you know King Yeomra?
My wife over there is
King Yeomra's sister.
Isn't Hyuneuiong and
Taleuipa's relationship so funny?
- They're so cute.
- I know.
Hyuneuiong always wants to be loved.
He wants to be loved
and seeks attention.
- He's a romanticist.
- Yes, he's so romantic.
HYUNEUIONG NEVER FORGETS
THEIR WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.
Do you love me at all?
My gosh, you surprised me.
TALEUIPA TRIES TO PROTECT
LEE YEON...
WHILE LEE YEON CHOOSES HIS FATE.
YU RI HAS FALLEN IN LOVE
WITH TALEUIPA.
- She's so strong.
- How dare you?
Stop!
They both have different views,
and I understand them both.
THEY CHERISH LEE YEON
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
TALEUIPA AND HYUNEUIONG
WHO IS THE NEXT DEITY
WHO PROTECTS LEE YEON?
It's the Snail Bride.
IT'S THE "SNAIL BRIDE"
FROM TRADITIONAL FOLK TALES.
Whenever we shoot
at the restaurant...
You always eat.
The table is always full of food.
IT TASTES GOOD LIKE ALWAYS.
I think our Food Team
is really good at their job.
The Snail Bride made that food.
What are you talking about?
What I liked most...
were the drumsticks I ate
with Sin Ju.
Oh, the chicken soup?
I WILL TAKE CARE OF
YU RI'S HEALTH!
HE BOUGHT HER CHICKEN SOUP
AT THE TRADITIONAL RESTAURANT.
Listen to me carefully.
WHY DID IMOOGI COME TO SEE
THE SNAIL BRIDE?
VIEWER MODE
Oh, no!
What did he whisper into her ear?
I'm so curious.
WHO IS THE NEXT DEITY
WHO PROTECTS LEE YEON?
DISTRICT MAGISTRATE?
WHY ARE THESE TWO DEITIES
FIGHTING?
It's Lee Kyu Hyong.
Hi, Kyu Hyong.
THEY FOUGHT LIKE CRAZY,
BUT THEY WERE ACTUALLY
BEST FRIENDS?
This was a surprising twist.
I thought he was a rival
with the district magistrate...
or an enemy,
- but they were old friends.
- Right.
He's one of the four
mountain spirits.
He looks great.
HIS REAL IDENTITY IS
A NATIVE BLACK BEAR.
A native black bear.
He said there would be an accident
on the third day of the month.
HE GIVES HIS BEST FRIEND
SOME IMPORTANT INFORMATION.
A human being.
- In that outfit?
- He's drinking...
- an Americano in that outfit.
- It's so funny.
The drink doesn't suit the outfit.
You're the best.
Suddenly?
Thank you for coming to
my birthday party.
We asked him so abruptly,
but he happily agreed
to appear on our drama,
so I feel so thankful to Gyu Hyong.
- He's really a good friend.
- Yes.
I'm going to leave now.
But you have to stay
until the evening.
He always calls me and leaves first.
- I have to shoot a night scene too.
- Sorry.
Say something to the viewers.
I hope all of you enjoy
Tale of the Nine Tailed.
Let's do this.
PLEASE LOOK FORWARD TO...
HOW THE DEITIES WILL HELP HIM
FROM NOW ON!
Do you know there's something
more amazing than the deities?
- What? Really?
- Something more amazing.
Is it something I don't know about?
Didn't you hear this term?
If actors change completely
after they get paid,
what about our drama?
It changes completely
after computer graphics?
That's correct. Let's see it.
Let's go behind the scenes to see
how a drama is made.
This is how Tale of the Nine Tailed
is made.
A TOTALLY NEW SHOOTING METHOD
FOR A FANTASY DRAMA
Tale of the Nine Tailed is famous
for it's computer graphics.
The computer graphics that are used
for each episode...
is capturing the eyes
of our viewers.
Do you want to know
how these scenes are made?
Shall we go to the set first?
JUNE 2020, ISLAND SET
Isn't that Lee Yeon?
LEE YEON IS PREPARING TO SHOOT
A SCENE WITH COMPUTER GRAPHICS.
Like this.
Why does he look so excited?
Gosh, it's been so long since
I did this, and it feels awkward.
Don't look at me.
What do you mean?
We can't take our eyes off you.
Wasn't he being shy
just a second ago?
He's suddenly immersed in his role.
Do you want to know
what scene it is?
It's this scene.
The scene where Lee Yeon gets angry
and turns into a nine-tailed fox.
Before computer graphics,
after computer graphics.
It looks more amazing like this.
This is how this awesome scene
was created.
Now, it's time to see Lee Yeon
being punished...
which hurt the viewers' hearts
as well as mine.
Wait, what is he doing?
Oh, he's getting bulked up...
in order to show his upper body.
LEE YEON IS A TRUE PERFECTIONIST.
The shoot has finally begun.
Gosh, I feel sad already.
If you add computer graphics
to this scene...
THE SNOWY PRISON COMES ALIVE
BY COMPUTER GRAPHICS.
Just looking at this scene
makes my hands feel cold.
This is the horrible Snowy Prison.
Lee Yeon suffered so much.
It's a truly amazing scene.
But Lee Yeon's suffering
hasn't ended yet.
I wonder if he knows
how much I'm worried about him.
I need to signal to Granny
on the next scene?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Shall we use a signal
or something else?
- I'll just tell her.
- Tell her?
"See you." Like this.
Lee Yeon looks so excited.
LEE YEON BEGINS TO PLAY AROUND.
Granny, see you.
Action!
He wipes off his smile
and starts to act seriously.
THE UNDERWORLD OF KNIVES
This is the frightening
Underworld of Knives.
IT MEANS A MOUNTAIN
FULL OF KNIVES.
EVEN LEE YEON GETS NERVOUS
TO STEP FOOT IN THIS PLACE.
It's a deadly place where knives
fly at you from here and there.
Why did he volunteer to go there?
He has such a long way to go.
Lee Yeon, are you okay?
This place looks nice and cozy,
but with computer graphics,
it turns into
the Underworld of Knives.
I will never go
to that frightening place.
The moment he steps foot,
knives fly toward him.
Every step of the way...
needs to be taken very carefully.
BEFORE VERSUS AFTER
LEE YEON SHOWS HOW TERRIBLE
THE UNDERWORLD OF KNIVES IS.
This scene shows the atrociousness
of the Underworld of Knives.
THIS SCENE TOOK THE LONGEST TIME
TO DO CG WORK.
I feel dizzy
just by watching it again.
Knives keep flying toward him,
and Lee Yeon gets covered in wounds.
Can't it stop?
He already got injured a lot.
I just can't seem to watch it.
What am I supposed to do
if she's just there?
MAY 2020, CHROMA KEY COMPOSITING
What scene are they
shooting this time?
It's where Lee Yeon saves Ms. Nam...
as she falls from the rooftop.
LEE YEON'S FIRST ATTEMPT
TO SAVE JI A.
HOW WILL HE DO
THE SECOND TIME AROUND?
He successfully saves Ms. Nam
by catching her at the right time.
Great job.
This scene starts off with
Ms. Nam falling from the rooftop,
and then Lee Yeon saves her.
And finally,
the added visual effect shows
that Ms. Nam has the fox marble,
and that resulted in
creating such an amazing scene.
This scene was not only great
in visual effects,
but it was also
the best ending scene.
THIS SCENE HAD THE BEST
VISUAL EFFECTS AND ENDING.
And at last,
the viewers and Lee Yeon...
were shocked to find out
that Ms. Nam was...
the reincarnated version of Ah Eum.
I found you.
Be born again.
I'll make sure to find you.
Lee Yeon's 600-year-old love...
was portrayed even more beautifully
thanks to the visual effects.
LET'S TAKE A PEEK AT
SIN JU AND YU RI'S DATE.
I'm kidding.
THEY'RE HAPPY JUST TO BE TOGETHER.
You look cute.
- Where should we go?
- Let's take a look...
- at the filming location.
- Let's take a look.
SIN JU AND YU RI WILL TAKE YOU ON
A TOUR AROUND THE FILMING LOCATION.
Where will we be going first?
Oh, this place? This is
the Afterlife Immigration Office.
- Yes, that's right.
- Do you know where that is?
It's where... You know...
THE PLACE WHERE LEE YEON
FREQUENTLY VISITS
IT'S NOT ONLY TALEUIPA
AND HYUNEUIONG'S WORKPLACE,
BUT IT'S ALSO THE FIRST PLACE
YOU GO WHEN YOU'RE DEAD.
We're actually not allowed
to go inside.
Because we're still alive.
That's right.
I don't want to go inside.
But aren't you...
- Okay.
Then shall we go inside?
Yes.
Let's go.
AFTERLIFE IMMIGRATION OFFICE
It's creepy.
The interior design is classy.
Gosh, it's scary here.
- What? What did you see?
- There's someone...
- who shouldn't be here.
- What?
- Oh, there he is.
- Oh, no.
You might not be able to see him
since we're so far away.
Lee Rang!
Hey.
WHAT IS LEE RANG DOING AT
THE AFTERLIFE IMMIGRATION OFFICE?
Don't cheat on me.
I'm against their marriage.
I disapprove of this couple.
What are you doing here, Beom?
Why are you here?
Am I not allowed to be here?
- Of course.
- Why?
You shouldn't be here.
I'm trying so hard...
to keep you alive.
You can't be here.
This is the last day
we'll be shooting here,
so I was actually taking photos.
But you guys barged in.
Lee Rang, why are you here?
I'm... The reason I'm here...
You'll find out why I'm here
if you watch...
what happens after episode 12.
- It's hard to fool him.
- Rang, why don't you...
say a word to the viewers?
Thank you so much...
for watching our drama.
You look really scary.
Oh, really? I'll go down there.
It's because you're
watching from above.
You're shooting
against the light, you stupid.
HE GETS INTO POSITION.
We've received so much love,
and I'm so grateful for that.
And thanks to the love you give
to all the other characters,
we were able to enjoy
a really fun shoot.
We still have
a lot of fun stories left.
So please continue to love
and watch our drama.
Thank you.
Bye. They'll probably just use
10 seconds of this.
Oh, thank you.
I guess that's all
they're going to use.
I must've talked too much.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Good luck until the end.
- Thanks.
Everyone, let me show you something.
- The doors to the Underworld.
- Is this the entrance?
- Yes.
- This is where Yeon went, right?
Yeon was sent to the Snowy Prison.
- Yes.
- From there,
he went to the Underworld of Knives.
- Yes.
- Let's open it. 1, 2, 3.
What's this?
It's freezing!
Sin Ju, it's freezing.
- They're still shooting.
- Oh, really?
- Can you take off your coat?
- They're still shooting.
Take off your coat for me.
It's freezing.
It's freezing?
She's so weird.
My gosh.
It's because she's still young.
Do you see the green walls?
What do you call them? Green...
- Green screen.
- Green back?
- It's called a green screen.
- Yes.
It's all for visual effects.
- Look at the background.
- Do you see all that?
It looks really tall, right?
- After this...
- But actually, it's not.
We're just acting.
Let's try looking up.
1, 2, 3. Shoot.
THE TWO FOXES ACT LIKE
THEY CAN'T SEE WHERE THE ROOF ENDS.
This is how it's done.
- Something's falling!
- Oh, gosh.
Yes, there you go.
- Over there, there's something...
- What is that?
that you guys have
all been dying to see.
- This is really heavy.
- Let me see.
- It really is heavy.
- Right?
I think it weighs about 4kg.
WHEN THE UMBRELLA IS OPEN...
Look at the mark right here.
That's what I'm talking about.
The embroidery.
Ta-da. Do you know what this is?
- "Temptation of Wolves"?
- Guiyomi. No, that's not it.
- Isn't it "Temptation of Wolves"?
- It's Guiyeoni.
He's just a wolf.
SIN JU SUDDENLY
TURNS INTO A WOLF.
Why did you hit me?
Let's move on.
Do you remember what this is?
I stole this from him.
It enables him to hear
what animals are saying.
Yu Ri, I just read your mind.
On the count of three,
tell me your favorite fruit.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Grapes.
- Watermelon.
Tell me your favorite color.
- I read your mind.
- Okay.
1, 2, 3.
- Blue.
SHOCKED
I swear we didn't
talk about this beforehand.
Are you filming properly?
- Yes, I'm...
- Let me hold it from afar.
I didn't press the button.
I'm kidding.
YU RI ENJOYS MAKING FUN OF SIN JU.
- I know what that is.
- Tiger's eyebrows.
- It shows you your past life.
- It shows you the path life.
No, it's past, not path.
I said "past".
That's what I said.
It shows you your past life.
The tiger's eyebrows enable you
to see your past life.
YU RI WAS ALWAYS CURIOUS
ABOUT SIN JU'S PAST LIFE.
I can't wait to hear it.
By any chance,
did you used to ride a horse?
A horse?
- Yes, I did.
- I see you riding a horse.
And you're half undressed.
Is that how you rode your horse?
- Yes, you're right.
- You have long hair and a mustache.
Yes, that's right.
I see you chasing after
Song Joong Ki.
You're from "Arthdal Chronicles"!
- What was your name again?
- Mu Kwang.
- Yes, Mu Kwang!
- I used to be Mu Kwang.
Let's go to the next
filming location.
- Off we go.
- We're at Imoogi's house.
This is the place.
He must be moving...
- to a nicer place.
- The moving company came...
and helped clean the place out.
This place sure is luxurious.
- How flashy.
- It was grander during filming.
Should we begin
our married life here?
Here? I guess it's not bad.
Where are the rooms though?
Let me see them first.
Even though you haven't
been around for that long,
you seem to be quite materialistic.
That's just the way I was born.
Is that so? Then let's
check out the second floor.
HOW DARE YOU PROVOKE
A RUSSIAN FOX!
What?
WHIMPERING
She always intimidates me.
May we come in, Imoogi?
THIS IS WHERE IMOOGI STAYED.
- Gosh, I'm scared.
- Look at these talismans.
See?
There are a lot.
This is the hallway
where the lady was dragged.
- Really?
- Remember the fingernails?
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
- On the other side.
- Stand behind the door.
- I'll play Imoogi.
- Sure.
SIN JU AS IMOOGI,
YU RI AS HIS POSSIBLE VICTIM
I ate her. I ate the person.
YU RI DOES HER BEST IN THE SCENE.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT?
Yu Ri!
YU RI!
I can't help it
being Sin Ju and all.
Tale of the Nine Tailed,
A 600 Year Legend.
It's now time to wrap this up.
Sin Ju, what was it like
to join me for this special episode?
I had a blast
hosting the show with you,
but I loved it even more
since it means I was joined...
by the viewers of
Tale of the Nine Tailed.
I guess it's the same for me.
I'm glad to have had...
this opportunity
to spend time with the fans.
It was also great
to go over the points of the show...
with you.
There are now four episodes
to go in the series.
Look forward to what happens
between Sin Ju and Yu Ri...
and please tune in.
There's nothing else
I can say to you.
Thank you for watching...
and please look forward...
to how the story will end.
Tale of the Nine Tailed,
A 600 Year Legend.
Our fate that travels back
to 600 years from now.
I wonder how we'll all end up.
Will all the couples
have their happy endings?
We hope for your ongoing
love and support.
So this is where we say goodbye.
I'm Hwang Hee who plays Gu Sin Ju.
And I'm Kim Yong Ji
who plays Ki Yu Ri.
Bye!
THE NEW SOUNDTRACK
WILL BE REVEALED SHORTLY.
"STAY WITH ME"
BY YOOA OF OH MY GIRL
I found you.
Did you test me?
I've been waiting for you.
I'll come to you.
"STAY WITH ME"
BY YOOA OF OH MY GIRL...
WILL BE RELEASED
AT 6PM ON SEPTEMBER 19.
I may not be myself...
for much longer.
Take me and save Lee Rang.
I'm about to end
this never-ending fight.
This dagger pierces one's sins.
It'll pierce the Imoogi's soul.
You must get out
of this fight alive.
- No.
- Move.
You altered the register?
No one can take Ji A.
Come at me.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED