Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
No, she must not see it.
Put them on, and look at
yourself in the mirror.
It'll give you the
answer to your question.
Rain is much needed at times.
For nature, for farmers,
and also for us.
Why are you looking
at me that way?
It seems like our time passes...
at a different speed.
You haven't changed since
that first time we met.
Does it scare you?
The life and death
of a mortal, I mean.
It does.
I'm not afraid of growing
old, falling sick, or dying.
But I do worry about...
how you'll be able to
manage the long years...
without me by your side.
As much as I want to stop
time, it never happens.
There we go. I stopped time.
I'll have a good life
even without you.
That's cold.
If that's how you feel,
you should lay down your
bow and focus on longevity.
Grow old with gray hair
and a bent spine...
and make me fall out of love.
Promise me that won't change
how you will feel about me.
If I ever betray you...
Then what?
Drive an arrow through me.
Ma'am!
I mean, my lady.
Where have you been? We've
been looking all over for you.
Must I report using
the privy too?
Goodness me.
There's a message from the
palace. You have been summoned.
- What?
- You should change first...
Who dares to summon...
the daughter of the King who
was expelled from the palace?
It was the King.
The King, you say?
There's no time to chit-chat.
The Majesty is in
critical condition.
You're a big girl now.
And you've grown weak.
How has life been
outside the palace walls?
My eyes have been stinging.
Your eyes...
have been stinging?
Because of the smoke
on the streets.
At first, I thought it
came from cooking rice.
But that wasn't the case.
It came from burning the bodies
that had starved to death.
It's your people, Father.
The country is...
in an unstable set.
That's what I thought at first,
but it wasn't the case.
It's the King's mind
that is unstable.
Because something evil...
has taken control over it.
I should've killed you
when I had the chance.
You must be Imoogi.
Back then and even now,
you're the only person...
who sees me for who I am.
Get out.
I said, leave his body.
Go on. Why not scream and alert
the others like last time?
Shoot away. His body is
almost destroyed anyway.
It wouldn't be so bad...
to have the foolish father...
die at the hands of
the daughter he saved.
Enough with the tricks!
Why do you think you got
kicked out of the palace?
That's because...
you took over my
father's body...
and manipulated him...
Your father chose
that path for himself!
What?
You were born...
to be offered to
me as a sacrifice.
Your father...
willingly gave up this
body of his to save you.
Bring me the mountain spirit.
Then I will let
go of your father.
If I stay in his body,
he will be dead...
within three days.
Fine.
I will bring Yeon to you.
However,
a mountain spirit
belongs in the mountain.
He cannot leave the
place he protects.
- What?
- Let my father go,
and come with me.
You may...
take my body.
First, let's get him
out of the palace.
Then let's trust in Yeon
to take care of the rest.
She means nothing to me.
- I do not believe you.
- You think you used her as bait.
But don't you get it? I used
her as bait to get to you.
Don't kill me!
I don't want to die.
You promised me.
You promised to love
me until the day I die.
- Yeon.
- Show yourself!
Did you see it?
Tell me. Did you see it?
Please look at me.
What did you see?
I was...
murdered in my past life.
You...
killed me.
Your sole purpose was
to find the Imoogi.
Yeon.
You used me...
to offer as a sacrifice.
Was that...
really you?
Yes, it was me.
You were the one
who always saved me?
And I was your first
love whom you've kept...
in your heart for
hundreds of years?
Yes.
I killed you.
I killed you with
my own two hands.
Why?
You don't want to see
the tragedy on replay.
Either one of you...
must die in the end.
I'm just that kind of person.
That's all you have to say?
You swayed me and
made me fall for you,
and that's all you have to say?
At least give me an excuse!
Please.
I had a lot more to gain.
I took your life to save
hundreds of other lives.
After all, I'm a
mountain spirit.
I don't understand...
why my heart aches so much.
Why did I worry about you even
until the moment you killed me?
And why am I still crying...
because of you?
Don't be mistaken.
They're not your emotions.
Don't act like
you're that woman...
just because you got to see a
small part of your past life.
You jerk.
Yes, I'm a jerk. So don't waste
your emotions on a guy like me.
Make sure you don't make the
same mistake in this life.
That way, you'll get
to live a long life.
Your rice is cooked.
CHAPTER 8: REINCARNATION
TRADITIONAL KOREAN
CUISINE: THE SNAIL BRIDE
Snail Bride, give me your most
expensive bottle of alcohol.
When will that punk grow up?
Should I open a bottle
of single malt whiskey?
Don't give him alcohol.
It looks like there's going
to be trouble tonight.
Did she see it?
I guess she saw her past
life. What did she say?
Will you please tell me? I
won't be able to sleep tonight.
Rang.
Yes?
What do you want to be
born as in your next life?
What an absurd question.
Tell me.
I don't really care.
If I must choose, a Dokdo
shrimp would be nice.
I like the whiskers on them.
And they're worth
a lot of money.
If I ever get to be born again,
I want to live as a human being.
What a pathetic wish.
I want my life to be filled
with firsts and lasts.
My first step. My first picnic.
My first love.
Why are you being such a loser?
It has been so long since
we chatted openly like this.
Do you feel sick?
Did you completely snap
after fighting with her?
Imoogi.
Where is he?
Do you think I'd tell you?
I expected as much.
So that's what you choose.
WE ARE PREPARING TO SERVE YOU.
How about a game?
We used to play often before.
It's no fun playing you.
You've never once beaten me.
Are you going to play or not?
Got you.
Yeon, why is the sky blue?
I don't know. I
didn't dye it myself.
When why do owls
go, "hoot hoot"?
I don't know. I
didn't make them hoot.
Why does this
flower taste sweet?
Why do flowers bloom
only in the spring?
Quiet.
Why did you hit me?
Why does a pip-squeak
have so many questions?
I just like hearing your voice.
You're too rash.
I told you to cut off the tail.
I told you not to leave
blank spaces for no reason.
I won!
I won again!
I'm angry.
Not bad, kid.
I'm not a kid.
Running like that won't work.
It worked! Yes!
It's hard raising a kid.
You're too slow. Again.
You think it's strange
too, don't you?
How did you win every single
time with skills like this?
Shut it.
I let you win.
There was never an exception.
I said to shut it.
I don't plan to let
you win anymore.
This is what I wanted to say.
Hey, you. Stop right there.
If you leave now, it's
really over between us.
Sorry.
You're sorry?
Now? What are you sorry for?
For saving you...
when you were abandoned by
your human mom back then.
Then...
we never would've been brothers.
Mom?
Get away! Get off of me!
No!
Mom.
Are you that?
The thing that my
father had with a human?
Are you a fox too?
I came to see you because I
heard you had my father's blood,
but you're pathetic.
You have no will to live either.
I wasted my time. I'm leaving.
Look. He's still alive.
It's an evil spirit. It
doesn't die even if it dies.
The grudge of those who died
of starvation is incessant.
I prefer them over those
who give up easily.
Hey.
Live as a human or a
fox. That's up to you.
But remember this, kid.
There is no salvation to those
who won't save themselves.
Wait for me!
Wait for me, big brother.
I'll wait for you right here.
Here? All day?
When it comes to waiting, no
one can do it better than me.
24 hours? I could sit
there even for 24 years.
Gosh, you'll even
outlive me too.
Would you like one? It
seems like you could use it.
I'll pass today.
A human's soul leaves a
stink every time you eat it.
Their memories invade your dreams
and disrupts your peace as well.
Still, I'm yet alive thanks
to sucking in their lives.
You too, Mr. Lee.
Why ground cherries though?
They give me the creeps.
I was told that they resemble
the human soul the most.
Is Imoogi home?
I'd like to see him.
Now's not a good time.
If he had all the dirty
work taken care of for him,
he should at least show his
gratitude and repay the favor.
If not, he's no different
from being a gold digger.
- I can relay the message.
- It's not what I want.
It's for your own sake. I
don't want to see you get hurt.
What?
Just because I let
you have your fun...
doesn't mean I'm a pushover.
You find this funny?
Please let him go.
Are you Imoogi?
It's good to meet you. I've
been waiting for this too.
What on earth?
You haven't answered
my calls or texts.
I have something to discuss. It's
about the dog you brought by.
My gosh. Did it die?
No, that's not it.
Well,
it doesn't have a name.
Just give it any random one.
No way. A name gives
them an identity.
Then carefully think
of one that will work.
You're its mother, so...
Its mom?
The mom...
Call it Anastasia.
"Anastasia"?
What a pretty name.
It suits even a male dog.
Of course, it does.
- Why are you gazing at me?
- No reason.
I'm glad to know that
I was right about you.
Gaze at me like that again...
and it'll be the
last thing you see.
I don't care how
your life has been.
For what purpose you
approached me doesn't matter.
I'll show you...
that the world is not all evil.
I'll make sure you
regret ever saying that.
I'll look forward to it.
What the...
I'll kill you!
See you around.
I thought you were
still a little boy.
You must've been
enjoying a feast.
Can you give us some room?
- Are you sure...
- We'll be fine.
Why so sad?
- What?
- You've been gravely hurt.
Cut the nonsense.
Was it your brother?
I see it, you know.
You're being
tormented from within.
I did not expect you
to be this annoying.
Don't we seem alike?
I personally detest
those who shed skin.
You'd better listen.
Regardless of your goal, I
will operate at my own pace.
I can't wait any longer.
I see you want to kill her.
But no can do, I'm afraid.
Why's that?
Because she was originally
sacrificed to me.
Thus, she will be my bride.
Congratulations
on your promotion
Thank you, thank you.
- Are you insane?
- Tell me about it.
Ji A, he's been promoted
to department chief.
As if he did anything to
deserve that promotion.
Just say you're jealous
since I know you are.
The higher-ups must
still not be aware...
of how you spend your hours
doing personal activities.
Playing pool, working out,
singing at a karaoke...
Hey, I only went to sing once
on the day I got divorced.
- He sang "She's Gone".
- Hey!
Who wants cake?
You seem down today.
- It's nothing.
- As if.
I've known you for years now.
Did you and your
boyfriend argue?
Just make up with him.
If you don't, he'll be the
last man you'll ever date.
Wake up, Ji A.
Apart from being younger,
you're way out of his league.
That's not the case!
Why would you shake her
confidence like that?
But I'm right. It's the truth.
- Only we can dispirit her.
- Exactly.
Where have you been? We've
been looking all over for you.
This is what you get for
acting all high and mighty.
- So do you have a new story?
- Yes.
I just decided on one.
What is it?
Stories about past lives.
How about a hug?
- Get lost.
- I'm relieved.
I'm glad you're still yourself.
I made some tofu rice balls.
I bet you barely ate or slept.
I'm fine.
Just have one. The hint
of vinegar is to die for.
I'm not in
kindergarten, you know.
Look!
- Seriously?
- Go on and eat.
You need the energy
to protect and serve.
I'm curious though. Why
didn't you tell Ms. Nam?
She's mistaken and that
there's more to the story.
You could've told her that.
It's all starting again.
If history repeats itself,
that's more of a reason for me
to stay as the bad guy to her.
You're scared, aren't you?
You're scared she might
sacrifice herself to save you...
just like A Eum.
Are you sure you
won't regret it?
No.
But you're still going
to protect her from afar?
Yes.
Even after you spent all
those years waiting for her?
Yes.
Do you really mean it?
I've made up my mind.
Please keep a close eye on her.
The tofu rice ball
tastes delicious.
I'll go with you.
It's okay. I know the
doctor personally.
- What about lunch?
- You guys can eat without me.
Mister.
Why are you ignoring me?
Because I don't
want to talk to you.
I've been waiting
for you all day.
Why would you wait for me?
I thought about what I
want to be in the future.
When I was six years old, I
wanted to be a Triceratops.
But when I turned seven,
I thought it'd be cool to be
an owner of an internet cafe.
And when I turned eight...
Get to the point.
When I grow up, I
want to be like you.
You're handsome, brave,
and you have superpowers.
We're different in every aspect.
- How so?
- Because I hit people first.
Judging by your face, someone
must've beaten you up.
Did it happen in
school? Or your home?
I... I didn't get beaten up.
It's your choice whether
to beat people up...
or get beaten up instead.
But apparently, there
is no salvation...
to those who won't
save themselves.
I heard they're stepbrothers,
but I guess it's much more
complicated than that.
I was touched...
by the wonderful smell
of his tainted soul.
Why don't we test...
whether or not he'll become
another Achilles' heel to Yeon?
How?
We're expecting a guest.
My goodness. Let me help.
Hurry up and take it.
- Here.
- Thank you.
What do we have here?
This plum tea smells amazing.
We received organic
plums from Hadong.
"Hadong"? Goodness, no wonder.
I once went to the plum
festival in Hadong for work.
- And that was back in...
- Ma'am.
The petals were falling down.
And the scenery was...
I'll take you there one day.
I promise. Goodness.
What... What are you looking at?
You never went to the
plum festival for work.
What are you doing here?
I came to a restaurant to
eat. Why else would I be here?
Everyone knows what
a great cook you are.
You should leave.
I might as well give the
leftover rice to mice.
But there's no rice for you.
You little wench.
Have you lost your mind...
after having lived as a
widow for hundreds of years?
If that's not it,
have you forgotten who I am?
How could I ever forget you?
I lost my husband
because of you.
My goodness, you
are unbelievable.
Are you still not over
that foolish farmer?
Why did you do that to him?
Everyone lives with
a painful memory...
of their own.
I just reminded your husband
of his trauma like I always do.
But he was the one who chose
to live in that bubble.
You should blame him for
being so mentally weak.
Why? Why did it have to be him?
To be more exact,
you should ask why
it had to be you.
What?
You see,
I really hate people like you.
The main characters of famous
traditional fairy tales.
Unlike you, no one
ever remembers my name.
Are you okay?
Do you need help?
- Don't let it bother you.
- How could I not let it bother me?
Listen, ma'am.
If you don't like it here,
just go eat somewhere else.
You could come out on the news
for being a rude customer.
What do you fear the most?
What?
You're scared of
boarding airplanes.
What?
Wait a minute. What
are you doing here?
I want you to leave right now.
I'll see you around.
Is she a shaman?
Is it written on my face
that I'm scared of flights?
CHEONHWA RICE WINE
Today's the anniversary of
your son's death, isn't it?
So you remember.
Where's Granny?
She's probably...
going hysterical somewhere.
I know you guys
suffered a lot...
after what happened to your son.
That's probably why...
she was so strict with you.
Yes, I've heard it enough.
"Love..."
"eventually dies
and disappears."
"I don't understand why you'd
sacrifice your life for love."
She always says that because
if you kill yourself,
you'll never get the
chance to be reincarnated.
Just like our son, Bok Gil.
I have a favor to ask you.
I'm willing to do anything now.
I'll do anything to save
both myself and that woman.
I'm sorry, Mom.
If you were sorry, why
did you kill yourself?
- How have you been?
- Well, as you can see.
So you really did quit drinking.
You don't look like
a corpse anymore.
I wish my son would be as
attentive as you, Ji A.
What are you digging
into this time?
Is this life really
our first life?
I'm talking about past lives.
"Past lives"?
I want to do a case study.
I hear there are many people who
say they remember their past lives.
That's just their claim.
But apart from approving
their claims...
"HASSAN, A BOY WHO REMEMBERS
HIS PAST LIFE, SOLVES A MURDER"
"A Syrian boy who
remembers his past life"?
Ever since he was
four, he asserted...
that he was a man named
Mohammed in his past life.
He went to a city he
had never been before,
and found the house where
he lived in his past life.
He even identified his
neighbor who had killed him.
How interesting.
May I borrow this?
But...
why past lives?
I need to come up with something
if I want to make a living.
Why?
She asked that exact question
while sitting right there.
- Who did?
- Your mom.
What?
I gathered those with your mom.
But my mom was a
surgeon. So why...
Do you really not
remember anything?
Remember what?
When you were nine,
you underwent hypnotherapy...
at your mom's request.
Do you believe in past lives?
Yes, I do.
Why?
You've heard of deja vu, right?
When someone you never met before
seems very familiar to you,
or when you go somewhere new,
but it feels very familiar.
You've felt things
like that before?
When I went
backpacking in Paris.
- In the Palace of Versailles.
- Hey.
- You?
- Whether or not I believe it aside,
I wish there was no such
thing as transmigration.
- Why not?
- I'm working so hard in this life.
What if I'm born as a
mosquito in my next life?
Then I'll be a
mosquito repellant.
Don't obsess over me just
because we held hands once.
JIKIMI PSYCHIATRY
I'm sure that will have the
answers on what you're looking for.
IMPROVE YOUR CHILDREN'S
CONCENTRATION
VIDEO EDITING ROOM
Which team are you with?
May I see your ID?
NAM JI A'S
HYPNOTHERAPY SESSION
You are falling...
slowly, very slowly,
into a deep sleep.
You get out, and you see a door.
Do you want to open it?
No.
It's okay.
I don't want to open it.
Why not?
I feel like something
scary will jump out at me.
Then Auntie and
Mommy will scold it.
Go ahead. Open the door.
You went in.
What do you see?
People. They're wearing hanboks.
But... They're so funny.
What's so funny?
What are the people doing?
They're lying down.
Why are they lying down?
Because...
they were killed like animals.
Ji A, do you hear me?
Ji A.
Keep it down. You're
too loud. I can't sleep.
Why did you wake me?
It isn't time yet.
You are Ji A, aren't you?
I am that kid, and I am not.
Who are you?
Give me some water.
That tastes good.
I was born in a
cave on a leap day.
The grave of people
who died of a plague.
Where the living and the
dead intermingled together.
It was an Underworld on earth.
One day,
an animal in the form of a
human walked out of the cave.
What did the people call it?
Yes. Imoogi.
Where is the mountain
spirit now? I must find him.
"Do not eat..."
"or drink here."
"Please turn off the
editing equipment..."
"if you are the last
person to leave"?
There you are.
Ji A. What are you doing here?
Hey... I was...
looking at some stuff.
- Why?
- I need to add captions.
Okay, I'll clean this up.
Excuse me.
I'm not interested.
Hey. You don't
have to pay for it,
so at least try it,
good-looking fellow.
Hey, lady. Can't you read?
DO NOT RING THE BELL
What do you fear
the most, young man?
Nuisances like you. Peddlers.
Come now. That's not true.
Get lost.
I saw it.
Out of all the places, it
had to be this old house.
I must be more wasted
than I thought.
The illegitimate child!
It's the illegitimate
child born from a fox.
Because of him,
the animals in this
town are all dead.
- He must've eaten their livers.
- Exactly.
- Kill him.
- Get him.
- Die!
- Kill him.
- Die, you scoundrel.
Take that.
- Die.
- Kill him.
- Get him good.
Die. Just kill him!
- Die! Kill him.
- Take that.
I knew it.
You...
saw everything that day, Mom.
should've never been born.
I tried almost everything
to get rid of you...
while you were still in my womb.
I drank the brewed liquid
from poisonous plants,
rolled down hills,
and even banged my
stomach against rocks.
Being the monster you are,
you just wouldn't die.
You even survived the beating
from all those fit men.
You...
are a monster, my boy.
Let's go. You're coming with me!
Don't touch me!
It's not...
a dream?
Could this be the
Forest of the Starved?
I hear a spirit.
I won't ever die...
because this is when...
Sorry. For saving you...
when you were abandoned by
your human mom back then.
Yeon...
won't come to save me anymore.
I need you,
Yeon.
I NEED YOU, YEON.
Miss, try one of these.
This one's for free.
Sure.
Is someone new making
the rounds here now?
I don't think I recognize you.
A special event takes
place today, you see.
An event?
You'll soon find
out what that is.
Miss, what do you fear the most?
It must be Yeou Gogae.
Ma'am!
Here's your birthday present.
YEOU GOGAE
"Yeou Gogae"?
Of all the places,
it had to be the
Forest of the Starved.
You...
I send my condolences
in advance.
If this were a video game,
it'll be the final level.
Was this your creation?
Just so you know, dying here...
will end your life for real.
I'll rip you apart.
How about this then?
Soon, I will tell your brother
what's happening to you.
Don't get too excited though...
because his girlfriend is
in a similar predicament.
Dad. Dad?
Dad, can't you hear
me? Stop the car!
Mom!
Dad, please stop the car.
Dad, stop the car!
Say that again.
As you can see,
there are two doors.
One leads to your brother while
the other leads to your girl.
Which will you choose?
Door number three.
I'd rather snap your neck.
Then go ahead.
Defy the rules and they'll
be stuck there forever.
Imoogi sent you, didn't he?
Let's just say that
we're partners.
Lady.
Just you wait.
I'll soon pay you
back for the favor.
You'd better hurry.
They're both
running out of time.
Mom! Dad! Stop the car!
Stop the car! Stop
the car right now!
I knew it. That jerk only
cares about his lady.
Hey, kid!
Yeon?
I heard what you
just said about me.
I don't need your help.
Now is not the time
to be so arrogant.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Will I be able to save
you from this Underworld?
I was at the office
just a moment ago.
Don't get intimidated and think.
What really scares you the most?
Being abandoned.
- I never once...
- No!
abandoned you.
Yeon already knew...
what he was up against.
I'm not alone. I trust Yeon.
Please. I hope I didn't
make the wrong choice.