Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Once you fall into
the Samdo River,
you'll never be
able to come back.
No.
I love you.
No!
Yeon!
Don't leave me.
I can hear her crying.
Yeon!
I must tell her...
that she shouldn't be so sad...
and that the love story
of a human and fox...
always ends this way.
From the beginning,
we belonged in two
different worlds.
Using our love as a bridge,
I wished to cross
over to her world.
I wished to be with her longer.
I wished to be a mortal.
My dreams...
never came true,
but my death...
is the most...
passionate love letter...
sent to my first and last love.
I hope...
that she doesn't wait for me.
I hope she doesn't cry too much.
And I'd give anything to
see her one last time.
I...
no longer can see her face.
CHAPTER 16: THE REWRITTEN
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Jae Hwan.
Ms. Kim?
Ms. Kim!
- Hold on.
- Are you all right?
Well...
Could a miracle actually
exist in this world?
The unknown contagious disease
that drove people to fear...
vanished as of last night.
Patients of this puzzling disease
and their family members...
who had no choice but
to succumb to it...
embraced with each
other with tears of joy.
Finally, everything has
come back to normal.
I couldn't...
save Yeon.
Once again, I lost a
young man I adored.
That's not true. You did
everything you could...
to help Yeon.
That's why I came back to you.
I hope Yeon didn't suffer.
He probably didn't.
He saved the girl which
is all that he wished.
Mr. Hyeonuiong.
Mr. Hyeonuiong!
It's Ji A, please open the door.
What do I do?
Don't open the door for her.
But...
She should forget about Yeon...
and live an ordinary
life among others.
Please tell me...
what I need to do to save Yeon.
Tell me what I can do.
Can you please...
just tell me what I should do?
Mr. Hyeonuiong.
Please open the door.
Please.
Why can't we just open the door?
Rang!
Mr. Lee, should I
buy you naengmyeon?
Get out.
You haven't eaten anything
but alcohol for three days.
I said get out.
It wasn't your fault.
You just did what
Yeon asked you to do.
Say one more word
and I'll kill you.
Do you want stickers?
I have a really cool car too.
Will both of you just get
lost? Get out of my house!
Thank you for letting me in.
I have no time to console
your broken heart,
so I'll just get to the point.
Yeon is dead.
You can't do anything
to bring him back.
I may not be able to do
anything, but you can.
You have control over life and
death so there must be something...
We also have rules
in this world.
There are things that
just can't be done.
Then at least let
him get reincarnated.
I don't care if he
doesn't recognize me.
I'm fine even if he forgets
everything about me, so please...
Yeon willingly chose to
jump into the Samdo River.
He knew he wouldn't be
able to be reincarnated,
but he still chose to do so.
So stop protesting in
front of my office.
You can't undo what's been
done by throwing a tantrum.
No, I'm sure there's a way.
There must be a way
to bring Yeon back.
That will...
never happen.
I let you in to tell you that.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, wait. Ma'am.
It's so dark.
The street lamps are out.
It would be so cool if you
could use your powers...
to fix them.
Submit a request to
the local authority.
Are you okay?
The street lamps are on again.
I called the local authority.
You didn't have to do that.
If you get hurt, I'll get
an earful from Mr. Lee.
Dr. Koo.
Are you okay?
I need to be okay
even if I'm not.
I have a lot to do.
I just met the gatekeeper
of the Samdo River.
She told me there's no
way to save Mr. Lee.
Yeon knew this would
happen from the very start.
But he still chose to sacrifice
himself for the woman he loved.
What am I supposed to do?
Just live your life like
nothing ever happened.
Forget having met Mr. Lee...
and everything you saw
regarding our world,
and live a normal life.
That's what he wants for you.
Shin Ju.
- Is he still inside?
- He won't even budge.
I'm worried he might collapse.
Let me talk to him.
- Why are you being like this?
- Isn't it obvious?
This won't bring Mr. Lee back.
I can't believe
you just said that.
But you look completely fine.
You always acted like you could
sacrifice your life for him.
You're an ungrateful
piece of trash.
You can call me
whatever you want.
But I need to say this to you.
Save the darn lecture and
give me back my alcohol.
Get it together.
You crazy punk.
Stop acting like a baby
and start living your life.
- Do you have a death wish?
- Mr. Lee told me to tell you that.
You can go ahead and
listen to the rest.
Is this working?
Okay, there we go.
Hey, it's me.
We just had naengmyeon together.
And you ate my egg.
If you're watching this,
I'm probably no longer alive.
My gosh.
This is so corny.
This kind of stuff
looked cool in movies.
I'm sure it'll be neat
enough to keep as a keepsake.
Say you agree.
Neat, my foot.
Rang.
Are you drinking?
You're probably
drinking wine, right?
How did he know that?
Soju suits you a lot
better than wine, you know.
And you're better off as a
social worker than a villain.
You could never pass
by an injured dog...
ever since you were young.
And I wondered why you
had changed so much.
But you haven't changed at all.
You haven't changed one bit.
So...
you'll be fine even
after I'm gone.
You jerk. How do you
expect me to be fine?
You need to be fine.
You have a family
to protect now.
I don't need any of them.
Stop talking back when
I'm talking to you.
I can already hear
you grumbling.
Remember what I told you in
the Forest of the Starved?
I...
I told you...
that I never once abandoned you.
So don't you...
discard yourself so recklessly.
Cherish yourself for my sake.
This is my final request.
Take care.
Also, this message will
explode after 10 seconds.
Just kidding.
I've always wanted to say that.
Yeon.
You told me to forget,
but I'll wait for you.
If I wish for it
desperately again and again,
maybe we'll be
able to meet again.
In my next life...
No.
The life after that is fine too.
That's why I've decided
to remember you...
and leave a record of you.
I'll use my skills.
You hadn't come for a while,
but you're coming often now.
I looked online, and they say
the salon is the best place...
to deal with losing a person.
Did you break up with someone?
Nothing beats sad music then.
I've tried them all.
I listened to ballads, binged
dramas, ate spicy foods...
Should I die my hair?
It's been a while.
I don't care how you're
doing. Get to the point.
What are you making?
"Tale of the Nine Tailed".
"Tale of the Nine Tailed"?
What a lame title.
"Tale of the Nine Tailed
Brothers". How about that?
No thank you.
You won't really
air it, will you?
It's to keep. I plan to meet
people that Yeon knew one by one.
Starting with you.
Sure. No one knows as
much about him as I do.
Okay then. Tell me everything
you know about Yeon.
Did you know that
he was a narcissist?
What?
All sorts of beings...
from all over the world came
to our woods to see Yeon.
He was already very
proud of his looks.
Imagine how much worse it got.
He always looked at his reflection
in the stream and said...
If you were to embody the
word "beautiful" into a form,
it would be this face.
I can't even imagine that.
That's as shocking as him
falling for voice phishing.
He fell for voice phishing?
He lost 20,000 dollars.
How ridiculous. A nine-tailed
fox fell for voice phishing?
Did you know? He's scared of
spiders because of their hairy legs.
He liked playing Go
with me the most.
Although he always lost.
I won!
I won again!
I guess you two were very
close a long time ago.
Naturally.
He spent much more
time with me than you.
Has he ever cooked for you?
He can't cook.
He's a bad cook, but he
can make rice. Only rice
He left me a video message.
Yeon bought me these.
He carried me on his back.
He waited for me
every single day.
I hate you.
Come to think of it,
you and I have received
so much from him.
Do you know what his wish was?
Human.
He wanted to be human.
Dear brother,
there are always
exceptions to the rules.
No.
He didn't commit suicide.
He sacrificed himself...
to save tens of
thousands of people.
There are 10 afterlife judges,
and you can't do that one thing?
Is King Hades that useless?
Hello? Hades?
Hades!
Hey, you!
Darn it. That jerk.
That's enough. You've
done all you could.
I might as well talk to a wall.
No matter how many times I talk
to him, he says the same thing.
Is he a parrot or something?
You'll be punished.
How is he so inflexible?
- Why are you laughing?
- Hearing you...
talk about being
flexible is funny.
Watch it. I've been
too lax with you.
Okay! Tteokbokki break!
It's spicy and mild
combined. Medium spicy.
Here.
Here. Look, they gave us
dumplings on the house.
When I look at you like you
I want to kiss you
When I'm alone
with you like this
I want to hold you
I love you
I love you so very much
I love you more than myself
Are you crying?
I'm so embarrassed.
Pretend you don't know me.
Yu Ri.
Marry me.
A fox loves only
one mate for life.
Will you accept my love
until the day I die?
What, with just one little ring?
I have an apartment too.
It's a new building.
If you want, I can add you...
No, I can put it in your name.
I don't need that.
I may bring some family with me.
If you don't mind, then...
Is that a yes?
If you didn't propose
to me, I was going to.
Congratulations!
You know, right? The day
you make Yu Ri cry...
will be your funeral.
Mr. Lee.
Go. You lived in
luxury living with me,
so try suffering with him.
I took care of your fake parents.
They won't wait for you anymore.
I'll be happy.
Congratulations.
It's on me today.
Thank you all so much.
Yu Ri. Thanks.
And although he
isn't here with us,
Mr. Lee...
Thank you, and I miss you.
He should officiate our wedding.
I wish he were here with us.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Sir, can you say a
few words to Yeon?
Yeon, my wife
finally quit smoking.
80 percent of it
is thanks to you.
I wish she'll stop
nagging me too,
but that seems impossible.
There's no need to
be grumpy about it.
Ma'am, what about you?
Mr. Lee,
when I fell in love
with a human farmer,
you were the only
one who supported me.
You said you once
loved a mortal too.
Now, that same woman...
is staying strong as
she waits for you.
I hope you two can
finally meet one day...
just like me and my husband.
- You're here.
- Right.
- Come on in.
- Hae Ja.
Yes?
- Here you go.
- What's this?
Honey-filled rice cakes!
You love those, so...
- Isn't he handsome?
- Hello.
Please have a seat.
- Right.
- Join us.
This is great.
- You should try this too.
- Goodness. Thanks.
Thank you.
Even on the days that I
desperately missed Yeon,
I didn't cry anymore.
Because I knew that my tears
would conclude this story...
as a tragedy.
6 MONTHS LATER
Then, on the day I
finally completed...
my very own version of
"Tale of the Nine Tailed...
"TALE OF THE NINE TAILED"
As if I were imagining
things, Yeon contacted me.
The end.
Yes?
Ji A, hurry downstairs.
- Why?
- Come on. It's urgent.
- Ta-da.
Happy birthday, my daughter.
Was it my birthday today?
I had completely forgotten.
Happy birthday.
Here's my gift.
- It's handmade.
- Gosh, it's so pretty.
- It looks great on you.
- I love it.
Mine was made in a factory.
Thanks, Mom.
Did you know that my watch
strap had fallen off?
- I saw it.
- How attentive of you.
Anyway, thank you.
Who sent that one?
You should open it.
On my birthday...
What would you like as a gift?
Something I've never
had before in my life.
Like a marriage proposal.
Sure. I'll make that happen.
It's from Yeon, right?
Did he come by?
A courier dropped it by.
It also came with a letter.
It was back when things
were tough for me.
I talked to my teammates and
tried to resolve the matter.
They suggested that we go out...
and helped me have a good time.
Becoming a member
of this team...
What did I say about
snacking on the couch?
I want my meal.
At least catch the
crumbs with a tray or...
Move. You're blocking the TV.
It was definitely hard for me.
Honey,
I told you to put your dirty
socks in the laundry basket,
I forgot.
Oh, wait. The other
one's over here.
How is it that only Soo Ho
cleans up after himself?
While singing and
dancing on stage...
The soup is a
little salty today.
Mr. Lee, until when
will you live with us?
Are you kidding me?
The three of us come as a set.
I'm good with it all,
but why must I suffer...
in my own home?
I ordered a new kimchi fridge.
Really? The model we saw
at the department store?
Mr. Lee bought it for us. It'll
be delivered this afternoon.
- I love you, Rang!
- Rang?
I'll call you that
from now on, Rang.
I love it.
We're like one big family
now. Don't you think?
TO MY BELOVED JI A
Do you like your gift?
I hope you do.
How stunning would
you be in this dress?
I wonder...
who'd get to stand beside you.
Whoever it is,
I wish it's someone decent.
If only I could actually
be that nonchalant.
But truth be told,
I already hate the guts of
this future husband of yours.
I liked you.
I liked how you
viewed the world.
Despite being born
with a terrible fate,
you never easily lost hope.
Drinking coffee with you,
watching you sleep,
all the paths we
walked together,
and even the time I
spent waiting for you.
I loved them all.
Ji A,
whenever I called your name...
that rolled easily
off my tongue,
butterflies filled my stomach.
You'll now...
have to walk those
paths without me,
but you'll get used to it.
You'll do well.
So please...
let me go now.
You must.
No.
I can't let you go.
Please come back to me.
I miss you so much.
Mister,
are you off to find the
nine-tailed fox again?
What did I tell you
about mentioning him?
Has there been any news?
I've been beating non-humans...
to see if they know anything
about how to bring him back.
- I'll give you a ride.
- Save it. It's cold outside anyway.
Hurry on home then.
The four of us will grill
pork belly for dinner.
Be safe on the road!
The key ring.
What brings you here?
What about you?
Rumors led me here
to that geezer.
FORTUNE-TELLING, PHYSIOGNOMY,
NAMING, COMPATIBILITY
Are you really...
one of the afterlife judges?
I am the king of darkness.
I am the 10th king who rules
the Underworld of Darkness.
And I am also...
the very last judge.
I get to choose what happens
to you after you die.
You'd better sit up straight.
By any chance, if you have
the power to decide...
what happens to
us after we die...
Yes, that's right. I'm in
charge of reincarnation.
"Reincarnation"?
Then are you here
because of Yeon?
Well, I can't say
that's the only reason.
But I have something
that belongs to him.
You have the fox bead.
Give me the fox bead.
The fox bead.
Can this bring him back to life?
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
King Hades' sister, the
gatekeeper of the Samdo River,
kept calling the afterlife
judges, so that's why I'm here.
but we don't do charity work.
You both know the rules, right?
We need to give you the one thing
that's most precious to us, right?
I'll do it. I can do it.
As long as Yeon
comes back to life.
But what if you're not
able to meet him...
even if he comes back?
- What?
- People get reincarnated randomly.
It means you could cross paths.
He could get reincarnated
after you both die.
And he might be born with
a different appearance.
I don't care.
Let's start the deal.
Okay then.
Go ahead and bring me
something enticing...
before the sandglass stops.
- What's the matter?
- The king of darkness is here.
No wonder something felt
unusual. He's finally here.
That's a crow crying.
It cried three times.
I see people in
mourning clothes.
It looks like there
will be another death.
I'll do it.
Tell me what you can give me.
The person I cherish
the most is Yeon.
But he's no longer here,
and my memories of him...
are all I have left.
I will sell you my memories.
I don't buy memories.
Forget that.
You have something else
that you received from him.
I'll give you anything.
Just tell me what you want.
For example,
the rest of your life.
If I give you my life,
- can Yeon get reincarnated?
- Hey.
If you want his life,
you can sacrifice yours.
There's no question about that.
I'll give it to you.
Hey, do you think Yeon saved
you just so you could...
cast away your life like that?
He didn't die for nothing,
you know. You're so pathetic.
Then will you give me your life?
Sure. I stole
people's lives anyway,
- so I have no regrets.
- Hey.
- Stay out of it.
- But...
if I remember correctly,
you had no will to live.
That makes your life worthless.
First, let's take a look
and check your worth.
Interesting.
It looks like you've
got yourself a family.
Now you're cherishing your life.
You pass.
We have a deal.
Deal.
- No!
- Wait.
We still have time.
Can you call the guys?
At least let me say goodbye.
This way.
Mr. Lee!
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my goodness.
HERE LIES LEE RANG
- Ms. Nam.
- Yes?
Take this.
Where did you get this?
I'm not sure. Someone
dropped it off...
to give it to you.
- When?
- It was before my shift,
so about five minutes ago?
But...
Yeon.
I'm sorry.
I told you not to
walk in the rain.
Yeon.
Is it really you?
You're not in disguise.
Isn't it a dream?
It's really you?
Then why are you standing there?
Why won't you come to me?
I'm not the same
person I used to be.
What do you mean?
I can't even fly.
Even if you fall from a high
place, I can't catch you.
Even if your path is dark,
I can't send fireflies.
It hurts if I get hit.
I get wounded if I get stabbed.
There's nothing
I can do for you.
It doesn't matter.
I don't need any of that.
I've become human.
Human?
You're in trouble now.
I won't let you go
until the day you die.
I've missed you so much.
So much, that I thought I
was going to lose my mind.
I was terrified that
I'd never see you again.
How did you do it?
What?
6 months felt like
6 years for me.
How did you wait for 600 years?
Do you develop a skill...
and get used to it if
you wait long enough?
I didn't get used to waiting.
I just couldn't get used
to being apart from you.
I wanted to be strong
like you as I waited,
but little things held me
back and knocked me over.
Like what? What
tormented you so much?
For example,
the night air from one night
when you walked me home.
The alarm from our rice cooker.
Remembering how warm your hands
were when we went for a walk.
Those little memories.
That's why...
you found me this time.
You found me.
These are real human hands now.
Yes. And a human body.
And human lips.
No. He isn't going
to sing there, is he?
- No...
- When I look at you like you
I want to kiss you
When I'm alone
with you like this
Sir, can you say a
few words to Yeon?
Yeon, my wife
finally quit smoking.
80 percent of it
is thanks to you.
Ma'am, what about you?
When I fell in love
with a human farmer,
you were the only
one who supported me.
You said you once
loved a mortal too.
Now, that same woman
is staying strong...
as she waits for you.
I hope you two can
finally meet one day...
You should try this too.
I want fish too. Fish.
- I'll bring you some more.
- I'll get it.
Let's eat baeksuk
after our walk.
Are you happy?
SHUNJU ANIMAL HOSPITAL
Mr. Lee!
How's the apartment? Livable?
You don't know the half of
it. They provide everything.
A sauna, a gym...
It's definitely worth more
than its current price.
There are even two
railway stations close by.
You're quite
materialistic for a fox.
I'm the manager of the
resident association.
So were you able...
to cherish me more
during my absence?
I've been enjoying being
a newlywed to miss you.
Then I'm leaving.
Just kidding.
Being human comes with mood swings,
so be careful with what you say.
This is the first time I
feel inferior to anyone.
Saying that with your face will
earn you a smack on the head.
Anyway, I'm glad you're back.
In our own ways, we've been
coping with your death...
while awaiting your return.
Sometimes, we whined and
leaned on each other.
And Rang?
He was a total wreck
from the day you left.
He cried all night for a month.
Things got better after
he moved in with us,
but he kept searching for you.
Were you with him
at his final moment?
He would've been so scared.
Despite what people think,
he gets scared easily.
Here's his phone.
Take a look.
It's me.
I'll be dead soon.
If you were here, you'd
come to rescue me.
Since you can't,
I'm totally doomed.
Anyway, this is payback...
for your final message to me.
I thought it'd feel
different to face death,
but maybe you're right
about me easily giving up.
I'm sad but relieved in a way.
So...
don't you be a fool
and cry over my death.
I never once cried
in your absence.
All I did was get drunk.
You liar.
I've been causing you
trouble for years,
but I won't apologize since
you're the bigger jerk.
Whenever we split a fruit, you
always gave me the bigger piece.
Despite your
obsession with eggs,
you always let me have yours.
So how could I not hate you for
choosing the girl over me...
after I've grown
accustomed to you?
I'm going to be reborn
as a humpback shrimp,
so don't eat them just in case.
I hope...
you'll be reincarnated too.
Preferably with an ugly face.
Still...
Still,
if we can,
let's meet again.
My brother.
My brother...
Kim Soo Ho, you don't
have parents, do you?
I heard that your mom ran away.
No, she didn't.
He lives in a shabby house too.
I saw it when we were
in the same class.
- You're a homeless beggar
- Soo Ho!
Let's go home.
And we're not beggars.
Come on.
Wasn't that perfect timing?
Rang unexpectedly
did good deeds,
and it was passed
down unexpectedly.
Still, in a slightly
uncanny way,
love is passed on.
My hands fit right
on your shoulders.
Yeon!
I missed you, Granny.
Don't be a drama
queen. It's tacky.
I heard you pulled some
strings to get me out.
Me?
She made at least 200 calls.
Her brother ended up
blocking her number.
You couldn't live
without me, right?
Shove off.
I will soon, anyway.
This will be the last
day you see my face.
How so?
I can't be back here now
that I've become human.
I should live among them.
You'll only see him
once he's dead now.
Why would you say that
and jinx his life?
Don't you know how hard
it was to get him back?
Thank you for adoring
a troublemaker like me.
You kept me busy
until Ji A returned...
so that I wouldn't lose my mind.
Because of you and Hyeonuiong,
I've made it this far.
Have a good life, Yeon.
Living as a mortal...
isn't as easy as it sounds,
but I'm sure you'll
do a good job.
Sure.
I wish you both live a
long and healthy life.
I'll get going then.
Hey!
Since you're here, stuff
yourself with some tteokbokki.
Am I supposed to
get some for you?
- Must you ask?
- Right.
Darn, it's spicy.
How is this spicy? Unbelievable.
I got medium level spiciness,
but it's still very spicy to me.
Sundae is good.
Like she has always been,
Granny is still a workaholic.
I like the fish cake.
- Only one thing changed.
- The fish cake is to die for.
Now, the married couple
sometimes stay up all night...
talking about
their deceased son.
Also, tteokbokki with a
medium level of spiciness...
is said to be somewhat
enjoyable too.
Gosh, it's spicy.
Well, I don't know...
if love really lasts forever.
But you like drumsticks,
and I like chicken breasts.
You like egg yolks,
and I like egg whites.
Therefore, that makes
us the perfect couple.
You're probably the first
woman who confesses love...
with chicken and eggs.
We're finally getting married.
And you've finally become human.
The Korean word "human"
is very interesting to me.
If you carve away the corners
of the final consonant,
that word turns into "love".
You see,
I don't have the
best personality,
and I'm not sure if
I'll do a good job...
of living as a human being,
but I know I will love
you more than anything.
I love you.
I love you too.
What? What's with the
raining flowers in fall?
They're congratulating him.
The flowers, trees, and wind...
are saying goodbye...
to their beloved master.
They're thanking him for how
much he took care of them.
And the extremely handsome
nine tailed fox...
lived happily ever after.
Hey, stop narrating
it your own way.
I'm married to a director,
so I only state facts.
- Turn it around.
- Okay.
Should we have a baby?
I'd love to.
But there's something
that worries me.
What is it?
What if our daughter thinks
I'm an embarrassment...
for not having
graduated college?
Then we can tell her you did
something even more amazing.
- And what's that?
- That you saved my life...
and the entire world,
although no one really
knows that part.
Well, it's the truth.
But who says we're going
to have a daughter?
- Did I say "daughter"?
- Yes.
That's weird. That can't be.
SHIN JU'S ANIMAL HOSPITAL
Be honest with me. How
does it feel to be human?
Is it better than being a fox?
I thought it'd be really
nice, but I was wrong.
How should I say this?
There are so many variables.
"Variables"?
Apparently, I have astigmatism.
And it's different in each eye.
Look.
This makes me look...
a lot less handsome in no time.
If you compare the
two of us right now,
I think I look a
bit more handsome.
- That's not true.
- You're right.
And that's not the only problem.
Did you lie to me?
You told me we're
going to eat ice cream.
I didn't lie to
you. I told you...
we need to go somewhere
before we eat.
I'd rather get
stabbed by a knife.
I really can't
stand anesthetics.
- Be a good boy.
- Let me go.
How can your love
change like this?
What are you talking about?
Root canal treatment was
literally the worst thing ever.
Living as a human
being is about...
fighting against
unexpected kinds of pain.
Ta-da.
What do you think? Is it good?
You cook the best instant
noodles in this entire world.
Honey, do we have soju?
Of course.
- Cheers.
You worked so hard today.
You did too.
Instant noodles and soju. This is
what's so nice about being human.
The next time you fall,
try to get back up
on your own, okay?
Here.
Thank you.
- Did you fall?
- Yes.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
You should've been more careful.
Does it not hurt?
No, this man helped me get up.
He didn't get to be reborn
as a humpback shrimp.
How was your day?
It was the same old.
I saw someone strange at
the police station today.
Why did that person
look strange?
He was an old man
wearing a Hahoe mask.
But that mask wouldn't
come off his face.
It was as if it was stuck there.
A Hahoe mask?
By any chance, did you
step on bird poop today?
No, not bird poop.
I did step on gum though.
Darn it.
Why?
He's a spirit of misfortune.
Misfortune?
MISFORTUNE THAT COMES TO HUMANS
EVERY 9TH YEAR OF 10-YEAR CYCLES
There may be entities
that we are unaware of...
cohabitating in
this world with us.
Perhaps those countless urban
legends that circulate...
are just stories about them.
I've overheard the secrets...
of the world.
Living as a human being means...
that life is full of firsts...
and lasts.
First snowfall. First step.
First picnic.
First root canal.
And...
Forever...
my first love.
Hey, you.
Are you the spirit
of misfortune?
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
"TALE OF THE NINE TAILED"