Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
- Give up your body.
Please don't die.
Don't die...
because of me.
I found you.
I also...
waited for you.
CHAPTER 4: I ALSO
WAITED FOR YOU
I know you got
hurt because of me.
But I didn't think it'd be
okay to take you to a hospital.
My mom was a doctor, so I
learned how to give first aid.
Open your mouth.
What?
- Open your mouth.
- My mouth?
It's candy.
When I was young, my mom used
to give me strawberry candy...
every time I went to the
hospital to get a shot.
After that, I wasn't scared
of going to the hospital.
It just reminded me...
of the sweet taste
of strawberry candy.
Keep talking.
Oh, right. When I was nine,
I got admitted in a pediatric
mental health hospital.
After my parents disappeared,
I told the police that
the culprit isn't human.
I wanted to get discharged,
but my doctor wouldn't let me.
I wouldn't have let
you leave either.
So I kept my eyes on him.
And later on, I saw
him stealing propofol.
So what did you do?
So I made him a deal.
"Do you want me to
shout and call someone,"
"or will you let
me get discharged?"
I can't forget the day
I got discharged...
and went home in my uncle's car.
Mom.
Dad.
I finally came home
in three months.
But I didn't like being all
alone without my parents,
so I sat in front
of the front door.
And the two fireflies I saw...
felt as if they were my parents.
I also...
waited for you.
ABSTRACT ALGEBRA
Yeon!
Look at you. You're
a complete mess.
You had me so worried.
- Will you please be quiet?
- "Be quiet"? Why?
Why?
You're the vet from...
Dr. Koo Shin Ju?
Director Nam?
You guys know each other?
No way.
What are you guys doing
together? Does that mean...
Yeon!
You finally did it!
You finally found her after
waiting like a fool for 600 years.
What did you call me?
Oh, sorry.
I'm talking gibberish
because I'm so touched.
Even if I die right now, I'd
be able to rest in peace.
- Are you crying?
- Why am I tearing up?
Excuse me.
Let me introduce myself.
I was his loyal subject ever
since he was a mountain spirit.
And right now, I'm
his doctor, bodyguard,
and housekeeper.
He doesn't even know how
to wash his own underwear.
He's only able to live a
decent life thanks to me.
Shut your mouth.
I finally get why you know
everything about animals.
You were actually a fox?
Don't look so close.
I can't trust anyone anymore.
- I interviewed you so many times.
- He's so full of himself now.
He made his own autograph
and practices taking selfies.
Let's just say it
was all meant to be.
My gosh.
I'll take this.
The bezel for this watch
is made with red gold,
so it's a bit expensive.
It costs 35,000 dollars.
Can I get a discount?
- Pardon?
- It was a joke. Wasn't it funny?
I've never seen you make a joke.
What kind of person
do I seem like to you?
You're the type of person
that every man wants to be.
From head to toe.
But in my eyes, I seem
like a complete wreck.
I'm sick of waking
up every morning.
No matter what I buy or eat,
nothing ever pleases me.
I must've lived
for way too long.
How much does that watch cost?
This one is really cheap.
Why do you wear
something so cheap?
It belonged to my late father.
It must be precious to you.
Yes, it's the most precious
thing in the world to me.
Give it to me.
Isn't the handwriting so cute?
My father never learned
to read, so I taught him.
Give me this.
- Pardon?
- I'll trade you for my watch.
You're kidding, right?
No. I wonder which
you'll choose.
Family?
Or...
- Shall we go?
- Let's go.
Okay, okay.
It's chicken porridge.
It's hot. I'll
blow on it for you.
Hey. I'm not a child. Get away.
You dressed the
wounds very well.
Thank you. Don't you
need to do anything else?
He heals at a different
rate from other people.
But he still has to rest
for at least a month.
He's in your care.
It would be better for you to...
The power of love. That's
the most effective treatment.
- Sorry?
- Mr. Lee...
has a nasty temper, can't
express himself, and he's stingy,
but he's the biggest
romantic in the world.
He owns properties worth
over 30 million dollars.
He's good looking. He
has no chronic diseases.
His life expectancy
is so long, it's sick.
Leave.
I'm leaving. Bye.
But...
Give him his ice cream after
he finishes his porridge.
Even if he whines, okay?
And when he takes a bath, give him
three rubber duckies. He loves them.
- Hey, I said to leave!
- I'm leaving.
I'm leaving.
What is that?
Something that was...
the most precious thing to a
young man until a moment ago.
He doesn't have anything
like that anymore.
Just like me.
What? What is it?
Give me come.
What are you thinking about?
Just...
that something simple like
ice cream could make life...
this sweet.
What was your first love like?
What kind of a person was she?
Not something like she
was pretty like a lotus.
Her name was A Eum,
which meant "high sound".
A Eum.
That was her name.
She didn't have a tacky name
like people used to back then.
She must have been from
a wealthy family then.
How did you meet?
Unforgettably.
She treated me like a dog.
Do you want to die?
That's odd. Our pet dog
loves it when I do this.
What? How dare you?
Do you know who I am?
You're a fox, right? I'm A Eum.
Don't come back here again.
- Why not?
- This is a spirit's resting place.
Why?
Are you stupid?
They say the nine-tailed
fly across the sky.
You must be very powerful.
Now that you know, scram.
Unless you want
to be tiger food.
I want you to serve me.
- What?
- I'll feed you rice every day.
I'll clothe you in silk too.
You'll live in luxury. Okay?
How cute.
She was too cute, so I gave
her a noogie and sent her away.
- And?
- And...
she went down, crying, and
came back within the day.
She's a persistent one.
Who won?
I let her win.
I was incredibly
magnanimous at the time.
Of course, I still am now.
I'm very magnanimous.
If you miss again,
I'm going to eat you.
Why can't you do
something this easy?
I told you. Shooting an arrow
is about riding the wind.
And I told you, I'm the
master of that wind.
- Let's do it again.
- You have no talent.
Human. Just go and do
embroidery or fly a kite, okay?
Don't you dare order me around.
You're testing my patience.
Look at this kid. Who are
you to have patience with me?
Throw it.
It wasn't that I couldn't
hit it, I didn't.
I didn't want you to get hurt.
Who are you to worry about me?
I like you.
You little human. Do you want
to be struck by lightning?
Isn't it time to tell me?
Why must it be an arrow?
Don't give me garbage
like, "Because it's cool."
I'm going to kill my father.
What? Your father?
Why? Who's your father?
He's the king of this nation.
Shoot.
As long as I'm around,
the wind belongs to you.
What an impressive first love.
It turned out she was the
king's seventh daughter.
An abandoned princess.
But why did she want
to kill her own father?
He was a king, and
yet not a king.
What?
Screams were heard
daily from the palace,
and hardship and suffering
were unending on the peninsula.
An evil being was in the palace
pretending to be the king.
An evil being?
Back in the day, people
called it the earth dragon.
Earth dragon?
A dragon buried in the ground...
Do you mean Imoogi?
My gosh. You are even
better looking in person.
You're very handsome.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
You sent a very generous
advance payment in cash.
- Does anyone know...
- Definitely not.
Anyway, whose child
is the baby...
that you're so secretive...
Actually, who cares
whose child the baby is?
All babies are angels.
The kid's room is the last
one on the second floor.
I see.
Then what should I do first?
As of now,
he only needs his meal.
Yes, of course.
Kid?
It's time for your meal.
Do you perhaps have
trouble hearing?
My gosh, your face...
Your wrist too.
Please don't tell me
that this is contagious.
I don't know.
How about you see for yourself?
What about the
rest of the story?
I never recollect
any more than that.
How did she die?
Your obsession will
bring about calamity.
To both you and
her who was reborn.
It's none of your business.
But it is. I know it is.
At times,
it's better to be in the dark.
So live your life as the
clueless person you have been.
I don't intend to live...
as the past version of
someone I do not know.
No, not yet!
It's fine. I've rested enough.
Let's get some fresh air.
It's hideous, isn't it?
I actually like it.
It suits you.
But I don't.
It's like I'm telling the
world that I was in a zoo.
- Says who?
- That veterinarian.
Unlike other men, he
doesn't push himself on me.
He looks at me with pity
and sadness in his eyes.
Then don't make him
look at you that way.
How?
How can one see without eyes?
Stop the car.
Let's raise the pot
from 5 dollars to 10.
- I'm in.
- It's mine anyway.
Here I go.
- No way.
- See that?
- Okay!
- What did I tell you?
Wait, it's not dead yet though.
- Hey!
- You're over the line.
- Take a step back.
- I'm not over the line.
Having fun, are we?
What the...
That's not how you
respond to your elders.
I asked if you were having fun.
Is he serious?
What's it to you anyway? Let go.
Let go of me!
How did such weaklings reach
the top of the food chain?
Don't just stand there!
- Hi, guys.
- And who might you be?
Did you just swear at me?
Die, die!
You're... You're bleeding.
Why you...
It stings, doesn't it?
You can't start
weeping just yet.
I have all the time
in the world, you see.
YEONGJU HANEUL FUNERAL HALL
A morgue.
Nothing can top this as
a place for an outing.
It's quiet...
and has coffins.
Sorry about this, but
I can never let go...
of anything that bothers me.
Okay.
Come out.
Come on out.
- Hey, it's a fox.
- A fox.
Yes, I'm a fox.
Young sisters,
please come closer.
It's all right. Come this way.
That's it. Come closer.
Yes, that's close enough.
First of all, you
deserve this each.
Spirits shouldn't
cling onto humans.
Especially this human.
Ask away then.
What are your names?
- I'm Min Seo.
- I'm Yeon Seo.
Min Seo and Yeon Seo, you
have something to say to me.
Are you the victims
of this accident?
"CHILD NEGLECT MUST BE ADDRESSED:
THE TRAGEDY OF TWO YOUNG SISTERS"
Brother.
Have you read this?
The reporters are adding
fuel to the flame.
Darn it!
"CHILD NEGLECT MUST BE ADDRESSED:
THE TRAGEDY OF TWO YOUNG SISTERS"
SISTERS FALL FROM APARTMENT WINDOW,
FATHER ABSENT FOR THREE DAYS
SAFETY FIRST
Eeny, meeny,
Miny, moe.
Catch a tiger by the toe.
Ding, ding dong...
I'd rather not choose.
Why are you doing this to us?
This being a pastime of mine
is none of your business.
- Please don't kill us.
- Fine, you choose.
I made these myself.
Chance cards that are
either good or bad.
The probability is 50-50.
What are those?
Just pick one.
I made these myself.
Chance cards that are
either good or bad.
The probability is 50-50.
What are those?
Just pick one.
You picked an interesting one.
TALENT DONATION
"Talent donation".
Congratulations.
What are you guys good at?
We're good at playing baseball.
We're baseball players.
I love baseball.
If you let us go,
we'll teach you well.
Yes, we will.
I know what you
guys are thinking,
but that's not it.
You won't be able to play baseball
for the rest of your lives.
In other words, you'll literally
be donating your talents.
Are you all right-handed?
He looks left-handed to me.
Gosh, whatever. Yu Ri, just
break both of their hands.
- Let's go.
- No, please.
- We're sorry!
- We won't do it again!
- We promise we won't do it again!
- Please don't do this to us!
- Please!
- No, don't!
We won't do it again!
Please...
Who... Who are you?
I was close with Min
Seo and Yeon Seo.
Oh, I see.
I'm a truck driver, you see.
So I'm rarely ever home.
Yes, I know. I also know
that your brother...
took care of the kids
when you weren't home.
My brother happened to have
a job interview that day.
Do you know that
there are cherries...
inside the bag?
You must've been really
close with my kids.
These cherries were
quite expensive.
But they didn't
even touch them...
because they didn't like
anything I got for them.
Will you come with
me for a moment?
Help!
How do you think it'll
feel to get burned alive?
I heard this is about 1000°C.
Gosh, it's so hot. You're the reason
why I'm here feeling all this heat.
Please... Why are
you doing this to me?
You did something bad to
your nieces, didn't you?
No, I didn't. Who told you that?
- Just go inside.
- No, wait! Wait!
Wait! Yes, you're right.
I did it. It was me.
Please don't kill me.
You sexually molested
them, didn't you?
Yes, but I swear
I didn't mean to.
I was too drunk.
I didn't mean to kill them.
But the kids ran
to the balcony...
That's good enough.
You piece of trash!
The police are on
their way here.
I can't believe I had no idea.
I was such a fool.
Sir, the reason Min
Seo and Yeon Seo...
didn't eat any of
those cherries...
wasn't because they
didn't like you.
They just thought the
cherries were too precious.
They couldn't eat them because
they wanted to cherish...
what you got for them.
I'm so sorry.
He must like you.
I can't believe he's
wagging its tail...
even after what
he's been through.
He's so dumb and foolish.
I feel so bad for him.
Why don't we take him with us?
Oh, no.
Why did you come back?
I told you to run far away.
Does it hurt?
Oh, my gosh.
There was only one
thing I could do.
And that was to end
the pain myself.
No.
I can't do it.
I don't want to.
Yeon. Help.
Yeon!
Geomdoong.
Here.
I'm so excited.
Give him a lot of love, and
take good care of him, okay?
Okay, Yeon.
I'm so excited. You're
excited too, right?
Good boy.
Run faster.
I never should've
let him grow on me.
given him a name.
I never should've slept
with him in my arms.
The day Yeon left the
forest, I lost everything...
that was precious to me.
Let's take him with us. Please.
No.
Why not?
I don't like dogs. Their
life span is too short.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Farewell.
Hey, go play somewhere else.
Go on.
Get going.
Who were those kids?
This used to be a
grave for little kids.
They need to resolve
their resentment...
in order to leave
the Living Realm.
But it's too late.
I guess they died
a long time ago.
Back in the old days, they didn't
make gravestones for kids...
so that their parents
wouldn't be able to find them.
That's sad.
It's a sad custom that
was created in the past...
to prevent parents from dwelling
on their children's deaths.
Just like now,
parents were devastated to have
their children die so young.
You keep looking at me. Why?
No reason.
You just seem a little
different today.
You were the one who helped those
sisters resolve their resentment.
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
My gosh.
Is it going to be
a meal or alcohol?
You told me humans treat people
to things when they're grateful.
I prefer alcohol.
Didn't you bring an
umbrella earlier?
I lost it.
- Are you stupid?
- Yes, I'm stupid.
No wonder.
You didn't sound very clever
when you interviewed me.
What? Why is a tree...
Let's go.
You always carry this
umbrella with you.
I hate getting wet.
It's bad for the fur.
It must be like how
dogs hate taking baths.
- Right. Hey.
- Yes.
I caught you because
of this umbrella.
I let you catch me.
Whatever.
Like I can't lose
someone you if I tried?
Even if it pours like
this, I eat chicken.
Shin Ju likes chicken.
Hey.
Why were you out
during business hours?
I was bored out of my mind.
What... What brings
you here today?
Treat him.
How is he?
His bone was crushed.
He's malnourished
and has skin disease.
The leash dug into his skin.
Where's my necklace?
I need to talk to him.
Hurry.
Darn it.
What happened?
It hurt a lot, didn't it?
Yes. So she didn't do it?
Okay.
He isn't a pet.
I stole him. I thought he'd
be better off being a pet.
- Yu Ri.
- What?
You did good.
I didn't like the necklace
thief, but I like the dog thief.
- Dog thief?
- I can't do it even if I wanted to.
I can't cross the line.
I have no boundaries.
If you don't mind,
would you wait there?
It's okay.
How could you not
watch "Toy Story 3"?
When Woody stays behind and
watches Andy leave, and goes,
"So long, partner."
How could you not know that?
Isn't that a kids' movie?
It made adults
around the world cry.
I can't stand it when people
cry while watching a movie.
- Then which movie do you like?
- Me?
"Mad Max", "Avengers",
and every zombie movie
that ever existed.
I see. What's your
favorite type of music?
Anything by a boy
band, of course.
- What about classical music?
- I can't distinguish the singers.
Not singers, composers.
- Hiking.
- Not even if someone carries me.
Single malt whiskey.
I'd rather drink cold medicine.
- Korean food or western food?
- Always Korean food.
Me too.
You don't have many
friends, right?
Me neither.
We're a good match.
"You Quiz on the Block"
or "Amazing Saturday"?
- "Amazing Saturday"!
Yeon, what is your dream?
A future dream? At this age?
You know, like opening
a cafe after you retire.
Coffee tastes the best
when someone else makes it.
Like traveling around the world.
I'm a homebody, so I prefer
watching videos at home.
Saving up a million dollars.
A million dollars?
What's your account number?
I'll transfer it now.
Put that away.
- What? I can do smart banking.
- No.
If something that can never
come true can be a dream,
I want...
to become human.
Gosh. This nine-tailed
fox got spoiled by luxury.
If you want to know what
it's like to be human,
take the subway
during rush hour.
The Underworld is
closer than you think.
That's not all. You work
late, pull all-nighters,
listen to your boss nag,
which is all he ever does,
and the stress about
ratings pummel down on you.
- Should I get rid of it?
- What?
The TV station. You
said it torments you.
Whereas that is a
very novel approach,
let's drink first and
then think about it.
What about you?
What's your dream?
For me...
I'm fine if I live in a hut,
but I wish my my mom and
dad will be with me...
in my future.
Do you have a picture
of your parents?
Send me one.
Are you okay?
It's so dark.
The street lamps are out.
- Can't you do things like that?
- What?
It would be so cool if you
could use your powers...
to fix them.
Submit a request with
the local authority.
What a useless nine-tailed fox.
Shin Ju closes the clinic
and comes running...
if a light blows out in my home.
He trained you all wrong.
Even a nine-tailed fox
is afraid of electricity.
- We're here.
- Yes, we are.
- Okay, bye now.
- Okay. Go on in.
Hey.
Good night.
You too. Good night.
It was Yeon...
back then too.
THE SITE OF GOBLINS CAN
BRING LUCK OR CALAMITY.
NOODLES, SAMGYETANG
VIEWER BULLETIN BOARD
"I can't reach a
babysitter I know."
Ms. Kim, have you
read this story?
I'm in the zone,
so don't bother me.
- It'll only take a second.
- Leave me alone.
What's there to work on when you
copy and paste your own pieces?
I dare you to say that again.
I heard him loud and clear.
He said, "copy and paste."
Ms. Nam!
Don't you know that the pen
is mightier than the sword?
Today, you and I will both
take our last breaths.
Don't they get sick
and tired of that?
All right. So from now on,
you will build a stone tower
in the Underworld for Children.
When it's all built, a
goblin will appear...
and knock it all down,
but you must keep on
stacking the stones.
It's how you can
someday be reincarnated.
I don't want to go there.
My sister brushes her teeth
well and listens to our dad.
It may be called
as an Underworld,
but you'll be playing a
game of stacking blocks.
Just imagine how fun it'll be...
to play this game
with your sister?
I don't like stacking blocks.
My sister doesn't want to.
I'm afraid you have
no choice though.
Can I watch cartoons
in the Underworld?
You can't.
Then can I bring
this toy with me?
Objects from the Living
Realm aren't allowed.
I'm sorry, my dear.
Must you really be
this inconsiderate?
Always such a
stickler for rules.
Why not ban the dead
from receiving money too?
My thoughts exactly.
You, stay out of this.
Take the children
to the Underworld.
Got it. Kids, this way.
This way, please.
Kiddo, take good
care of your sister.
What a sap.
This way, please.
Is the Underworld for
Children still in operation?
They must be punished for
breaking their parents' hearts.
Isn't it bad that their
lives ended early?
Must they be framed
as unfilial as well?
It's to quicken the process
of their reincarnation.
The Afterlife desperately
needs a face-lift too.
We need a younger King
Hades for starters.
And a trip to the Underworld
of Tongue Ripping...
will snap some sense
into your head.
Again with the torture. This
isn't the Middle Age anymore.
Ripping of tongues in an era...
where we now brief
the dead via monitors?
Did you come by to pick a
fight with me this morning?
Of course not.
Here you go. It's
an iced Americano.
What do I need to do
to locate someone?
Are you a PI on the side now?
Here.
I already checked the
list for their names.
They're not dead but haven't
been in contact for 20 years.
- So?
- Let me use the Clairvoyance once.
Get that out of my face.
You know where they are, right?
- I don't.
- Don't be...
so stingy with your powers.
I meant that I can't see them.
- What?
- Those who I can't see...
They're not in the Afterlife
or the Living Realm.
I'd ask the ones who
initially took them.
Who took them?
And who may that be?
Why does my list of assignments
keep getting longer?
I know that this is to
keep food on the table,
- but you take it too far.
- Sandwiches.
Guys, stop!
Here comes the president
of our network.
It's been a while.
Hello, sir.
Has the job been fun lately?
We work to earn paychecks,
not to have fun.
You're as feisty as ever.
I heard your show had the
highest ratings last month.
That's right, so treat
us to a meal, sir.
Sure. I'll take your whole
team out for a meal soon.
Thank you, sir.
Have a good day!
Pubyokru of the Taedong river.
I miss sailing.
Who sails these days?
We now enjoy beer to the
crashing of the waves.
What nonsense are you spewing...
You're the old
totem, aren't you?
I am,
but I prefer makgeolli
over beer now.
You should know better than
to show your back to me.
I heard you're the
totem of Yeou Gogae.
I'm looking for some people.
Have you seen them before?
Yes or no?
I don't know.
I won't ask this again.
I really don't know!
You should've answered
me when I asked nicely...
instead of being
an intolerant brat.
So you're saying that someone
else knows about them?
Who may that be?
The g...
Louder, please.
The governor!
The governor?
For some reason,
the president of the
network only addresses you.
I know.
What's your secret?
For one, grow some balls.
That simple, is it?
You'll see once
you're at my rank.
Meeting the president from
an administrative position?
You'll cower just like me.
It's not like you to
eat honey-garlic bread.
When life takes you on
a roller coaster ride,
nothing grounds you like the
combination of sweet and salty.
Want some?
What flavor is that?
Blueberry. But don't you dare.
I'll let you once
you quit smoking.
You're such a jerk,
you know that?
Is this for real or am I
living in virtual reality?
Fit as a model and
just as handsome.
He also drives a sweet car.
Meanwhile, what's in
front of me is a tragedy.
That's verbal
harassment, you know.
Let's go.
Why are you here?
But...
What the...
What on earth?
- Where are we going?
- Just get in.
Hurry.
What just happened?
Beats me.
Where are we going?
To make your dream come true.
No way.
I even picked out some
songs you might like.
"NEWTON" BY MONSTA X
I'm looking for something.
What... What is it?
The eyebrows of a tiger.
- That's just a legend.
- So am I.
But I'm right here
holding onto your collar.
I'm only going to ask you once.
Did you see it or not?
No, I never saw it.
Really? Then you'll
just have to fall.
No, wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait a minute!
Those darn foxes.
Come and check this out!
Consider yourself lucky!
I'm doing this because I
never got to get married.
Check it out! 1, 2...
Over here!
Wait here for a moment. I
need to take a look around.
- Don't go anywhere.
- Okay.
HANBOK RENTAL SHOP
Please be reincarnated.
I promise...
to find you.
Where were you? I looked
everywhere for you.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Who do you keep looking for?
Yeou Gogae falls under
your jurisdiction, right?
You should focus
on staying alive.
You always get
hurt because of me.
You just need to find your family
and live like nothing ever happened.
You have the item that helps
us see the past, don't you?
What are you doing at
Korean Folk Village?
I came to check something.
It disappeared.
Something awoke
from the kid's body.
I know that Imoogi isn't dead.