Lee Dong-Wook
Jo Bo-Ah
Kim Beom
Kim Jung-Nan, Ahn Kil-Kang
Hwang Hee, Kim Yong-Ji
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
I knew it.
That jerk only cares
about his lady.
Hey, kid!
Yeon?
I heard what you
just said about me.
I don't need your help.
Now is not the time
to be so arrogant.
You're not him.
Yeon wouldn't come to save me.
You're not wrong, I guess.
Show me proof that you're Yeon.
Proof? Like my social
security number?
Jwibulnori on the night
of the first full moon.
After having fun with flames,
you wet the bed.
- I called you this for three years.
- Shut it.
Bedwetter!
- I'm going to kill you.
- Them first.
Run!
Mom?
Dad?
Today, Ji Ah had...
a hypnotherapy session.
What did Dr. Kang say?
She's never seen a
case like hers before.
I know I shouldn't be,
but I can't help but be scared.
Would we be able to
protect our girl?
Will I be able to keep her safe?
Mom.
Mom?
Ji Ah, you're up.
I was going to wait
until we get home,
but here's your
birthday present.
My birthday?
This music box.
Could this be...
YEOU GOGAE
"Yeou Gogae"?
We must not go.
Do you like your gift?
We'll end up in that accident.
- Stop the car!
- Once Ji A is better,
we'll go to the park and
ride the merry-go-round.
Dad, can't you hear me?
Stop the car!
Dad?
Mom!
They just won't die. When
did they get this strong?
- Maybe we've gotten weaker.
- As if.
Forget the lightning. Not
even the wind will shift.
Your powers aren't working?
Where could we actually be?
Isn't it obvious? The
Forest of the Starved.
Are we, really?
Dad, stop the car!
Stop the car, Dad!
CHAPTER 9: SPIRIT OF DARKNESS
I'm surprised.
I honestly thought
he'd come for the girl.
But he went to his brother.
So much for being at
each other's throats.
A mountain spirit
isn't an easy opponent.
Sorry?
Even at this very moment,
he's challenging me.
Are you saying he chose
his brother on purpose?
He probably figured it out...
that this isn't just
a test for these two,
but a test for him as well.
You've got to be kidding me.
How did the juice lady know...
that I can't get on planes?
- Is that for real?
- What happens if you do?
I suddenly go out of breath
and then sweat excessively.
Once I put on the seat
belt, I black out.
What did the juice
lady say to you?
She asked what I feared
the most in my life.
What you fear the most?
Could it be...
My gosh.
What is it?
There's a similar urban legend
that's been floating around online.
WHO KNOWS ABOUT
THE JUICE LADY?
- "Who knows about the juice lady?"
- It's similar, right?
A lady hands you a juice box
and asks what you fear the most.
We think that this
is an urban legend...
similar to that of
the Hong Kong Granny.
There's one big difference
though. Once captivated by her,
you hear a song.
- A song.
- Did you hear it?
It's this one.
Isn't this the song that's sung
when dancing the ganggangsullae?
The lyrics give you
the chills though.
One tells you to
open the door...
while the other says
that there is no key.
Those two phrases repeat
throughout the song.
I'm loving this.
Is there anyone who
actually heard this song?
We couldn't find anyone which
is why we dropped the story.
How so?
Rumor has it that
no one wakes up...
after listening to the song.
- Forever?
- Yes, forever.
That's ridiculous!
What the...
Is this the "Unveiling
Urban Legends" team?
- Ji A, what's wrong?
- Ms. Nam?
- What's going on?
- Wake up!
Ji A! Ji A, wake up!
- My goodness.
- What happened?
Yeon, wake up.
Yeon.
Mr. Lee!
She would've crossed
Yeou Gogae by now.
Will I be able to
save them both...
from this Underworld?
Please. I hope I didn't
make the wrong choice.
Is this the best you can do...
to thank me for
saving your life?
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
Why are you here?
There's no way you
came here to save me.
I just had some free time.
I figured I'd use this chance to
see my one and only brother...
get sent to the Afterlife.
Don't joke with me. Why
did you choose me over her?
Good question.
I picked the wrong door.
You're lying.
I thought I was on
my way to save Ji A.
But when I got here, a bedwetter
was close to losing his life.
- How did this happen?
- I got bitten.
I guess I was pretty yummy.
The bleeding is one thing,
but you even have a bad fever.
I guess the poison
has started to spread.
It takes only an hour for the poison
to spread throughout the body.
I need to get him out
of here before that.
This is why I told you...
not to hang around with Imoogi.
Don't try to be a big
brother. It's really annoying.
You jerk.
Now run for your life.
What can I do to wake him up?
No one can wake him
up from the outside.
I tried everything I could,
but I wasn't able to
wake my husband up.
- Was it the same person?
- Yes.
In the past, she was a peddler
who sold items for women.
She'd approach people
with shiny things...
and ask them what
they feared the most.
That's how she bewitched them.
My husband was scared of tigers.
The things she makes people
see... Are they not illusions?
I also thought they
were hallucinations.
But Shin Ju,
I saw...
my husband get
bitten by a tiger.
His bones broke, and
his flesh got torn out.
My goodness.
Mr. Lee, please wake up.
Mr. Lee!
My goodness.
What...
What is she called?
The Spirit of Darkness.
"The Spirit of Darkness"?
She lives off the things
that are hidden...
deep inside our dark souls.
Ji A.
Mom?
Sweetheart, wake up and eat.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Why do you think?
It's Sunday today.
Did you work until
late yesterday?
Why does your company always
send you on business trips...
and make you work overtime?
"Company"?
Where do I work?
- Are you still sleepy?
- Answer me.
You're a director at a
broadcasting company.
You always get summoned by the
Press Arbitration Commission.
Why did I become a director?
- Because...
- To find you and Dad.
In 1999, at Yeou
Gogae, my life...
No, not just me.
Our entire family...
got destroyed.
What are you talking about?
You're not my mom.
You can't fool me twice.
Stop talking nonsense and
come eat your breakfast.
You really need to stop
joking around with me.
- What?
- Stop bringing up the accident.
Your dad and I were
completely heartbroken...
back when you were
in a coma for years.
I was...
in a coma?
Do you remember what
you used to give me...
every time I went to the
doctor to get a shot?
Strawberry candy.
Now stop it and come outside.
Wait.
What is it this time?
I want...
walnut cookies.
Walnut cookies?
Mom, I want...
walnut cookies.
We never buy walnut cookies.
I had to go to the hospital
because it turned out...
I was allergic to nuts.
Oh, right. I forgot.
You're not my mom.
Where's my mom?
I am your mom.
Stop talking nonsense.
My goodness, you're
allergic to nuts.
She got to meet
her family again?
How nice.
I thought her fear would be those
fake parents, but I guess not.
I guess that's not...
what she's really scared of.
It looks like her family
is what drags her down...
just like how it was
in her past life.
Is it getting colder?
Her subconscious
created this place.
She probably won't welcome us...
since we're outsiders.
Let's go.
Nice! Cheesecake!
Did you see?
My plan failed.
Yeon didn't show.
Then why are you back?
She can try to use her brain,
but she won't get out alive.
When you really look at it,
the mind is much more
fragile than they think.
It's the world that the lifelong
wounds of the heart created.
If she dies in there,
will she die for real?
Do you want to try too?
Let go of me!
- Spirit of Darkness.
- Yes?
Don't touch my things.
I was just playing.
Forgive me.
There was a lot more
after "Forgive me."
"He may be Imoogi but was
asleep for over 600 years."
"He can't be as strong
as he used to be."
"Why don't you..."
"try me?"
I want to see as well.
How dare I think such a thing?
Please forgive me.
Will you please give me a hug?
Mom.
My mom.
It's okay if it's a dream.
Please don't go.
Don't leave me all alone.
Did you have a
scary dream again?
Yes.
I wish it were all a dream.
What was the dream about?
About losing...
you and Dad.
Why are you crying?
It was just a dream.
I'm sorry...
for surviving alone.
I tried to be strong
all this time,
but to be honest, I was
terribly scared and lonely.
I hated going home,
so I used to sit...
at a bus stop for hours.
I'm sorry, Mom.
To be honest,
I hated you and Dad a little..
You left me all alone,
and you wouldn't come back
no matter how long I waited.
You didn't forget me, right?
How could I forget...
a daughter this pretty?
I've missed you, Mom.
We've been going in circles.
We don't have time for this.
I wonder if Ji A is okay.
Please. Please hang
on a little longer.
Let go.
You're in no
condition to be proud.
I'm a corpse without my pride.
You look like a corpse already.
You've heard of
phantom pain, right?
You mean how a soldier who
lost his leg in a war...
complains of pain in his
leg all night long, right?
The moment you sense pain in
a leg that is not there...
is when true pain begins.
Once pain begins, the door
will have disappeared.
That is the world
she shows them.
Doorkeeper, doorkeeper,
open the door
I can't I don't have the key
- What is it?
- I can't go any further.
The poison spread
everywhere. I can barely see.
I'm sick of walking
with this leg.
So?
You'll sit here and become
food for evil spirits?
Go to your woman. It's
too late for me anyway.
You haven't changed.
You're just like
when we first met.
You still give up easily
and you still whine.
Why are life and death
so simple for you?
Because nothing
is precious to me.
I don't have a first love to
protect with my life as you do,
and I don't have a family that
I'm waiting desperately for...
as she does.
I shouldn't have come.
Neither then nor now.
I came to see you because I
heard you had my father's blood,
but you're pathetic.
You have no will to live either.
I wasted my time.
I'm leaving.
Once I die,
bury me in the woods of
Baekdudaegan where we used to live.
Am I your will?
I wish we could go
back to those days.
There were azaleas everywhere.
It's strange.
I can't remember how
the azaleas tasted...
back then.
If you don't remember
how the azalea tasted,
get out alive and
eat some, you idiot!
At least try to
survive, will you?
Be honest. Why
did you come here?
To save both Ji A and you.
- You expect me to believe that?
- I don't care!
I almost died by your knife.
You massacred an entire town.
- You deserved it.
- Exactly.
Why are you saving
someone you tried to kill?
Listen carefully.
My sword has never
missed, not even once.
I have never...
missed the target.
Think hard with that stupid brain
of yours why you survived my sword.
I'm leaving. And I'm
never coming back.
Boat number four just set
sail down Samdo River.
Tell the captain to
turn the boat around.
An elder in the ICU
passed away just now...
still hooked to the machine.
So where were we?
- The Spirit of Darkness.
- The Spirit of Darkness?
Is such a thing still
present in this realm?
After talking to her,
Mr. Lee and Lady A Eum...
I mean, Ms. Nam. Anyway,
they're out cold.
Please tell me how
I can help them.
You're in over your head.
The girl is with her family...
and Yeon is at the
Forest of the Starved.
The Forest of the Starved?
Probably to save
his younger brother.
- Then his brother too?
- Let me ask though.
Since when were those two tight?
How's that the issue right now?
- It is to me.
- Honey!
He takes on too much
of the burden himself.
He's the kind that
digs his own grave.
That's what made him
a mountain spirit.
The spirit of the mountains...
had his heart touched by
each and every organism.
So how could he not
care for his brother?
Brother, my foot.
Rang committed too many crimes.
Honey, how can you be so...
Please help them, ma'am.
I will give up my life
instead, so please.
You're making a
fool of yourself.
Why give up your life for
something Yeon chose to do?
Please let me know
how I can save them,
and I'll do everything
you order me to do.
Everything I order?
Don't you care about your life?
How could you trade it in
for that piece of cloth?
I'm sure this is
what Mr. Lee wants.
You and Yeon both. It
must be a fox thing.
I don't quite get it though.
Why did he choose Rang
instead of Ms. Nam?
They're both in a world created
by their unresolved issues.
For them both, that's family.
If she is reunited with the
family she's been searching for,
there wouldn't be
room for anyone else.
There will be no way for
him to enter the house.
Do you mean...
Yeon probably already knew...
what he's up against.
Does an exit even exist?
There was an entrance, so
there must be an exit too.
I came through the wardrobe.
The wardrobe door
led to our old house.
Not the Forest of the Starved?
No.
Tell me everything you saw.
The village people came
with weapons in their hands.
My mom watched as they
beat me to a pulp.
- Then...
- The Forest of the Starved.
Yes.
No wonder. I knew it.
That's why we
couldn't spot a door.
What do you mean?
Haven't you figured
out who that lady is?
Is it someone you know?
She's been gouging you
with your worst memories.
Are you saying...
What's her name again?
The Spirit of Darkness.
MISSING AFTER CAR
ACCIDENT AT YEOU GOGAE
This room...
may seem like
mine, but it isn't.
Where on earth...
am I?
What's that noise?
Sae Rom.
What did the doctor say?
They ran every test on her,
but they can't figure
out what's wrong.
Unbelievable. What
on earth is going on?
Ji A, open your
eyes. Please wake up.
Up until a minute ago,
I was at the office.
OFFICE LOUNGE
The juice lady.
Miss, what do you fear the most?
It must be Yeou Gogae.
That's right. After
my encounter with her,
I was taken to Yeou Gogae.
OFFICE LOUNGE, JUICE LADY,
YEOU GOGAE, WHERE AM I?
Then what is this place?
Kiddo, are you
trying to starve us?
- Dad?
- I'm hungry.
- Dad!
- Goodness.
My little princess.
- Let's go and eat.
- Sure.
Come on.
OFFICE LOUNGE, JUICE LADY,
YEOU GOGAE, WHERE AM I?
The path ends here.
Just keep going.
Not on this leg.
A path and a door will appear
when you overcome your fear.
- I don't see any door.
- Don't be a wuss!
Stay strong and think of
what you fear the most.
What...
What I fear the most?
Being abandoned.
Mom abandoned me...
and so did you.
You've got to be kidding me.
I...
never abandoned you.
I see it.
Let's go.
Make sure you stay alive.
Keep climbing!
Don't look!
She's not your mom! Don't look!
Mom?
Darn it.
Darn it!
No!
Mr. Lee!
I need to go.
Go where?
Where do you need to go?
To Yeon.
I must go to Yeon.
Where are you trying to go?
To Yeon...
I need to go to Yeon.
Gimbap.
Dad, it's your handmade gimbap.
Yes, he made gimbap again.
The end parts always
taste the best.
- Let's eat the ends first.
- Let's sprinkle some sesame seeds.
Let's eat.
Let's try it. It's
going to be delicious.
- Does it taste good?
- Yes.
It's delicious.
Ji A.
Thank you for the meal.
- The soup is delicious too.
- Really?
Spinach, carrots, cucumber,
ham, and pickled radish.
What's wrong? Don't you like it?
It's not that.
The ingredients are very
simple, but for some reason,
no other gimbap ever
tastes this good.
Is that a compliment?
It's a compliment, right?
My daughter just complimented
me. I'm so happy.
It feels great.
- Eat up.
- Okay.
It's even more delicious today.
Really? Thank you.
Suddenly, I started to think...
that the life I've lived until now
might've been a long nightmare...
and that this one
might actually be real.
If this is a dream,
I really hope I never wake up.
OFFICE LOUNGE, JUICE LADY,
YEOU GOGAE, WHERE AM I?
What's going on?
- Is something happening to her?
- Hey.
- Ji A! Ji A, wake up!
- Wait.
Doctor! Doctor!
Where's the doctor?
Go get the doctor.
Doctor, over here.
It's delicious.
I spilled some here.
Your dad is unbelievable. Here.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Who was that just now?
Who was he again?
Does it taste better than the ones
I made for you when we got married?
I can't remember.
Why can't you remember? I
made you gimbap so often.
It was too long ago.
You must not be late.
If you're late, they'll never
be able to leave that world.
We didn't do anything. We
were just by her side...
Where did she go?
- What?
This is all I can do.
I hope you both return.
This was when you made us...
carnations for the first time back
when you were in kindergarten.
You know the safety
pin that comes with it?
You accidentally poked
my chest with that.
And I ended up bleeding so much.
- I did that?
- Yes.
You were an amazing daughter.
Don't we still have the
carnation somewhere?
I made sure I kept
it nice and safe.
Ta-da.
"Mom. Dad. I love you."
You still have this?
Of course. It's our
family treasure.
My goodness. Let me see.
You really preserved it well.
Of course. It's precious to me.
- Let's see.
- You smudged your fingerprints.
- The phone is ringing.
- You're right.
- She's adorable.
- Look at the other hand.
I know. Gosh, it's
all coming back.
- Don't you hear the phone ringing?
- She's so adorable.
Look at all the baby hair.
Exactly.
- She has baby hair here as well.
- You're right.
- She's so cute.
- This was so long ago.
Hello?
It's me.
Who?
Lee Yeon.
"Lee Yeon"?
I'm sorry I couldn't go
there to bring you back.
Who are you?
I think I know you,
but I don't remember.
You must remember.
You need to realize where
you are and why you're there.
You need to realize that on your own
in order to come back to reality.
What do you mean?
Come back, Ji A.
I'll always be waiting for you.
Don't hang up.
You must come back.
I wonder who that was.
I don't know who he was,
but I feel like I left behind
something really important.
It's a bundle of mugwort.
It's special enough.
At least to me today.
I'm sorry I couldn't go
there to bring you back.
What if I've been bewitched?
You're here.
You must remember.
You need to realize where
you are and why you're there.
Come back, Ji A.
Did you sleep well?
I'll always be waiting for you.
You'll be able to
find your parents.
I'll make sure of it.
Thanks, Yeon.
Yeon.
It's the poison of
the evil spirit.
Do something.
Mr. Lee Yeon isn't back yet.
No! You can't go.
I'll die if he dies.
I'll repay you for this somehow.
I'm begging you.
Help him. I'm begging you.
- Look at this hat.
- It's so cute.
Isn't this hat pretty?
- Did you knit it?
- Yes.
How is she so tiny?
Oh, my gosh.
- She's tiny even now.
- I know.
Ji A. Look at this.
It was the day you
started babbling.
You threw up on your mom's chest
right after we took this picture.
It was because we tried
new formula that day.
How do you remember all of that?
Gosh. Because we love you.
Because we love our
daughter's every gesture,
kick, babble,
and cries so loud that
it woke up the neighbors.
I see.
I was very loved.
So cute. Look at that face.
So cute.
Look at this.
You know...
How would you feel
if you lost me?
Why would we lose you?
I'm just asking.
Things happen in life.
My gosh. Don't you worry.
We'll search the corners
of the earth and find you.
- Of course. You're my baby.
- Of course.
I'll do the same.
I promise I will find you both.
What do you mean?
Someone asked me...
what I feared the
most in the world.
What I fear the most...
is being parted from you.
What's wrong?
Sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
- Honey, stop her!
- Ji A!
If you walk out there,
you may never see us ever again!
Ji A.
Why are you trying
to abandon us?
I'm not.
Ji A.
Stay here and live with us.
This isn't reality.
Who cares?
Our family is happy here.
That's all that matters.
Why are you trying to be alone?
Mom and Dad are here.
I'm not alone.
Yeon is with me.
Ji A.
- Please.
- Ji A. Please.
I have faith in Yeon.
Ji A!
That wench woke up too.
Isn't this cheating?
It looked like fair play to me.
What should we do now?
- This is good enough.
- What?
I simply wanted to look
into the abyss of her heart.
And I got Yeon thanks to that.
Yeon.
You woke me up.
You said you'd
always wait for me.
Where are you?
Just where did you go?
So this is my
personal Underworld.
Consumed by loneliness...
and dying in a world...
without her.
How's Mr. Lee?
It'll take a few days for
the poison to leave his body,
but he'll be fine in no time.
Why aren't you
asking me anything?
You can see...
why I approached you.
You knew already.
I happened to see
you two together.
I was taken to a junkyard
and beaten up thanks to that.
- By Mr. Lee?
- Yes.
Then why did you treat him?
Because I didn't
want you to cry.
Shin Ju.
Mr. Lee.
How's Yeon?
Is he back?
Mr. Lee. Please...
wake up.
What do we do? Mr. Lee...
I wonder...
whether Ji A
returned home safely.
I wanted to tell her...
how pretty she looked
when eating dakbal.
I wanted to wish her...
the most typical
good night's sleep.
I wanted to spend...
more time with you
in this lifetime.
I wanted to protect
all your nights...
and all your days.
It seems like I'm
stuck here though.
I miss you,
Yeon.
Even a nine-tailed fox who
was also a mountain spirit...
can't do better.
Hey, don't die.
It won't be any fun if you do.
At least he's not dead yet.
This sweet body of yours
will serve Imoogi...
and bring disorder
to this world.
Spirit of Darkness.
What on earth?
You're awake.
Did Ji A get back home safely?
Why does that matter when
you're at the brink of death?
Please...
Please tell me.
But I don't want to.
I'm desperate.
Please tell me.
Stop making a fool of yourself.
Fine. She made it out.
But she would've been
better off staying though.
First her parents and now you.
She's barely
hanging on as it is.
So she's back home.
You're smiling?
Of course. Did you
expect me to cry?
It wasn't easy luring
you to this place.
What?
Do you really believe...
that one lousy spirit could
pull me off that cliff?
You deliberately...
Spirit of Darkness,
it's my turn to say
your signature phrase.
"What do you fear the most?"
I am darkness itself and the
embodiment of your fears.
Why would I fear anything?
You're dying, aren't you?
People have forgotten
all about you now.
No one speaks stories
of you anymore.
You seek attention by
giving out juice boxes...
and take your anger out
on Ms. Snail Bride...
since she's more well-known.
How... How dare you.
My brother couldn't
even recall your name.
Shut it!
You...
will be trapped in the
endless torment you created...
and live wishing you were dead.
Not so fast.
I see you forgot
one crucial detail.
This isn't the Forest
of the Starved.
It's the subconscious
of a mountain spirit.
In other words, you're
on my home ground.
I can't see anything.
What is it that you want?
Not you, that's for sure.
I found you.
I'll soon be coming for you,
so sit tight.
The nine-tailed fox who fell
in love with a human girl.
Once again,
you'll be the one
to end her life.
That is your destiny.
I'd worry more about
your fate if I were you.
Don't come to me.
Stay where you are.
From now on,
I'll go to you.
I...
waited for you.
TALE OF THE NINE TAILED
Repay my kindness, Yeon.
No.
I was supposed to have it all.
I was meant to be the
mountain spirit...
and have that woman by my side.
You woke up late.
I want to break the contract.
It's not entirely impossible.
You must kill your brother
with your own two hands.
I will.
Sacrifice the mountain spirit. Then
you can have your parents back.
Yeon, if you give up your body,
I will let everyone else live.