EPISODE 8
Excuse me.
Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
My lady!
Where on earth were you? I
looked for you everywhere.
We should go.
Young master!
Do you perhaps know her name?
Judging by her servant,
she must be the
daughter of Lord Lim.
The daughter of Lord Lim?
Someone with such
pretty hands...
must also have a beautiful face.
I should write a love letter.
A love letter?
Welcome.
I'd like to see everything
from here to here.
All of them?
Yes, all of them.
- Are you buying a birthday gift?
- No.
I'm going to confess
my love to her.
I will confess my love.
HE WILL CONFESS HIS LOVE.
Let me see. Those
two are friends,
but they like the same girl.
That's right, but
he liked her first.
He already said that she
was his and was off-limits.
Then why is he now being a jerk?
He only approached her to
get revenge on the other guy.
He's now being clingy after
falling in love with her.
What a jerk.
But falling in
love isn't a crime!
FALLING IN LOVE ISN'T A CRIME.
Shut it and take your
underwear to your room.
I need this and this.
Don't you have enough
makeup products?
Darn it.
By the way, if you
go on a school trip,
you'll have to show
your no-makeup face.
I'm planning to be the
last one to fall asleep.
Once everyone falls asleep,
I'll wash up and put
my makeup back on.
You'll do all that just not
to show your no-makeup face?
What was with you a
few days ago though?
Did Soo Ho reject you?
What are you talking
about? What rejection?
I thought you had
feelings for him.
We're just friends.
Whatever you say.
My female friends tend to
tell their feelings for me,
saying things like how they
see me more than just a friend.
Anyway, be careful not to
lose your friendship over it.
I could've taken
the bus, you know.
But your bags are heavy.
Thanks.
- I said, thanks.
- Oh, right.
- I'll get going then.
- Bye.
- Don't be a handful.
- Sure thing.
Joon Woo.
Joon Woo!
What's going on?
I currently am living in debt.
Debt? How much?
Is it from a loan shark?
It's a student loan.
A student loan?
How old are you?
I was born in 1990.
1990?
This is all I have saved up.
I bet you're disappointed.
This is why I never even
dreamed of dating...
The blood, sweat, and tears
you shed to save this up...
are evident in this money,
so the amount can
never be disappointing.
Hee Kyung...
Gosh. Come here for a second.
Joon Woo.
Sit right there.
You popped into my head, so I
bought it on my business trip.
They fit perfectly. You can
walk toward me in these.
I'll be good to you. So
be with me, Joon Woo.
Hee Kyung!
My cell phone.
- Hi, Mr. Han.
- Hi.
- What now?
- I forgot to bring my cell phone.
Gosh, you klutz.
You left it in the car?
- Squat down properly!
- Left foot.
- Right foot. We're sorry.
- Open the can.
- They're only potato chips.
As if.
Is this what they call
potato chips these days?
Join them!
- Would you like one?
- You must be thirsty.
Should I pour you a shot?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Join them.
- Gosh, it's cold.
- Look at you. Open your jacket.
You've got to be
kidding me. Join them!
We're off to enjoy
a new scenic view.
Did you all get jobs as waiters?
- Mr. Han.
- What's with all the alcohol?
- Have a safe trip.
- Oh...
Thank you.
You guys look adorable.
Gosh, what an eyesore.
I should also get
myself a girlfriend.
If you had control over that,
you wouldn't still be single.
What's with that hat? Are
you Kim Sat Gat or what?
This is why you don't
have a girlfriend.
- Show me some hearts.
- Are you kidding me?
Are you guys also going out?
Did you guys wear
matching outfits...
to announce that you
guys are a couple?
No way.
Ju Kyung, I feel like
that's what you had in mind.
Did you want to be my
girlfriend that badly?
How about we just date?
What's the matter with you?
- Wear your jacket.
- No, it's hot.
- It's not hot. It's cold.
- It's really hot right now.
Should I draw stripes
on your shirt?
- I have a marker.
- Hey, Soo Ho.
Take that.
- Sit here.
- What?
Soo Ho, you're
sitting in the front.
Let me sit next to you.
007, bang!
Bang!
No, wait. Time out.
Are you sitting next to each
other because you're a couple?
- Go on a date! Go on a date!
There are tons of empty
seats out in the front.
I like sitting in the back.
SAEBOM HIGH SCHOOL SCHOOL TRIP
You guys, look over here!
- Go to your tents and unpack.
- Okay.
Let's meet here
after 30 minutes.
- Okay.
- Go on.
- Let's go.
Come on.
Ju Kyung.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Soo Ah.
1, 2, 3.
- Okay. It all came out nice.
- Let's go.
- Nice.
- Come on.
This is so heavy.
My goodness, the mountain
feels so lively...
now that there are lots
of young people here.
- Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm the manager here.
Let me know if
you need anything.
Thank you.
By the way, your bird
is really pretty.
What?
Your bird.
- What bird?
- That bird.
There's a bird...
What's that microphone for?
I brought it so we could
have fun all night.
Dating is a must.
But marriage is a choice.
Amor fati.
Look at you all excited.
No one will be able
to sleep tonight.
No one will get to sleep!
- Dating is a must.
- It's a must!
I've never slept
in a tent before.
I haven't done this
in a while either.
The last time I went camping
was with Soo Ho's family...
when I was little.
You and Soo Ho must've been very
close since you guys were young.
Oh, right.
This girl from class 6
apparently asked Soo Ho out.
But he rejected her saying
he likes someone else.
Really? Are you serious?
Soo Ho likes someone?
Do you think that
might be you, Soo Jin?
You actually believe that?
He probably just made it up.
Stop getting me
involved, Soo Ah.
Some people thought you guys were
a couple ever since freshman year.
I mean, you guys make
a really good couple.
It's hard to believe that you guys
were just friends for 10 years.
Be honest with me, Soo Jin.
Haven't you ever had
any feelings for Soo Ho?
Yes, tell us.
Stop being absurd.
Haven't you? Come on. Tell me.
- Haven't you? Really? Seriously?
- Gosh, stop it!
Guys, look over here.
- Over here.
- Let's take selfies.
- Make me look pretty.
- Got it.
1, 2, 3.
Stop joking around.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Let's take a photo.
If you do it one more
time, I'll kill you.
- Stop fooling around.
- My gosh.
Let's turn this way.
- There. 1, 2, 3.
- You guys!
Gather together. Let
me take a group photo.
Don't get in my way.
Stop it.
Soo Ho, you should join.
- No, I'm good.
- Okay.
You have no sociability.
Why don't you go and join?
No, I can't be bothered.
- I'll take the photo now.
- Cheese!
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Gosh, Mr. Han!
- What was that for?
This is how it
comes out natural.
Mr. Han, take a photo of
the couple right here.
Hey! Who's dating in school?
- These two!
- I'd better not catch you together.
- They're dating.
- Sir, you're in the way.
- Let's do the heart signal.
- I'll take the photo now.
- Okay.
- 1, 2.
There you go.
- Mr. Han, come on.
- What's going on?
Are you guys really dating?
You're dating, aren't you?
Listen up guys! They're dating!
No, we're not.
Hurry up and take
off your clothes.
Why are you trying to make
me take off my clothes?
You're so weird.
I meant you should get changed.
- Look at them!
- They're having a lovers' quarrel!
I'm MC Jae Rong,
the cutest recreation MC ever!
It's nice to meet you all!
- Do you know the newspaper game?
- Yes!
A team consists of four people.
Choose someone whom you think
is going to be really good.
Or someone you really like.
I want you to gather
in a group of four!
Get together. Go on.
Find someone you like.
- Someone you have a crush on.
- Ju Kyung!
- Come on.
- If you don't like the guy,
just kick him.
That's right. There
need to be four people.
You can't be in a
group of 3 or 5.
- Go on. Just go.
- If there's a group with five,
- you need to let go of one.
- Go on.
Why would you leave
your girlfriend behind?
- What's wrong with you?
- Gather in a group of four.
Is there anyone
who's not in a group?
- Come on.
- Is everyone in a group of four?
- Yes!
If you're in a group,
gather together.
Nice.
Did you see that?
Let me explain how
this game works.
Fold the newspaper...
and stand on top of it.
If you manage to stand on top
for five seconds, you succeed.
Stand on top of the
newspaper. Go on.
Stand on top of the newspaper.
We'd better win.
- Hang on tightly.
- Got it!
- Good luck.
If you step out of the
newspaper, you're out.
Are you all standing on top?
- Don't step out of the newspaper.
- Hey.
- Do it properly.
Soo Ah, it hurts.
Good luck.
Now let's begin!
You're out!
- My gosh, careful.
- Hey, hold on tight.
Okay, there you go. You're out.
Let's give a round of applause
to the remaining three teams.
They're doing great.
They're so passionate.
Okay, now listen up.
This is important.
Concentrate. These three
teams are too good.
So let me upgrade
the game a little.
Fold the newspaper into one
fourths of the current size.
It's okay. Don't be scared.
Have some passion for the game.
- Okay then.
- Let's do this.
- What are you doing?
- Let's see who will...
This is what I'm talking about.
Where are you going?
Soo Ah, get on my back.
1, 2, 3.
No, no.
I'm so impressed.
You guys are doing great.
Let's count down.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
The all guys team is out!
The remaining two
teams passed the game.
They're doing great, but
there has to be a winner.
So the team that fails this
time will be the loser.
Ready, guys? I want all
the guys to raise one leg.
I can't do that.
- I can't.
- Raise one leg.
- Raise it. Go on.
- My gosh.
I'll start counting down as
soon as you raise your legs.
Raise one leg. 5, 4...
- Gosh, your hair stinks!
- 3, 2,
One!
Unbelievable.
Will you please wash your hair?
We did it!
- We won!
- Congratulations.
You guys did great.
- Good job.
- My shoulder hurts.
Where does it hurt?
Right here.
Haven't you ever had
any feelings for Soo Ho?
This place is a restricted area.
- Hey, wait.
- Isn't this place a little creepy?
You're such a scaredy-cat
for someone so big.
- No, you can't go in there!
- My gosh.
Goodness.
- You're not allowed to go that way.
- Why not?
Is there something in the woods.
I can't afford to
lose anyone else.
- What?
- Lose what?
Over there...
Never mind.
Just forget about it. Anyway,
make sure you never go that way.
Okay? You understand?
- Okay.
- You got it?
- Yes, okay!
- Okay.
- Yes.
I wonder what's there.
I'm getting really curious.
- No, let's go.
- No.
- Come on.
- Let's just go.
No one will buy it! Get out!
Stop pressuring my clients!
What am I supposed to do?
Should I burn these
candles at your funeral?
Give them away or throw
them away. I don't care!
HELP WANTED ON WEEKENDS
PRINCE COMICS, HELP
WANTED ON WEEKENDS
Never have there been
candles like these.
- Are they candles or perfume?
- I'm not interested.
I'm giving them to you.
If you're going to talk about
hunting for treasure, just leave.
The proudest moment
of my life...
was when I didn't invest in
your search for buried treasure.
Why are you bringing
up the past?
Look. Hey, so...
Here. About that weekend job...
Can I do it?
That? I found someone already.
Already? Okay, then.
Is it good?
Then give me a bite.
Give me a bite.
Darn it.
Today, it's jjajangmyeon.
What are you doing?
- Just one bite!
- Darn it!
- Can I have this?
- Yes, have it.
It's yummy.
Hey, Shi Hyun.
What's this?
It smelled pretty bad earlier,
right? I just washed my hair.
- Enjoy.
- At least you have a conscience.
Hey, Hyun Kyu.
It wasn't that terrible.
- Don't lie.
- It was gross.
- It was not.
- What's wrong with you?
What?
What is that smell?
- Go.
- Have some mushrooms.
- Let me know if you need more.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- You're red.
- It stank though.
Hey. Is Ju Kyung an
artifact in a museum?
Is she a Goryeo
celery or something?
Goryeo celadon.
Whatever. How long will you
just look at her from afar?
I'll set it up for you.
Find out how she feels.
I'll help you...
Hey.
- Is it cooked?
- Yes, it's perfect.
This is so good.
Are you a wild animal?
Let it cook first.
Don't eat like a pig just
because you're eating one.
- Eat like a person.
- Sir.
I am a person.
Are you enjoying the food?
- Yes.
Let me check the fire.
It's good.
Sir. What were you trying
to tell us earlier?
That? Just something
that happened long ago.
What was it? Tell us, please.
Why do you want to
know? It's nothing.
- Please!
- Please tell us.
Fine. You give me no choice.
- Listen carefully.
- Okay.
A long time ago,
there was a well...
deep in the forest that way.
Wife. The wedding is over now.
Why do you not
show me your face?
I am embarrassed.
You are extremely shy.
The rooster will crow before
we consummate our marriage.
Then please tell me something.
Do you like bright-colored
wild apricots?
No matter how bright it is,
it is still a wild apricot.
That which is inside a pot is more
important than the pot itself.
Why do you ask?
Enough about wild
apricots. Come here.
Do not be why, and
lift up your head.
Then do you not be shocked.
- Husband!
- Is this why you hid your face?
You said it is what is
inside the pot that matters.
- Husband.
- Let go.
- Where are you going?
- Let go!
Soon Dol! Soon Dol!
- Husband!
- Let go.
Soon Dol!
I was never...
embraced by my own husband
because I was born ugly.
My life...
is worse than that
of a wild apricot.
What do you like
so much about me,
that you follow me
around like this?
I like your broad
chest, my lord.
No way.
I like these solid, long legs.
I like those too.
I like everything.
What a great night!
Let us have fun tonight...
until the sun rises.
- That sounds good.
That woman who died
carrying a deep grudge...
became an ugly spirit
and roamed the land,
and if she ran into
anyone, she'd...
steal their face.
That's why people don't go
anywhere near there at night.
People went missing before,
so they even held offering rituals
to the ugly spirit by the well.
An ugly spirit that steals
faces? That's so silly.
It's too hard to
pretend to be scared.
Is that why you told us
not to go into the woods?
She only takes pretty
and handsome faces,
so judge for yourself.
Don't walk around
alone, got that?
It'll be dark soon.
Don't worry. None of you will
have anything to worry about.
Don't worry.
What... No way.
All of you except me...
Hold hands, okay?
JEONG SE YEON
MEMORIAL ALBUM PROJECT
SE YEON AND LEO,
"MISSING LOVE"
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Lim Hee Kyung from
Move Entertainment.
Haven't we met before?
I doubt that.
Right? I must have
been mistaken.
What is it?
I'll get right to it.
We plan to release an album...
in Jeong Se Yeon's memory on
the anniversary of his passing.
But most of the songs
he left behind...
were collaborations
with a person named Leo.
Do you know how long
we've searched for you?
You're Leo, aren't you?
I am not.
Do you want to keep it a secret?
Don't believe me if
you don't want to.
This is laughable.
You kicked him out as soon as...
the school violence
scandal came out...
and made a kid kill himself.
But now, what?
Your company can never
produce a memorial album.
I will stop that
from happening...
no matter what.
How do I persuade him?
- Hey.
- Hi.
When are you coming
home? I'm home alone.
Let's start the game now.
You have 30 minutes.
Order the chicken.
Will you eat it or not?
The choice is yours.
Stop messing with me.
Hello, sir.
You must be tired
from working late.
Not at all. Have you had dinner?
No, not yet.
Mr. Oh. How about chicken?
The choice is yours.
Sounds good to me.
You seemed embarrassed.
Was that funny?
Yes, thank you.
That's right. Sir.
I met Han Seo Joon.
I see.
He denied he was Leo
and rejected me hared.
He was friends with Se Yeon,
so he isn't fond of us.
I think it would be a waste
to lose this opportunity.
And he's too good a songwriter
to let his talent go to waste.
I'll keep working on him.
I like your enthusiasm.
Please keep up that attitude as you
take care of our rookie artists.
Sure thing.
- Good work.
- Thank you, sir. Good night.
Fried chicken!
Is the memorial album
still being considered?
I thought the lack
of company support...
would make her do drop it,
but it looks like she hasn't.
I'll handle it though.
Good.
Yes, Hee Kyung. The other
teachers are sleeping now.
Why are you still up?
Were you thinking about me?
I have trouble sleeping
in foreign settings.
How about I sing a lullaby?
No, I'll just go to bed.
- Good night.
- Good night, my Joon Woo.
My adorable Joon Woo.
Come on. It's not like
I'm actually cute.
Was that a poor song choice?
I love you, I love you
I love you.
I love you, I love you.
- Love?
She loves you?
Mom... I mean, Mother,
are you at a karaoke bar?
Mr. Han, are you
in a relationship?
No!
Sorry, guys.
- Good night.
I love you.
Now I've lost my appetite.
I love you, I love you
I love you
- I love you
- Enough!
Ahn Hyun Kyu, have you
pooped your pants before?
Are you kidding
me? Of course not.
- Nice!
- Come here.
Take that!
- Kim Shi Hyun.
- Gosh, he stinks.
Do you think of
yourself as a princess?
No way.
- Take that!
Lee Soo Ho, have
you kissed before?
3, 2, 1.
- Take that!
You should've answered
before your time was up.
I bet he's never played
this game before.
Love or friendship?
Love.
- Must he be that cheesy? Get him.
- Get him!
- Take that!
- But it's the truth.
Darn it.
- Am I handsome?
- Yes.
- Take that!
- Yoo Tae Hoon or Eighteen?
- Of course, it's my darling.
- Truth!
- Soo Ah!
- Get them both.
- Yes, get them both.
- Take that!
Is there someone you like?
Yes!
- You lied.
- What a liar!
- Take that!
- You liar.
Have you ever wanted to
break up with Soo Ah?
No.
Who's next?
Again.
Have you ever wanted
to break up with me?
No. No way.
- See? It's the truth.
- Again.
Have you ever wanted
to break up with me?
No. Never!
No?
The device says you're lying.
- No.
- I see.
So you wanted to
break up with me?
It's over!
- Soo Ah?
- Soo Ah!
Soo Ah!
I am a girl.
It's working just fine.
There's someone I like.
What? It worked
perfectly this time.
Soo Ho?
How long have you
been standing there?
You should've let me know.
Anyway, I'll get going.
- Ju Kyung.
- Yes?
- What is it?
- Can you...
- follow me?
- What?
Sure.
Is he mad about something?
I wonder what it's about.
Why were you avoiding me today?
What? That's hardly the case.
- Really?
- Of course not.
Should we ask the lie detector?
That device gives
random readings.
Whatever.
Gosh, it's prettier
out here at night.
There's not even a single bench.
Look at all the
stars in the sky.
Where?
I blame it on the clouds.
In movies,
zombies jump out of the woods.
What did you want to say? Why
did you bring me out here?
- Well...
- Look!
It's so pretty.
It's as if I'm
looking at a painting.
I know.
Why don't I turn on some music?
I'm low on battery.
I'll turn the
music on with mine.
"WHAT DO YOU REALLY WANT" BY
CRASH, "FIRE" BY REAL BOYS
"MISSING YOU", UNKNOWN
I love the voice.
Whose song is it?
Se Yeon's.
It's nice.
I don't think I've ever
heard of this song.
It was never released.
You're the first one to hear it.
I see.
But I don't want to.
Let's go!
Where are you headed?
He's off to see the ghost.
A ghost is said to
appear at the well.
A video of us searching
for a ghost will go viral!
Come with us.
I can't be bothered,
so have fun.
Seo Jun, I see you're
scared of ghosts.
So where's this well?
- There.
- There!
- Let's go.
- Seo Jun is going with us!
Sorry about that. You hate
being on camera, right?
Why do you hate it?
I had a rough time growing
up because of the paparazzi.
I get it now.
It must've been tiring.
Why did you stop?
What?
Do you like taking photos?
I never used to before,
but makeup changed it all.
Now, I like it.
- You like it?
- Yes, I like it.
Do you like being on a boat?
Yes, I do.
Then,
do you like listening to music?
Of course, I do.
Would you like to
take a photo with me?
Ju Kyung!
Guys, it's not too
late to go back.
Will you stop it?
- Cut it out.
- My gosh.
There's... There's nothing here.
I think we might find something.
- My gosh.
- This is freaky.
- Hurry up.
- Come on.
Gosh, there's nothing here.
I'm really sorry for making
you jump into the lake.
But by any chance, did
my makeup come off?
Yes.
Gosh, what should I do?
I can't let anyone
see me like this.
Should I go fetch your makeup?
But there's also my
underwear inside my bag.
No, it's okay. I'll
try to hide my face.
It's cold, isn't it?
No, it's not cold at all.
You don't want your body
temperature to fall.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
This isn't a scene
from a romance movie.
It's more like a scene
from a survival scene.
Soo Jin?
Soo Ho?
Why are you all wet? Did
you fall into the lake?
I accidentally tripped
and fell inside.
You should've been more careful.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I heard you were with Ju Kyung.
- No.
- Oh, really?
What was that sound?
- A wild boar.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Hey.
Go on inside.
- What about you?
- I need to go find something.
Soo Ho.
- Are you scared?
- This is creepy.
Look, guys. That over
there is the well.
Doesn't it give you goosebumps?
Look at him all scared.
Gosh, stop it.
Cut it out, okay?
It's not funny.
What was that sound?
- Let's go.
- I want to go back.
Guys, it's nothing.
We just heard a strange
sound coming from the well.
- Let me check it out.
- Oh, no...
I hope they didn't
recognize me. My goodness.
Cheol Ho!
Hey, the well is right here.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
Why won't he just go away?
My gosh, that
startled me so much.
LEE SOO HO: WHERE ARE YOU?
Why aren't you picking
up? Where are you?
Hey, I just got back.
It got all wet.
It felt like a fairy tale.
But in reality,
my life is a mess.
Ju Kyung, are you up already?
Yes, of course, I'm up.
You're pretty even
in the morning.
Why did I suddenly get
transferred to the PR team?
It's not even time for
personnel appointments.
I know, right? I also found
out after I saw the notice.
Then what about my projects?
Hee Kyung.
Did you do anything to cross
the CEO or anyone high up?
It's weird that you were the only
one who got sent to another team.
I didn't do anything wrong.
And even if I did, they can't do
this without any prior notice.
Do you know what the best
part about a school trip is?
- Having fun with friends!
- Speaking without honorifics!
The highlight of a school
trip is doing a treasure hunt.
- My gosh.
- That's lame.
I hid things here and there.
So I want you guys to look
around and find what you can.
Mr. Han, we're not
elementary school kids.
Mr. Han, we're 18
years old, not 8.
- Seriously.
- Mr. Han, I'm hungry!
- You ate not too long ago.
- This is boring!
The winner will get a gift
voucher worth 50 dollars.
- What? 50 dollars?
- 50 dollars?
- 50 dollars!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
- Let's search!
Let's go!
Mr. Han, I'm not
feeling very well.
- Go find something!
- Hurry!
Hurry up! 50 dollars!
- Come on!
- Run!
Keep looking!
Ju Kyung, are you sick?
You're burning hot. How
did you end up with a cold?
- I found something!
- Me too!
What kind of treasure is this?
Knowing is power.
- Nice! 50 dollars!
- Hey!
- It's my quote!
- I found it.
- Did you find it?
- Did you find something?
- I found it.
- You found it?
- Let me see.
- What is it?
- You know the depth of love...
- "You know the depth of love..."
- only in the pain of separation.
- "only in the pain of separation."
It's okay.
- Get out of my way.
- Where are you going?
Hey, wait!
I won't let you go even if I die.
How do you expect me to let go?
If you wish to leave, fix
my heart before you go.
You're not going to die!
Whoever loves Choi Soo
Ah, raise your hand.
Who can never forget Choi
Soo Ah? Raise your hand.
Who wants to stop Choi Soo Ah
from leaving? Raise your hand.
Honey.
What are they doing?
Wake up.
I brought medicine for you.
How did you know?
Get some sleep.
Thanks.
Don't get sick.
I hate it when people are sick.
Did you find one?
Hey, Soo Ho. I found
the first place prize.
Have you seen Ju Kyung?
Ju Kyung?
- You'll wake her.
- Let go.
What if I refuse?
Come out.
What is that? Are they fighting?
- Do you still call yourself human?
- Are you blinded?
What do you think I am?
- You know I like her!
- Was it first come, first served?
Who cares if you
liked her first?
Are they really fighting?
- Why does it have to be Ju Kyung?
- I don't know either!
Why does it have to be her?
- Give up on her!
- Why should I?
Her feelings are what matters.
I said to give up.
It's beyond my control.
Look at my eyebrows! What
will you do about these?
I told you yesterday...
that it would look awkward for
a week if you want it dark.
It'll be fine in a few days.
People are laughing
at me to my face!
Must I put up with
that at this age?
I should've gotten
them done in Gangnam.
I came to this hick town
because they said you were good.
I want a refund,
and put my brows back
to how they were!
Then go to Gangnam!
Why are you causing a
scene in this hick town?
Is that how you treat customers?
What are you doing? This
is our place of business.
It's because she did
this to my eyebrows...
Sir.
If you look funny a
week later, come then.
And if you mistreat my
Hyun Sook ever again,
I will make you pay.
Are you okay?
What?
Thanks.
"Thanks"?
That's right! Thanks!
What about it?
You just thanked me, right?
You thanked me!
Was it first come, first served?
Who cares if you
liked her first?
Her feelings are what matters.
Soo Ho! My best friend!
- Hey. What do you think?
- What?
Did you and Soo Ah make up?
You must experience a breakup
to appreciate the depth of love.
Who knew my love was this deep?
It goes 3 levels
underground, no, 4 levels...
You haven't asked her out?
You should do it today.
You need to do it nonchalantly
in an unusual location...
for it to have a high
probability of success.
Understand, man?
Hey, Ju Kyung! I heard you were
sick and had to take medicine.
Are you feeling better?
You're eating well, right?
I'm fine. I'm going to go.
Stay healthy!
Tae Hoon!
Are you bugging Soo Ho again?
He hates you.
Get a clue.
- What are you saying? Enunciate.
- What?
- "What"?
- Are you copying me?
- "Are you copying me?"
- What?
Why did you set
a table out here?
The moon is nice tonight.
Ju Kyung isn't home,
and Hee Kyung and Ju
Young will be late.
So I thought we could have
a romantic dinner. Sit.
My gosh. You must be giddy
you got a compliment...
instead of a scolding for once.
Stir-fried kimchi with tofu?
Do you remember our first date?
We had stir-fried kimchi with tofu
and makgeolli in Cheongpyeong.
You remember everything.
I should've run away.
Why did I fall for you then...
and make myself
suffer at this age?
I'm the fool for falling
for a pretty face.
Stop killing the mood.
Still, you used to be
really good-looking.
You even sang well too. How
could I not fall for you?
I haven't changed.
You came.
To me.
With a rose.
Between your red lips
I fantasized.
As I looked at you, so
pure and transparent.
Can I empty myself.
What has gotten into you?
I fantasized this.
Can I dive into your eyes.
Tonight.
I'm home...
Oh my eyes.
- Get out.
- Gross.
Darn it. Gross.
Instant jjajang noodles please.
What about the radish?
That's self-service.
Oh my gosh. Did you follow me?
Freak.
She got a job here just
so she could see me.
Her efforts are commendable.
Here. Go on.
I don't usually
give out my number,
but I'll make an exception.
Freak. Why did you want
pictures of yourself?
Go Woon, it's time to go, right?
Yes. I'll go now.
Sure. She couldn't even imagine
that I'd ask her for her number.
Of course, not.
My dear man. Why
are you so dashing?
What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
My heart raced a little.
Let's hear it for them.
Next up. The Rainbow Team...
will show their Super Strength Show.
Let's welcome them to the stage.
All right!
What is he pulling
with his teeth?
It's a car. No, a bicycle!
The show goes on.
Nicely done.
Okay.
Look at the size of that.
Did you see all those
balloons pop? He's so good.
Finish. Good job.
Let's dance!
Clap to the beat, everyone.
Looking fun.
Shameless, aren't they?
I hear Saebom High
School has a celebrity.
Apparently, one student used
to be a K-pop idol trainee.
Where are you?
- Here.
- So the rumor is true!
- All right!
- Seriously?
Handsome and charismatic.
- Let's bring him up here.
- I can't believe it.
Just how far has
the rumor spread?
- Just sit down.
- Don't be a joke and sit down.
What else can we do but
bring him up on this stage?
You told him, didn't you?
You're a great singer,
so sing us a song.
- Just this once.
- No way.
You really won't?
I'd love to hear you sing.
Han Seo Jun!
- Han Seo Jun!
- Han Seo Jun.
- Do you want to hear me sing?
- Of course.
- Don't tell me you're embarrassed.
- Han Seo Jun.
- Go on up there.
- Then grant me a wish.
- Han Seo Jun.
- You're just like my brother.
Sure. Sing a song
and you get one wish.
- Nice!
- Seo Jun is so cool.
How sweet.
You and me under
a starlit night.
Making me anew and
bringing me warmth.
Is your gaze and your smile.
That I'll forever
keep in my heart.
My heart is filled
with thoughts of you
I become more like you.
A gift for you.
More beautiful than a dream.
In our embrace.
In which we'll walk
endlessly tonight.
I wish to give you
all the days I have.
I want you to know how I feel.
My feelings that
can never stay calm.
Light up this night so brightly.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Enjoying.
Everyday moments with you.
Do you know that brings
me my biggest joy?
You become the
light of my world.
So stay as you are.
Just by my side.
Ju Kyung, wait.
Here. Can you take
this to Soo Ho?
What? Me?
Listen to me carefully.
Walk southeast and you'll
find Soo Ho on a walk.
Hold on a second.
Gosh, nature's
calling. I'm sorry.
What about the jacket?
Oh, right.
Soo Ho!
Walk southeast and... No, wait.
Walk northwest and Ju Kyung
will be by the stream.
Tell her how you
feel, my friend.
Wait. I forbid you to be moved.
Hey, Soo Ho.
Ju Kyung?
Why are you still out here?
- You see...
- Have you seen Soo Ho?
- Soo Ho?
- You still didn't ask her out?
You should do it today.
I saw him go that earlier.
- Isn't that Soo Ho's?
- What?
Yes, Tae Hoon wanted
me to give it to him.
Really? Then I'll get it to him.
Sure, I guess you could do it.
That's probably what's right.
I heard he's by the stream.
Really? Well, head
inside and get some rest.
Lim Ju Kyung.
Don't you forget that
you should grant my wish.
So how was it?
You said you wanted
to hear me sing.
Why? Was it that touching?
My singing has been known
to bring many to tears,
but don't you cry as well.
Hey, what's wrong?
- What is this?
- What do you mean?
Ju Kyung asked me
to get this to you.
- She asked you?
- Yes.
Hey, wait. At least
take your jacket.
You dropped this.
What is it?
Is it because you're sick?
I'm sorry, all right?
Whatever it is, I'm sorry.
Why?
Why doesn't Soo Ho like me?
- I...
- Don't say it.
- You see...
- Don't say it!
I like Soo Ho.
I told you not to say it.
I thought I'd be okay with it,
but it hurts.
Keep this a secret though, okay?
Why couldn't you keep
it a secret from me too?
Let me see.
Crying makes you
look ugly, you know.
Don't cry.
Forget it. You'll only
rub my makeup off.
I can't believe I wailed
like some ugly duckling.
I hope the show-and-tell
isn't over.
I should touch up my face
before they come back.
You said you
weren't avoiding me.
Did you cry?
Why? Was it because of Seo Jun?
Why would you cry
because of him?
Do you like him?
- What?
- Do you like Seo Jun?
- Why do you care?
- Answer me.
What's the matter with you?
Why do you care that I cried?
And why do you want
to know whom I like?
Why do you keep confusing me
when you like someone else?
What do you mean?
I know you like Soo Jin.
So why do you keep being nice to
me and making my heart flutter...
Ju Kyung.
I think there's a
misunderstanding.
- Did you see that?
- I really rocked the show.
- You didn't do it properly.
- I know.
I have no makeup on. My gosh.
It's the ugly spirit!
My gosh, it's the ugly spirit!
Oh, gosh!
- It's that ghost!
- I caught you this time.
- Let's go catch the ugly spirit!
- Let's go!
- Go catch her!
- Wait for me!
- Catch the ugly spirit!
- Go!
Let's catch her!
My gosh, why are they
chasing after me?
What am I going to do?
She went that way!
- Come on!
- Go down!
- Go!
- Run!
- There she is!
- Over there!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
Go get her!
I don't like Soo Jin.
The person I like...
There she is!
It's you.
SPECIAL THANKS TO WOO HYUN
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE
EPILOGUE
He must know that
what's inside a pot...
is more important
than the pot itself.
TRUE BEAUTY
You don't see anyone
from school, do you?
Duck.
Is this really necessary?
I'm just a bit embarrassed.
Why do you want a part-time job?
So I can afford to pay
for the makeup academy.
Do you want me to help
you find a part-time job?
- I'm really bad, aren't I?
- No.
You're unbelievably horrible.
I brought you here because I
want to show you something.
I like Soo Ho.
Ju Kyung, let's break up.