THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
Hwa Jin.
What are you doing down there?
- Oh, my. I'll get some help.
- No.
Nobody can know that I am...
That I am...
Hey.
EPISODE 10
Why would you go into a
place with such bad memories?
Is it okay for me
to not call anyone?
What if he ends up dying?
Are you having
another nightmare?
Hey. Wake up.
Hwa Jin.
Fine. Whatever
you want to think.
This won't do. I'll
go get someone.
You're doing this again.
I had a nightmare...
that I died as an
incompetent king.
A scary nightmare where...
I could not do anything and
died as I was watching...
the world falls apart.
Nobody asked.
Let us stay like
this for a moment.
Just for a moment.
I'll pretend to be Jo Hwa
Jin for just one minute.
EPISODE 10, LIVING A NIGHTMARE
You have finally
become the Queen.
I knew this would happen.
CONFIDENTIAL
I will tell His
Majesty everything.
I will not be swayed
by the past any longer.
Your Highness.
I need to speak to His Majesty.
The King has gone
out with the Queen,
and Lord Kim is not home either.
O Wol.
I can help the King and
ruin the Queen as well.
What should I do?
Your Highness.
It is time to wash your face.
Good morning.
- What happened?
- Good question.
I almost touched you...
I mean, I almost died.
You were so heavy.
That was dangerous.
The ledger was not in there.
Did you save me...
by yourself?
You didn't want
anyone to find out.
I used up all the
strength that I had.
I can do it. Remember the days
when I used to lift 150kg.
Your strength doesn't
come from your muscles.
It comes from your
determination.
Why did you go into
the well at that hour?
It was dark, so I did not
see the well, and I fell in.
Do you have night blindness?
It's hard to climb
out of a well.
Are you awake?
Hold on.
Come over here. Hurry.
Wait just a moment.
Yes. Come in.
If I had known you would
stay in the main house,
I would have prepared
bigger bedding.
Father, no! Please no!
Father! You cannot do it!
No! Father!
Father!
I apologize.
There is no need.
Because of your efforts,
I was comfortable here.
I should not bother you anymore,
so I will return to the Palace.
What do you mean by "bother"?
Please do not say that.
I came in to relay a message...
that the Grand Queen
Dowager has sent.
Seeing how the Grand Queen
Dowager asks for you daily,
she must really need you.
The Palace does not run
properly if I'm not there.
Okay.
Even if you are busy and
exhausted, it is a good thing.
Do not worry about anything and
focus on your role as a queen.
I may be a father who lacks in
many ways but do not forget...
that I am always
standing behind you.
Okay.
Have a safe trip
back to the Palace.
I know that it is shameless, but
please take good care of the Queen.
I will pay more attention to
her so that she is not lonely.
Goodness. I am
grateful and sorry.
Shall we go?
He acts like such a caring dad,
but he's just a greedy person
who uses his child as a tool.
He married his daughter off to
the person he tried to kill.
Is that why he tried
to kill Kim So Yong?
Why do you look like
you've lost your country?
I do not.
If you didn't lose your country,
did you lose something else?
Wait? Did you really?
Of course not.
It is a joyous day where you are
returning to the Palace safely.
Despite my appearance,
I am very happy.
As long as you're happy.
Is the bloody revenge
about to start?
But it feels like I'm forgetting
about something important.
I feel like I had an
important mission...
He is so handsome.
He is really handsome.
The investiture of
the Royal Concubine.
How could I forget about
such an important thing?
I have something important
to take care of, so bye.
Hong Yeon. Let's go. Hurry.
Wait. Why are you running?
I apologize.
Take your time.
My goodness. My Queen.
Your Majesty.
Let us go first.
- Where is the Head Eunuch?
- I made sure he is occupied.
Were you unable to find it?
It disappeared into thin air.
Do you think your father-in-law
figured it out and moved it?
That is not the case.
There were no changes in his
behavior until the moment I left.
He is not adept at hiding
his feelings for sure.
Do you think it was him?
The masked member of the
Department of Justice.
If it was in the
hands of Kim Jwa Geun,
the ledger must
not exist anymore.
There is no way he would
know where it was moved to.
It is a problematic item,
so your father-in-law will not be
able to tell anyone he lost it.
He will have to suffer alone.
In return, he will begin
looking for the ledger.
He will search for it himself.
Have someone follow him.
Yes, sir.
I think the ledger
is a lost cause.
Give up on it.
If we do not have it, our
plans will go to waste.
I cannot give up so easily.
Act as though the Queen
is always here. Be polite.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Your Highness!
Hello, Court Lady Choi!
Your Highness...
I missed you.
Court Lady Choi. Bring in
all the ladies of Joseon.
Don't leave out any of the
Han family registers...
and bring them to me.
As of this moment, I will start the
investiture of the Royal Concubine.
I'll naturally look into that family
by using the selection as an excuse.
The investiture of the Royal
Concubine is the answer.
Oh, right. I need to say hello
to the Grand Queen Dowager.
Just you wait.
The combination of Jang Bong Hwan's
soul and Kim So Yong's memories...
will create the perfect act...
as Queen.
Grand Queen Dowager.
Have you been well?
What has changed?
You seem different
for some reason.
I was able to start fresh
after returning home.
That is good news.
I apologize for worrying
you all this time.
And I am grateful
that despite it all,
you were so understanding of me.
To make up for
everything in the past,
I will work hard
to do my best...
to fulfill my role as Queen.
Then will you start doing what
is most important right now?
I know exactly what that is.
I came as soon as
I felt better...
to do just that.
As expected.
I was only gone for two days,
but I could not stop
thinking about that.
How do you feel exactly
the same as I do?
- Then...
- Right now...
- As of this moment?
- Shall we?
- Queen.
- Good job!
This was not what I had in mind.
Your Highness.
I am looking forward
to learning from you.
I must be irreplaceable
right now.
I can't believe I'm
sharing my recipes.
I'm not ready to
become an educator.
What is this? Step aside.
Gosh.
You might have been able to
walk in here as you pleased.
But I am afraid you cannot do
the same when you leave here.
Your Highness.
His Majesty has
returned to the palace.
Is that so?
Shall we head over to
Seonjeongjeon Hall now?
No. I will head over
to the royal villa.
Come on. The fire is too small.
At this rate, the ingredients
will become mushy.
Come on. The flames
are everywhere.
I see your eyes in flames too.
My goodness. That cannot be.
I am determined
to learn from you,
so my eyes are
full of enthusiasm.
By the way, when will
you teach me your recipe?
I'm sure you know how things run
in the kitchen. Don't be like that.
When you start working
at a Chinese restaurant,
all you're allowed to do is
peeling onions in the first month.
Keep the fire going.
Even so, I have been working in
the royal kitchen for 30 years.
And I have been the royal
chef for 12 years now.
I don't need your
detailed resume.
Why don't you start
counting days then?
I don't like your attitude.
Forget about this.
Your Highness.
How is this? Is this better?
Is it better? Like this?
Hey, open it.
Move.
Did you just glance?
What an industrial spy.
I was wondering if I
adjusted the heat correctly.
You don't get to think.
I'll do all the thinking.
Why do you keep
crossing the line?
Gukbap is the comfort
food of the common people.
And gomtang is the comfort
food of the upper class.
And I'll add a bit of consomme,
a French-style beef gukbap.
I'll get rid of the gamey
flavor with egg whites.
She is using egg whites
in a revolutionary way.
- Your Highness.
- My gosh.
Will this do?
Nice.
May I ask what kind of food
you are trying to make?
Food that will move one's soul.
Soul?
Great.
And then, this is
the finishing touch.
- They are on standby, right?
- Yes, Your Highness.
"If the foam dies,
I will die too."
With that attitude, try to keep
the food safe and be swift.
All right. Go.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Hurry.
she'll love it more as she
already knows how it tastes.
Your Highness!
Dam Hyang!
I was so scared that I might
not be able to see you again.
Seriously. Thank you so much.
I made you worry, Dam Hyang.
I ought to be scolded.
My gosh. I'm sorry.
What...
Am I seeing this correctly?
Is this rice in the soup?
Well, it looks like
rice to me too.
Did she serve me
gukbap for my meal?
Rice and soup must be
separated for royal meals.
How dare she put rice in the
soup like some peasant food?
Should I bring this back?
Of course, you should...
but,
the Queen has put a lot of
effort into making this.
I will taste it, at least.
Yes, Your Highness.
I have counted the
days of my career...
in the royal kitchen.
And I have lived a proud
life as a royal chef.
However, I became a mere servant
who just tends the fire overnight.
This is all because
of the Queen.
It is not because
I am a bad chef.
It is because the Queen
is strangely too good.
Darn it.
- Your Highness!
- You too?
Come on! You are
being too harsh!
You are still wet
behind your ears!
You little...
Darn you. Come on.
Do you think I am a joke?
Come on. I am a good chef!
Gosh, that hit the spot.
When did you get so
close, Court Lady Choi?
I do not hate her that much.
Her Highness has been
on my back lately.
I must have gone bad like those
spoiled vegetables in summer.
I have been blowing into
the fire all day long.
What are you doing?
No. I was not trying to kiss...
- I was trying to explain to you...
- Go away.
- I...
- Go now.
Fine.
Excuse me.
My gosh.
I cannot badmouth
Her Highness...
because I might be on
the same level as he is.
But I must get
things off my chest.
I was really going to
quit looking at this.
Why is his face in there?
No. No!
No. Please, no.
No! No! This cannot
be happening!
Grand Queen Dowager, the Queen
seeks an audience with you.
She may enter.
I'm dead meat.
This heartless woman obviously
won't appreciate this soul food.
Your Royal Highness.
I must have lost my skills
because I was away...
from the royal kitchen
for a little while.
It tastes familiar yet
foreign at the same time.
Foreign yet familiar.
Your outstanding cooking talents
are beginning to scare me.
You even brought back old memories
that I had completely forgotten.
Here.
Good girl, eat up.
Mother.
Your Royal Highness.
- You have rice right here...
- How dare you!
But I hear that you are not willing
to share these skills of yours.
Do you not think that you
can teach the Royal Chef?
Well...
That old fogey does get
on my nerves a little.
Then we shall get rid
of him immediately.
There was that arsenic
incident as well.
Arsenic?
Did you not know?
You fell into a
vegetative state...
because you ingested poison
in the royal kitchen.
Poison?
Then I wouldn't have
recovered so quickly.
The Royal Chef may be a
close-minded old fogey,
but if you dismiss him from
his job suddenly like this...
"His job"? What do you mean?
What I meant was,
we will behead him.
I wonder who has the ledger now.
More importantly,
why did this person take it?
Will this bite us in the end?
Or will this help us?
Whether he loses
his job or his head,
why do I care?
They keep telling me to
share my recipes and skills,
so the talks about my
dethronement weren't a joke.
I can't afford to worry
about that old fogey now.
I'm about to lose my head.
Oh, Cheoljong!
Your Majesty, the Queen is here.
What are you doing?
I heard this is how
royal ladies walk.
I am your perfect
queen, you know.
What? Who?
That's what Court Lady Choi
told me. Is it not true?
No, what I meant was...
Who is my "perfect queen"?
Me, as you can see.
You are scaring me.
Just be your usual self.
By the way, what's
Your Majesty's type?
Sexy? Cute? Or innocent?
What are you talking about?
The Grand Queen
Dowager told me...
to select a few royal
concubines for you.
They're your concubines,
so I figured I should ask you
what your preferences are.
"Concubines"?
Royal concubines...
Look at this punk.
Are you finally showing
your true colors?
That is a great idea.
My apologies. I was overjoyed.
Well...
Let me make this one
thing clear to you.
Just because you're a
king doesn't mean...
those women belong to you. That's
primitive and old-fashioned.
You don't own them.
That is excellent advice.
- So you mean...
- They're mine.
- What?
- I own them.
So don't come anywhere
near the royal villa.
You have Royal
Noble Consort Eui.
Oh, right.
On one condition though.
- Lend me your ears.
- What? Why?
It's okay.
I will choose the family.
What?
No! I care more about their
looks than their backgrounds.
Then I shall tell the
Grand Queen Dowager...
that I really do not need
any royal concubines.
Okay, fine.
But let's not overstep
each other's boundaries.
I'll evaluate their looks
while you vet their families.
You truly are my anti-fan.
I was very concerned, but I
have figured out a way now.
Don't smile.
You're no longer
allowed to smile.
Also, you're not allowed to grab
my hand like you did earlier,
and you can't lie
down on my belly!
What? So I am not
allowed to do anything?
That's right. You're not
allowed to do anything.
Don't do anything!
I don't have time for this.
Let's go.
That is my queen.
Would you like to go
speak with His Majesty?
No, I will return
to the royal villa.
Is this what you're looking for?
Did you say a court
maid sold this to you?
Yes, she looked young.
She was clad in the
court maid uniform.
Do you remember her face?
That depends on how much
you're willing to pay me.
I will return with a painter.
The clearer your memories are,
the higher my offer will be.
Hello...
GENERAL STORE
GONE FOR BREAK
This is fake. I'm sure of it.
You mean, these are
forged identities?
But they didn't create
completely fake identities.
They restored the ones that belonged
to the deceased or the missing.
And they sure didn't do
a clumsy job at that.
It must've cost quite a bit.
Thank you.
He did all this work...
just to become a low-ranking
military officer?
Your Majesty, there is something
I must give to you in secret.
I will wait for you
where we always meet.
Your Highness.
Prince Yeongpyeong has
stepped out of the palace.
Then I would like you to
deliver this to His Majesty.
Sure, Your Highness.
She has something
to give to him?
If she could not give it to him as
he seemed content with the Queen,
then it must be
something special.
The royal conference will commence
in about 15 minutes, right?
Yes, Your Highness.
You should take a little break.
Royal Noble Consort Eui
wrote Your Majesty a letter.
CONFIDENTIAL
You must have been very
busy while I was away.
Thanks to you, I have
nothing to do here.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
To show you my appreciation
of your hard work,
I would like to hold a
banquet on Surit-nal.
As there are many natural disasters
and complaints from the people,
your generosity will
make them think...
we are not interested
in keeping order...
and we only want to have
extravagant parties.
I believe this is not the
way a king ought to behave.
However, Yeongjo...
celebrated his recovery after
being sick for several months...
by holding a banquet.
The Queen had been exhausted
due to her hard work...
and made a recovery after
falling into a vegetative state.
We ought to celebrate it.
We are still investigating
the cause of her illness.
So we cannot pinpoint
the cause yet.
She has made a full recovery
after resting for two days.
She must have needed some rest.
- However...
- The Queen...
overcame a serious illness
and made a full recovery.
We must hold a small party to
celebrate this good occasion.
I believe this occasion
deserves a celebration.
Yes.
That is my duty as her
husband and the king as well.
Your Majesty, you
cannot proceed.
An attempt to assassinate the
Queen is a serious offense.
If you rush to clear the
occasion by holding a banquet...
Minister of War.
Are you not happy that
the Queen has recovered?
Do not tell me...
you wanted the Queen to
be harmed by someone.
No. I did not.
Is using this occasion...
for your political agenda more
important than her health?
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
If that is your wish, we will
gladly accept your kindness.
Then, look forward to it.
Perhaps, it must be all the rest
you had. You are full of energy.
I will use my enemy's enemy.
I will defeat a barbarian
with another barbarian.
We must establish...
a new clan that will go
against the Kim clan.
- "Establish"?
- We will use...
the selection of the royal
concubine the Queen is in charge of.
Royal Chef, please
take a look at this.
Okay. Sure. Does
it taste similar?
Let me taste it.
- Bring me more seasonings.
- Yes.
I must add more.
Hey, that is too
watery. Do it again.
Why are you working so hard?
Dishes made with milk
will be very popular.
We cannot starve the
calves whenever we want.
I am sure we can bring out
similar flavors without real milk.
Molecular gastronomy
in the Joseon Dynasty?
He's working so hard
especially today.
Royal Chef.
I can feel his
sorrow on his face.
I bet he has a whole
family to feed.
Yes, Your Highness.
Make a bigger fire here.
Goodness.
He's probably shouldering the
burden as the head of the family...
with those small shoulders.
Come to think of it, I
don't even know your name.
What's your name?
It is Man Bok.
Tell me about your family.
I bet you have like 10
family members to support.
I am single.
What?
I have enjoyed the life of
a bachelor for a long time.
But don't you have
a family to support?
Think carefully.
I do feed stray cats fish
heads from time to time.
That's right. See?
Without you, the stray
cats will starve.
I won't do it for you. I'm
doing it for those cats.
I'll teach you my recipe.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Gosh. You're creeping me out.
Hey. Bring me some paper.
Hong Yeon.
Get the food palanquin. Deliver
this to the royal physician.
Yes.
Recommend me fragrant herbs
that are good for our skin.
If your answer doesn't satisfy
me, you'll get a new assignment.
"A new assignment"?
There is more on the back.
I need eunuchs who will help
me select a royal concubine.
How come she is always looking
for a way to make me a eunuch?
Your Majesty.
Please slow down. You
might hurt yourself.
Where can I find books
on royal banquets?
I will look for them.
I would like to read
Yeongjo's royal banquet.
Yes. Your Majesty.
I went to Seonjeongjeon Hall.
I was informed that
you were headed here.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
I just thought you and I have
not spent any time together.
I wanted to have a talk.
Please.
Is it because you
brewed the tea yourself?
It tastes more interesting.
When I look at you, I am
reminded of the late king.
That was why I had a hard
time keeping you close.
I am sorry that I did
not realize it sooner.
I assumed that I knew a
lot about the late king.
Perhaps, the late king,
my son...
must have been a greater
king than I thought...
seeing how he tried...
to restore the sovereign power
by going against the Kim clan.
I regret it very much...
that I was not able
to ask my clan...
to support the late
king and his agenda.
Do not blame yourself.
I am sure the late king
would not want that.
I was wondering if I
would be able to...
correct my mistake against
the late king through you.
I fall short of the
late king in many ways.
Is that so?
If you come across the
same goal as the late king,
please let me lend you a hand.
I will not make the
same mistake again.
I will keep that in mind.
I am happy to have gotten
to know you a bit today.
The pleasure was all mine.
Please rest now.
I WILL WAIT FOR YOU
WHERE WE ALWAYS MEET.
His Majesty is here.
I am sorry. Did I make
you wait for a long time?
Wait outside for a moment.
I thought you would not come,
so I came right back in.
I read the letter late.
You must have been busy.
So busy you could
not read the letter.
To be honest, the Queen
Dowager came to see me,
so we had a conversation.
What did you talk
about with her?
It was just a
friendly conversation.
You seem to have...
more things that I
must not know about.
Then what did you
discuss with the Queen?
When you were in
front of the lake.
- Did you see that?
- Should I not have seen it?
No.
We were discussing the investiture
of the Royal Concubine.
The Royal Concubine...
I am sure you refused.
We need to avert the
focus of the Kim clan.
If we give them another
power they can fight against,
they will be less
focused on the throne.
So did you agree to it?
- I did.
- This is the Queen's scheme!
Royal Noble Consort.
Why are you calling me
Royal Noble Consort?
Why are you not calling
me by my name anymore?
You used to say that I was the one
who can make you happy and sad.
But now,
has it changed to someone else?
- Hwa Jin...
- Please tell me how you feel.
Have you...
fallen in love with the Queen?
The foundation of western
food is sauce and dressing.
In particular, the dressing
is the flower of western food.
Try it.
If I use this, can I
make milk out of beans?
Why are you single by the way?
Pardon?
I missed my chance to get married
as I was so focused on my work.
What about your
parents and siblings?
In 1839, they killed
all the Catholics.
That is how I ended up alone.
Why did they have to
believe in such a thing?
That is why I do not
believe in anything.
The Gihae Persecution.
You must be lonely.
I am not the only one
who ended up like this.
It is a bit sad to spend
the holidays alone,
but the good thing is...
they all died on the same day, so
I only need to hold one memorial.
My gosh. What's
wrong with everyone?
How did you know I was weak to
men who gave off a sad smell?
- A sad smell?
- The food smells sad.
When a chef feels sad,
the food becomes sad too.
I know.
That is why whether it
is happiness or sadness,
I leave all my
emotions at the door...
before I enter
the royal kitchen.
You always get mad.
That is because whenever
you come here, you upset me.
You should blame yourself for lack
of practice. Not someone else.
Look at this. Look at this.
"Look at this"?
Did you call me "this"?
Look at you. Look at you.
That irritates me even more!
I should've just
left you to die.
My gosh. I'm so weak-hearted.
It has not been that
long since I had a meal.
I am not sure either.
Do not eat it. Share it...
with your skin.
This is how I become
irreplaceable.
From K-food to K-beauty.
It's the perfect
weather to dry seeds.
Your Highness.
I did not see you
all day yesterday.
I hope you did not suffer
too much from your hangover.
I apologize for leaving my post.
I have something to ask you.
Do you remember the situation before
you ended up in a vegetative state?
Was there anything suspicious
or any suspicious behaviors?
Regarding suspicious behaviors,
who are you referring to?
Whomever.
Well, to be honest,
I think that the other world
is connected to my collapse.
By "the other world", are you
talking about another power?
No.
In any case, I mean it was
something that occurred naturally.
You may be shocked, but
I will tell you anyway.
I suspect that the King
is connected to it.
According to my investigation,
the person who tried to
harm you near Oktajeong...
was sent from the King.
I knew you would be shocked.
How did you figure that out?
I'm the only one who knows that.
Were you aware of that?
Well, the thing is...
we were both intertwined
in various ways,
so we agreed to let
it go and move on.
Did you act that way
despite knowing all along?
Does your love remain unchanged
despite what the King has done?
What? Love?
Why would you say
something so disgusting?
If I want to live well here, I
need to get along with the King.
I'm just getting along with
him as I have no other choice.
Then, how could
you do that with...
I'm already confused
about my identity.
Why would you talk
about love now?
How is the investiture
of Royal Concubine going?
Court Lady Choi!
Ladies, I'm here...
Where are the candidates
for Royal Concubine?
They are over here.
What is this?
I endured an exhausting
day while waiting for this.
What is all of this?
I will not be able to quit
looking at the kaleidoscope.
She went that far for
the sake of our family?
What is this called again?
She said it was a beauty cover.
I was looking for
someone to replace her,
and she gave me
a new technology.
Your Highness,
I am the head of the Department
of Justice, Kim Byeong In.
At this hour?
Come in.
I did mention you to my brother
so he can tell you to visit me,
but it is too late.
I never received such a message.
I dared to seek an audience
with Your Royal Highness...
for I must tell you something
without letting my father know.
My father...
probably told you that His Majesty
is different from his predecessor.
My father was wrong.
What?
No...
No, do not follow me.
This is just something little.
I brought you some red ginseng.
- Here, take it.
- Thank you.
By the way, is everything okay?
With what?
Stop being so cryptic.
Just get to the point.
What do you mean?
I am just asking you
how everything is going.
Anyway, I suppose Byeong
In is still at the palace?
Hello, Lord Kim.
- I am back.
- You came back late today.
I never had a chance to spend
some time with my colleagues,
so I had a drink with those
in the Department of Justice.
Good.
It's getting late. Go
in and get some rest.
Okay, I will let you get
back to your conversation.
All right. Good night.
- You.
- Yes.
You seem anxious.
Biting off more than you
can chew can cause anxiety.
What... I am not
quite following.
Why do you not know
that you can...
put yourself as well as the Queen
in danger by being reckless?
If I seem anxious,
that is because...
I have not managed to capture the
person who tried to harm the Queen.
- Is that so?
- My gosh, it is getting late.
You must be tired.
Since I only stopped
by to deliver my gift,
I will get going now.
He lost the ledger.
If he was not involved, did
Byeong In do it by himself?
If that is not the case...
No, that can't be.
I'm thankful that it's not me.
It took a while to
find a corpse...
with a similar physique.
Tell me about this corpse.
The person drowned.
The face is not recognizable as
it was submerged for a long time.
Please tell me how
you truly feel.
Have you...
fallen in love with the Queen?
I...
must not love the Queen.
You are not denying that
you are in love with her.
You are just saying that
you must not love her.
Your Highness, Prince
Yeongpyeong is here.
Yes, come in.
I apologize for
visiting you so late.
I have news you have
been waiting for.
Did you find O Wol?
Did you give it to her?
Yes, I am sure of it.
A court maid sold it.
That means O Wol is
alive. Thank goodness.
Why ask me to get water in
the middle of the night?
Should have asked me
to get it earlier.
Did something get stuck?
What is that?
I hired an artist to draw the
court maid's composite sketch.
Once we see it, we
will know for certain.
I actually have figured out
a way to help His Majesty...
Your Highness.
In the well...
- The well?
- They found a corpse inside it.
And it looks like O
Wol, your court maid.
O Wol?
- What do we do?
- My gosh.
It will be traumatizing for you.
- Let me...
- No.
I must check with my own eyes.
- Did you see that?
- My gosh.
Looks like she was left
underwater for a long time.
My gosh, it must have been
awfully suffocating and painful.
Please stop.
I am only getting started.
Your Highness.
I wish to be alone.
The one...
who makes me happy and sad.
Your Majesty, the Grand
Queen Dowager is here.
What brings you by?
What were you reading?
Just one of the appeals that I
hadn't gotten around to peruse.
You seem much more
enthusiastic than usual,
which makes me curious about
your time outside the palace.
Hence, I came to
ask you about it.
It was good to temporarily...
forget about the matters
of the royal court.
I am glad to hear that.
You see,
I want you to be happy.
I am much obliged.
You have been through a lot.
Have you already
forgotten all about it?
Perhaps fate can be inherited.
If you learn to be grateful for
your situation and do nothing,
both you and all your
loved ones will be safe.
So why is it that you cannot
just sit back and do nothing?
Be good, Your Majesty.
I will, Grand Queen Dowager.
CONFIDENTIAL
Be good,
my baby.
Some people live
inside a nightmare.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
NO TOUCHING
MEANS TO SEEK
ONE'S OWN HAPPINESS
ANTI-FAN: A POWERFUL
SPIRIT GUIDE
AWESOME, MAGIC HOUR,
ATTENTION SEEKER
SHOWDOWN, JASMINE
TEA, ILL-MANNERED
SPECIAL FORCES, LOTTERY, ISSUE
But they often find...
their own ways to
overcome their nightmares.
- Your Highness.
Join us.
Please join us.
Come join us now, Your Highness.
But just as you're about to...
have a nice dream for a change
after overcoming your nightmare...
- I want a hug too.
- You do?
All right.
- My gosh!
- Your Highness.
Another nightmare...
finds you.
Your Highness.
My, did you lose your voice because
you've been calling me nonstop?
What on earth are
you doing here?
My Queen.
Today,
I shall forget "No touching".
MR. QUEEN
Is my heart telling me this?
Or is this what my body wants?
Secretary Han?
It is all rotten!
We will do whatever it takes
to get the ingredients.
His Majesty will want to look like
a strong king at the ceremony.
Fire!
There are always those who
take sports days so seriously.
What's with that glare?
Then I shall teach you
a thing or two again.
Let me show you who
this palace belongs to.
I will not forgive you.