[This is a work of fiction.]
[Names, businesses, products,
events and places are used fictitiously.]
Moisturizing foundation?
Yes, we put in
our basic skincare ingredients.
It moisturizes the skin
and gives the skin a healthy glow.
I can feel the moisturizing effect.
What's the percentage?
70%.
How to apply it? By using your hands?
Oh, right.
The researcher told us to use the hands,
but we think it'd be better to use a puff.
We'll develop them together.
Yes, I agree with you.
I'll focus on the basic ingredients,
and its moisturizing glow effect
during the training, okay?
Also, emphasize how it
differs from the existing ones.
We'll send you the material.
By the way, ABM Hyun-seung
can do it all by himself now.
The newbies from other teams
are still struggling.
He's quite outstanding.
I wonder who taught him.
She taught me.
He knows how to survive at work too.
Send me an adequate amount of samples.
Okay.
You're heading back, right?
I have another meeting.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I'm glad I taught you well.
It's so rewarding.
You think I'm a kid, right?
Not a kid, per se.
Why? Did I offend you?
Not exactly.
But you're treating me more like a kid
as compared with my older sisters.
I'm only a year younger than you.
It's a one-year difference in age,
but two-year difference
in working experience.
You really are a kid.
Let's go, we'll miss the bus.
Okay.
Did you pack all the samples?
Yes, I did.
-You'd better not leave anything behind.
-Huh?
What?
Sir!
Sir, wait!
Wait.
Thank you.
[Meeting Room 1]
[She Would Never Know]
[Executive Office]
[Marketing Department 1]
[Marketing Department 2]
[Large Meeting Room]
We're back.
-We're here.
-Welcome back.
So-mi is getting married.
Really?
-Yes.
-Congratulations.
Thank you.
Should we really congratulate her?
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Marriage isn't easy.
Your husband's name sounds familiar.
Yes, he's Assistant Manager Oh
from the department store sales team.
Really?
I'm sorry, we've been dating secretly.
You've dated behind our backs for 3 years?
How did you manage to do that?
We have our tricks and methods.
So cheeky!
If anyone wants to date secretly at work,
please come to me.
I'll teach you everything.
Yes, office romance must be kept a secret.
It's good if it turns out well,
but if it doesn't...
I can't bear to think about it.
And it's worse for the woman.
It labels you for the rest of your life.
Right,
I don't understand why
women have to suffer more.
It's ridiculous.
The world is a ridiculous place.
Assistant Manager Ahn,
you're even more ridiculous.
ABM Yoon Song-ah.
Yes?
Was he watching?
Let's go.
Yes, BM Lee.
You're going to the headquarters, right?
They've set up a new display stand.
Yes, I'm going with Hyun-seung later.
Are you coming, too?
No, I'll go later on.
I'll go with the director.
Check carefully
so that he doesn't find fault.
Okay, I'll check carefully.
Get going now.
Hello, this is Lee Jae-shin from KLAR.
Once again, Seolyoon is the only product
[KLAR Cosmetics Division's Sales Budget]
in our department that
hasn't reached the monthly sales goal.
What should I do
if it's always like this?
I'm sorry, Director Lee.
-We're doing our best, but...
-Stop!
Other BMs are doing their best as well.
I'm sorry.
Come in.
You called for me, sir?
Yes.
You may leave, BM Seo.
We'll talk about responsibility later.
Take a seat, BM Lee.
You know why I called you, right?
Not really, Director Lee.
Seolyoon doesn't have any star products.
We need those for sales.
What do you think is the problem?
It's your job to figure it out.
I'm just a BM, I don't know anything.
But if it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't be able to get this title.
Help me out.
Is Seolyoon willing to make an effort?
They're already at their limit.
What about Bayer and Lassiere?
I'll only do as much as
Seolyoon is lacking.
Okay.
What would I do without you?
Our chairman has no mercy
for the untalented
even if I'm his grandson.
My team members will do all the work.
Please reward them well.
It must be so easy for KLAR.
It's a brand that is
good enough to sell itself.
How in the world
would sales go up on their own?
It goes up because
our BM and ABMs work hard.
We just follow BM's instruction.
Are you saying that my brand
has poor sales
because I'm incompetent?
Don't take it the wrong way.
He knows himself well enough.
What did you just say,
Assistant Manager Kang?
Were you talking to me?
I didn't say anything.
You heard it too, right? Didn't you?
Me? I didn't hear anything.
My mist was making a noise, so...
Seriously.
Nothing scares you
because you're hotshots, is it?
You have no basic manners,
just because Director likes you...
Assistant Manager Kang.
Yes, sir.
Sort out the monthly achievement
for every team
and bring it to me.
Yes, sir.
I owe you again. Thanks, BM Lee.
It won't happen again next month.
Our new product will hit the jackpot.
Right, I really hope it will.
Of course it will.
I have manners
and so I want to repay your kindness.
You still play tennis
with the director, right?
Let's play tennis together
and head out for a meal.
It's on me.
Are you going to play this weekend?
The world is so unfair.
Competent employees
should have more spare time,
but instead they're given more work.
But the incompetent ones...
It's almost time for evaluation.
Be concerned about your sales, BM Seo.
By the way,
you should only play tennis
for the sake of your health.
Serves him right.
What do you think about office romance?
What?
I was listening back there
and wondering if
it's really that inconvenient.
You have to be careful.
When you're dating,
people make a huge fuss about that.
And you have to keep seeing
that person after breaking up.
There are more cons than pros.
So you won't date at work, is it?
Me?
I'd be reluctant.
But still, if you like someone,
what can you do but date them?
If you see anyone dating secretly,
just ignore them.
Okay.
-Keep on looking.
-Okay.
How's the new product?
The sales aren't bad.
Yes, it's selling well.
But can you make us a mirror
for sales promotion?
That brand's got a pretty mirror.
Over there.
May I help you?
It's okay, I'm just looking around.
What are you doing?
Senior Yoon!
Checking out a product?
I'm doing market research.
You're making it obvious that
you're from a competitor.
Am I?
Do you need any help?
It's okay, thank you.
Yes, please!
Your lipstick seems great.
Can you pick one
for my girlfriend?
Pick one, honey.
Your girlfriend is so beautiful.
Right? What's the best one here?
In this line, this product
is the best seller.
Would you like to test this out?
Do you want to try it on?
You are unbelievable.
We can't do market research
out in the open.
I'll let it slide. Just this once.
Don't you remember what happened
the first time we worked together?
People suspected if we were dating.
Things have cooled down now,
but they still want to ship us.
What if someone saw what happened?
Well, I just...
I know.
It's because you feel at ease with me.
Still, it's better to be careful
to avoid misunderstanding.
I might seem like an old fossil,
but that's the office life
I've experienced.
You understand what I'm saying, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry, I didn't think it through.
Forget it, it's fine.
Take it to the
Product Development Team tomorrow.
and file an expenses claim.
Senior, you should take it.
It's okay, I have a lot of lipsticks.
But you don't have this one.
Even if you have a lot,
you only apply the same one.
This one looks good on you.
Well, anyway. You should take it.
Take it as a thank-you gift
for teaching me well.
Can't you accept it?
Well, I did work really hard.
You're a troublemaker.
Thanks, I'll use it well.
Okay, but
you have to use it.
Don't give it to someone else.
Do you want to get something to eat?
I have a dinner plan.
Dinner with whom?
My boyfriend.
Bye.
You don't have one.
Welcome.
Oh! Over here!
You came just in time.
I lucked out in the food department.
Wow, it looks delicious. Let's eat.
-I'll pour for you.
-Okay.
-A lot of rice cakes?
-Yes.
Hey, about your trainee.
Hyun-seung? What about him?
Does he like you?
What?
You two seem like you're dating.
Did your colleagues not say anything?
They used to.
But now...
He doesn't like you?
He's just friendly.
Perhaps because he has two sisters.
Wow, he has two sisters?
Forget it, it won't fly anyway.
[Mother]
What is it?
Nothing serious, I'm sure.
I'll call back later.
It could be important. She's living alone.
[Song-ah's mother]
Don't answer it.
You don't even know.
Don't answer it. Period.
[Song-ah's mother]
[The number you dialed is temporarily
unavailable, please try again later.]
They're not picking up.
They never pick up
their phones right away.
It's soggy.
[KLAR Reception]
[Urban Cotton Reception]
[2 - 3 p.m.]
[Lunch time!]
[Let's find job together.]
Excuse me!
Are you here for career counseling?
Yes, but it's...
It's okay. Come in.
[KLAR Job Fair]
Oh, no.
I had something to do, but I forgot.
I'm sorry, I'll come back later.
I have something else to do.
But...
If you come back later,
you might have to wait for hours.
It's our last day.
You might not get counseling at all.
Would you at least complete
the papers before you go?
You're very kind.
Usually they won't be like you.
This could be a desperate opportunity.
It was for me.
I think this is how a marketer
should've acted.
We must make the users
our first consideration
although I'm not doing marketing now.
Well...
Wait a moment.
Wait right there!
[Big Sister]
Wow, this is great.
Isn't this place popular?
It's hard to make a reservation here.
The chef is a friend
of Yeon-seung's husband.
I see.
You don't even have a girlfriend.
How do you know this place?
Do I need a girlfriend to know this?
I know because I wanted to
bring the two of you here.
You didn't even bother to contact us.
Stop lying.
He must be really busy.
What do you mean?
He doesn't even have a girlfriend.
That's why he has time for us
whenever we call him.
I've come to the wrong place.
I'll go eat instant noodles.
-Hey! Sit!
-Come on.
What's wrong with you?
This is all your fault.
Why me?
The lower stream will be dirty
only when the upper stream is dirty.
But the upper stream is so clean
that it's become a natural reserve.
What will the lower stream learn from you?
You make bridal dresses
for others every day, but...
You are exaggerating.
She can take care of herself.
Is that why you never tell us
about your girlfriend?
I won't tell you because it's you.
What's wrong with me?
Am I going to eat her alive?
Of course.
Stop laughing!
By the way,
how are you going to celebrate
your birthday? Do you have any plans?
I've made a lot of plans.
So, don't worry about me,
and take care of Ha-eun.
You two are worse off than Ha-eun.
At this rate, she'll get married
before her aunt and uncle.
I should've taught you better,
but men wouldn't leave me alone.
That's why I had no time to teach you.
Slightly to the right.
Lift your chin.
Lower your hand.
Lower.
Look at the camera.
Not like that.
Like this.
This angle is the best for you.
Okay, last ten shots.
Director!
What's the matter?
Do you
have a boyfriend?
No.
Give me your phone number then.
I have a husband.
What?
Honey!
I had fun today.
He has such a unique hairstyle.
I did well, right?
You were creepy.
When someone helps you,
you should say thank you first.
I'm hungry. Just drive.
Alright.
[How are you going to celebrate
your birthday? Do you have any plans?]
[You should take it.]
[It looks good on you.]
[You have to use it.]
I'm going upstairs for a meeting.
-Yes, sir.
What would you like to order?
One Iced Americano
with two shots of espresso
and two pumps of vanilla syrup, please.
I'll have one Iced Americano.
I'll have the same as the first one.
Love you, my colleague.
I'll buy it for you next time.
Yuck, why is it so sweet?
This isn't your style.
How is it?
Whoa, man.
What's wrong with your taste?
I like it.
What?
You poor scoundrel.
If your work life is tough,
you must say it out.
How could you do this to yourself?
Why are you here?
Assistant Manager Jung
told off Min-seong again.
Seriously, that guy...
He's a total disaster for a trainer,
but he said I'm the disaster.
I have the worst boss.
I might stand up against him one day.
-You haven't done it yet?
-No.
But when he goes back to the office,
he'll say he admires
the assistant manager.
Man.
Of course, that's what I'll do.
I'm going to work here for a long time.
As long as they don't kick me out,
I won't leave on my own.
Honesty is your biggest charm.
Have you fallen for me?
Do you want to go out with me?
I'm not really into office romance.
What should I do, Hyun-seung?
-What should you do?
-Stop.
Hyun-seung!
It's your birthday soon.
What are your plans?
When is it?
Thursday.
Oh! Let's hang out that day.
No!
We won't meet up. No. Never.
I'll get going now.
Hey, hold on.
He downright refused.
Senior Yoon.
Yes?
What are you doing on Thursday?
Do you have any plans?
♫ Happy birthday to you! ♫
♫ Happy birthday, dear Hyun-seung! ♫
Cheers!
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you.
That hits the spot!
Wow, I'm full.
Beef for dinner and drinks afterward.
The birthday boy is buying everything.
Sorry for being a freeloader.
Stop being one then.
You buy the drinks.
-Me?
-Yes.
You said you feel sorry.
You should be paying then.
Are you finally paying?
Hey, I paid once in a while.
Everything is on me tonight.
You're all celebrating my birthday.
-You should've said that earlier.
-I was holding back on my appetite.
She never says she'll buy.
Why are you spending
your birthday with us?
You must have a lot of friends.
Right. Even if you have no girlfriend,
do you not have any friends either?
Come on, sir. I have a lot of friends.
I'm here because I like my teammates.
He's buttering me up.
Poor Hyun-seung,
you should meet people outside the office.
With your face and your talent!
I'll set you up...
He'll do well on his own.
What decade are you living in?
Stop bugging him.
Good job.
What? Bugging?
Assistant Manager Ahn, stop bugging him.
You're a terrible matchmaker.
Sir, you are nagging me now.
I didn't tell you, but
there are eight couples...
Are you waiting for a phone call?
No.
By the way, it's my treat here.
As a birthday gift.
I refuse.
Why? It won't be much.
That's why I refuse.
Tell me what you want then.
Nothing expensive though.
It doesn't have to be an object, right?
Later, when we finish here...
Excuse me.
-I need to go to the restroom.
-Okay.
-Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
You should make more friends.
Cheers.
BM Lee has finished his meeting.
We'll have one last drink when he comes.
Already? Why?
Let's hang out some more!
Karaoke! How about karaoke?
Karaoke? Sounds good!
Not for me.
I thought you liked it.
Why not? It's not that late.
Hyun-seung, you're coming, right?
-Of course, he will.
-Me?
Let's go to a karaoke bar. It's on me.
I don't know.
Let's go.
You're making me uncomfortable.
You have to go.
You'll go, right? You're going, right?
Stop, you're making me exhausted.
Let's go together.
I have to go to the restroom.
The restroom? Not karaoke?
Make it quick! Be ready!
It's dangerous.
You startled me! When did you get here?
Just now.
Seriously.
Did you have dinner?
Yes.
-Shall we go?
-Yes.
Did you drink a lot?
Moderately.
Which means you drank a lot.
Aren't you going to ask me
how the talk went?
I'm sure it went well.
It's you who did it.
It didn't go well.
It didn't?
What should I do?
What else can you do? Go see them again.
Why aren't you heading back?
Do you really want me to go?
Yes.
I'm leaving!
I actually did well.
Seriously.
Let's go, everyone's waiting.
Did you get home safely last night?
Yes.
You disappeared while
I was out for a second.
Did your friends call you?
Yes.
You were up all night, right?
You look really tired.
Chae Hyun-seung,
aren't you getting on the lift?
You two go ahead first.
What's the matter with him?
Who?
Hyun-seung. He doesn't look good.
I wonder if he's okay.
Aren't you paying
too much attention to him?
He's my trainee.
Are you jealous?
Maybe?
Have a good day.
-I'm going upstairs for a meeting.
-Yes, sir.
General Manager Yoo.
[I'm going upstairs for a meeting.]
Do you want another beer?
Come by the shop tomorrow
and get your present.
She's taken.
That never crossed my mind.
That's why she doesn't care about me.
I had no idea.
How pathetic.
Is there someone you like?
Did you tell her?
I didn't even get to that part.
You like her a lot, right?
I guess so.
Are you trying to figure out
what to do now?
The weather is so nice.
It's so depressing.
Nobody asked me out on a day like this.
You're right, the weather is so nice.
Why aren't you on a date?
He's busy.
Again?
Why is your BM always
busy on the weekends?
It's suspicious.
It's because he's meeting the director.
Hey!
Darn it.
I heard that they are friends.
Yes, since high school.
They studied abroad together, too.
But why do I hear that they are cousins?
Probably because their names are similar.
Also, he got the BM position
soon after he got in.
-Is that a good thing?
-Nobody cares about it now.
Because
he's very capable.
You're so hyped when you
talk about your boyfriend.
-Do you like him that much?
-Yes, I like him a lot.
Will you introduce him to your mom?
Do you think about getting married?
You said you weren't interested.
I used to.
Used to?
If I introduce him to my mom,
she'll go berserk, right?
Are you really thinking
about marrying him?
It's okay, I have one here.
You always draw a hard line.
Play easy. It's not a tournament.
You'll blow out my knee.
One more round?
No, I need to leave now.
Where are you going?
Oh,
poor fellow.
You really are thinking
about marrying him!
So, stop suspecting him from now on.
No gossip, okay?
Okay.
What about your mom?
She'll go crazy when she finds out.
Why think about that already?
I don't even know
if he feels the same way.
Of course he feels the same way.
You guys have been
going out for two years.
If he doesn't feel the same way,
then that son of a...
Man.
Anyway, I'm happy for you.
You have someone you love.
I envy you.
You should start dating already.
Did you get some sleep?
Right, your present.
I should
stop, right?
She looked so happy.
Get back inside. Thanks for the clothes.
Call me whenever you need
a drinking buddy.
No way.
When I'm with you,
people think you're my girlfriend
and no woman will come near me.
You only think about yourself, is it?
You should think about yourself too.
They're here.
Bride Lee Hyo-joo,
groom Lee Jae-shin,
welcome.
I'll escort you to the second floor.
Do you know them?
Yes, they're our customers.
Why? Do you know them?
So, are you saying that
those two people
are getting married?
Ji-seung,
I can't give up
on this crush.
What?
What kind of dress should I make you wear?
A simple one?
Or a glamorous one?
What are you talking about?
Your wedding dress.
We need to think about that.
Hey! I'm not getting married right away.
It's good to be prepared in advance.
You have no friends or siblings,
but me to help you.
I'll be your big sister
and make arrangements for your wedding.
Thank you, Big Sister.
I'm so honored.
But first, take that eye booger out.
Eye booger?
The other side!
Stop talking nonsense
and get ready for work.
Bye.
Let's talk some more later.
Come home early!
-Okay?
-Whatever.
[The wedding is three months later.
What are you going to do?]
Did you have a good weekend?
Not so bad.
What about you? How are you doing?
Hello.
Hi.
Pardon me.
Get on, Senior Yoon. Over here.
Okay.
Did you have a good weekend, sir?
I did. How about you?
Not so good for me.
I saw something nasty.
You look really tired.
You must've been busy
going here and there.
Why don't you get off first, sir?
Sir?
Hyun-seung, what...
What's the matter?
It's not bad.
The title already says about
requesting for container purchase,
so you don't have to write that again.
I think you should take this phrase out.
The numbers are accurate, right?
Owing to the high expectation
for the new essence,
we received a good response for
Evaluation Team.
It's better than what we thought.
We're considering increasing the quantity.
We ran a cost simulation.
Even if we double the quantity,
it's still within the monthly budget.
If you approve it, the factory has agreed
to supply additional products this week.
What's wrong, Hyun-seung?
Sorry, my clothes caught on something.
Shall we do that?
Yes, check with the factory one more time.
[What on earth has gotten into you?]
Why are you acting like that to BM Lee?
What is it? Tell me.
I'm asking you now. What's going on?
Hyun-seung!
If you see anyone dating secretly,
just ignore them.
I'll put up with it for now
since you don't want to be discovered.
What are you talking about?
Put up with what and discover what?
-Can't you see BM Lee is...
-However,
if I think it's gone far enough,
I won't just stand by.
Because I'm protective.
I'll get going now.
Come on in.
Why are you drinking all of a sudden?
I just felt like it.
Why do you want to drink?
Did you talk with BM Lee
about getting married?
Did he say no?
Then what? Did something happen
with your product?
It's about Hyun-seung.
I think he wants to quit his job.
Your trainee? Why?
He's good at his job
and gets along with everyone.
He's doing great.
Did he confess his love for you
and get rejected?
Seriously.
I thought he was doing well too,
but it wasn't what it seemed, I guess.
I did my best because
he's my first trainee.
Well, if he wants to quit,
let him quit then.
It's his life anyway. What can you do?
Don't let it bother you.
That's right,
but I still hope he makes
the right decision.
[One month later]
[Mr. Lee Jae-shin has
made a reservation today.]
Two months...
Wedding dresses are really pretty
these days.
Look at this.
What is it?
If you start looking at wedding dresses,
it means it's time for you to get married.
I don't even have a boyfriend.
You don't need one to want to get married.
You should date someone.
Is that so?
It's good to date.
It's time, you know.
What style would be suitable for me?
You have to try them on first.
Get a boyfriend and go on a dress tour.
Are you going to get married
all of a sudden?
No, I'm not!
Ahn, doesn't your mouth hurt
with all the talking?
I'm going upstairs for a meeting.
Yes, sir.
I'm going back to work.
We'll get back to work too.
You should work, you know.
Over here.
What's up?
I'm sorry, but about tonight...
Director Lee said we have to go somewhere,
but I forgot.
Is it something important?
Yes, it's work. I can't get out of it.
I'm really sorry.
Since it's work, there's nothing
you can do.
Didn't you mention that
you have something to tell me?
It's almost our second anniversary.
Do you want to go on a trip?
Yes.
Think about where to go.
-We'll talk about it tomorrow.
-Okay.
You'll be late for your meeting. Go on.
Senior Yoon!
What are you doing here?
Are you free tonight?
Why?
It's something important.
There's something I need to show you.
You're free, right?
I think you are
because you were turned down.
-What are you talking about?
-I heard everything.
You were turned down
by the guy who seems like your boyfriend.
I wasn't turned down. He's not my...
You were turned down for sure.
Compared to what you'll face
in the near future,
this is nothing.
Anyway, you're free, right?
No, I don't have time for you.
Even if you're busy,
make some time for me.
That doesn't suit you at all.
Senior Yoon.
Don't put on that lipstick.
Please eat first if it's okay.
-Thank you, I'll pay you
-I can call you senior, right?
But I'm not an alumna.
Okay, sure.
If you're a marketer,
what brand do you represent?
KLAR.
Marketing Team at KLAR.
I'll see you at work next time,
[Yoon Song-ah]
Senior Yoon Song-ah.
You can treat me to a meal next time.
Okay.
[KLAR Job Fair]
Right,
my name is Chae Hyun-seung.
Chae Hyun Seung.
Chae...
Hyun-seung.
Yes.
That really goes well with you.
[2 - 3 p.m.]
[Lunch time!]
[Job Fair]
Let's go in.
Sorry, it's lunchtime until three o'clock.
There are 20 minutes left.
We'll come back later.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
It's lunchtime until three o'clock.
-Three o'clock?
-Yes, It's not time yet.
-If you haven't eaten, go get a bite.
-Okay.
You startled me.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
My bag...
Sorry!
[KLAR Job Fair]
[Next episode]