#ROMANTIC
#FREE-SPIRITED
#GIRLCRUSH
#VOLUNTARILY SINGLE
#IN A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP
HOW IS YOUR LOVE?
LOVESTRUCK IN THE CITY
-Let me go home. Take it off.
-How could you say that?
-Calm down.
-Hold on. What?
-Are you going to hit me?
-You know what? Fine.
Since you're so petty,
take them with you. Happy now?
-Gosh.
-Do you have spare shoes?
He returned everything.
-Please calm down.
-Okay.
-Good.
Okay.
What?
-Take off your underwear.
-What?
-Are you crazy? Come on.
-Take it off!
-Stop it!
-Wait!
-Take off your underwear!
-Hold on.
-That's enough, miss.
-Are you insane?
-Why do you want him naked?
-Hold on.
Hey. Give me your bag.
-I bought it for you. Give it back!
-This?
I should give it back to you. That's fair.
-Take it.
-Give it back.
-Take it. Take the bag!
-You're crazy. Come on.
-Take it!
-Goodness. Hold on.
-Hey, hold on.
-Stop her.
-Hey, are you crazy?
-Take it.
-My gosh.
-You don't think I can?
-Hold on. I'll leave after I give it back.
-Wait.
Hey, take it!
I think I've seen that woman before.
She was beating up a man
when I was moving out a few years ago.
Name, Oh Seon-yeong.
I've seen her at another division.
She does that often.
But she still keeps falling in love.
Yes. She doesn't get sick of it.
I'm jealous.
However, gifts are donated properties,
so she can't get them back.
Don't come to the police after a fight.
It's tiring for us, too.
It gets worse when they're drunk.
Hey. Damn it.
Take off your underwear before you go.
TAEPYEONG-RO POLICE BOX
Catch the thief.
The camera thief.
She
stole my cameras.
Her name is Yoon Seon-a.
I'd like to report
this heinous camera thief.
-Sure. Okay.
-112. You're the police.
Yes. Come this way.
Okay. Right here.
-Where do I sit?
-Right here. Sit here.
All right. Goodness.
Officer, I had
some cameras.
Three, to be exact.
Those cameras were special.
After I got my first paycheck,
I saved up what little I got to buy them.
But she stole those cameras.
The name of the woman
who stole those cameras is…
-Yoon Seon-a.
-Kang Geon.
-And I first met her at…
The karaoke.
-A beach in Yangyang.
That's where we first met.
You met Yoon Seon-a
during your surfing trip in Yangyang.
Yes.
And that girl stole your cameras,
right, Mr. Park Jae-won?
She stole them.
She took more than my cameras.
She took my heart.
She took my heart, too.
I have to get the underwear back.
My heart.
I won't cry.
By the way,
how do you know my name?
-Mr. Park Jae-won?
-Yes.
Aren't you an architect?
How did you know that?
Look. It's written here.
"Park Jae-won."
-What?
-"Drunk."
-And it's written here, too.
-This is…
"February 7th."
Everyone at this police box
knows who you are.
Everyone knows me?
And the camera thief, Yoon Seon-a.
-You know me, too?
-Yes.
-Mr. Park.
-Yes?
You're a regular here.
"Regular"?
For the past year,
you came here five times.
-Five times?
-This is your sixth.
Sixth?
Sixth? I came here way too often.
How come I don't remember anything?
Right. I bet.
-You can't remember because…
-I don't remember.
Why did I come here?
You were always drunk when you came here!
Why are you yelling at me?
-Don't yell at me.
-Look.
-Oh Dong-sik.
-Okay. Look.
-Name, Oh Dong-sik.
-Right here. Look at this.
-December 15th.
-Okay.
-That was your first time here.
-"He was drunk."
Yes. And then,
-February 7th.
This is for this year.
June 14th. August 9th.
-And October 27th.
-But are you sure that was me?
Yes.
-Are you sure?
-I beg you.
-Please stop coming here.
-Please catch her, then.
Can't you go to another precinct
and ask them instead?
Why do you always come
to our police box, Mr. Park?
Did we do something wrong?
Do you not have any patrol division
in your neighborhood?
We need more than a name to find her.
We need more information,
like her resident registration number
or home address.
Don't just say that she is a camera thief.
-We need other information.
-She was pretty.
Thank you.
She was so beautiful.
Earlier tonight
in Seongsu-dong,
I ran into Yoon Seon-a.
She changed her style.
And she looked prettier.
Well…
But I've always been pretty.
And I'm super stylish, too.
She's not Seon-a, is she?
Okay.
Why don't you lean back? Sit comfortably.
Kyeong-jun.
Hey. You're up.
Are you making salad?
Yes. I wanted to do something nice
for you this morning.
You're not eating at Eun-o's?
We're going to have bread for breakfast.
Really? Are you craving bread?
I see. Then, I'll stop by a bakery
and pick up some bread.
Head over there first.
-This shoulder is too rounded.
-Hey, square your shoulders.
-Yes. Like that.
-But it hurts.
I'm always sitting down.
What's your relationship?
We're kindergarten friends.
We've lived around here
ever since we were kids.
I've never left this neighborhood.
After my parents moved to a farm,
I thought about moving,
but I decided to stay here.
I was born and raised here.
I like it here.
-This is my home and office.
-I live in a studio in the next alley.
It's nice to live close.
We can hang out a lot.
I can't date because of them.
You won't believe me, but it's true.
It must be our fault that you haven't
slept with a girl for two years, then.
-Of course, it's their fault.
-Don't blame us.
There's only one reason
why girls leave me.
They ask me a question, and I answer them.
And then, it's over.
4 YEARS AGO
Hey.
Do you like me or Lee Eun-o?
I like both you and Eun-o.
Do you like me or Suh Rin-i?
Are you asking me to choose
between love and friendship?
No. I don't believe
men and women can be friends.
Is it me or Eun-o? Is it me or Rin-i?
I like you as my girlfriend.
And I like them as my friends.
I bought this for you.
Ask your nice "female friends"
to buy one for you.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Rin-i.
She's here.
Hello, Seon-yeong.
Seon-yeong.
Girls shouldn't fight with each other
over stupid boys.
For your boyfriend.
She's so cool.
Girl crush.
There's no way they broke up
because of us.
I bet it was something else.
-You were a bad kisser.
-Or you were bad in bed.
Or both.
He had skills, but not passion.
Or he was passionate,
but he didn't do it often enough.
-Are you done?
-Yes.
Keep going. Are you done?
Here's what I don't understand
the most about my ex.
How could she think…
How could she think that
I would fall for girls like these two?
I don't see them as women.
Do you think we see you as a man, then?
I realized you were a boy
when we were eight.
Didn't he wear his sister's dress
to kindergarten?
Hey!
-They were shorts.
-Right. He did.
You did wear them!
And it drove your mother crazy.
Guys, I'm here!
Rin-i, I got some bread.
It's cold outside. Let's go in.
-Did you get cream buns?
-Not sure. You can check.
-I need to use the bathroom.
-Pushover, play some music.
-I'll play something sexy.
-Eun-o, I'll get the milk.
Okay. I'll get the plates and cups.
-These will do, right?
-Yes. Good.
-I'm hungry.
-I'm so hungry.
-I've been digging this song lately.
-Same here.
This is why I can't see them romantically.
I like sexy women.
Yes.
Don't come near me. Move back.
You guys are the opposite of sexy.
What are you talking about?
Rin-i is so sexy.
Are you okay?
Don't do it. Stop it.
I told you to stop it.
If you don't, I'll dance, too.
What's he doing?
I know that dance. It's the Fly Dance.
Hello?
Where?
The police?
Hey, turn it off.
Park Jae-won is at the patrol division?
TAEPYEONG-RO POLICE BOX
Hello.
Thank you for your hard work.
-Thank you.
-Accepting this will get us in trouble.
No, it's nothing big.
You're working so hard at this early hour.
I hope these drinks will help
boost your energy.
Think of it as my gesture
to wish you a good day.
Good day!
-The Constable Oh Dong-sik I spoke to…
-It's me.
You're Park Jae-won's cousin,
Choi Kyeong-jun, correct?
Yes, that's me.
By the way, where is Jae-won?
If he keeps this up, he could be charged
with public intoxication
based on the Minor Offenses Act.
It wasn't a big scene,
but he's done it many times.
"Many times"?
What was the reason?
You came quickly.
Isn't it quite cold in there?
The floor is cold.
-Why did you come here? Tell me.
-Well, I…
Did that girl really steal your cameras?
Hey, Kyeong-jun.
You should have some ox blood.
-Have two pieces.
-Can't you eat it?
I like it,
but I'll give it to you.
You made a fool of yourself.
What is this? It's embarrassing.
-I don't live here.
-Fine. You're so cool.
I'm glad you don't live here.
I'll do all the client meetings
for a month.
Meetings with constructors, too.
Okay. You can have my rice, too.
Don't tell Rin-i about the cameras.
Hey, Rin-i. This is crazy. Listen.
-Don't.
-Do you remember Yoon Seon-a?
He didn't give his cameras to her.
She stole them from him.
Exactly.
They probably cost 20 to 30 million won.
-Stop it.
-Yes. I'll tell you later.
Okay. Talk to you later.
-A bottle of soju, please.
-Ma'am, ignore him.
No. Ma'am, five bottles of soju, please.
Drink them all and die.
Where and when did we agree to meet?
Cheonggyecheon's third stepping stone,
last Saturday of this month, at ten.
Hey.
What are you staring at? Let's just go.
What is it?
-What are you looking for?
-Nothing.
Come on.
My gosh. There you are.
Darn it.
I'm confiscating them.
Did you think I couldn't find them?
Drink again,
and I'll inject you with alcohol.
-Hey.
-Thanks for the liquor.
ALL ABOUT MARKETING
O3
What? Are you throwing that out?
Yes. Go ahead and throw it out.
You can do it, Jae-won!
-Are you done?
-Yes.
Let's see.
-Gosh, they look great.
-We're done.
-How are the waves?
-I heard the waves would be great.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let's check.
What is this? The waves suck today.
Right. They never get anything right.
Let's do something else.
Okay? Let's do something else.
Hey!
Come here! Come here.
-Give it back.
-Here you go.
Give it back. Come on. Now!
-Right here. Here you go.
-Give it back now.
-Right here.
-Forget it.
Right…
Okay. I'll stop.
Let me dry your hair. Just like this.
Hold on.
How beautiful. You look gorgeous, Seon-a.
-Stoop down.
-Down?
Here.
-Take that!
-Stop it.
Stop that.
YEOKSAM-DONG COMMUNITY CENTER
Hello.
How do I throw out this surfboard?
I need to pay first, right?
Take a number first.
A number? I'm sorry.
I want to throw this out.
You're here to buy stickers
for oversized garbage.
Hold on.
I'll throw it away.
I'll forget her.
You do need to buy the sticker
to throw it out.
-Okay.
-But we no longer sell them.
-You can buy them at other stores.
-I see.
Do you want the list of stores?
Yes, please.
-Here.
-Thanks.
Isn't that a surfboard?
It looks fine.
-But you want to throw it out?
-Yes.
-Really?
If you're really sure about that,
leave it here.
Give it to me.
Well…
No.
Why not?
You said you were throwing it out.
If I take it, you won't need a sticker.
Okay. Keep it.
That felt nice.
-It's so refreshing!
-Isn't it nice?
It's raining like that day.
I can't throw it out today.
This rain will pass.
Right. Even if I put off
what I can do today until tomorrow,
I'll be okay.
That's my life philosophy.
It will pass.
We should decide on this
after we discuss it with the client.
Okay.
What on earth is Mr. Park carrying?
Don't mind him.
It might be better for us
to think that at our office,
we have a drunkard who went crazy
after getting dumped by a girl.
-The project in Bongcheon-dong--
-Hey, Kyeong-jun.
The dashcam.
-The dashcam in my car.
-What are you talking about?
I went to the police box last night
because I saw Yoon Seon-a
in that neighborhood yesterday.
In Rin-i's neighborhood?
My gosh. Why didn't I think of that?
It's in my car.
I have a dashcam in my car.
Wait. Where's your car?
TOW NOTICE
Hey! Where's my car?
Damn it. Gosh. No!
It's been towed away.
Kyeong-jun.
Hey, my car was towed.
Why are they so diligent?
My car…
Hey, can you comfort me?
Come on. This is not cool.
I'm about to go crazy.
Hey, Rin-i.
-Jae-won is officially insane.
-Don't tell her about the car.
He said he saw Yoon Seon-a
in your neighborhood.
So he parked his car here
and went to drink.
-Don't tell her.
-But his car got towed.
I think Jae-won is seeing things
because of alcohol addiction.
This is pretty serious.
Right? Don't you feel bad for him?
Now? We're on our way to
the storage facility for towed vehicles.
What a crazy morning.
He's been dragging me along all morning.
No. We can keep talking.
Did you eat lunch, baby?
What did you eat?
A salad?
I told you to have some rice.
What? "Alcohol addiction"?
"Feel bad for him"?
You just wait here.
I'll show you how she looks.
-How will you do that?
-With the dashcam.
Gosh. Why didn't I think of this sooner?
You're dead meat.
Yes. I'm calling
from 310-23, Seongsu-dong.
I'm reporting an illegally parked car.
Yes. Tow it away, please.
Okay.
Wait. Is it okay if I pay the fine?
Oh, I can't? I see.
Okay. Please tow it away carefully
without damaging the car.
Okay. Thank you.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs