♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 13
Yeah.
Just now,
I blew off the Dragon Incense,
and broke the Dragon Flag.
It may not end well.
General Wen comes just in time.
Your Majesty.
Give my order,
to evacuate people!
-Aye!
Kai
Sir, what happened to you?
My old wounds haven’t recovered.
Just now, I was punched by Feng Wuyan.
But I’m fine.
Before getting what he wants,
Feng Wuyan will not
let it go.
If he follows us in,
you must fight with him.
Me?
I’m going to teach you
some little Eight-trigram Formation.
Before he realizes,
we’ll break into
the Eight-trigram Formation
and run out.
This?
I... I saw this before.
Is this
the Eight-trigram Formation
of Daoist magic?
You know it?
I did some light readings at home.
I had a memory of it.
Great!
Senior brother.
You rushed in so hurriedly.
Are you hurt?
Let’s go.
Go!
Where... Where are we going?
Qian, three Yang.
Kun, six Yin.
-Answer me, or I’ll break in.
-Go.
Sir, sir, are you alright?
Zhen, six Yin on the top.
Senior brother.
Gen, six Yin on the bottom.
Come out and let’s talk.
Li, Yin in the middle.
Senior brother.
Kan, Yang in the middle.
Dui, three Yin on the top.
Xun, three Yin on the bottom.
-Wrong.
-We can’t go this way.
Take three steps right forwards.
How stupid you are!
Go.
I haven’t heard of this before.
Give me some time to digest it.
In this Eight-trigram Formation,
even switchable screens
represent divinations.
Qian, three Yang. Kun, six Yin.
Didn’t you read books
about Daoist magic?
According to it,
Only Kai, Xiu and Sheng Doors
are available doors.
Unavailable doors are full of traps
which are not passable.
I think I understand.
According to books about Daoist magic,
there are eight doors.
When we find Sheng Door
in the northeast,
we can go out, huh?
Senior brother.
If you hear me, say something.
I didn’t expect you to be so clever.
Let’s go west
for Jing Door.
Weird. Isn’t it an unavailable door,
with traps?
You can’t give the chief’s whisk
to an outsider,
right?
How about this?
Give it to me.
And I’ll let you go, all right?
Feng Wuyan.
Because you wanted it,
you brought disaster to us.
Now, our sect is in such trouble!
Do you still not regret?
Regret?
My father was partial to you.
You’re now partial to a young man.
You’re going too far!
I’m taking back what belongs to me!
Don’t walk to Jing Door.
Get away in time. Hurry.
Jing Door
You’re obsessed!
Feng Wuyan!
Former Chief gave the whisk to me.
I can’t let him down!
Don’t use my dead father as the excuse!
I didn’t mean to kill you.
Don’t force me!
Jing Door
Go.
Sheng Door
Qian, three Yang. Kun, six Yin.
Zhen, six Yin on the top.
Gen, six Yin on the bottom.
Li, Yin in the middle.
Kan, Yang in the middle.
Dui, three Yin on the top.
Xun, three Yin on the bottom.
Do you remember the formula
I just taught you?
Almost.
I almost remember it.
Sir?
Sir!
You’re now
in the Big Dipper Array,
among eight famous arrays
of Mystery Forest.
Think about how to get out of it.
Big Dipper Array?
Qian, three Yang. Kun, six Yin.
Zhen, six Yin on the top.
Kan, Yang in the middle.
Li, Yin in the middle.
He’s too honest.
He thinks
he owed you!
But I don’t owe you!
Honest?
How dare he say that!
He said
he gave his life to me,
so that I could kill him as I wished.
But in fact,
you’ve been hiding
and I couldn’t even find you!
In my opinion,
you’re as hypocritical
as before!
Pei.
Don’t worry.
I don’t have martial arts now.
You can kill me,
sooner or later.
But if the North Blade vanishes
in my hand,
I’ll feel bad.
The North Blade?
What about the Mountain Sword
of my family?
You’ll feel bad?
My father didn’t even have a chance
to feel bad!
But don’t worry.
I will get back
what you owe me.
You can’t get away today.
So,
you led Dragon Master to this place
so that he would kill me?
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
Ms. Kou.
A message from the secret service.
Leave me.
Aye.
Madam.
A disciple sent a message,
saying there’s no news
about Ms. Wang and others.
I see.
Ms. Kou.
I feel something fishy.
Please send some capable disciples
to keep looking for them.
If there’s still no news,
I’ll go personally.
Aye.
Hua, I’m afraid we’d better leave.
Oil
You saved
my life.
I’ve already enjoyed it.
I’m not afraid of death.
But I don’t want to leave the inn.
Your Majesty.
Guests have been evacuated.
Please go back with me.
I’m afraid
Dragon Master is arriving soon.
I messed up with Dragon Master.
As long as there’s one last guest,
I can’t leave.
But...
Oh,
where is Zichen?
He’s on his way back to Jiankang.
Luckily,
you used a wise strategy
in Huarong.
Or his problem wouldn’t
have been solved.
I just met him
and helped him out.
Your Majesty, you must go back with me.
General Wen.
Pretend you didn’t see me, will you?
I can’t.
Your Majesty.
So many people saw you.
Please don’t embarrass me.
You’re having me surrounded
with so many men.
Even if I want to embarrass you,
can I?
When General Wang Lin
commanded the armies,
we were so proud.
Now, he has gone.
Our soldiers
have been expecting you
to come back and take charge.
Why don’t I remember anything
about this?
I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
Oh,
ask the cook downstairs
for two jars of beef paste.
If I don’t have any now,
I’m afraid I can’t have it anymore.
I can finally give this back to you.
Fei.
You’re still angry with Xie?
Him?
Besides legs,
he has only a rich stock of lies.
If he wants to talk,
he can keep talking for the whole day,
even when the pigs fly.
But...
He’s an emperor.
Why is he wandering about?
Well,
he’s a poor man, too.
His name was Xiao Chuan,
a prince of the former dynasty.
When he was little,
he suffered a rebellion.
-The palace was besieged.
-This way.
Later, there was a fire.
No one was expected to run out.
Unexpectedly, an old eunuch
risked his own life
to send him out of the palace.
General Wang Lin of the former dynasty
got Mr. Xie back to the palace.
Good days didn’t last long, though.
He was sent to the neighboring country
as a hostage.
During this period,
another general rebelled
and built a new dynasty.
The former one was then overthrown.
General Wang Lin supported Mr. Xie
as the Emperor,
trying to recover the former dynasty.
Is this why
he concealed his identity
and became Xie Meimei?
But why didn’t he tell me?
His kingdom was gone.
Here is the new dynasty.
Instead of living a rich life,
Mr. Xie wanders around alone.
There must be some reason.
It’s understandable
when he didn’t tell you who he was.
I nearly stabbed the Emperor
of the former dynasty.
Whatever!
I don’t care if he’s an emperor.
In my eyes,
he’s just the unlucky Xie Meimei
who always lies.
Oh,
you told me
when you came,
you received a letter of my mother’s
from our secret service.
Yes. I have it.
To General Feiqing
From Li Jinrong
My mother asked the secret service
to send you back to the Fortress.
She has a point.
A rich girl like you
should live in big house
and a lot of people should serve you
when you leave home.
You shouldn’t have been wandering around
with us.
Life in the Fortress of the Forty-Eight
can’t be as good as before.
But at least,
you’ll be taken care of
and well provided for.
Fei.
I’m no longer a rich girl.
Letter
Weird.
Why did my mother only mention you,
but not your younger brother?
Theoretically,
she shouldn’t have been so calm
after she knew
what had happened in Huarong.
Unless...
This letter is fake?
There’s something wrong
with the secret service?
I must go home and check.
No way.
About the problem of Dragon Master,
Xie Yun and I are also involved.
If we leave like this,
I’m afraid
everyone in the inn will be doomed.
Chuchu.
I’ll have General Wen
send you to my father’s place.
He’ll take good care of you.
I’m not going anywhere.
I just want to follow you.
No way.
If General Wen fights
with Dragon Master,
I don’t think I can take care of you.
It’s because I’m not strong enough.
If only I could be as powerful
as my grandpa!
Fei. Fei.
I believe no one,
but you.
Besides,
I’m not a thing.
Don’t always deliver me.
Fine.
Stay in the room, then.
Don’t go downstairs
before I tell you to.
Help
Sorry, but I can’t help.
Your Majesty,
what the hell are you doing?
Heroine.
Take me with you, too.
You’ll take her, anyway.
Take me as well.
Besides, if there’s danger,
I can run away.
I won’t get you in trouble.
You heard it?
I did hear it.
You’re not angry with me anymore, huh?
From now on,
we’ll go our own ways.
Why should I be angry with you?
Heroine. Heroine.
I beg you.
Get me out of the inn!
I’ll do anything I can in my next life
to repay you.
Fei. Fei.
I wondered
if you really wandered about
to help the weak!
Turns out
you’re just the same as Li Sheng.
You both fool around
and even run away from home.
After handling the problem here,
I’m going home.
Listen.
You’d better go home early, too.
You have poor martial arts.
Don’t get your families
to worry about you.
I also want to go home.
I wish to have a family
to expect me back.
You... You don’t have a family?
Family?
Speaking of relatives,
I think there are many.
But...
They’re not a family at all.
You...
You have a younger sworn brother,
don’t you?
Zichen?
Yeah.
I watched him grow up.
He’s also close to me.
He’s the Third Prince of this dynasty.
We’re of different status.
But...
Luckily, I have him.
-Run!
-Go!
Get in.
Why are they beating the gong
in the day?
You don’t know, huh?
I won’t tell you.
Oil
Ji.
There’s sound of gong out there.
Seems like Dragon Master has arrived.
Zheng Luosheng, Dragon Master
of Four-guardian Mountain
Wen
Our general asked me
to take his regards to you.
I wonder
what you come for.
I see.
General Wen asked his man
to send a message.
So, Dragon Master is using
his way.
He also sent a subordinate.
He is putting on airs!
Good.
You guessed it right.
You’re getting smart.
My master said
this place didn’t belong
to north or south.
But when he knew you were here,
he wouldn’t make trouble.
But,
he has lost a dog.
He heard
his dog was locked up in this inn
and someone burned the Dragon Flag
and put out the Dragon Incense.
We come for an explanation.
General Wen is reasonable.
I don’t think
he’ll blame us.
Who do you think
is more powerful,
Dragon Master, Shen Tianshu
or Duan Jiuniang?
As famous as Mu Xiaoqiao,
he must have something great.
In such a big world,
there are many powerful men.
It can be a difficult job
to compare them.
But I believe
you’ll be as powerful as them.
Under the premise
that we can get out of the inn.
I don’t mean to be unreasonable.
But an important man is living here.
I think you’d better leave.
We’re leaving early tomorrow morning.
Why don’t you wait for one more night?
Tomorrow,
you can fight
whomever you hate.
I won’t interfere.
People like us don’t want
to be your enemies.
Fine.
General Wen, take it easy, too.
We’ll wait outside the inn.
After you leave tomorrow,
we’ll come again.
Leave.
Dragon Master.
I destroyed your flag
and your incense.
I’m your enemy.
Let go of guests in the inn
and fight me!
You’re doing this on purpose?
I don’t have a choice
under this circumstance.
General Wen!
What is your mission of your trip?
To protect you.
Yeah.
You’re right.
We’ll have chances
to see such occasions.
Now, we should run away.
But the whole inn is besieged.
Do you remember
when the young man came this morning,
Mr. Hua asked him to search,
but he found nothing?
So,
you mean
there’s a secret tunnel in the inn?
What, General Wen?
Could this arrogant young man
be your master?
I came for several times,
but you avoided me.
When I tried to fight that girl,
you showed up in time!
I’m sure
you’ve got a hiding place here.
Run away from your doghole, then!
Since you’re awesome,
you’ll make great achievements!
Why are you staying here?
Just leave!
Don’t, Miss Zhou.
If you push him out,
you’ll get him killed.
He nearly got you killed!
He made so much trouble!
Why are you still defending him?
I’m sorry.
I don’t want to get involved.
Mr. Ji,
where is the doghole
you just
mentioned?
What?
You want to get in?
Not before you kill me.
If you promise not to hurt him,
I’ll take you there.
Chuchu is still upstairs.
I’ll go get prepared.
I’ll see you in the granary
in fifteen minutes.
-Okay.
If we really fight,
General Wen,
it’s hard to see who will win.
You’re right, Dragon Master.
If you can
let go of local people
for the sake of my young master,
I will visit you
and thank you
with generous gifts.
Fine.
I’ll let them go, for your sake.
I’ll forget about
the incense and flag thing.
And I won’t kill local people.
But...
My dog is clever.
If I can’t get it back,
I’m afraid...
I don’t want it to happen again.
So today,
I must get in and search.
This has nothing to do
with your young master.
General Wen,
you will help, won’t you?
Dragon Master.
Please.
Search it!
-Aye.
You...
You won’t fight?
Young Master, this is the end.
Don’t embarrass me anymore.
Wait!
These two girls are families
of our young master.
They two
look gorgeous.
You just promised to let people go
for my sake.
What?
You regret?
I thought about it again.
I think
we’d better fight.
Cloud
The secret tunnel is near the granary.
Go.
You’re brave.
When Mr. Zhou knows,
he’ll be relieved.
Fei.
Don’t show off your bravery.
Go find Mr. Ji.
I’ll go with my beautiful girl.
Is beating an emperor against the law?
You shouldn’t beat anyone.
Beating ordinary people is
also against the law.
Good, then.
Don’t go too far!
Are you really an emperor?
Do they get the wrong guy?
Wait.
General Wen looks reliable.
I don’t think he gets the wrong guy.
So,
you get the wrong identity, huh?
Exactly.
You know me best.
You’ve seen me through.
I get to like you more.
If today,
General Wen gets hurt for you,
you’ll lose a lot.
Don’t worry.
General Wen is the strongest subordinate
of your father.
Dragon Master can’t hurt him.
Go.
Let’s go to the granary for Mr. Ji.
Where’s Chuchu?
Stop looking. Here she is.
Fei.
I don’t have great martial arts,
compared to great people
like you.
But I think
it won’t be a problem
when I want to kill such a girl.
That’s all you can do?
Take your hands off her!
If she’s hurt even a little bit,
I won’t let you go!
Why does she look
much more beautiful than you?
Girls should be as gentle
as her.
But you keep fighting.
You’ll get wrinkles on your face.
Oh, I forgot.
When you keep fighting,
you won’t even be old enough
to have wrinkles.
Besides,
do I look like I’m afraid of death?
Pei!
I heard Mr. Ji called you like that.
I guess that’s your name, huh?
Are you Mr. Yin?
What do you know?
Miss Zhou.
Don’t kill him.
I didn’t expect him to learn
the acupoint-shifting way
from Dragon Master.
I’m sorry for my neglection.
Do you think
I only joined Four-guardian Mountain
for shelter?
No wonder you were so evasive.
Turns out you were just lying,
so that you could kill people
and run away!
Miss Zhou, let him go.
For the...
For the sake of Old Master Li.
Why do you mention my grandpa?
Fei.
If I guess correctly,
he’s the offspring of Yin Wenlan.
The Mountain Sword?
One of the most famous marital artists?
Sword stands for gentlemen.
The Mountain Sword Yin Wenlan
came from a decent sect.
He became a master after he grew up.
Sadly,
he and his family were all killed.
He? Offspring of the Mountain Sword?
What are you staring at?
If you were really proud,
why did you do dirty things before?
We’d better leave soon.
Let’s go.
Wine
Welcome Guests
Master.
We’ve searched two floors of the inn,
but didn’t find him.
Losers!
Animal on screen is an example of CG
Go.
Go find him out.
Animal on screen is an example of CG
The North Blade stays
in such a small inn
as a cook.
He’s so scared
that he has even dug a secret tunnel.
I don’t understand.
Why are you a rat instead of human?
What about you?
You’d like to be a dog, too.
You know nothing!
I’m a human.
I don’t understand you, without doubt.
I’m kind enough to let you follow us.
What are you yelling for?
I’ll beat you!
Everybody, I dug
this secret tunnel
for my fiancée and me.
We wanted to live in seclusion
and hide here.
In case enemies come to fight us,
we dug this secret tunnel.
It has nothing to do with Ji.
Miss Zhou.
Mr. Xie.
Miss Wu.
Please go first. Hurry.
You go, first.
Okay.
Mr. Hua.
Is your hand okay?
Yes.
Thank you, then. We’ll go first.
Please.
Fei, go.
Pei, go with us.
Go.
Animal on screen is an example of CG
Seems they went this way.
After them!
Animal on screen is an example of CG
Pei. Pei.
Mr. Hua.
Ji, I trusted you
that he was just young and impulsive.
But you saw what he did today.
Why do you still defend him?
You saved me.
But I won’t let him go!
Hua.
You always say
he saved your life.
You just helped a woman
when you were young.
You were badly wounded and nearly died.
He saved you, huh?
Ji Yunchen.
The woman he saved
found you, huh?
Yes.
Why did you give her
the last Reviving Pill
to save him?
When I came inside the pass,
my master gave me a Reviving Pill.
It helps ordinary men
to get recovered from old wounds.
You had been sick since you were born.
I wanted to feed you with it
when you grew up.
It may help to refresh your body.
Unexpectedly,
the secret was exposed.
I knew what you had done.
How would I take your pill?
Yes.
I exposed that when I was drunk.
Ji Yunchen.
Why don’t you think about it?
Who got you drunk?
Who asked you for the secret?
Who got me there?
Shut up!
That woman seemed to be pure.
But she was scheming.
She did everything,
to set a trap.
She wanted me to hate you,
just to get the Reviving Pill
and save this man.
You’re alive,
partly because of me.
But you want to kill me?
Two ways?
Where are they?
They have their own grudges.
We’d better not interfere.
Hua, go!
Ji, you saved my life.
Since you want to defend him,
I’ll let you be.
Take care.
Hua!
When I dug the secret tunnel,
-You!
-I set a trap.
I didn’t know I could use it today!
Why are you following up?
What? You built the tunnel?
Shame on you!
You!
Miss Zhou.
Where’s Mr. Hua?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Master.
General Wen’s men are still around.
Animal on screen is an example of CG
My baby.
After General Wen leaves,
Animal on screen is an example of CG
you must help me
to find my dog.
Animal on screen is an example of CG
He is familiar with this place.
I guess he has run away.
Where is this way leading?
This way leads
to the foot of Mount Heng.
A secret tunnel
at the foot of Mount Heng?
Does Mount Heng Sect agree?
Miss Zhou, you have no idea.
When two armies fought in this place,
local people were suffering greatly.
Mount Heng Sect was always respected.
Many disciples came from local families.
They would certainly try to help.
But once they helped,
they would be involved in the war.
What happened later?
In that battle,
the chief and some elders
all died.
The remaining young disciples
couldn’t afford to hold such a big sect.
Those who had families went back home.
Those who didn’t have families
left with their new chief.
Where have they gone?
I hear the new chief was
the last disciple of the old chief.
When he left,
he was just sixteen
or seventeen years old.
No one knows where they left for.
We’d better leave now.
Go.
Fei, why does he know everything?
I guess he only cares about gossips
when he wanders around.
Hit your nose?
Your tears are running?
-Let me have a look.
-Fei.
Are you having a nosebleed?
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
What are you doing?
Believe it or not? There’s a bug.
Make way. Make way.
Disgusting.
You stepped on my foot!
Sir.
How much time did I use?
Less than fifteen minutes.
Much faster than last time.
The formation of your school
is wonderful.
The more I think about it,
the more interesting I feel.
It took me a long time
to understand it.
You’re a clever man.
You’ve learnt all our formations
when you learn for the first time.
It proves I have a good taste.
You’re a young talent
from the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
I can’t take you as my disciple.
But I want our formations
and martial art books to be inherited
instead of vanishing with me.
What have I done
to deserve your gracious kindness?
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪