♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 26
Come on.
Hold tight.
I’m going to have a good fight.
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt♪
Guards!
♪In my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
I can’t die now.
Not now.
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
If more Demon’s troops come,
we won’t be able to hold!
Our lives mean nothing.
Kill as many as we can.
Leader is back!
Charge!
Hyah!
Pull back now.
Shen Tianshu.
We’ve got into their base.
Why will we pull back?
Shen Tianshu!
Li Jinrong and her elite disciples
are coming back.
Once Anping Army arrives,
we’ll be trapped!
Pull back!
Fei.
Sheng.
Answer me, Sheng!
Sheng!
You beast!
How dare you come again!
-Madam.
-Pull back!
Don’t chase them.
Madam.
Li Sheng is down there!
Here he is!
Be careful.
Pull.
Sheng.
Are you all right?
Aunt.
You’re finally back.
The Fortress.
Are the enemies repelled?
Yes.
I’ll take some sleep.
Go ahead.
Take good care of Sheng.
I’m going to find things out.
My father always said
this blade was a legacy.
It means to be.
Mother.
Don’t move.
You injured internally.
You’ll be fine soon.
Certainly Ma Jili won’t hit you hard.
What happened with your inner power?
Who did you meet before?
I... A long story.
I met Duan Jiuniang at Huarong.
She transfused Yellow and Green Spirit
into my system,
and told me about her past with Grandpa.
She is a true master.
You were lucky to meet her.
Mother.
Li Sheng...
He’s fine.
Chuchu found him
hanging under the Feihong Bridge.
Just mind your own business.
Mother.
Where is Xie who came back with me?
Do you know who he is?
I do.
He travels around in the world,
and makes a living by selling songs.
With two mustaches,
he’s nicknamed Qian Suiyou.
Back then
he trespassed Ximo River
and was supposed to be punished,
but he was ordered to do so.
-Thanks to him, we could...
-Save it.
Leave his matters aside.
Take a good rest
and get recovered first.
Then explain to me
what you have done during your travel.
Time is running out.
Aren’t you dead?
I am not that easy...
to get killed.
You...
Nice blade.
Do you like it?
But you can’t take it.
I mean,
you are more talented
and have better understanding
in martial arts.
Over so many years,
I’ve been trying to catch up with you,
but I can’t.
I’m reluctant to fall behind.
Don’t gloat.
Listen to me.
The saying has that
he who laughs last,
laughs best.
You’re better than me now,
but soon I’ll surpass you.
Alright.
Wait and see.
Have... Have some tea.
It’s hot.
Thank you, Brother.
Who was talking with me?
I didn’t hear it clearly.
Brother.
Take a good rest.
I’ve got goose bumps.
What is Cloud-impelling Palm?
He is so powerful.
But why did he follow me
all the way here?
What is the tune?
Depart in Departure Sorrow Pavilion.
You’ve heard it a lot along the way.
Why asking again?
I come to see you.
Can I come into
your room?
You can’t.
Something is wrong with my ears.
I can’t hear some words clearly.
Since you say I can,
I’ll come in.
Thanks. Come on.
Come on in. Be seated.
We are not strangers.
No need to receive me outside.
Sit.
Miss.
Why are you staring at me like that?
I’m handsome.
You should pay money
if you keep watching.
No money.
You can watch me, too.
You...
What?
I find that
the more worried you are,
the happier you look.
Yet you talk in a serious way
when you feel relaxed.
Is there
anything you want to ask me?
Shen Tianshu said
you used Could-impelling Palm.
What is that?
You have top martial arts.
How come you were bullied
by a gang of rascals?
Moreover,
what is the Color of Ocean and Heaven
that you are after?
Xie Yun.
Why do you have
so many secrets?
Judging from your look,
you must be thinking
how to fool me with your lies.
I won’t ask.
No.
OK.
I’m leaving
if you don’t.
By the way.
Take this back.
Things are done.
You can take it back.
When Miss Wu asks about it,
you can explain.
What is it?
Xie Yun.
Are you pretending nothing happened?
You...
Where will you stay?
The guest room here.
This place is indeed a wonderland.
It’s cool and pleasing in summer.
I want to stay a while longer.
Get yourself recovered.
Then
take me to have a tour around.
You know the scenes here
better than me, don’t you?
You are acting.
That’s not like what you would say.
What should I say then?
Should I say you may
put on some weight
and be my princess?
Are you all right?
Of course.
I’m absolutely fine.
Why are you after
the Color of Ocean and Heaven?
I don’t want it to fall into
the wrong hands.
Since you’ve known it,
I can tell you the truth.
Chuchu’s Longevity Lock,
the Mountain Sword’s scabbard.
And your family’s gold bracelet.
These are
important items to open
the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Alright.
Stop asking.
You have so many questions.
Xie Yun.
I...
I won’t be so impulsive again.
I’ll tell you wherever I go.
I’ll talk to you first.
How is it?
Sure.
Anything else?
And...
No more.
I thought you’d hold back for some days.
I knew you couldn’t help asking me
and caring about me.
But in this way,
I’ll know, in your heart,
I mean something to you.
I’m just meddlesome, maybe.
Why bother to come here?
Chuchu.
Sheng.
I... I come to see
if you get better.
I... I’m much better.
Sorry
to let you worry.
Now
you are safe here.
Your brother
is out alone.
It’s worrisome.
Why don’t you get him here
to be with you?
You can take care of each other.
It’s fine if you don’t agree.
I agree.
Are you back alive shamelessly?
He’s my man.
You have no right to punish him.
Tianxian.
Rise.
Lord Shen.
How do you explain it?
My men were about to break through
the gate.
Who ordered
to pull back?
I didn’t expect,
Shen Tianshu, a top master,
the Head of the Demons,
could be defeated by a gang of boys
from the Fortress.
Who do you mean the boys?
I found it weird in Chunhui Town.
He should have died.
Yet he was alive and kicking,
and played the Cloud-impelling Palm.
The power of the Palm
is impossible for people of his age.
No way.
He got hit by Bone-chilling
ten years ago.
That was the fiercest poison
in the world.
It’s incurable.
How could he survive?
If a great master
used his own energy
to resist the poison in his body
and save him one life for another,
he could have a chance to survive.
Xiao Chuan.
Are you really so lucky?
Not really.
Xiao Chuan survived,
but he couldn’t use his own energy.
Once he uses,
the poison in his system
will be let loose.
His life
can only last for months.
He used Cloud-impelling Palm
against you.
Didn’t he know he’d die?
If that’s the case,
the attack to the Fortress
is worth something.
Although we lost some men,
Xiao Chuan will die soon.
It’s not bad.
Why did he risk his life
to protect the Fortress?
Is he also after
the Color of Ocean and Heaven?
It’s hard to tell.
If it’s true,
his men will surely
go after other
Ripple-shaped objects.
Lord Shen.
You’re hurt badly.
Yet we don’t have much time.
I wonder if you can get
the Ripple-shaped objects
before then.
All my lords are
top-notch masters in the world.
If you don’t trust us,
you can have others do it.
Lord Shen.
Lord Shen. I’m joking.
Wish you a quick recovery.
I’m waiting for good news from you.
Tomb tablet
Mourn
Which is Fisherman’s tomb?
He liked to be neat and tidy.
Feng Yuping’s tomb
I’ll come often to see him
and weed for him.
Mourn
Everyone.
My fortress survived the attack.
It is you who helped us
and defended it with your lives.
Tomb tablet
We will never forget
what you did for us.
Today,
the disciples and I
pay our last respects to you.
The world is full of danger.
No one is immune to it.
As the code of our sect says,
may we live with no regret.
We vow to
wipe out the evil.
-Save the people,
-and bring justice to the world.
-We don’t have to be remembered,
-and don’t have to be fairly treated.
-We will never fail the Heaven,
-the Gods, and the Fortress.
-All the sects, together,
-we unite as one.
-All the disciples shall keep the vow.
The view here is stunning,
people extraordinary.
In a turbulent time,
there should be no wonderland like this.
Wait, Young Master.
Madam asks for you.
What’s the matter?
You’ll know
when you meet her.
Please.
Madam. Mr. Xie comes.
Please, Mr. Xie.
Greetings, Mr. Xie.
The Fortress got attacked.
The injured are being treated around.
It’s inconvenient to talk.
So, I ask you to be here.
Please don’t mind it.
Not at all, Madam.
I’m no longer a stranger here.
Mr. Xie, you helped us
repel the Demons.
I’m grateful.
My pleasure, Madam.
I was just escorting Miss Wu
back to the Fortress.
We encountered the battle.
Given my friendship with Lord Gantang,
and also for the righteousness,
that’s what I should do.
You are young and highly skilled.
Who is your master?
I’m nobody.
My background doesn’t matter.
I just lead a free life
as I please.
Alright.
Where a hero comes from matters not.
You saved my daughter.
I keep that in mind.
If you need help someday,
the Fortress will help you as we can.
Thank you, Madam.
Miss Zhou fought gallantly
to defend the Fortress with the elders.
I was afraid to hold her back.
Madam.
Please pardon me.
Miss Zhou has been
following your example,
because she wants to
be recognized by you.
I suggest
you may praise her
more often.
Thank you, Mr. Xie.
By the way,
you look kind of pale.
Are you unwell?
Were you injured
by the Demons in the battle?
No. No. I’m fine.
The Fortress
is kind of humid. I’m not used to it.
Glad to hear.
Take good care of yourself anyway.
You are going to leave here.
Be safe.
Madam Li is kicking me out.
This is the token to leave.
Fortress
Have a safe journey.
Take care, Madam.
I’m leaving.
She’s kicking me out.
Time to say goodbye.
Chuchu.
Li Yan.
These cakes are from my brother,
as a gift for you to move here.
You may take here
as your home.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Chuchu.
My brother said
your brother would come here, too.
Tell me your childhood stories.
Nothing special, actually.
I’m serious.
Chuchu.
I only dare to tell you this.
I want a brother as well.
When he comes,
I’ll take him to tour
all over the Fortress.
Keep yourself busy.
Brother.
We can be reunited soon.
That guy hit my drowsy acupoint.
Did he want to run away?
What are you doing?
The friends here are so hospitable.
I eat too much and take a walk here
to digest.
And see the moon.
There is no moon tonight.
What are you looking at?
Are you avoiding me?
No. No. Absolutely not.
Fei. You’re seriously injured.
Go back and rest now.
I’ve slept the whole day.
My injury is not serious.
Come. Let’s go somewhere.
Where to?
Xie Meimei.
I’ve made up my mind.
I’ll go with you to look for
the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Why?
Because that item is evil.
A rebellion occurred here ten years ago.
Now it got the Fortress devastated
again.
The Color of Ocean and Heaven
was the cause.
I have to destroy it
before I can feel at ease.
Fei.
There’s no clue
to look for it.
For the Lock, Demons burnt the inn.
For the scabbard, Dragon Master
was after us.
The Fortress suffered great casualties.
Even you nearly got killed.
Why bother to do this?
I still have you.
You are not a jinx.
You are a mascot to me.
You got me out of danger so many times.
What am I afraid of?
What’s wrong?
You are numb today.
It’s not like you.
Nothing.
Maybe it’s too pleasing to live here.
I get idle and lazy.
It’s indeed a good place
to recuperate here.
Fei.
If it’s fine,
I’m willing to stay here with you,
free from the affairs
in the outside world.
But,
aren’t you looking for
the Color of Ocean and Heaven?
That’s not my wish actually.
I am forced to do that.
♪Though the world outside is chaotic♪
♪Travel freely with the flute♪
Xie Mascot.
I have something for you.
But,
wait for some time. I haven’t finished.
♪Ignore the troubles♪
Weed Spirit.
Do I have to wait
to get a gift?
You have to.
Give me another day.
One day?
Alright.
♪So lucky to get the wooden peach
from you♪
Fei.
♪It makes me miss you♪
Thank you.
♪You don’t know♪
♪My love is pure like ice and light♪
♪Even the dragon ages over time♪
♪So does the hero braving the world♪
♪Petals fly in the dream♪
♪Like greeting the old friend♪
♪Keep the vow we made until death♪
♪Travel freely with the flute♪
♪You got me caged in your heart♪
♪Ignore the troubles♪
♪Hold your hands and smile in wind♪
♪So lucky to get the wooden peach
from you♪
♪It makes me miss you
You don’t know♪
♪My love is pure like ice and light♪
♪Even the dragon ages over time♪
♪So does the hero braving the world♪
♪Petals fly in the dream♪
♪Like greeting the old friend♪
♪Keep the vow we made until death♪
♪However far to go♪
♪However high to reach♪
♪This moment is worth my forever love♪
She’s the promising heiress
of South Blade.
I am
just like the vulnerable dust
fighting against the fate.
Time to say goodbye.
It’s not rude, is it?
Whatever.
Embroidering this even
got my fingers hurt.
Like it or not, he must accept it.
Xie Meimei.
Where has he gone?
Fei.
What are you doing here?
I’ve been looking for you.
What’s the matter?
Madam asked us to go out
and buy medicine.
Oh, I forgot.
Let’s go.
Chuchu.
Please take the lock back.
It’s too important. Take it back.
It is too important.
I don’t know martial arts.
It’s safe being with you.
Keep it.
No.
I always travel around.
What if I lose it?
Leave it with my mother.
It’ll be safe with her.
You’re right.
Leave it to her then.
-Let’s go.
-Sure.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪