♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 25
Bonehead.
No! No! No! Don’t cry!
Be quite.
Other Demons might find us.
What are you here for?
When I was in town,
I saw Yu Wenzhi’s private army.
He is a man of noble blood.
Why is his heavy army stationed
at Chunhui Town?
There is certainly something fishy
about this.
I was worried,
so I came back to take a look.
Who are you worried about?
None of your business.
It’s definitely not you.
Bonehead.
I’ve never thought that
I would be so happy to see you.
Don’t try to be smart.
I’ll leave you alone now.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
Why did you leave the Fortress?
The Demons are plotting against
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
with Yu Wenzhi.
My brother asked me to deliver a letter
to look for help in the town.
Fine, I’ll go with you.
I’m not afraid of death.
Me neither.
Heaven bless us!
-Let’s just take them with us.
-Just die together.
Sister.
Haven’t you just said that
it’s dangerous out there?
Don’t go out.
I’m here to protect everyone.
You’ll be safer inside.
Young man,
it’s your responsibility
to protect everyone here.
I need to go out to
find some information.
I’ll be back soon.
When you grow up,
you can become a real man.
Then, you can protect the nation.
Okay?
Okay.
This is how we’re supposed to be.
We must not let the youngsters beat us.
Slow down.
Bonehead.
This is not working.
How about this?
That is the road to Chunhui Town.
You can go find Fei.
I’ll deliver the letter
to our secret service myself.
No!
How can you go there on your own?
I must go with you!
No way!
You’re a strong fighter.
You’re not afraid to die, too.
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
needs a man like you right now.
But...
But what?
My martial art is not as good as Fei’s.
But delivering a letter is an easy task.
No! No!
The Demons have their pawns everywhere.
What can you do
if they’re after you?
Besides...
Bonehead,
this is not the time to worry about me.
Who’s worrying about you?
I’m concerned only because
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
will be upset with me
if you get hurt.
Right.
That’s it.
Cut it out.
You’re the master of Cloud Ravine.
Why can’t you act like one?
Go.
Yang Jin.
Be careful!
Anybody inside?
You know what you should do, right?
Talk sense.
Go. Open the door.
Who’re you looking for?
Sir,
why isn’t there anyone outside?
Who’re you?
I don’t know you.
I’m from Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
I’m here to ask for your help.
This letter.
You must give it to
Lord Gantang, Zhou Yitang.
Tell him that
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
is under the siege of the Demons.
You’re talking to the wrong person.
I don’t know anyone from
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Sir, please help me.
Young lady,
where are you going?
What do you want?
We’ve been hiding around here for days.
We’ve found this place suspicious
early on.
You’re unfortunate
that we catch you today.
So, you’re the secret spy
sent from the Fortress.
You’re here to deliver this letter.
Why is this all blank?
What’s your trick?
Go.
Go now!
May you have all five luck in the world.
May I inquire
What color is the bat?
Actually, I’m not with the Route Gang.
I have an urgent matter.
I need to talk to Chief Xu.
My brother and Fei
must have sent me to deliver this letter
because they wanted to protect me.
I need to find help.
Report!
We’ve searched everywhere.
But we couldn’t find Li Sheng.
How’s that possible?
We must still be able to
distinguish his remains.
Maybe he has fallen into Ximo River.
What?
Sheng sacrificed himself to protect us,
to keep away the Demons.
How are we supposed to tell Leader
if we can’t even find his body?
Chuchu,
wait for me.
Those animals!
One day,
I’ll kill them all.
Commander, something went wrong.
Our spy at Fortress of the Forty-Eight
told us that
they have already sent out people to
ask Zhou Yitang for help.
Their reinforcements will arrive
very soon.
How can someone
leave the mountain successfully?
Lord Shen has the fortress surrounded.
Those from Fortress of the Forty-Eight
can’t get away from the main road.
Spinning Wire Formation of Ximo River
has their rear protected.
I suppose they won’t dare to
close the formation.
If those cunning bastards
don’t come out soon,
we have to fight our way in.
But Yu Wenzhi’s defense is impenetrable.
He has his private army
and Mingfeng Building.
We do not stand a chance
if we choose to fight our way in.
Xie Meimei,
you said that Yu Wenzhi
is prone to suspicion.
Spinning Wire Formation failed
last time.
It must have compromised
his faith in Kou Dan.
I’ve heard that there’s a secret path
behind Ximo River going downhill.
Why didn’t you tell us earlier?
It’s just hearsay.
I don’t know if it’s true or not.
Chief Kou,
you’ve been hiding important information
again and again.
What are you plotting?
Fine, Commander.
This is not the time to
fight against one of our own.
Lord is under the siege in the mountain.
Reinforcements from Zhou Yitang
might come at any time.
I think
if that happens, we’ll be screwed.
The most urgent matter right now
is to send out your help immediately.
People are most off guard at night.
We’ll strike then.
I’ll send people to help Lord Shen
right away.
Is there any news about Zhou Fei?
We’ve lost track of them
ever since they rescued the people
at the ancestral hall.
This is not right.
This is not right, everyone.
It’s not safe for me
to stay here anymore.
Ms. Kou,
we’re fooled.
Kou Dan.
It’s indeed you.
Leader,
what are you here for?
General Wen,
I’m here to talk with Yitang.
That’s very unlucky.
Lord Gantang left for
North camp yesterday.
You’ve been really busy recently.
How’s everything going in the camps?
The pressure is
from both inside and outside.
I first met Gu Tianxian
at Hengyang.
Now the enemies in the North
are getting restless.
If you need help, I can arrange someone
to deliver the letter
to Lord Gantang for you.
Leader,
take some rest in the camp.
No need.
Since the Demons have arrived
at Hengyang,
they’re not far from
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Safety comes first. I’ll go back now.
General Wen, goodbye.
Leader, take care.
Where has Yu Wenzhi been?
Don’t worry.
His disguise will crack soon.
What are you drawing?
Can’t you speak?
If you’ve successfully
sowed discord among them,
with Yu Wenzhi’s suspicious nature,
he will replace his current guards
who’re from Mingfeng Building
with his private soldiers
for the sake of safety.
You mean...
Yu Wenzhi will be at the place
where the Mingfeng guards
have been replaced.
Smart.
If he has replaced those guards
from Mingfeng Building,
our chance of capturing him
will be higher.
Ms. Kou.
It’s time for the shift.
Lord.
There are so many of them.
I’ll create some distractions
to cover you.
Don’t go! It’s too dangerous.
Take care of yourself.
Go after him.
Yes.
Li’s Mansion
Lady, may you have all five luck.
This is Route Gang’s Five-bat Token.
Take it with you when you travel.
Route Gang will take care of
everything for you,
from accommodation
to transportation.
My name is Huang Zifu.
I’ve been working undercover here
for a long time.
Chief Xu has given me the secret order
to stay at Yu Wenzhi’s place
and wait for you.
Chief Xu is also at Chunhui Town?
How did he know that
I’m looking for Yu Wenzhi?
I don’t know about that.
Thank you.
Second chief,
Commander-in-chief asked me to
give Lord Shen this present.
Report.
Yu Wenzhi’s private army has arrived.
We can have full control of them.
They come right in time.
According to our secret spies
in the town,
Kou Dan said that
there’s a secret path
leading into the Fortress.
Hou Zuo. Hou You.
-Yes.
Arrange a small team to find the path.
Surround their back.
-Yes.
Team number two.
Search the back.
Let’s surround them.
Report!
Yu Wenzhi’s private army is attacking.
They’re trying to take down the fortress
with Shen Tianshu.
That’s bad!
A lot of Demons have gathered
at the back.
We don’t know what they want.
If this keeps going,
we can’t guard the fortress.
Nonsense!
Whether they’re
plotting something or not,
I just don’t believe that
they can take down
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
with us, Qianzhong Sect, guarding it.
Everyone, listen up.
Everyone who can still move
must come with me.
We must fight them till our last breath.
Yes.
Let’s go!
Wait.
I’ll go with you.
Zhao.
Don’t go.
Just guard here.
You must take control of the situation.
Zhang.
The fortress is about to fall.
There’s no sense in
my giving command here.
What we can do now
is just take our chance.
Fine.
Let’s put our life and death behind.
Let’s fight them.
Zhang.
I’ll leave you to
defend the fortress gate.
I’ll inform Ma Jili to
take the rest of our people
to fight the Demons
at the back of the mountain.
We’ll catch them unguarded.
Great. That’s the way.
Zhang.
If...
If we can’t guard the fortress gate,
do as we’ve planned.
Shoot two whistling arrows in a row.
Inform Zhou Fei and the rest
to abandon the fortress
and flee for their life.
Sure.
Commander-in-chief, report.
Words came from the mountain.
Although the enemies
have burned Feihong Bridge yesterday,
their leader has been captured.
Lord Shen has arrived at the gate
and arranged the formation today.
This fortress
will definitely fall.
I don’t care about
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
at all.
I only want to revive Mingfeng Building
right now.
I hope you can really be so carefree.
-Catch him.
-Hurry.
Stop there.
Who are you?
I’m just a nobody.
Nobody?
Since when does a nobody
have such great footwork?
It’s just a small trick.
There’s nothing to brag about this.
Come.
Assassin. Catch him!
Lord Gu hasn’t returned till now.
Did anything happen to him?
There’s nothing to worry about that.
Have you finished replacing the guards?
Replacing the strong fighters
from Mingfeng Building
might not be a smart decision.
Really?
But I’ve just received words that
a secret man practicing
Mingfeng’s martial art
tried to catch me.
You have my utmost loyalty.
Even if I believe you,
can I trust every one of your pawns?
Report!
We’ve found an assassin nearby.
How did they find this place?
I’ll arrange reinforcement
to protect your safety.
So, you’re Zhou Fei
from Fortress of the Forty-Eight?
I’ve heard your name for long.
I expected you to be savage.
But you’re quite pretty.
Surrender yourself today.
The martial art of Giant Leopard
certainly lives up to its name.
I really admire you.
Go after him!
Catch him!
Giant Leopard,
this has been such a long pursuit.
You’ve done a great job.
Stop there.
He’s fooled us.
Let’s go back to commander-in-chief.
Let’s go.
Go.
You’re not from
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Who are you?
Tell me your name.
Tell you my name?
You don’t deserve to know my name.
You, a bunch of lowlifes.
How dare you act against
a man of noble blood?
No one can get out of
this yard today.
Yang Jin, why are you here?
I met Li Yan on the way.
She told me that
you’re coming to catch Yu Wenzhi.
She cried and begged for me to help you.
She’s so annoying.
I can’t go against her will.
Look.
I’ve brought help with me.
Miss Zhou,
I haven’t seen you for a while.
Thank you, Kou Dan.
You can leave the rest to us.
It’s really you?
Commander-in-chief.
This is her trick.
This place is not safe.
Come with me.
Let go of me.
How dare you betray me?
Commander, listen to me.
Back away.
Protect Commander.
Someone!
It seems that I’m faster than you again.
Girl.
You’re very brave.
I’m not brave,
nor am I a kungfu master.
My success today is
attributable to Kou Dan.
You’re so cunning.
This trick has sowed discord
that I can’t repair.
I didn’t expect that
I’d be defeated by you today.
It seems that you’re even smarter
than Leader.
I’m flattered.
You.
Will you retreat your army or die?
Girl, do you really believe
you can walk out in one piece today?
-Commander-in-chief.
Yu Wenzhi.
You’d better behave yourself.
I might accidentally cut you.
Don’t say anything
other than answering my questions.
Don’t make any unnecessary moves.
If you hurt Commander,
even a little bit,
all the army will attack, and everyone
from Fortress of the Forty-Eight
will die a horrible death,
whether you believe it or not.
I surely believe it.
What else are you here for?
Aren’t we already
in the middle of your attack?
-Or are we having a feast?
-You...
Can we really survive
if Yu Wenzhi is not harmed?
A horrible death?
That’s just irrelevant right now.
Let me ask you again.
Will you retreat your army or die?
This South Blade is indeed
a good knife.
But you don’t seem to be a good person.
I didn’t expect that during my stay
at Chunhui Town,
the thing that impressed me most...
Back off.
Back off!
Thanks.
Weed Spirit.
Nice job.
It’s indeed him.
Hold it.
Prepare the arrows. Hurry.
-Yes.
The shield.
Shen Tianshu.
Bastard.
We haven’t seen each other for years.
Your look still disgusts me.
Chief Zhang,
your temper hasn’t changed a bit either.
Great.
Now that you’re here,
let’s fight until death.
Shoot! Kill him!
Chief, are you all right?
Don’t mind me.
Take the injured to get treated.
Okay.
Come.
Come if you’re not afraid of death.
Hurry.
Chief Zhang. Chief Zhang.
-Why are you here?
-Chief Zhang.
What’s going on at the back?
Shen Tianshu somehow knew
there’s a path at the back.
We’re losing the ground there too.
Where’s Zhao?
Why hasn’t he come back with you?
Chief Zhao
has been severely injured.
Hyah.
Aunt. Aunt.
Aunt.
Yan, why are you here?
Things went sideways
at Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Mingfeng Building has turned against us.
The Demons have invaded
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Let’s go.
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
This way.
Don’t mind me.
Mr. Ma.
Miss Chuchu,
why are you here?
Go back.
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
might fall at any time.
I’ll fight with you.
This is dangerous, Miss Chuchu.
Yes.
You’re hurt.
Let me take care of you first.
It will hurt a bit.
Stay here, Miss Chuchu…
Crap.
Come. Let’s take them with us.
Tear Fortress of the Forty-Eight down.
Yes.
What happened?
Lord.
This is the horn for a truce.
Truce?
Report!
Lord.
Commander-in-chief ordered us
to retreat immediately.
Why?
Because he had been held hostage by
people from Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Retreat. Retreat.
Great! Great! Great!
Retreat.
Ma.
What is this bastard
Shen Tianshu doing?
Chief.
Is that Fei?
Where?
Set up the formation.
-That’s Fei.
-Zhou Fei’s back.
That’s Fei.
Hurry.
So, you’re Shen Tianshu.
When I was in the dungeon,
I should have fed the cake
to the dog.
Kid,
you’re so disrespectful.
Fei,
I’ve retreated as you wish.
When will you release
Commander-in-chief?
I’ll release him, but not now.
Why should we trust you?
You have no other choices.
If you want us to perish together,
I won’t complain.
Wait.
The others can leave now.
But Kou Dan has betrayed
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
She has turned against
her masters and ancestors.
She has abandoned her humanity.
Kou Dan must stay.
Betrayed my master?
The reason I’m like this now
is all because of the old loser.
She trapped me here
in this shitty place,
being isolated from the world.
Who have I really betrayed?
Ma Jili,
don’t forget my advice to you.
Chief Kou.
My disciples
told me when they returned
from the town,
they heard that Fei
has gotten herself in a lot of troubles.
You must remind her not to
mess around with the government.
I’m responsible for taking care of her.
I’ll definitely keep her safe.
You watched Fei and those kids
grow up.
If the government is onto them,
the whole fortress will be screwed.
That’s your fault then.
I know.
Go.
Fei has made up her mind to kill.
Ma Jili, do it.
Fei.
Actually,
I can get you out of here.
No,
I must not flee from
my own battlefield.
This item is more valuable than my life.
This item is about a promise
worthy of my life.
Give it to Chuchu for me.
Find someone trustworthy
to take care of this for her.
This is the key
to the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
This might be the most important key.
You know that
I’ve been investigating
the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
I know.
So I trust this one with you.
I need to use the other one
to stop them.
Ma Jili,
you said that Kou Dan is the traitor.
But what are you doing yourself?
Why did you do this?
Yu Wenzhi has royal blood in him.
If you kill him,
You’ll bring destruction to
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
As a noble,
Yu Wenzhi harms the civilians wantonly,
and commits all sorts of wickedness.
What’s wrong if I kill him?
Fighters like us
rid the world of evilness,
save people from misery,
and bring righteousness to the world.
We don’t seek immortal fame.
We aren’t afraid of being misunderstood.
But we must not go
against the law of heaven,
the law of earth,
nor our own conscience.
That’s the motto of
Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
We’re not taught to be cowards.
I’m sorry.
I was being silly.
Cut the nonsense, Ma Jili.
How can I defeat Zhou Fei
if I don’t lie to you?
Kou Dan.
I’ll kill you.
You shameless traitor.
All the traitors of
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
will be killed by me today.
You’re no exception.
If I don’t kill you,
I can’t live with my conscience.
Fighters like us
rid the world of evilness,
save people from misery...
Fei.
Are you slacking off again?
Don’t even try to.
You must be diligent.
To be a righteous person,
you must live up to your conscience.
Fei.
I’m sorry.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Soul-searching Needle
can energize you
for forty-five minutes.
Zhou Fei,
when the battle is over,
let’s fight again.
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪I dare not ask if you’re doing well♪
♪The first time I’ve felt terrified♪
♪Youth is like a sweet dream♪
♪The hope in heart never fades♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
Pass my order.
Let the main army come back
to strike again.
We must take down
Fortress of the Forty-Eight today.
Yes.
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
Cloud-impelling palm.
Wait here.
Hold it.
Let me have some fun.
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪