Sub by kisscambodia
♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 37
Miss Zhou.
What are you doing?
Are you lost again?
I’m going
to get the Flaming Sage for you.
Or how can I save you
with the Three-kind Decoction?
Am I drunk?
You roasted the fish poorly.
♪Stars flow like river♪
This side has been roasted.
But the other side is still raw.
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
How can you eat it?
♪I dare not ask if you’re doing well♪
♪The first time I’ve felt terrified♪
♪Youth is like a sweet dream♪
Fine.
If you could stay when I was drunk,
I’d like to be drunk.
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
When I get recovered,
I’ll roast a delicious fish for you.
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
When you wake up,
the first thing I will do
is to punch you.
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
Why?
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
When you were little,
Eunuch Wang bound you to the throne
with his life.
Your Junior Master
kept you alive
with all his force.
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
Now,
you’re using the same trick on me, huh?
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
It’s so clever of you.
What do I do?
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
Xie Yun.
Wait for me.
Junior Master Chen.
Why do I feel
the sun above Penglai Island this year
isn’t as warm as before?
Yeah.
Before you get rid of Bone-chilling,
you wouldn’t feel warm
even if there were nine suns.
You talk
as directly as before.
Xie Yun.
Mind your words.
You know what?
I’ve got
a present
for Miss Zhou.
You still
get to the point as ever.
Speaking of Bone-chilling,
when I was in a coma,
I had a dream.
In it,
I saw many people I knew.
Including Pathetic Clam,
who invented Bone-chilling.
It’s been years.
It’s your first time to speak of her.
Do you hate her?
She’s just a borrowed weapon.
When someone is hurt,
he won’t waste time to hate a weapon.
You suddenly bring her up.
Is there anything on your mind?
I’m just curious.
After Shen Tianshu was defeated
in the Fortress of the Forty-Eight,
could she still stay
in Demons Manor?
-Hyah!
Weird.
Why are there so many Demons?
Since the token for
the Color of Ocean and Heaven appeared,
the Demons are coming out
more frequently.
I’m an off-staff disciple
with Qianzhong Sect.
I come to take over the secret service.
Greetings, Mr. Li.
What are those Demons doing?
They’re heading
for Cloud Ravine in the south.
Looks like
they’re after someone.
Bonehead.
Drink the water
and let’s get into the town.
Someone is there?
A thief, I guess!
He ran away so fast.
He must be a spy,
instead of a martial master.
I must run after him, too!
Or he will think I’m scared of him.
Our priority is
to deliver Flaming Sage to Lingling.
Don’t ask for extra trouble.
Fine, then.
Let’s go.
Wait.
We won’t ride the horses.
There’ll be loud tramping hoofs.
Get the horses that way.
We will walk.
You sound
much more like your cousin.
What’s the problem with that?
We risked our lives
to get the Flaming Sage.
If we lose it,
we’ll be sorry to Ying Hecong!
Hurry!
Okay.
Have we got rid of them?
They must have followed the horses
and won’t come back.
Let’s go.
Someone is here.
Sheng?
Why is it you?
Oh, Li Sheng!
Finally, you’ve come!
At last, I can give her to you
without any wound!
We had such a hard trip.
So hard!
Sheng, you have no idea.
I asked you to go back home, didn’t I?
Why did you mess up with the Demons?
If you don’t
practice martial arts carefully,
you will regret!
Didn’t Aunt say so?
Didn’t I say so?
You have good luck today.
But can you have good luck every day?
Can you have good luck all your life?
Li Sheng.
Yan suffered quite a lot.
Stop complaining about her.
Yeah.
She saved our sect.
She isn’t that weak.
You have such good luck?
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
My sister always makes trouble.
Sorry to have bothered you.
It... It doesn’t matter.
Oh,
what about the medicine
you looked for Fei?
Here.
This is precious.
We must give it to Fei right away.
Hyah!
A timely arrival is better
than an early one.
You’re all here.
Chuchu.
Take Yan to find Fei.
We’ll stop him.
Okay.
Yan, let’s go.
Wanna run away?
Don’t run after them.
They’re not who Lord wants.
Don’t waste our time.
Li Sheng.
I know you have the Flaming Sage.
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Shoot it.
Take them down.
Yan, we have to count on you.
Chuchu, I can just do poses.
You should have told me earlier.
What do we do, then?
Do you think we can convince them?
Let me do it.
Hold your breath.
Hurry!
Yan.
Chuchu.
What powder did you use?
It wasn’t powder, but flour.
Go!
Li Sheng.
Did you send the signal
because you knew
I was just on my way to the south?
I didn’t!
I didn’t know you could come so quickly.
Where is the Flaming Sage?
Where are Li Yan and Chuchu?
They left before us.
Chuchu, I’m too tired to run.
Hold your breath.
This is true powder.
Are you using the same trick
to sprinkle some flour?
Do you think
we’ll fall into the trick again?
Go!
Chuchu.
What was that?
The sleeping drug your brother gave me.
So,
you’re Zhou Fei,
the heiress of the South Blade
my Lord mentioned?
Lord Tong.
Long time no see.
You still look strong.
Why are you greeting each other?
We should, of course.
Lord Tong and I are destined to meet.
We’re also old acquaintances.
When I was little,
he tried to snatch the Bracelet from me
in the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
I poked one of his eyes.
Lord Tong.
For the sake of our acquaintance,
please turn a blind eye
if my cousin has offended you.
I’ll pay you with the other eye.
Very well.
Chuchu and Li Yan may be in danger.
Go help them.
I’ll hold him back.
No way.
He can turn a blind eye,
but I can’t!
He’s my enemy!
So,
he’s your cousin?
Go.
Can you handle him alone?
He’s a mere Demon.
Just go.
Lord Tong, the other day,
Lord Lu tried to snatch
a Fire Lotus from me.
Now you want
to snatch the Flaming Sage from me.
Why do you people
always want medicinal materials?
Shame on you.
Does Lord Shen want to run a pharmacy?
How arrogant you sound!
My Lord wants
to exchange the Flaming Sage
for the Seal of Cautiousness!
You’re not too stupid.
Unfortunately, I don’t have the Seal.
You can’t get it even if you kill me.
Not to mention you can’t kill me.
Think about it carefully.
Lord, Mr. Shen received a secret letter.
Phoenix Master had
the Seal of Cautiousness.
Very well.
You have good luck today.
Let’s go!
I’m too busy to kill you today.
It’s your luck.
Demons Manor
Since when was my sister so strong?
Sheng? Bonehead.
Are you alright?
We are fine.
Fei came to handle those guys.
But you...
Since when were you so strong?
You defeated so many Demons.
I didn’t defeat them.
Chuchu did.
Don’t look at me.
I don’t have martial arts.
I just used the sleeping drug
you gave me.
Are you idiots?
So,
Zhou Fei gave Phoenix Master
the Seal of Cautiousness?
Yes.
Who?
My Lord.
People with Xingnan Sect are coming.
Very good.
They’re just in time.
Young Master.
In my opinion,
we shouldn’t interfere
with strangers.
Miss Zhou isn’t a stranger.
She saved us.
Do you want my brother
to be ungrateful?
Young Master.
We’re a small sect.
After we annoyed the Demons
and Qinghui, the Immortal
with Four-guardian Mountain,
I’m afraid there’ll be constant trouble.
It’s okay, Mr. Lin.
We’ll just leave Lingling overnight.
Did I allow you to leave?
Kill them!
Sir, you...
It’s okay.
Let’s go to Liu’s Manor.
Aye!
Ying!
Last night, I heard
someone was fighting against the Demons
in the suburb.
I didn’t know it could be you.
Do you want to take revenge?
Then you must be strong.
I can help you with that.
Take it.
Wait.
After you swallow it,
put it on.
When will your lord come?
Please wait a moment.
Mr. Li.
I’m terribly sorry
to have kept you waiting.
Where’s your lord?
I’ve been so busy in the forecourt
the whole morning
that I didn’t know he was sick.
Sick?
How was he sick?
He caught a cold, I guess.
Since we’ve come,
I’ll go check on him.
No, no, no.
He’s nearly fine.
You don’t need to go.
He said
when he got better,
he would visit you personally.
I don’t think he’s sick.
He’s just scared of Qinghui, I guess.
He’s getting old.
He just wants as much peace
as he can have.
So, Mr. Li,
please leave
and ask someone else for help.
Mr. Chen.
Here I am!
Where is he?
Inside the cave.
Go check on him.
He can barely hold on.
The Flaming Sage from the south.
Junior Master.
When will Fei arrive?
She has arrived.
Long time no see.
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
It’s not a long time.
You didn’t see me.
But I saw you every day.
♪I dare not ask if you’re doing well♪
I was so annoyed.
♪The first time I’ve felt terrified♪
♪Youth is like a sweet dream♪
You could be annoyed
with my handsome face?
♪The hope in heart never fades♪
What else would you like to see?
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
A fairy?
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
Come over.
Let me look at you.
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
Did you fall into the sea?
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
Why do you smell so fishy?
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
There were huge waves.
It took me great trouble to come.
I’m lucky enough to be alive.
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
Junior Master told me
you went to get the medicine.
You must have been in trouble.
I just met a few Demons.
There was no trouble.
I didn’t need to bother
when fighting them.
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
It’s been days since we last met.
You’re better at boasting.
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
Oh,
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
when you were away,
I made you a small gift.
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
Try it on.
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
Fei.
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
I miss you so much.
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
Before I woke up,
♪I’m willing ♪
I had a long dream.
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
I dreamed that you took great trouble.
I didn’t.
Let me finish.
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
I’m afraid I don’t have enough time.
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
I knew you would say
you didn’t take trouble.
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
You would also say
you should experience that.
But I was afraid you would be in danger.
When you were in danger,
I wasn’t around you.
Fei.
When you fight desperately,
you must protect yourself.
When I woke up the other day,
I could do nothing but write and paint
when I missed you.
Remember
to review them.
Xie Yun.
Are you asleep?
Last time, I didn’t want him
to fall asleep.
I was afraid he wouldn’t wake up
after falling asleep.
But this time,
I feel different.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
These days,
the things against the cold you found
have brought big benefits
to his health.
You’re really a great girl.
The Flaming Sage, for example,
isn’t an ordinary thing.
You flatter me.
You thought I was useless, huh?
I just didn’t know
how powerful you could be.
After taking three doses, he...
What can he do?
Think about other people.
Some go uphill.
Some go downhill.
Some remain where they are.
They take steps on the ground.
But you’re different.
You don’t go up the slope,
but the cliff.
There’s no path between stone steps.
Every time,
you must jump up desperately.
When you just seize the rock
on the cliff,
you must struggle up again.
If you fall instead of climbing up,
you will be smashed into pieces.
You’re going a way
where there’s no turning back.
Tell me.
Did you fear?
I did, of course.
What did you do
when you feared?
Fear?
Fear is a common feeling.
Whenever I’m in danger,
I feel like being stuck
in the crack of rocks.
If I don’t want to remain stuck,
I must move on.
Fear doesn’t help with anything.
So,
I pretend I were on a higher
or even a far higher stone step.
When I believe my own lie,
I can certainly get to it.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
You’re welcome.
I’m just teaching you
how to cheat yourself
so that you’ll feel better.
Go.
Optimistic Man
This is what you wrote and painted?
Looks like you’ve waited
for quite a long time.
♪Travel around with a long blade♪
♪Live freely and don’t get old♪
♪The sun shines in the Fortress♪
I had a long dream.
I had a long dream...
In it, flowers look as beautiful as you.
I feel like I see you.
It makes me so happy.
Optimistic Man.
I guess
you can only read my name smoothly.
It’s so optimistic of you.
Look at you.
You must have helped
other people on your way.
You were too busy to come back for me.
♪Like ice and light♪
Let me make you another gift.
♪Even the dragon ages over time♪
♪So does the hero braving the world♪
♪Petals fly in the dream♪
♪Like greeting the old friend♪
♪Keep the vow we made until death♪
What are you doing?
Giving vent on a branch
when failing to practice martial arts?
That was what I did.
You still remember.
Young Weed Spirit.
Young Weed Spirit
You’re Weed Spirit.
You’re Turtle Spirit.
When you wake up, I...
Luckily, I lay down.
Or I couldn’t have defeated you.
Strong Weed Spirit
went down the burrow alone
and fought hundreds of
evil Demons.
How does it sound? Stick to the topic?
It’s so optimistic of you.
Seems like you’re not dying.
Now,
I’ve experienced that life is short.
♪Misty smoke blurs my eyes♪
If I wear such a red dress,
I will look beautiful, too.
This fairy in the picture is...
Guess.
♪The blowing wind♪
Guess?
♪Frost and snow fall by the window♪
It’s the name of the painting?
You’re wrong.
This is my wife.
♪Warhorses race on the turbulent cloud♪
♪Guard the lucid water♪
♪Chaos is the last thing I want♪
Fei.
There’s much sea food by the East Sea.
It’s of the same race of you.
With all kinds of seasoning,
it will taste great.
You can get familiar with it.
The brush and ink are ready on the desk.
Please show some mercy.
A long letter will be better.
A short letter will be good, too.
Please write something in reply
to relieve me of lovesickness.
Oh, by the way,
you can only use
the brush and ink on paper.
Don’t use them on anything else.
♪Red dress makes me enchanted♪
♪Plenty of memories followed♪
♪You were brandishing broadsword
at first sight♪
I didn’t know what to write.
But you enlightened me.
You asked for this.
♪Ever hid the worries♪
♪No dim light at dawn♪
♪Candles in still♪
♪But right to shade your beauty♪
♪It has three kinds of life-saver♪
♪If I cannot wait for your back♪
♪Hope I can still love you
20 years later♪
♪I won’t be regretful♪
♪The black hair falls down♪
♪The good-looking face♪
♪Is pure enough♪
♪But push away cloud palm for you♪
Wang
♪Live on remaining year sin degradation♪
♪It’s just I thought♪
♪Now I am sealed by love♪
♪Only want to see you more times♪
♪Red dress makes me enchanted♪
♪Plenty of memories followed♪
♪You were brandishing broadsword
at first sight♪
♪The youth not know retreat♪
♪Who is to be favored by fate♪
♪Ever hid the worries♪
I’ll punch you.
♪No dim light at dawn♪
♪Candles in still♪
♪But right to shade your beauty♪
♪It has three kinds of life-saver♪
♪If I cannot wait for your back♪
I’ll punch you.
♪Hope I can still love you♪
♪I won’t be regretful♪
This place is as hot as a stove.
But your hands are as cold as ice.
Wang
When there’s even a bit of hope,
I won’t give up.
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪I dare not ask if you’re doing well♪
♪The first time I’ve felt terrified♪
♪Youth is like a sweet dream♪
♪The hope in heart never fades♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
I made you a small gift.
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪
Fei.
I miss you so much.
Girl.
Why hasn’t Abbot Tongming come back yet?
Do you think it’s so easy
to collect the herbs?
I just fear Xie Yun can’t hold on.
Don’t worry.
Xie Yun will not die for the moment.
This is for you.
What is it?
Looks so much like the Muyun Gauze
Yin Pei was wearing.
That’s rubbish.
But this isn’t very precious, either.
When I made the fishing net,
there was some scrap material.
It’s too small for others.
But it just fits you.
Girl.
I’ve named it Rosy Cloud.
What do you think?
What are you laughing at?
I’m laughing
because it’s such a good name.
Sounds glorified.
Do you want it?
If you don’t, give it back to me.
I want it. It’s your gift for me.
-You girl...
-Thank you.
Liang’s Mansion
We’re terribly sorry.
Our chief isn’t in lately.
Where...? Where has he gone?
We’re not sure.
In a few days,
it will be the birthday
of Lord Liu’s mother.
Did he invite you?
He did. But I’m not going.
Tea
When Lord Liu invited you,
it was your great honor.
You don’t understand.
A friend of mine works at Liu’s Manor.
He told me
Qinghui asked Lord Liu for money
the other day.
Unexpectedly,
Lord Liu didn’t respect him at all.
I’m afraid
if we meet Qinghui that day,
we’ll suffer.
You’re right.
Lord Liu
Mr. Liu.
I asked nearby martial artists.
No one wants to help us
deal with Qinghui,
We have few men.
I’m afraid we can’t kill him.
Since we’ve decided to kill him,
we must do it,
no matter how many men we have.
Look at the martial world.
Huo’s Manor is ruined.
Yin Wenlan is dead.
Qi School has disappeared.
Even people
with the Fortress of the Forty-Eight
are busy fighting against the Demons!
If we can’t unite as one,
how can we kill Qinghui?
A lot of people are enemies of Qinghui!
As long as we unite,
we will kill him.
Good point!
Master.
A Mr. Li asked to see you out there.
He said he was Li Sheng
with the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Li Sheng?
Grandson of Li Zheng?
I’m Li Sheng
with the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Greetings, everyone.
Mr. Li, what brings you here?
I come here,
for Qinghui.
Qinghui?
Lord Liu, you must know
what Qinghui has done.
The longer he lives,
the more people will suffer.
I want to unite everyone
to kill him once for all.
What’s your plan, Mr. Li?
I’ve got a plan.
To be honest, we do want to kill him.
But we’re worried
if we have enough men.
I’ve travelled around, asking for help.
I didn’t get as much support
as I expected.
But still a lot of martial masters
are willing to help.
Today, I come to you.
If we can cooperate,
we’ll stand a big chance.
I’d like to set a trap in a few days.
As for the place...
Your yard looks good.
As long as we can kill Qinghui,
I won’t care for a mere yard!
Good!
Fei didn’t come?
Miss Zhou Fei arrived yesterday.
She was wandering around this morning.
I don’t know
where she is now.
I had thought she wouldn’t stay
and I would miss her
when I went for the herbs.
She probably knows
Xie Yun is getting weaker and weaker
and she won’t see him for many times.
She’s stayed for a few more days.
I put the thing she brought
on your bedside.
It’s the Flaming Sage.
She must have suffered a lot
to collect these things.
You’re lucky enough.
I’ll let you go
to pray for Xie Yun.
I feel he’s waking up.
How long has he been asleep?
It’s about time.
Yeah. Yeah.
Anzhi, you’re awake?
Junior Master.
Come on.
Be careful. Slow down.
Get up slowly.
Anzhi, I guess you’re waking up.
Master.
Come on. Take the decoction.
Oh,
how long were I asleep?
Not very long.
Where’s Fei?
You really are a couple.
No wonder you like each other.
When you woke up, she fell asleep.
She’s next door.
Come on. Take it when it’s hot.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪