Today is the debut
of YG's newest girl group in seven years.
Introducing BLACKPINK!
♪ BLACKPINK… ♪
Please give it up for BLACKPINK!
Hello, we're BLACKPINK!
Our next guests are the best-charting
female Korean group of all time.
…wildly popular K-pop group…
K-pop sensations, BLACKPINK!
♪ Hit you with that ddu-du ddu-du du ♪
BLACKPINK has become
the highest charting
K-pop girl group ever.
They also made history as they became
the first K-pop girl group
to perform at Coachella.
Performing it live
for the first time ever on US television,
here is BLACKPINK!
- BLACKPINK!
Congratulations, BLACKPINK.
BLACKPINK!
♪ Hit you with that ddu-du ddu-du du ♪
- I'm so hungry.
- Are you?
- Did I eat something today?
- No.
There's a dessert.
It's like a croissant with injeolmi.
Ah!
You guys don't like injeolmi?
It tastes really good.
Says the Thai girl in the car.
Every time a new album comes,
we're just excited. We're like,
"Ah, yay. Finally, one more," you know?
I think we're halfway there, maybe?
We're always halfway there.
We're like, "We have the songs…
there. We just need to record them."
Seeing so many people love our music
motivates us
to try something new and different.
It's time for us to do some music.
Yeah.
We just have
so much to show people.
I don't think
we've done something really girly yet.
We've practiced
and explored so many different things,
um, during our trainee days,
and so it's just a matter of how much
of that we could end up showing
as BLACKPINK.
I think, for me, when I say girly,
I want to do more like…
like… "Hello…"
Like what?
Like, ooh…
Why is that delay
so strong right now?
Can you bring it down a bit?
Push it forward a bit.
I'm their producer, songwriter.
I've written and produced
every single song that's come out so far.
It's been about four years now.
Our initial approach was more like…
single, smash, single, hit.
Now, we feel like we need
to tell more of our personal story.
And I know the fans are mad.
Like, "We want more and more."
We do have a lot in here, but…
we're very particular
with what we put out.
Hello!
Oppa, you got some
leather jackets going on there?
Awesome!
Stop acting
like I overdressed today.
I always dress like this.
I should've had a nap today.
- I'll slap your wrist. Sleepy right?
- I didn't get a nap.
Ah!
Better?
So, I have the…
Lady Gaga featuring BLACKPINK
that's about to come out.
Oh!
♪ Sour candy ♪
So sweet!
We worked hard before New Year's for this.
♪ So-sour candy ♪
♪ I'm sour candy ♪
♪ So sweet
Then I get a little angry, yeah ♪
♪ Sour candy… ♪
They're huge,
and they're so successful.
I don't think any
of us even expected this.
Sometimes it gets to me,
like, "Oh, my God."
How do we live up to this hype?
♪ I'm hard on the outside ♪
♪ But if you give me time ♪
♪ Then I could make time for your love ♪
♪ I'm hard on the outside ♪
♪ But if you see inside, inside, inside ♪
♪ I might be messed up ♪
♪ But I know what's up ♪
♪ You want a real taste ♪
♪ At least I'm not a fake ♪
♪ Take a bite, take a bite ♪
♪ Sour candy ♪
Sour candy.
It's addictive.
Take a bite, take a bite.
♪ Hard on the outside… ♪
Should we re-record
certain parts of "Crazy Over You"?
Every group has
their own different cultural background
that makes them who they are.
But the combination,
that's what makes BLACKPINK unique
and stand out.
Who thinks
they can nail their part in this song?
Rosé, want to go in first for the intro?
♪ Can't get you outta my head ♪
♪ My head… ♪
Rosé, a Korean girl
that was raised in Australia.
And she stays here 'til, like,
six o'clock a.m. just in the studio.
Sometimes I'm like, "Wow! You still here?"
♪ Can't get you outta my head ♪
Ooh… you really killed that one.
Jisoo.
Straight-up Korean girl
that grew up in Korea.
She's the unnie of the group.
She's the oldest.
♪ I'm ready for love
I'm ready for love ♪
She does have
that professional poker face.
I've known Jisoo for,
let's say, a good six years.
I've seen her cry…
once.
She's super smart.
A lot of people might think
she's book smart,
but I would say she's street smart.
♪ I'm ready for love, I'm ready for love ♪
Oh, that scared me.
Lisa, from Thailand.
She's always got that cool, calm,
"it's gonna be okay,
we're all good" smile.
♪ I'm ready for love
I'm ready for love… ♪
But when it comes to certain moments,
when the music starts,
when it's crunch time,
she has this executioner killer instinct.
Jennie, born in Korea,
but moved to New Zealand.
She's super clear.
Her opinions, her emotions.
She's a perfectionist.
All those different cultures in one pot,
it's just different how they walk,
how they talk, and how they dress.
And the perfect balance,
how they complement each other.
It's fascinating.
We're just Korean people
trying to do music,
so if Korean people make music,
it's K-pop? I don't even get it. Like…
It's Korean pop.
The only thing is language.
Why don't they do that
for every country?
What is K-pop?
K-pop.
K-pop is taking the US by storm.
K-pop has become
a worldwide cultural phenomenon.
The genre has been around
for at least two decades.
This is a three-member group
named Seo Taiji and Boys.
Please welcome them.
Powerful rhythm and flash dances
are the hallmarks of Seo Taiji's music.
They sing well, look cool, and dance well.
The interest in Korean pop music
is unusually high from foreigners.
A few big music agencies
began making these polished groups
of singers, rappers, and dancers.
One of the heavy-weight companies
is YG Entertainment.
…responsible
for the insanely viral "Gangnam Style."
The industry
brings in billions of dollars a year.
Grooming these singers
is an industry all in itself.
Trainees can start
as young as 11 years old.
They're raised together.
They train together.
Perfecting every pitch.
Mastering every move.
Stakes are high.
Some make their debut
after just a few months' training.
For others, it could be up to a decade.
Many never make it to debut at all.
How many do I have to pick?
Preparing
for a new album, that's definitely fun,
'cause it's like trying
to come up with something new,
but fittings like this,
it is one of the biggest,
like, creative parts that we do.
Oh, Jisoo!
- Wow… - Oh là là.
You look naturally sexy!
- Really!
- You can't help yourself!
If we wear something,
we all try to see how it fits as a group,
but that's... Well, it's case by case.
It takes a long time.
Shouldn't we make it
a bit tighter? What do you think?
- Because this side goes up.
- Mm-mm-mm.
Okay.
Lalisa. Oh là là!
Lisa! Lalisa!
Oh là là.
Lisa has diverse tastes.
- She can wear whatever.
- She pulls off anything.
It's so hard to define style.
I don't think there's any,
like, boundaries within that.
We don't go, "This is Korean,
and this is Western. This is Asian."
I think fashion
is really just international.
The more that there aren't any boundaries,
I think that's when you can get creative.
And since we do
crazy choreography on stage,
it all has to be
really engineered, basically.
Make sure nothing flops out anywhere.
Yeah.
- What's this?
- Coachella.
I missed my note at the "eh."
See, this is why
we can't watch our old footage.
We're like,
"You missed your note at the 'eh',"
and, "I should've gone slower
at this part of the choreography,
but I did it too quickly."
I missed my note. That wasn't good.
We were so nervous…
Yeah.
If anything, it's stressful.
Sometimes if something's not working,
or I'm not doing my best performance,
it can be stressful.
Compared to other stages,
it was much more overwhelming
because we were so nervous.
For us, it was our first time
in a country we weren't familiar with.
I used to dream
of that day when we were trainees.
This is what we wanted.
- This is it.
I always avoid interviews
or any questions about me
because I would rather
not talk about myself, but…
♪ Used to be your girl
Now I'm used to being the GOAT ♪
♪ You're sittin' on your feelings
I'm sittin' on my throne ♪
♪ I ain't got no time
For the troubles in your eyes ♪
♪ This time I'm only lookin' at
Me, myself, and I ♪
♪ I'm going solo ♪
Jennie's personality?
At first, it was hard getting to know her,
but once we became close,
I could tell that she's very loyal,
very sweet, and a lovely friend.
I see her every day, so I'm used to her,
and she's like my little sister.
But when I see her on TV,
I'm like, "Ah, Jennie is a star,”
but she's really down-to-earth.
You're doing so well.
She's my friend. One of few that I have.
Slowly.
We're going to lift one leg up
and do an arabesque.
I'm always aching
after tours and stuff.
I feel like, out of all the members,
I'm always sick.
You know, some days,
just like every other human being,
you feel extra happy.
And some other days, you're feeling down.
Singing, dancing, and rapping,
I always enjoy it all the time,
but we always have to be on stage
looking perfect
and performing the same thing.
It's like working out
for two hours every day.
It never gets easy.
Gets harder, actually,
'cause you age.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
I was born in Korea.
It's just me and my mom.
I'm the only child.
I was raised in Seoul until I was ten.
I went to Australia
and New Zealand to travel with my mom,
and by the time we got to New Zealand,
it was so nice and peaceful.
She asked me,
"How do you feel about living here?"
And I said, "Yeah, I would like that."
So, from ten to 15.
I was in New Zealand by myself.
I never really got to spend
so much time in the house with my mom…
until recently.
I did a homestay.
I got to just run around,
learn so many things.
I understand English
better than when I began.
In the beginning,
my friends helped me a lot
and showed me their notes.
Now I can do it by myself.
They have classes in school to go out,
go camping, go learn instruments.
If you want, do art.
Everything was up to you.
Even if you're ten,
you still got to make your own decisions.
That was very important
for me to have at a young age.
That built me as who I am right now.
I am super shy.
I was one of those people
where I can't even
order something on the phone.
Like, I hated that.
Good work.
Took me a while to get this far.
Ta-da!
When I turned 15. I was deciding
whether I should move to America.
I went there, I checked the school out.
Everything was kind of decided, like 80%.
And I came back
to New Zealand to pack my stuff up,
and that's when I realized
I don't want to go to America
and do another study there by myself.
I actually want to become a singer.
I don't know where it came from.
As soon as I came back, I did an audition.
And luckily, I got in right away.
I was like, "Wow!
These people are so in to it!"
"They know what they're doing."
I was like, "Let's catch up."
That's all I had in mind.
♪ I only call you
When it's half past five ♪
♪ The only time that I can call you… ♪
So pretty!
♪ …love it when you touch me ♪
♪ Now feel me
When I'm fucked up, that's the real me ♪
♪ When I'm fucked up,
That's the real me, babe… ♪
Oh, that’s really long ago.
I used to do a lot
of dark and strong songs.
So I often wonder,
"What am I doing right now?"
It's so different
from what I do now.
Wow!
- Your gestures!
- You're always so cool.
It's sad to say,
the very first group
of people that trained with me,
none of them are here with me right now.
And as soon as Lisa came in,
that's when I thought…
"Wow, there are people born to do this."
♪ Uh, I'ma fall in love, baby ♪
♪ You gon' finna catch me ♪
♪ Uh, give you all of this, baby ♪
♪ Call me pretty and nasty ♪
♪ 'Cause we gonna get it
My love you can bet it on ♪
♪ Black, we gon' double
The stack on them, whoa! ♪
My role…
I'm a rapper and also the lead dancer.
Hello.
Oh, this is cute.
I love vintage clothes.
So wherever I go,
whether it be America or anywhere else,
I try to look for vintage shops.
Oh, wow. Voilà!
This is 1.1 million.
- And this is 320.000.
- And this one?
That's 750.000.
This is 1.1 million?
Yes, because it's from the early '90s.
Oh!
This is so cool!
Can I... Can I get this?
My mom manages my finances.
She's gonna be like,
"No, Lisa, no. Stop shopping for now."
She's always like that,
but I don't really listen to her.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Whoa!
1997.
When I was born.
I was born in Thailand.
I was born in Buriram Province.
Then I moved to Bangkok when I was three.
My auntie had a music group,
so they had mic stands,
and I always played with them.
I would lower it
until it was the same height as me.
Then I would just dance
and sing to myself.
That was how my mom knew I loved dancing.
So she signed me up
for a course when I was in kindergarten.
This is behind the scenes.
That was how it all began.
She signed me up to many contests…
…dance competition and stuff.
How long have you
been practicing break dancing?
For a long time.
I participated in a contest.
I was around 12 or 13 years old then.
Then a talent scout told me to try singing
and asked if I wanted to be a singer.
Then I realized
that I loved both singing and dancing.
And YG happened
to have an audition at the time.
So, I made a decision.
Okay. I should try, for sure.
Is this an audition?
How many layers are you wearing?
Why are you wearing pants on top too?
- What is this?
- Oh, wow!
- Oh, my God.
- This is amazing.
Wow!
You look so cool.
I'm trying so hard to be cool.
After the audition ended…
…I waited for the call.
I was waiting and waiting.
I waited for the call.
I waited for two months!
And then they called me.
I was like, "What? Is this possible?"
I was a mama's girl.
So, when I had to go to Korea without Mom,
I felt that I had
to take care of myself now.
I was 14.
Such a kid.
I didn't speak any Korean.
I only knew how to say "hello,"
so it really was a new start.
♪ I'm in the club
High off purp', with some shades on… ♪
Fortunately, there was Jennie.
♪ In the club
High off purp', with some shades on… ♪
She was the only one
who could speak English
among the trainees.
I spoke English with her…
♪ J's on my feet, so get like me… ♪
…and if something
were to happen, I would talk to her.
That's it.
However you feel comfortable. Like…
You choose how to sing it
because we're all doing it differently.
♪ I'm ready for love, I'm ready for love ♪
- ♪ I'm ready for love ♪
- There you go.
- Okay.
A great thing with us
is everyone wants the best
for the group as a whole.
♪ I'm ready for love,
I'm ready for love ♪
That's cool. I'm happy with that.
Okay.
Since we perform as a group,
we try to strike a balance
that works for everyone.
I think.
♪ Oh, wait 'til I do what I do ♪
♪ Hit you with that ddu-du ddu-du du ♪
What's up? What's up?
Sit here, Jisoo.
What do you think?
Do you think I'll be able to learn today?
I think it’ll be nice to learn
how to draw my eyebrows properly.
If you show me, I'll follow it.
- Okay.
- I'm learning from you today.
Do you teach makeup like this too?
- To regular people? Yes.
- Really?
- There are classes for that?
- Of course!
I should've taken
those classes then.
There are people
who come to learn BLACKPINK makeup.
- BLACKPINK makeup?
- Yes.
When I was younger,
my relatives treated me
like an outcast because I was ugly.
What?
They called me a monkey.
It's okay. You're the prettiest one now.
I grew up in Sanbon
in Gunpo city, Gyeonggi-do region.
I lived with my parents,
my sister, my brother,
and my grandparents.
I'm living a very different life
than the one I thought I'd be living.
I used to want to be a writer
or a painter.
Although, I couldn't paint well.
And then I joined
the drama club in 11th grade.
Should I try acting?
They were saying
I should start auditioning for stuff
because I needed the experience.
My first audition was at YG.
I didn't know much at all about YG
before I arrived there the first day.
It felt like something
far removed from me.
I never thought
I'd actually be doing it for real.
How about now?
Do you think I really lost my baby fat?
Back then, it was more baby-like here…
I guess I'll just have to eat ramen
before I sleep tonight.
Maybe then you'll get your old self back.
No, you're perfect right now.
Anyways, you were like a baby back then.
But you're different from back then, too.
You have your own shop!
Who told you to open your own shop?
Say it! Who told you to?
You did.
It was my big plan.
And I'm still planning big things.
I think that
there are very few who truly think,
"This is what I have to do.
This is my path."
People like that are really lucky.
I don't think there are many like that.
I have a really hard time falling asleep.
I have a lot of thoughts
running through my head.
And singing is kind of like stress relief,
and everything just kind of makes sense
when I'm doing this.
That's a really hard song.
I didn't think
I could ever perfect that one.
Sometimes,
I actually have missed my trainee days.
Because, back then,
we were surrounded by music all the time.
But these days we've got a lot of work,
so I actually have to make time for this.
That's why it's always at night,
when I'm supposed to be sleeping.
Hi, girls and boys.
I'm called Roseanne…
and I just woke up.
And welcome to Pajama News.
I was born in New Zealand.
And then I moved
to Australia when I was eight.
Back then, I was always on the piano.
I'd like sit there,
and I'd play this lullaby for myself,
but I'd be really sleepy,
and I'd fall asleep,
and then I'd put my chin on my knee.
I went to church every Sunday
and had a lot of Korean friends there.
But then at school,
I was just a normal Australian kid.
Congratulations, Rosé.
And I think I enjoyed having two lives.
Kind of like Hannah Montana.
It's funny.
♪ If you look me in the eyes ♪
♪ And catch a glimpse of heaven… ♪
My dad saw on the news
that YG was coming to Australia.
He was like,
"Rosé, do you wanna audition?"
And I was so shocked.
I think I asked him,
"Do I like music? Do I?"
And he's like, "Yeah, obviously."
"You're gonna have to,
you know, try do something about it."
"Otherwise you're gonna be 25.
and you're gonna regret
that you didn't try anything."
♪ 'Cause even the stars, they burn ♪
♪ Some even fall… ♪
I was 16.
Then I went and auditioned,
and then they called me,
and they were like,
"Can you fly to Korea within two months?"
♪ God knows we're worth it ♪
♪ And I won't give up ♪
And then my whole life changed.
I dropped out of school.
In Australia, I dropped out of school.
I had never even imagined myself
living apart from my family.
I hadn't even slept
more than two weeks out of home.
It was a really...
Oh, my gosh. I'm gonna cry.
It was...
I'm gonna cry.
Yeah.
The first night in the dorm,
they were all in the same room.
Everybody was sleeping.
She brought a guitar
from Australia, and I was like,
"Play something for us."
It was us four.
I don't even know why,
but it was us four.
We covered songs 'til morning.
All four of us, we were singing.
Somebody was harmonizing.
I think Jisoo was harmonizing.
It was so funny. Can you believe it?
My eyes.
- It's really pretty.
- Wow!
Here, stand here.
One, two…
- Nice.
- I wanna have a look.
After my Korean classes
on the fifth floor,
I took the elevators to the basement.
And there was this girl
with short hair, tied back.
It was kind of awkward.
- I was nervous.
- I'm sure you were nervous.
So weird.
I was like, "Oh! A new girl?"
I was like… so wary of competition.
- Right. Competition.
- Competition, it's so competitive.
Everything was
gyeongjaeng at that time.
She thought I was competition,
and I was just really intimidated.
Like, everybody is so good.
We were the same age,
and we had similar tastes.
Since we both came from another country,
we relied on each other
when we were having a hard time.
We become like two peas in a pod.
We were like genuine twins.
We have so many days where we walk out,
and we're wearing the same thing.
And during our days off,
we'd always be together.
She started getting an Australian accent.
See, she still has it sometimes.
No.
- Yeah.
- No.
I don't even know how to say...
I never knew I would live in Korea.
Then all of a sudden at 16. I'm like…
Now Korea is my home.
Was it hard for you?
Of course.
Even though you have me?
You?
You're not any help.
I'm joking.
- Yeah, 'cause I grew up with a sister.
- Mm.
Think about not having a sister.
But Lisa was there.
When I was having a hard time,
I'd look at Rosé, and she'd be the same.
I thought I was really sad,
but I'd look at you, and I'd go, "Okay."
I think what makes K-pop K-pop
is the time that we spend as a trainee.
We all live together,
sort of like a boarding school,
like a training version.
I think there were nine girls.
They were planning
on creating a big group,
so they had a lot of girls there.
They need you to be at their standard
in every single subject.
For me, there were
so many lessons in the beginning.
I took three to four dancing lessons a day
and practiced.
I had vocal lessons
from two to three teachers.
It was a rough time.
We'd get a day off every fortnight,
and then practice again
for another 13 days.
So 14 hours a day just training.
♪ Look at y'all lookin' ass hittas
Stop lookin' at my ass, ass hittas… ♪
It's not easy,
the repetition.
But at such a young age, they are able
to absorb all the techniques and the tools
that they need for their next ten years.
There's this basic routine
you have to learn in dancing.
Jennie was like, "The first thing
you have to learn is that,
and I'll just teach you the first moves."
And she was like, "Do this."
And I was like, "I don't know how."
I can still remember the first day
that you had a dance lesson.
'Cause I'd never danced in my life.
It was cute.
If you ask a 16-year-old
to dance for the first time,
it's the funniest thing. I looked like a…
And then after that,
I got so angry at myself.
I was like,
"I am going to become like Lisa."
'Cause Lisa was the dancer.
She was like… She was at the top.
At the end of every month,
our boss and all the producers would come,
and we'd perform a solo song,
a group song, and a group choreography.
For that,
we'd have to plan everything ourselves,
but we each had a role.
If someone was in charge of vocals,
we'd give them that role,
but I always took on
the role of the dancer.
So I'd always design the choreography.
Every month! Literally every month
for five years.
After a monthly review,
you would be graded.
You had those who got an A,
those with Bs and those with Cs.
I remember having to send
a good friend of mine home every month
because they got eliminated from the test.
There were so many rules,
so many things to just be like,
"Okay, they don't like this.
They don't like that."
Everything that I did was wrong.
Being told
that I'm not good at stuff face-to-face
and trying to keep everything together
when I hear those things…
It's really harsh.
It wasn't a very happy vibe.
We're not allowed to drink,
or smoke, or get a tattoo.
I rarely went home
and had to practice on the weekends.
So my parents
were quite upset and worried.
But they're not really…
the protective, overbearing type,
and they knew
this was something that I had to do,
so they told me
to stay strong and get it done.
I would always call my mom…
…and I would always call her
and tell her, "Mom, it's so hard."
She'd say, "Come home." I'd say, "No."
My dad sent me,
and he was like, "Rosé, come home."
He's like, "We want you back home."
And I hated that. I hated it
whenever they would say, "Come home."
That was the last thing I wanted to hear.
♪ High dive into frozen waves ♪
♪ Where the past comes back to life… ♪
I started a bit later than the others,
so I was able to make memories
with friends and go to school.
I consider it a blessing now.
♪ She told me, "Don't worry about it" … ♪
I don't regret spending time
as a trainee, learning how to dance,
how to sing.
But one thing I wish
is to maybe have lived at home
until I was like 18. 19.
A lot of people make lots of memories
as a high school student.
But I never had that.
Waiting was the hardest part.
I didn't think I would make it.
I was on the verge of letting it go.
It was just days on end
with just a bunch of girls
not knowing where this was going.
I'd ask myself,
"Do you want to give up
because it's not easy?"
I knew I could do it.
The tougher they treated me,
I'm like, "I'm gonna get through it,
and I'm gonna show them
that I'm worth it."
♪ I should be more cynical
And tell myself it's not okay… ♪
After all of this,
I'm not gonna go back
without doing anything.
That would be embarrassing for me.
That's what I thought.
♪ 'Cause your eyes, nose, lips
Every look and every breath… ♪
I had to keep fighting.
I had to give it my all.
"I don't care how long
the training will take."
"Bring it on!
I don't care about that anymore!"
So, the CEO would put us
into different groups
every other month just to see.
And there was a point
where he pointed the four of us out.
We were evaluated together,
and the four of us did screen tests
and recorded demos together.
It happened naturally.
We just clicked.
♪ Do you recall not long ago ♪
♪ We would walk on the sidewalk… ♪
We just got along so well.
Because usually there's like,
"Oh, I wanna sing more."
Or, "Oh, I wanna be in the middle."
There's always those little fights
going on in the groups.
But when it was the four of us,
it was clear what we were doing.
And that's what made it possible
for us to be in a group.
You know, four girls
being in one group is not easy.
♪ …fire a gun
All we need is someone to lean on… ♪
When you're working in a group,
everyone has their place and a role.
And when everyone settles
into their roles,
that's how synergy is born.
That realization changed my outlook.
When everyone is where they need to be,
big things can happen.
♪ Blow a kiss, fire a gun
All we need is somebody to lean on ♪
When I first came in the picture,
there were seven, eight, nine girls.
Then we started cutting some songs,
and sonically,
whatever that sounded the best.
The four girls right now, the combination.
And of course
you start looking at their individuality,
like their character.
The four of them just felt right.
Teddy felt like a CEO to us.
If somebody did something
with Teddy or met with Teddy…
…it was considered
to be a big deal.
I didn't know much about him.
I knew he was a 1TYM member.
It's a different time,
and I just wanted to become
someone that I needed when I was young.
I didn't have somebody
that's a little more outside looking in,
telling me where to go.
The first time we met was when...
When I was a trainee.
I was so nervous.
I couldn't really talk to him.
Meeting you
was like the final stage of the debut.
You were the final boss.
If we meet you, we get to debut.
You're right.
Oppa, do you remember…
how we had to record
that whistling sound 1.000 times?
That I'll never forget.
I cannot forget that.
And we almost didn't come out
with "Whistle" for our debut song, but...
Too many people
thought it was risky.
But last minute,
we were like, "It has to be that one."
'Cause it has
this weird country vibe to it,
and it's super minimal.
It just sounded
too empty for a lot of people.
Most people were against it.
We just pushed forward, whatever.
Hey, you know that photo there?
That's our very first photo session
as BLACKPINK.
Yeah.
It's oppa's favorite photo.
As soon as I saw that photo,
how it turned out, I was like,
"Oh, this is gonna be fun."
YG Entertainment is expected
to showcase its first new girl group
in seven years since 2NE1 debuted.
Under the direction of producer Teddy,
this new group is being prepared.
Its members and debut songs
have been shrouded in secrecy.
I'm shaking!
So shaky!
"Various… diverse colors…"
How does it go?
All I wanted
was people to see the potential in us.
It didn't necessarily have to be,
"Wow! This group came out,
and they're so perfect
in every single way."
Like, I wanted people
to be curious about us.
Hello everyone.
I'm BLACKPINK's Rosé.
Hello everyone. I'm BLACKPINK's Jennie.
Hello everyone.
I'm BLACKPINK's Jisoo.
Hello everyone. I'm BLACKPINK's Lisa.
Uh… after training
with my members all this time
and finally being able
to debut on this stage,
I'm nervous and excited.
In the future,
we will work hard to show everyone
BLACKPINK's unique colors.
Please love us!
Thank you!
As soon as we debuted…
…I think it happened
just the way I thought it would.
I look intense.
Let's go!
Hello.
I can't wait. Can you tell us
who's performing next?
Two of their songs
debuted exclusively at Inkigayo last week
and could be number one!
Shall we see the performance
of BLACKPINK,
the hottest rookies right now?
- Music… - …start!
♪ Make 'em whistle like a missile
Bomb, bomb ♪
♪ Every time I show up, blow up, uh… ♪
YG's new girl group, BLACKPINK,
has reached number one
only 14 days after their debut,
which is the shortest time ever
by a girl group to reach number one.
I remember making our debut
and winning awards.
Wow!
And feeling like, "Wow! We did it."
"Whistle" kept going up and up,
and when it hit number one,
we were just so happy and excited.
Honestly, I think I was most surprised
when "Whistle" reached number one
on the music charts.
That was the most exciting.
I remember we were…
…in a practice room
when we heard the news
that we were number two.
I kept on checking and checking,
but we had to go to practice.
We'd check every hour.
And then someone came in
and said, "Oh, my God!"
We jumped up and down.
I remember my friends
telling me that they heard it.
They were like, "I'm outside,
and they're playing your song!"
It felt really weird back then.
I was like, "Oh, my God, that's so cool!
Shoot a video! Send me the video!"
Lisa! I love you!
I just really like their style.
Their sound is super different
from other K-pop groups.
It's 'cause they have
so many foreign members,
and it really shows
how anyone can achieve their dreams.
They own the stage when they're on it.
Their dance is so powerful.
When their music is played,
you just instantly start dancing.
They have the strongest
friendship I've seen in a K-pop group.
You can see they love
what they are doing and are born to do it.
I felt like this is a girl group
that I can actually vibe with.
You know, they cool.
They the baddest bitches alive.
When I was a trainee,
nobody knew about me.
But after I debuted as BLACKPINK,
everyone would follow me
no matter where I went.
I didn't know
that we would become this famous.
How much did you sleep last night?
Three hours.
- Three hours?
- Yup.
- Clear in front.
- Everybody get out.
During trainee days,
I was desperate. I really wanted it.
But after debut, that's when you start
getting a lot of responsibilities.
Everybody look into the camera.
Then came the pressure for our next thing.
"What now? What do we do?"
"Let's come up with something fresh."
I felt like we were being chased.
Action!
The winner is BLACKPINK!
Thank you! I love you all!
It's a big day for BLACKPINK
as "Ddu-Du Ddu-Du" has become
the most viewed Korean music video
in 24 hours.
Three music videos
with over 400 million views.
One billion views on YouTube.
I think when things get faster,
it also becomes
very overwhelming at some points.
Yeah.
I still remember the first time…
I went back to Thailand after my debut.
Because Thai teens see me
as a Thai who has made it this far.
They would say, "I want to be like Lisa."
Lisa!
WELCOME HOME LISA WE MISSED YOU
But at that moment,
I wasn't sure if I was really good enough
to be their role model.
I'm a singer…
but I didn't know
what kind of singer I wanted to be.
I kind of lost the goal.
I was trying to find myself.
Could I really become their role model?
What should I do to not let them down?
These kinds of thoughts
kept running through my mind.
We need sugar.
- One spoon.
You like this too.
Tanghulu is different.
Tanghulu has
the sweetness of the fruits.
The ratio is a little off
because we haven't made it in a while.
- There was too much sugar.
- It's a bit burnt.
- It still looks delicious.
- Yeah.
This is actually
a Chinese traditional snack,
but it's hard to find it here in Korea.
We almost started a fire once.
- We were making too much.
- Yeah, we almost burnt it.
We almost made
this dorm disappear.
This is a way
of me teaching Jisoo to speak English.
She got better in the last six months.
She understands everything that I say,
so I do talk to her in English sometimes.
- How is it?
- Mm.
Is it good? I want a taste.
It's warm.
It's a bit burnt.
Mm!
Not bad.
Not bad but not good.
Yeah. Let's be honest. It was a fail.
Yes.
No. We didn't add any water.
- What are you talking about?
- No, you don't add water.
Unnie! You add water.
You add water? No, you don't add water.
What am I going to do about you?
Nothing works without me.
In Korea,
one of the first things you ask,
other than your name, is how old are you?
And as soon as they say they're older,
it's like, "Oh, you're unnie."
So, unnie is basically
what you call an older sister.
It's like...
Other places don't have it.
We don't call each other by names.
It's normally unnie
if you're older than me,
and oppa if you're a guy.
It takes a while to get used to,
but once you get a hold of it,
it's better than calling their names.
She's not Jisoo. She's unnie.
It's like family, in a way.
When I first came to train as a singer,
I had never tried
singing or dancing before.
I was lost, but you taught me a lot.
For two of us, it was...
The competition was fierce at the time.
There were about 20 to 30 trainees.
Because we are
the older ones of the group,
the others came to us
with the issues they were having.
I knew what their problems were.
They'd ask us, "Unnie, what should we do?"
And I'd advise them to speak their mind,
but they have a hard time doing that,
so I end up taking care of it.
There's no doubt
I feel a sense of responsibility.
I try the best I can
to take care of the other girls.
It's okay, actually. I could eat this.
Semi-success.
Okay.
It's just Rosé and the beat.
- Oh, my God!
- No words, no melody whatsoever.
So here we go.
♪ Can't sleep at night ♪
♪ But would it be all right ♪
♪ If I stay, if I… ♪
♪ No, it shouldn't be a problem
No, it shouldn't be a problem ♪
You know how
when people say they're afraid of heights
or they're afraid of water?
I've always been so afraid of getting
in the studio or writing something.
I always thought just someday
I have to just start it. I have to.
- I'm gonna still keep this one.
- Okay.
- Let's try one more time.
Do I change the rhythm?
I keep going for the same thing.
- Do you feel uncomfortable singing it?
- Do I feel uncomfortable singing it?
Like slightly.
Maybe I'll try singing it one more time.
I've seen Joe a few times,
and his music's like amazing.
I was just like, to Teddy,
"What do you think if he helps me out?"
So here's what we worked on.
This is Rosé's first recorded song.
We even saved this whole file
in this secret folder
because I said nobody can listen to it.
I was like, "Hide it from everyone."
♪ Wouldn't be a problem
No, it shouldn't be a problem ♪
When it comes to writing songs,
Rosé has certain stories in mind.
And she's shy about sharing that story.
It's just super personal to her.
It's like her diary.
Oh, my gosh!
You sounded nervous in that one.
Yeah. I'm like,
"I don't know what I'm doing."
I was thinking
it'd be fun if I write something like…
♪ After two, three o’clock… ♪
♪ When I call you ♪
♪ And when you see my call… ♪
Something like that.
- I think it's fine.
- I want to hide right now.
- No.
- I don't think I can do this.
Teddy told me yesterday too.
He was like, "You need to learn
how to be more vulnerable in the studio."
That's something I can't do too easily,
but I was gonna say...
- I mean, it takes time.
- Yeah.
I really have a lot of respect for music,
so I don't wanna be
just like another girl who sings
and just kind of tells everybody
that she writes music.
That's the last thing I wanna be.
- Whoa, I need one of these.
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
I feel more intimidated
when I'm by myself.
When I'm in my room by myself,
and I go,
"Should I try and write something?"
I think I'm way more intimidated then.
'Cause it's just me.
I don't know if my opinions are right,
and that scares me.
I feel like I scare myself the most.
Okay, let's record that.
What's our tempo?
I found these chords
maybe like a month ago.
I was like... I liked it.
I was like, "This sounds cool."
And ever since then, I just play it.
If anything, I was gonna put you
in the booth and sing over it.
Okay.
Do you think I could do it?
I've never tried this.
I think you can do it.
Let's just give it a try.
It's nice to have just the right amount
of people in the room,
who are just there
to accept whatever is there
and make it into something.
Joe always says, "This is the safe ground.
Everything's a secret in here."
"You can make a fool out of yourself,
and we won't tell anyone."
Ah.
It feels just like expressing myself.
Whereas I would always
sing songs of other artists.
That's more like borrowing
their emotions and making it mine.
Whereas this is totally
just speaking from my point of view.
I'm almost like a baby
trying to speak in the music,
trying to sing… for the first time.
- I lost it again.
- We got it.
Lisa,
should I wear this on my way back?
Kuma!
BLACKPINK hoodie?
- I think you should.
- Right?
Hello. Ah, ow! You just bit me.
Coco bit me. Ah!
Coco like, "I don't care."
I have so many clothes,
but there's not enough space,
so I keep them on the balcony.
Don't we have to pack
for the event in Japan?
You have to bring
something like this. It's cold.
- Bring a scarf too.
- Oh, I don't have a scarf!
- Give me one.
- You are funny.
- I can't.
That's not a scarf.
It is so tiring when we work,
but when we don't work,
I get stressed out about not working.
I think it's that. It's a dilemma.
When we work, I really want to rest,
but when we don't work,
I end up wondering, "What am I doing?"
This job has a lot of ups and downs.
There's nothing we can do about it.
It's very random,
and there's no regularity.
The thing is, you can never tell
how long this will last,
so estimating is impossible.
That's most challenging.
This year has been on the road.
This year has been pack and unpack,
and unpack and pack and unpack.
That's a song.
At least right now,
we're prepared enough
to plan the resting part,
'cause last year,
we were just like spending time like…
And then the tour hit us,
and we're like, "Oh, my God."
Yeah.
I think we were together for three years
before we went on the world tour.
It was a long tour, about nine months.
We started the world tour in Asia,
but Coachella marked the start
of our tour in North America.
When they said that we're gonna
start going outside of Asia,
that was like a dream.
And blow them kisses here and stuff,
because you're coming out
during the chorus before you kiss.
Oh, the next chorus?
You're coming out
during the chorus before you kiss.
You want me
to come out before that chorus?
Come out slowly and play here.
It was getting boring
when you stay out there for too long.
A much more diverse group of fans
will be looking forward to seeing us.
We wanted
to bring them the best show possible.
Whether it be
"Playing With Fire" or "Boombayah"…
you don't look like
you're dancing hard enough.
- We're not dancing hard enough?
- Not hard enough.
The audience needs
to be mesmerized by your energy, up close.
I know that you guys know the dance well,
but put in a bit more effort.
Jisoo, you need to get the notes right.
You messed up
on the rhythm before, right? Too fast?
I practiced with MR
for the first time when I got here.
The notes are
a bit unstable when you first go in.
But we shouldn't have said that on camera.
Hey…
They'll never air this.
The media says
that K-pop queens have landed.
BLACKPINK, welcome to Thailand. Yay!
Girl group BLACKPINK heat up
their first world tour stop, Thailand.
It's special to have a concert
in Lisa's hometown.
This is the first concert
where BLACKPINK has been able
to meet our Thai fans.
We will do our very best
and will not disappoint the BLINKS.
BLACKPINK!
I want to give a performance
that I can look at and be content with.
My focus is leaving the stage
having given a performance
I have no regrets about.
So when I get out there,
I'm thinking, "Don't mess this up."
"You've got to nail this."
Since it was our very first world tour,
it's amazing to see all these fans
filling up the big arenas
that we didn't expect.
Everything was new to me on my first tour.
It was so great
to meet so many fans around the world.
Once it gets going,
for, like, the next 30 days,
to try to give them the best stage
every day is a lot of pressure.
After so many plane rides
and so many environment changes,
our body just gives up on us.
- It feels like it's sprained.
- Is it worse on this side?
When I'm home, I like to workout
and take care of my body
'cause I'm like a grandma.
I'm sick everywhere.
Honestly, I need to take care of myself.
I lose breath a little easier
than other people,
and I can't jump as much as other people.
I think, at first,
I didn't know what I was headed towards.
Okay. Let's go.
I thought it would all be
just really exciting and fun.
I’m going to eat it without ketchup.
In the middle of it,
I didn't feel like I had a personal life.
It felt like there was
this big hole in my life.
What I'm basically living for
is tomorrow's show.
I love being on stage
because that's when I feel the most alive,
yet when we come back to the hotel,
I felt so empty.
I'm hungry,
so I ordered something simple.
Poached eggs. Ta-da!
And that's when I realized I'm homesick.
Delicious.
Yeah! Let's go!
Lisa is the most constant one.
She brings positive energy into the group.
If someone is fed up one day…
…she makes that person laugh.
She keeps us energized.
Sometimes I feel like…
…I think I overreact a lot.
Or I tend to try
to bring too much positivity
when the mood is sour.
- But it really helps.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'll keep doing that.
- Keep going.
- Yeah, keep going, Lisa!
How we stay tight as a group
is we try to take care
of ourselves individually,
and then come together healthy
and happy so that the whole thing works.
Sometimes, when I look like
I'm really tired and angry,
that is my happy face.
We're all human, and we're ladies,
so we have our moments.
But when you have
the good positive energy going on,
it helps.
Los Angeles, what's up?
We're BLACKPINK on 97.1 AMP radio.
You guys,
the first female Korean group
to perform at Coachella.
- Oh, my gosh!
- What?
The K-pop girl band called BLACKPINK
is in the US this weekend.
Because it's such a big festival,
when I was told that we were going,
I couldn't believe it.
Are we going to Coachella?
BLACKPINK? Are you sure?
Is this for real?
Look over there!
I'm so excited. This is cool!
It was really nerve-wracking.
We're a group
from South Korea representing our country.
We were just
so ready to tell the world
that we've been waiting for this.
Since we don't have much time…
…we're gonna skip "Stay,"
and we're gonna go
from "Whistle" and "Kiss and Make Up."
I was so nervous because I didn't know
how our American fans would react.
Usually, a BLACKPINK tour
is filled with fans who come to watch us,
but people who come to Coachella
are just people who love music in general.
I personally was really worried
that not many people
would walk up to our show.
I didn't even think we would have,
I don't know,
100 people or 200 people at least.
I was just hoping
to have somebody watching us.
I was so sick.
That was the sickest I've ever been.
My back was killing me. It hurt to move.
- I was pretty worried.
- We were very worried.
Break a leg.
We're following Coachella.
Let's go.
When I got onto that stage,
I actually didn't realize
that there were so many people.
Why are there so many people?
I don't know.
There are so many people.
- We can do it.
- We can do it. It's fine.
One, two, three! Go!
Jennie and Rosé, that way.
Water, water, water!
Eye drops, somebody!
Relax.
We're starting now!
I was so nervous.
The moment I stepped foot on the stage
and saw all the crowds
shouting and cheering…
…I got the feeling, "This is it!"
♪ BLACKPINK! ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah ♪
I think Coachella
was the moment where I felt like
there are people that understand
that this isn't just K-pop music.
They see us as doing something new,
and I really like that.
All races and all kinds
of people came together there.
So it helped emphasize…
…this represents BLACKPINK.
I'm happy to be in an era
where people are open
to new culture, new music.
Who would have imagined, at Coachella,
thousands of people singing in Korean…
"- Playing with fire"? - What?
♪ My love is on fire ♪
♪ Now burn, baby, burn ♪
It doesn't matter
the size of the audience.
It just matters
if it's the right atmosphere.
Everybody's on the same vibe.
This was a moment
where I felt really satisfied
with our work.
Like all those
training years were worth it!
It makes me feel that…
I had chosen the right path.
This was what
I really wanted to do in my life.
We had so much fun.
I think I'll remember today
for the rest of my life.
We love you guys!
- Thank you, guys!
- Thank you so much.
Goodnight!
There's been lots of news
coming from Coachella,
but one group
that has everybody talking is BLACKPINK.
If you didn't know who they were before,
you definitely know who they are now.
After Coachella, I think I figured out
how to have fun on stage.
Don't concentrate on just yourself,
but feed off this passion
raging around you.
Have fun. Have fun with this.
It doesn't matter if we grow old
and get replaced
by a new younger generation.
As long as there is still
someone talking about us.
Because they will still remember
how we shone so bright.
♪ Uh, I'ma fall in love, baby ♪
♪ You gon' finna catch me ♪
♪ Uh, give you all of this, baby ♪
♪ Call me pretty and nasty ♪
♪ 'Cause we gonna get it
My love you can bet it on ♪
♪ Black, we gon' double
The stack on them, whoa! ♪
♪ I'll be you Bonnie and you be my Clyde ♪
♪ We ride or die Xs and Os ♪
♪ Tonight won't you set me free… ♪
I want everybody to stand up!
We all have dreams, hunger to make it.
When you're really invested
in what you do,
that's what makes things happen.
We love you, Bangkok!
Thank you so much!
Thank you.
Sadly, very, very extremely sadly,
um…
Like we said before,
this will be our last concert
on this tour.
And I feel like all four of us,
we did really well,
and I'm very proud
of each and every one of us.
'Cause we went through a lot.
Like, I know you guys only see
the stuff that's on stage,
but I feel like
we all go through so much else…
…and I'm very proud.
Aw!
During the shows,
we're always looking out
and talking to the audience.
Then I was talking,
and I kinda looked at my members,
and I was like, "Ah!"
Then I started crying.
Because it felt like
the first time talking to, you know, each.
Like, I feel like it's so hard
that everybody stays away from home…
Happy tears.
- Happy tears.
- Happy tears. It's okay.
And every time we're in Thailand,
I get really emotional.
I don't know why.
- Now I'm gonna cry. I don't want to cry.
- Everybody's gonna cry.
- Everyone, cry.
- Everyone, cry!
Aw!
So, it's like a train.
It's me and then Jennie unnie.
And if she cries,
then Lisa cries, and then…
I don't cry.
I don't cry. I cry last.
Thank you so much for coming. Bye!
Bye.
Watch your step. Be careful.
Good work!
Bye!
A fan?
I'm very proud
of what we've created as BLACKPINK.
We grew into something
that we didn't even know was possible.
And as much as fans
are surprised with the outcome,
we are as well.
And so, it feels like a journey
that they're on with us.
Bye-bye!
When somebody asks me,
"Do you have pressure about it?"
I'm like, "No," because I feel like
we're doing a great job,
and we have more to show you guys.
It's just the beginning.
Meat, meat!
Careful of the hot plate.
- That looks amazing!
- Can I have a bite?
Thank you.
- Do you know us?
- Yes.
- Weren't you here before?
- Yes, that's right.
- We were here when we were trainees.
- Yes, you guys ate here.
- I remember.
- I've been here since the start.
I didn't give you good service.
Really?
Is that why you're so nice now?
Yes. I hope you enjoy the food.
- Thank you.
Totally.
Halsey contacted me all of a sudden.
She was at Paris?
She's like, "You in Paris?"
I'm like, "Don't tell me you're here."
It was my first time meeting her.
I felt like it was my fifth time.
And she said the same.
Like, "Was this our first time?"
I'm like, "Yeah." She's just like us.
She just talks like us.
- Is she from America, or…
- Yeah, I think she's from LA?
LA! Come on, LA!
- I want to live in Paris.
- Me too! For a year.
- We will stay for a year.
- You're Parisian already.
After a year, I'd like to go to the US.
I want to live in Paris, but I also want
to live in the US and England.
Twenty years?
I feel like Lisa
would be traveling around the world.
Forty three?
- I'm gonna be 40?
- I'm gonna be 42.
- Gonna be 40.
- We're gonna be 42.
I feel we'll all be...
Do you think we'll all be married by then?
- I think we might.
- Of course! It's 40… Like, come on!
I don't know about babies, but…
…I think we'd all be married.
We'd have babies by then. Forty-two, 44…
We'll have children?
If not,
we could also get married later in life.
We'll be freshly married?
No newborns!
Aren't we going to make a comeback?
At that age?
BLACKPINK!
We'll injure our backs!
I don't think we'll be able to dance.
We'll have to stand.
♪ May seem similar
but different to the core ♪
♪ May seem shy
but kill it when put on the spot ♪
♪ Born skinny bish still skinny
after some gain ♪
♪ Slow at calculating but fast and witty ♪
♪ There’s no point to discuss
about popularity ♪
♪ F boys not my boys cut them all out ♪
♪ If you get our names wrong
get hit like ddu-du ddu-du ♪
♪ Drip drip ice it out
bust it down top to the bottom ♪
♪ All up in it make it lit like ♪
♪ Yeah we some bishes you can’t manage ♪
♪ We pulled this off once again ♪
♪ We’re pretty savage.
We some pretty savage ♪
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org