[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 16]
Kill anyone who gets close!
Qin Bing.
If you can illuminate
all twelve Spiritual Lines Pillars,
you can have my position
of the sect leader.
With such a talent,
the Artefact Forging Sect
will be the strongest power
in all of Chilan.
That's 11 pillars.
Sir, Palace of Hell
will not give up so easily.
We are going on the offensive.
What do you propose?
You can decide.
As everyone knows,
throughout the years,
the five main sects
have not stopped trying to plant
spies in Artefact Forging Sect.
Today, we are forced to fight.
It is likely they will defect.
Attention, Bloody Spear Guards!
Yes!
Capture and interrogate apprentices
related to the five sects.
Together,
we will fend off the enemies.
Even if blood covers Spiritual Lines Hall,
we will ensure Qin Bing's safety.
The Palace of Hell
has done its job as the vanguard.
What now?
Are the sect leaders going to back down?
Such mediocrity!
We're not backing down.
Ying Xing Ran is known to be a coward.
Why why did he suddenly
become so ruthless this time?
Some shining pillars
are enough to drive him crazy.
He's crazy?
Then Lang Xie is even crazier.
Our disciples are in there.
We can't abandon them.
Exactly because our men are inside,
so we must attack quickly!
Your son
is in Artefact Forging Sect, right?
How sure are you
that they won't harm your son?
Senior.
The Blood Fiend Array has been set.
Anyone who dares breach it will not live.
Do not underestimate Di Shi Jiu.
Shadow Tower's expertise
is in sneak attacks.
They hide in your shadow
and strike when you're unaware.
Don't worry.
It's not our first time dealing
with Shadow Tower.
You are...
Cheng Yu of Purple Mist Sea.
Li Yi Shan of Cangyu Assembly.
Take them away.
Pang Feng of Cloud Sky Mountain.
Ouyang Qing.
Take them away.
Yi Yuan of Purple Mist Sea.
Yi Yuan of Purple Mist Sea!
Where is he?
He's escaped.
After him!
I am not deploying troops
because I'm trying to protect my son.
Fine.
Master Wu.
Master Jiang.
Granny Jiu.
You guys don't have sons in there, right?
Might as well let
Shadow Tower take the lead.
Others may fear Lang Xie,
but I do not.
Lang Xie and I will fight to the grave.
See that?
Shadow Tower of the Palace of Hell
is the true hero.
Dear sect leaders.
Seeing how Di Shi Jiu
is willing to risk his life like that
must make you shout with joy inside.
You're being a little harsh, Master Yuan.
Putting aside the other sects
and just talking about Qisha Valley,
we are made up of mostly female disciples.
They are not made to go to battle.
The Bloody Spears are killing machines.
You can't expect them to take them on.
The Shadow Tower is happy
to do the dirty work.
But when the job is done
and it is time to be rewarded,
I hope everyone will behave
in a fair manner.
Otherwise,
I'm sure you all know about
the rules of Shadow Tower.
Di Shi Jiu.
Are you confident?
Considering my ill fate
with the Bloody Spears,
there is none more confident than me
in killing him.
Lord Wolf, Commander Feng.
We have swept the place.
All apprentices from other sects
have been rounded up.
Only Yi Yuan, young master of Purple
Mist Sea, is unaccounted for.
Also...
Speak.
Senior Tang Si Qi
is also missing.
Get more men to search of Yi Yuan.
As for Tang Si Qi,
she should be able to protect herself.
Understood.
Senior.
Was that necessary?
Apprentices from other sects
have been dutifully learning here
without causing trouble.
Do you really believe
that the five sects did not plant spies
within the apprentices?
Feng Rong.
Seems like after you
got married to Mo Hai,
you've absorbed some of his naivety
and detachment from the world.
Don't worry, Senior.
I will do what I need to do
without hesitation.
[Inner world of
the twelve Spiritual Lines Pillars]
[Blood Progenitor, Xue Li]
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
You must have triggered
all the line pillars.
One thousand years.
I've been locked away for 1000 years.
Now I can finally be free!
Well?
What's going on?
The Palace of Hell's deputy chief
led an attack.
They're after you for
what happened to its young master.
The chief has given order for
the Bloody Spear Guards to protect you.
The attackers have been apprehended.
Protect me?
You are the first person
in a thousand years
to fully comprehend 11 of
the Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Palace of Hell.
No.
There is no way Palace of Hell
would breach
Artefact Forging Sect alone.
Other sects must be involved.
Doesn't matter. Lang Xie is ready
to fight
and has cleared the scene
of suspicious outside apprentices
by capturing or killing
in order to keep you safe.
What about Yu Shi?
She is with Qisha Valley
and came with her senior.
Don't worry.
I knew they are your friends.
They're guests and are safe.
I'm going to look for her.
Don't stop me.
I said they are safe.
These Spiritual Lines Pillars
hide a secret.
Each pillar corresponds
to the ways of the world.
I was able to quickly decipher the
Spirit Diagrams of the first few pillars.
But the later pillars
contain Spirit Diagrams that are
progressively harder to read.
Let me go.
Or else if I'm flustered,
I won't be able to comprehend
the 12th pillar.
Let him go.
Come back quickly.
If I were to compare,
a genius that has managed
to comprehend 11 pillars
to me, who only deciphered two,
I suddenly feel so insignificant.
Where is Ling Yu Shi?
She said she was going to find
a Shadow Tower assassin.
She beat us up and took off.
Shadow Tower assassin?
Gao Yu.
Senior.
All the exits have been sealed.
It's too quiet.
Yes.
It is very quiet.
I could almost smell the presence
of Shadow Tower.
I smell the smell of death too.
A smell similar to ours,
but different.
Reporting.
Someone from Hell Cliff
buckled and confessed.
There are indeed spies
from the five sects.
They've found the secret passage.
No wonder it's so quiet.
The secret passage.
Pass the order to get ready for battle.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Si Qi.
Si Qi!
Si Qi, where are you?
Why are you yelling so loudly?
Are you trying to alert others?
Si Qi.
What's the matter, Si Qi?
The sect is in danger
and yet you're hollering for a woman.
Because we're in danger,
that's why I wanted to see you.
I don't know if I'll make it
through today.
Stay far away from me
if you don't wish to die.
From now on, we're on different paths.
Best that you leave this place now.
With your skills,
you're of no help to the sect.
I won't go.
I'm going to stay and fight to the end.
If you won't go,
I'll go.
Si Qi!
What is it you're afraid of?
Tell me.
Let us share the burden together.
You can't bear it.
This is bad.
They're about to breach.
Come with me.
Who's coming with you?
You can go by yourself.
You're useless, an idiot!
Listen to me.
I don't care why it is
you're purposely turning on me today,
but I'll only say three words.
Come with me.
The messenger spirit birds
used by the five sects.
Why are they here?
You guys return to the alliance first.
Okay.
Go!
Child's play.
Lang Xie!
I, Di Shi Jiu, is here! Come out!
Listen up.
Even if you have to flatten the place,
you'll find Lang Xie for me!
Attack!
Where is Qin Bing? Tell me.
I came to save you guys.
Where is Gao Yu?
Watch out!
Greetings, Saintess Xie.
Saintess Xie?
Who would've thought I'd meet you here,
Saintess Xie,
who was supposed to have died months ago.
You've got the wrong person.
Even if I couldn't remember the face,
I would not mistake
Saintess Xie's Fireworks Chakram.
There have been rumours
of you being spotted.
But I told them it was nonsense
and that Saintess Xie is dead.
But thinking about it again,
Saintess Xie most likely faked her death
in order to do covert work
for Eight Extremes Temple.
Of course,
she could've pretended to be dead
out of mischief.
I wonder which one is correct, Saintess.
Can you let me go?
Let you go?
That means,
you did pretend to be dead
out of mischief.
If your father,
the chief of Eight Extremes Temple,
knew you faked your own death
because it was fun,
how would he think?
I helped him find his beloved daughter.
That is an incredible merit.
Die!
Once I finish what I came here to do,
I'll take you back to your father.
Don't you run!
I now get why it is so hard to meet
the sect's eldest apprentice.
Turns out Senior Tang Si Qi
is Saintess Xie Jing Xuan.
I am Xie Jing Xuan.
Stop running away.
I don't want to go back!
Because of him?
You want to die?
She said she doesn't want to go,
so I won't let you take her.
If you die on her behalf,
I'll let her go.
Good.
Protect her well.
Let's go.
Saintess Xie.
Do I have to bow and greet you formally?
Were you really going to die just now?
She could've really killed you.
My life
was given by you.
You're being silly.
How did Saintess Xie
become Tang Si Qi?
Because I don't want to be a saintess.
I want to live a carefree life.
I want to find someone
whom I love.
A man that loves me,
who I can share my life with.
Is this why you, the most fearless person,
is so afraid of being hauled back?
I'm not afraid of being hauled back.
Since the beginning,
I've already expected this day to come.
I'm afraid.
There's no rush.
We can talk slowly.
Whoever dares intrude,
I'll kill them.
Or maybe
we'll charge out and kill them together.
If we survive this,
I'll use my whole life
to listen to you talk.
I do not care for power and authority.
I only want a sincere love.
I've gotten a taste of it.
I've found it.
But I didn't think it'd be so scary.
I'm not scared to die.
I'm not afraid of being caught
and punished.
But I'm scared of never seeing you again,
putting you in danger.
I fear that when I go back,
I'll never be able to forget you.
Silly.
I'm afraid too.
I'm afraid of not being able
to ever let you go.
If you dare lie to me,
I'll kill you.
Let's go.
We'll leave this place
and go somewhere that no one can find us.
We'll be together forever.
I won't go.
You're the man I love.
We should have lofty ambitions.
You are a Bloody Spear Guard.
I am the sect's eldest apprentice.
We will charge out
and annihilate everyone!
You're not scared?
Scared of what?
I have more artefacts than you can count.
What to do?
Don't worry. I told you.
I have plenty of artefacts.
What about me?
What?
I mean,
you're Saintess Xie.
I'm with you.
If we head out together
and people recognised us,
what should I do?
Guess we'll have to die together then.
Let's go.
Song Ting Yu, move aside.
Come with me.
Why should I go with you?
We'll go and see my father,
master of Profound Heaven Alliance,
Song Yu.
I'm looking for Yu Shi.
I have no time for you.
Don't you want to save
the Artefact Forging Sect?
What do you mean?
The five sects are out for blood.
You guys won't last very long.
Forget about your Ling Yu Shi,
the whole Artefact Forging Sect
would be destroyed.
Only my father can save you all.
Come with me to talk to my father.
That's the only way you'll live.
What are you scheming this time?
I'm just a mere sect apprentice.
I have no right to meet with
the Alliance master.
If it's to ask for a favour,
it should be our sect leader
doing the asking.
Ying Xing Ran may be the sect leader,
but he has always avoided conflict.
He's a weakling.
My father wouldn't bother with him.
He likes people with guts.
You dared to kill Du Hai Tian.
I'm sure he'll be willing to hear you out.
Only if you save the Artefact Forging Sect
can you and Yu Shi find a way out alive.
Let's go.
Keep up.
Stay focused.
Gao Yu!
Qin Lie.
Qin Lie!
Stop!
Where is Yu Shi?
You have no shame asking about her.
This is a perilous time
and you left her by herself.
I'm not like you.
I'll take her away from this battlefield.
Stop looking.
Gao Yu is probably not here.
We should find a place to hide.
What is it?
It's Gao Yu.
Where?
I can sense him.
How?
Since obtaining the Heavenly Water
Spirit Record,
I'm particularly sensitive to breath.
Gao Yu's evil aura,
I can sense it.
Yu Shi!
Yu Shi.
What happened? Stay still.
Who hurt you?
Where is Qin Lie?
How could he leave you alone?
It's none of your business.
Leave.
Yu Shi.
I know.
I was wrong.
I won't ever hurt you again.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
That's right.
You're here.
No need to be afraid.
Shadow Tower is attacking.
I've guessed it.
You, the hidden dagger of Shadow Tower,
will surely appear.
I am devoted to you.
How could you lie to me?
Does devotion mean you could
do whatever without repercussion?
I'll kill you myself.
Yu Shi.
Are you alright?
This ring
is a sacred offering from
the alter of the Evil Nether God.
It's an item symbolising the god's
power and authority as the most evil.
It is of great value.
Evil Nether God?
The ring belongs to the Dark Nether Race?
But the Evil Nether God
died thousands of years ago.
The Soul Reaping Beast.
It ran from the nether world
to the far north.
Perhaps it's related to the ring.
But why is the ring
on him?
It seems suspicious.
In other words,
there might be a bigger conspiracy.
I will keep this ring for now.
Does this mean
what he's done
is all because of the ring?
What did he do?
What did you do to Ling Yu Shi?
It's none of your concern.
Let her kill me.
What I did to her
is beyond forgiving.
Even if you don't kill me,
I'll commit suicide.
Did you tarnish her?
I did not!
Stop your quibbling.
He told you that?
Yes.
Why did you say that?
Because I want Qin Lie to suffer.
I want him to suffer more than death.
You lied to me?
-You did not...
-Senior Lu saved me in time.
Let her go!
Scoundrel!
He didn't get his way,
but he slandered my innocence.
If I don't kill him,
I won't be able to live with myself.
You're truly despicable.
A woman cares most about her chastity.
Your careless words
will mean the death of an innocent girl.
No wonder she doesn't like you.
You deserve to die.
I should be the one to die.
I did it on purpose.
Senior.
What are you saying?
Yu Shi.
It was I who had a bad thought.
I had lured Gao Yu there.
I thought
if you had been violated by him,
senior would no longer
be interested in you.
But I couldn't follow through
with the wrong.
I couldn't stand watching the scoundrel
continue to take advantage of you.
That's why I stepped forward to help.
I had thought
I would feel relieved
from doing a good deed.
I didn't expect
to be trapped in the illusion
of Huanyu Beast.
I kept trying to avoid you.
Whenever I saw you,
I'd start trembling in fear.
Although
I extended help in time,
but
I've harboured evil intentions
since the beginning.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Senior.
He should be the one to die.
Let him go.
This scoundrel deserves to die.
But I won't let you kill him yet.
I need him to help me find
the truth behind
the Evil Nether God's ring.
As the commander-in-chief
of the Nether battlefield,
I will not condone any threats
from the Dark Nether Race on Chilan.
Once this is over,
even if you don't kill him,
I'll kill him myself.
This is a crucial matter.
Give me three months.
No way.
One month.
Fine, one month.
If you're still sheltering him then,
I don't care if you're the saintess.
I'll make you pay.
It's a deal.
Let him go.
Set your priorities straight.
Gao Yu will be incarcerated here.
The Artefact Forging Sect is in peril.
I need to discuss with Tang Si Qi
on how to proceed.
Ling Yu Shi is from the five sects.
It'd be troublesome
if the Bloody Spears find her.
I'm here to look after Yu Shi.
You need not fuss.
Yi Yuan.
I'm here.
Over here.
Looks like this is the safest place.
No way. I don't want to become snake soup.
So what should we do?
How about handing me over to Lian Rou?
Okay.
Wish granted.