[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 15]
You killed Yuan Xiao?
I didn't.
It was you.
Gao Yu. It really is you.
Scum!
He's dead?
How dare you, a new disciple,
kill the young master of Palace of Hell?
Believe it or not,
I didn't kill him.
[Cheng Ping]
You...
Elder Cheng.
Let's listen to what Saintess Song
has got to say first.
Greetings, Saintess Song.
If Yuan Xiao didn't die,
there will be a bigger trouble.
How are you doing, Saintess Song?
The pill made from Huanyu Beast's blood
is indeed extraordinary.
I have recovered.
Chief Elder,
Yuan Xiao and his men
waited at the exit of Secret Realm,
intending to kill us
and steal the treasure.
We were all wounded back then.
Yuan Xiao started this.
If Qin Bing really killed him,
he was compelled to do so.
And if Yuan Tian Ya has a question,
tell him to come and ask me.
I would like to know
will it be him blaming me
for his son's death
or I condemning him
for his son's murder attempt.
But...
Ask all the disciples to stay back.
We'll make a decision
when things are cleared.
Sure.
My answer won't change
no matter how you ask.
I don't know why
I wanted to kill Ling Yu Shi.
The mirage shows
the deepest desire in your heart.
And you dare to say
you never intended to kill her?
Yes, I don't hold any grudge against her.
Why would I want her dead?
Maybe it's another person
that you wanted dead.
When you tried to kill me,
you said this.
[Gong Mu Lie, leave that woman!]
[To you at that time,]
[Qin Lie was not himself,]
[but another person.]
So,
I wasn't Ling Yu Shi as well.
Qin Lie told me
that you were obsessed with Gong Mu Lie.
But you took him as Gong Mu Lie?
And in the book,
I'm the person that is
always beside Gong Mu Lie
whom you loathe.
I don't know.
I really don't.
If you don't believe me,
kill me now.
I believe you.
I believe Yu Shi.
Then, don't bring this up
or ask about it anymore.
Save ourselves the headache.
I know you didn't kill Yuan Xiao.
But everyone thinks it was you.
I'm afraid whatever you say now
won't do any help.
That's why I'm not wasting my effort.
I'm more interested
in knowing why he did that.
Since it's your problem,
do something about it.
Yu Shi,
why did you call Gao Yu a scum?
This is the note
you left for me at Qisha Valley.
You said to read it
when I meet Gao Yu.
What is it that you know?
Nothing.
It's just that when he
took me back to Ling Borough,
I felt like he was a different person.
Maybe the war at Purple Mist Sea
has dealt blow to him.
Anyway, I don't believe
a single word he said.
So, I was just reminding you.
The war at Purple Mist Sea
hit everybody hard.
But,
why only he changed?
I don't know.
When we meet again,
I'm going to make him tell me everything.
You knew Du Shao Yang would kill me,
didn't you?
Yu Shi.
Why're you acting like
a different person too?
You won't tell me anything.
Prophecies?
Warnings?
I dreamed about watching meteor
with you since young.
I thought that was just a dream.
But then, I realized
that that could be a prophecy
or a warning.
In case staying by your side
would spell disaster for you,
I decided to go to Qisha Valley.
But when you were cultivating there,
you saw me getting eaten by a Fire Dragon
and someone trying to
kill me with a dagger?
The prophecies came true.
I'm not sure
if he was Du Shao Yang.
Then,
about being eaten by the Fire Dragon...
That could be a prophecy too.
It'll happen sooner or later.
Since grandpa left in quiet,
and my mind being concealed by
Soul Suppressing Orb,
my background became a mystery.
But all prophecies that you saw
are about me.
Could you be part of the mystery
of my background?
If that's the case,
then it was not an accident
that your grandpa
left you at Ling Borough.
I'm glad that's what happened.
You're the person I trust the most.
Having you share the mystery with me
is perfect.
[The Mother of Land]
[and the son of God of War
can't fall in love.]
[If the evil people find it out,]
[before they can even
enjoy the relationship,]
[troubles have already been awaiting.]
[But now,]
[love is already born between you two.]
[You want a fierce battle]
[or you'll breakup?]
[It's your choice.]
The Mother of Land
and the son of God of War
can't fall in love?
Had this been a warning
about you and me,
we would end up
fighting a fierce battle.
Qin Lie,
I can't stay with you.
What? So for our sake,
that strange woman
put Forbidden Spell on us
to break us up easily?
You're the Mother of Land?
What's that?
And I'm the son of God of War?
In my whole life,
I've never heard about any God of War.
I think this is just an excuse.
Is this the time for a joke?
After Xingyun Pavilion's
disturbance at our wedding
and your confession,
I kept asking myself
but still couldn't find the answer.
I think I'm fond of you.
I want to.
Or you wouldn't be the person
that I worry the most
at moments of life and death.
When I almost died at the Ice Land,
and when I was taking the Soul Reaping
Beast down with me at Silent Abyss.
Even the mirage in God Trapping Cave
was you.
But I feel like
there's an unknown power
that is stopping my feeling for you.
Is that true?
It has always been in my heart.
I... I dare not tell you.
And now that I do,
it's more like a heartless excuse.
No.
I'm very happy.
At least
you want to like me.
Even if we'll face
a fierce battle in the end,
I won't regret it.
I never believe in fate,
or the so-called destiny.
If the Gods want me dead,
I'll destroy them.
Yu Shi,
as long as we have the courage to face it,
we can make a change.
[Spiritual Lines Pillars Plaza]
You already learned
about the Spiritual Herb.
Today, I'll be teaching you
the artefact forging skills.
To forge an artefact,
Spirit Diagram is the key.
An weapon without Spirit Diagram
is not a magical weapon.
To become a true armourer,
it's crucial to know
how to carve Spirit Diagram.
Since you've passed the test,
I believe you're all smart people.
Why don't we get started already?
All the best in forging
the magical weapon of your dreams.
You may leave now.
-Okay.
You finally show up.
Usually, you wouldn't
work with the weapons
even if I asked you to.
And you'd rather chat with others.
Do you join the Sect
to make friends
or learn artefact forging skills?
I'm here to learn more about my grandpa.
Found anything?
The Master is retreating.
When he comes out,
get Master Mo Hai to ask him.
Why were you giggling just now?
I... I wasn't.
I was getting insight.
You were obviously thinking about a woman.
Yes, I was thinking about Lian Rou.
So, what?
It's perfectly normal for a man
to be attracted to a woman.
You think they're all
trying to understand the skill?
Maybe they're also thinking about women.
You won't think about Yu Shi?
How do you know that?
You both keep exchanging love glances.
Even a blind man would notice.
But the disciple of Artefact Forging Sect
becoming a couple
with the disciple of Qisha Valley
could make a beautiful love story.
She and I
grew up together.
So, you're some childhood sweetheart.
A better story it is.
She...
What? A long story?
Make it short, then.
I think she's hiding something from me.
And she seems to be less dependent on me.
Meaning, in the past,
you always looked after her?
Of course.
Or she was the one looking after me?
I don't know too.
Fine.
In conclusion,
a man
who doesn't even know
if he looked after his woman
or being looked after by her
is not trusted by the woman.
That actually makes sense.
Good job.
Well done.
Although Shadow Tower
belongs to the Palace of Hell,
all these years,
Palace of Hell achieved success
because of our brothers' sacrifice.
Even the Master treats us with respect.
But Yuan Xiao
dare to
boss us around because of his position.
He has lived long enough.
Yuan Xiao
was too arrogant.
He tried to steal the treasure,
disregarding even Saintess Song.
Someone like him
will be killed one day
even if it's not us.
Gao Yu, I like your fortitude.
The door of Shadow Tower is open for you.
The Shadow Tower is cunning,
while I'm cruel.
That's great.
After Yuan Xiao's death,
the five great sects
will lash it out
on the Artefact Forging Sect.
I will destroy the Sect
once and for all.
Since you're all silent,
I'll take my leave
as there are works to do
at Cloud Sky Mountain.
Why the rush, Master Wu Tuo?
How can we not avenge
Master Yuan's son?
[Wu Tuo, Master of Cloud Sky Mountain]
Nice.
You want me to owe you, huh?
[Yu Dai, Master of Purple Mist Sea]
My son's death
actually gave you an excuse
to eliminate the Artefact Forging Sect.
Those who are too cowardly to go
may get lost now.
A bunch of sect leaders
who want to save face.
I'll speak my mind, then.
The armourers and magical weapons
in the Sect
also belong to Qisha Valley.
Grandma Jiu is straightforward.
How admirable.
Count the Purple Mist Sea in
in the event of eliminating the Sect.
I, Jiang Heng,
the master of Cangyu Assembly,
agree.
Jiu Liu Yu, Mistress of Qisha Valley,
Very well.
Since everyone has agreed,
we shall attack Firetop Mountain.
Attacking the Sect
is not an easy task.
We need the approval
of the two higher-ups.
I have
sent them the message.
Now,
all we need is their approval.
All of you
just focus on preparing for the battle.
You're scared?
Don't join Bloody Spear
if you're a coward.
Greetings, Master Lang Xie.
When the Sect was established
1000 years ago,
[Lang Xie, Bloody Spear Guard
of Artefact Forging Sect]
the blood pool was already here.
In order to become
an outstanding Bloody Spear warrior,
one must enter the pool
and be immersed in blood.
The water in the bloody pool
is made from the juice
of over 70 spiritual herbs.
It can strengthen your body quickly.
But the pain the you feel while in there
is not bearable by simply anybody.
Those who enter the blood pool
must endure unbelievable pain.
The physical pain,
when impregnated with blood demon,
may turn them into blood in an instant,
leaving no bone behind
the moment they get in the pool.
Du Shao Yang,
do you dare to enter the blood pool?
I do.
Du Shao Yang.
Where are you?
Do you miss me?
Fine.
I do.
Where are you?
I won't tell you.
Listen,
I'm in grave danger now.
In case something happens,
you won't see me again.
Don't worry.
The blood pool can't hurt you.
How do you know I'm in a blood pool?
Are you nearby?
Bad guy.
You tricked me.
You left as soon as
our lessons end every time.
Who are you dodging?
No one.
You hide away
whenever Saintess Song comes.
Are you avoiding her?
That's why you wouldn't show up
at the Secret Realm.
No, you're wrong.
At Purple Mist Sea,
you talked about Saintess Song
like you know her well.
I already suspected it back then.
Du Shao Yang, I'm warning you.
Don't make assumptions about me.
Also,
don't ever talk about other women with me.
Pass the test of blood pool
or get the heck out of the Sect. And...
And...
When are you coming back?
I miss you.
I'm not coming back.
So that you'll miss me more.
It's not funny.
Si Qi.
[A man who doesn't even know]
[if he looked after his woman]
[or being looked after by her]
[is not trusted by the woman.]
[That actually makes sense.]
Who's there?
Gao Yu?
You're an assassin of Shadow Tower now?
What about Shadow Tower?
I think it's good.
You're now Qin Bing too, aren't you?
Shadow Tower is Palace of Hell's subject.
Why did you kill Yuan Xiao,
the young master of Palace of Hell?
It doesn't matter who I killed.
The thing is, the blame is on you.
I don't like it when you're doing well.
Why?
Your grandpa helped Ling Borough,
and they were extremely nice to you.
I was jealous.
You're a more talented cultivator
than I ever am.
I had to train hard for one year
to reach your one-month level.
That makes me more jealous.
Yu Shi loves you madly
to even notice me.
But I'm no longer jealous.
Because I'm going to destroy you.
I'm surprised
that you hate me so deeply.
I have hated you since young.
I just didn't notice that before.
Killing you would actually satisfy me.
What did you do to Yu Shi
that she's furious at you?
I love her.
When a man loves a woman,
what will he do?
I just did what I was supposed to do.
Why are you glaring at me?
You think I was wrong?
From the moment I got the insight,
I don't think I did anything wrong.
I was right.
You let her down.
She was in pain because of you.
Seeing her like that
made me more pain.
And the source of our pain
was your ruthlessness and arrogance.
I finally got it.
So,
I treated her nicely
in a more aggressive way.
What did you do to Yu Shi?
She didn't tell you that?
I knew she wouldn't.
Because you're not
worthy of her trust anymore.
That's why I came to see you.
Qin Lie,
she's already mine.
Although she didn't consent to that,
and was trying hard to fight back
while crying,
she belongs to me now,
and she'll realize how good I am
sooner or later.
What's the point of hitting me?
Kill me.
Come on, kill your buddy.
What made you turn into this man?
If I spread words
that Qin Bing is actually Qin Lie,
countless of people will after you.
But I won't do that.
I'm going to torture you slowly
and have you tormented
before killing you.
Qin Lie,
put on your mask.
From now on,
live in the dark like I do.
What did you ask to see me
at this hour for?
You took off your mask?
What if someone recognizes you?
Yu Shi,
I'm a wanted man now.
A fugitive.
Will you be disgusted by me?
No matter what you are,
I won't despise you.
Marry me.
Sorry?
I'll leave the Artefact Forging Sect.
And you don't have to
return to Qisha Valley.
If you'll come with me,
let's travel the world together.
Or
we can find a quiet place
and live there.
Which one do you prefer?
What have you learned?
Was Gao Yu here?
I'm sorry, Yu Shi.
I didn't know
things would turn out like this.
I don't need your pity.
It's not pity,
-I'm...
-Do you love me?
Only the Moon knows my troubled mind.
There's moon only once in a year
in Ling Borough.
But it can be seen here every night,
shining very brightly.
Will you confess your love to me
before the moon?
You may lie to me,
as well as yourself.
But can you deceive the sky above you?
You're in this situation.
Yet, I was asking if you love me.
That must be annoying.
Don't blame yourself.
My love has always been one-sided.
You don't owe me anything.
Stay there.
Where are you going?
Out.
Didn't you notice
the place isn't guarded?
So?
The Chief Elder wanted you
to run away badly.
I was ordered to stay here
and grab the chance to capture you
to be given to Palace of Hell.
I'm on my way to the Palace too.
What are you going there for?
To apologize?
To look for someone.
Who?
I can't tell you.
You're boiling with anger.
What happened?
Do me a favour.
Let me go out.
You killed my father.
Yet you're asking me
to disobey Chief Elder and help you?
Why must I help?
Qin Lie!
I had a fight with him.
That's why he lost his temper
and insisted on going to the Palace.
-Come back with me.
-Let me go!
What can you do there?
Come back.
What's wrong with this couple?
You want to take Gao Yu's life?
Why didn't you do it
when he came to see you?
No!
I wanted to kill him then.
But I couldn't beat him.
He seemed to have learned
some evil technique.
In that case,
why did you insist to go?
It's like walking towards your death.
So what if I'm dead?
I'll take him down
even if that cost my life.
What about me
if you die?
My father is dead.
Xuan Xuan has gone missing.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
I don't know how to comfort you.
With his death,
-maybe...
-He can't escape it.
Calm down for the time being.
If you want to get back at him for me,
stay here and cultivate.
Become stronger.
If something ever happens to you,
that will only make me more painful.
Don't go back to Qisha Valley.
Stay here.
Stay with me so I can protect you.
I'll stay.
I'll be with you.
Whether you love me or not,
or if you'll be able to love me,
we can only
depend on each other now.
Promise me.
From now on,
don't keep anything from me.
Okay.
[Palace of Hell]
We've waited for so long.
What did the two higher-ups say?
They aren't responding.
That's their answer.
I'll head to the Sect
and have them hand over Qin Bing.
If they do,
what will you do?
Whatever they do,
the Sect must be made accountable.
Exactly.
Since he's a disciple of the Sect,
then his action
must've been instructed by the master.
So,
they must answer for it.
Master Yu, I heard
that your son's at the Sect.
Send him a message.
Father wants me to be the spy?
What spy, all of a sudden?
This is strange.
-Lian Rou?
-What's your problem?
Where are you hurt?
Move.
Don't try to take advantage of me.
I won't.
I'm just showing my concern.
Such a smooth-tongued.
The Chief Elder told me
to give you the Spiritual Herb Recipe.
Collect all the herbs.
Why were you
murmuring just now?
Are you troubled by something?
No, nothing.
I was just bored.
So, I walked around.
Oh,
I was training. Training.
Training?
-Is that true?
-Yes, it is.
Very true.
The Alliance Chief
wants you back immediately.
And you're told to stay out of
whatever you see on the road.
The magical weapon is not yet forged.
Why does he want me back now?
I have no idea
about the reason why.
What will I see along the way?
The Chief must have his reason
for saying that.
Saintess, we should
go now.
I think something is brewing.
What is going on in the Alliance lately?
Tell me everything.
[Everything in the world is ever-lasting.]
[Spirit Diagram is the key to all. ]
Master, the assistant master
of Palace of Hell wants Qin Bing.
Should we stop him, Master?
No need. Let him in.
Mo Hai,
what do you think?
Everything
must be a fair play.
The young master of Palace of Hell died.
[Ying Xing Ran,
Master of Artefact Forging Sect]
They want justice.
But they failed to stop him
from trying to murder
the saintess of the Alliance
and our disciples.
How should we settle this score?
Well...
Cao Xuan Rui,
the Assistant Master of Palace of Hell
[Cao Xuan Rui of Palace of Hell]
is here to greet Master Ying.
The Spiritual Lines Pillar!
Qin Bing has comprehended one Pillar.
Another Pillar.
Hey,
is he going to continue?
Cao Xuan Rui, you don't look like
you're here to see someone,
but to kill someone instead.
Is Palace of Hell an impolite place now?
Get lost, wench!
What if she doesn't?
Knock it off.
Ying Xing Ran,
you, a leader of the sect,
allowed your disciple to commit murder.
And when the victim came,
you refused to hand over the culprit?
Even Yuan Tian Ya
won't talk loudly to me.
Who do you think you are?
You're not handing him over, are you?
So, you will fall out
with the Palace of Hell
over a new disciple?
There's no need to
fall out with them, Master.
We won't hand him over.
You barged in. That's unacceptable.
Wanting us to hand him over
before investigation
is also unacceptable.
Saintess Song has left.
Without the witness,
how do we find out the truth?
Chief Elder, you're wrong.
The Artefact Forging Sect is independent.
When did we ever rely on an outsider?
Master Cao,
how about this?
I'll bring Qin Bing here.
We'll interrogate him.
If you wish to take my disciple away
without an interrogation,
you'll have Bloody Spear Guards
to deal with.
Fine, an interrogation it is.
I'd like to see how you do it.
Bring him here.
Oh, no!
This is amazing!
Qin Bing has comprehended three Pillars.
What?
Qin Bing has comprehended
three Pillars, Master.
Everyone saw that.
Three Pillars?
Great.
Let's take a look.
What?
You're leaving us here alone?
Let's go.
We'll take a look too.
One, two, three, four.
Seven, eight, nine.
Nine Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Since our establishment,
besides the founder,
the largest number of Pillars
comprehended was only four.
The Spirit Diagrams
from only the four Pillars
have brought about the Sect's
greatest achievement of all time.
Nine Pillars
mean the number of
Spirit Diagrams we obtained
has more than doubled.
We can be on par
with Silver Class in term of strength.
What is going on?
Ten Pillars!
It's ten Pillars!
The 12 Spiritual Lines Pillars
were set up by our founder.
Those who comprehended the Pillars
would become remarkable armourers.
Throughout his life,
our founder managed to comprehend
ten Pillars
in the Spiritual Lines Formation.
And he gained nothing after that.
But Qin Bing
comprehended ten Pillars
so easily.
His future is very promising.
Qin Bing?
So, that's Qin Bing? Capture him.
You're too noisy.
What?
Are you asking for a fight?
Bloody Spear Guards, protect Qin Bing.
Yes, Master!
Attack!
Kill anyone who takes a step forward.