♪How to separate♪
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 18
East Gate
Chen Cu
Hello.
Hi, bro.
We’re so busy right now.
I really need your help.
What?
You’re again doing hellish night shifts?
Don’t even start it.
I’ve been busting my ass for two hours.
Come and help if you’re not occupied.
Fine.
I’ll be there in ten minutes.
You agreed?
You agreed so easily?
Let me make a wild guess.
Did your girlfriend bail on you?
So you don’t need my help?
I’m not going then.
I’ll go on a date.
No. No. No.
You must sacrifice yourself
for the greater good.
I’m waiting for you.
Shenzhen Yun Ji Hospital
During the operation
Clock Beijing time
Fine.
Stitch it up.
Do you know?
These youngsters
like to conduct operations with you two.
Really?
Because
they not only can observe
delicate surgery techniques,
but also admire your charm.
That’s pleasant to hear.
Let’s go.
Let’s revive ourselves in the lounge.
Come on.
Cousin.
Your perfect boyfriend
is like an old man now.
Life has cracked him.
Dr. Wen, Dr. Chen.
There’s another surgery now.
It’s going to be a long night.
Get ready for the surgery.
Okay.
I see.
What happened?
Are you ill?
I was caught in the rain.
I might have caught a cold.
I’ll go check out the patient now.
You get some rest.
Call me if you need my help.
Sure.
Boss.
Brother-in-law.
What?
So brother-in-law is
the right way to call him.
Well.
We have another emergent patient.
Come on.
Cousin
What are you hiding?
Give it to me.
Cousin.
Your perfect boyfriend
is like an old man now.
Life has cracked him.
You’re watching me closely?
I’m sorry.
If I ramble again,
I’ll donate my tongue,
and never speak again.
Zhong Zhen, are you looking for trouble?
He’s not cracked.
He’s glowing. Right?
If you have one tenth of his diligence,
your mom will be so grateful.
Why are you shaking?
Hold it steady.
Boss.
Why haven’t you slept?
If Zhong Zhen texts to you on WeChat
in the middle of the night,
don’t respond.
Go to sleep.
It seems he had many surgeries tonight.
His hands are red from too much washing.
Shenzhen Yun Ji Hospital
This night is so exhausting.
My ankles are swollen.
Last night isn’t the toughest at all.
What?
The moment we came to take our turn,
I heard that you stayed up all night.
Last night, the east wind
prevails over the west wind.
Are you suggesting that
Dr. Chen Cu prevails over Dr. Wen?
Nonsense!
How dare I do that?
So our Dr. Chen
has always been at the bottom?
Tell the doctors who arrange the shifts
not to put us in the same shift.
His temper is too strong.
We’re not compatible.
What?
I’m wearing a red underwear for luck.
Don’t you know it’s banned
on night shift?
It may cause accidents.
We have all received higher education.
Don’t be so super...
Shut up.
Superstitious...
Petition.
Letter of authorization.
Contract.
Great.
Wen Shaoqing.
What happened to you?
Are you all right?
Why did your trip to the grocery store
take so long?
Are you feeling ill?
Come. Let me give you a hand.
I went back to the hospital last night.
I haven’t eaten yet.
Low blood sugar.
Low blood sugar?
I have peppermint candy at home.
Wait for me.
I’ll get it for you.
Peppermint candy?
It’s still candy.
Beggars can’t be choosers.
I have some in my pocket.
Get it for me.
In my pants pocket.
Pants pocket.
Are you still
trying to play with me now?
Get it yourself.
Bending down will engage
the lower back muscles.
It burns massive calories
which causes
cerebral vascular insufficiency
and then oxygen shortage...
Fine.
Shut up.
I’ll get it for you.
Come.
Let’s get inside.
Your lips are so pale.
Are you having a fever?
That is inaccurate.
This is.
That’s even more inaccurate.
I’ll get the thermometer.
It’s in the study.
Second drawer on the right of the desk.
There’s a medicine kit.
He’s on the verge of fainting.
He’s still flirting.
I’m going crazy.
I found...
Wen Shaoqing,
don’t sleep here.
You may get a cold.
Go sleep in your bed.
Come on.
You’re awake?
Let’s take your temperature.
Open your mouth.
Can you not go to the law firm today?
I’ve meetings with my clients.
It’s about the Online Loans case.
I have to go.
Your mom does know you the best.
No wonder she doesn’t want
you to be a lawyer.
I can stay with you a bit longer.
I’ll stay for another ten minutes.
Oh.
This is for you.
If you wash your hands too frequently,
you need to apply hand cream.
Or your skin will crack in cold weather.
Apply it for me.
I’m too tired.
You’re taking advantage of your ill.
My hands are smooth, right?
It’s done.
Give me the thermometer.
38.5 degrees.
Why is it so high?
Fine.
I’ll ask for a leave.
No, you shouldn’t.
My body temperature
is normally higher than the others.
Really?
It’s true.
I’m a doctor.
I can take care of myself.
I’ll be fine with
some medicine and sleep.
Am I really a bad girlfriend?
No.
You’re amazing.
You did your best.
How about this?
However late it is,
I’ll come home and cook soup for you.
Is that okay with you?
Chicken soup?
Chicken soup it is then.
I’ll leave now.
One Palace Home
Wen Rang
Hello.
Can you do me a favor?
Burang Barbeque
It’s wired.
It’s deadly silent today.
Rang Kai Bookstore
Are you going to see someone?
Yes.
You just can’t move on, can you?
What do you suggest?
Some people just can’t
take care of themselves.
Wen Rang.
I didn’t really know you until now.
I despise you.
What?
Why are you so mad at me?
And you despise me?
Yes.
You’re spineless.
Aren’t you tough
when you turned me down?
Why are you suddenly spineless?
Wait a second?
Why is it spineless
to take care of my nephew?
You are...!
Wait. Take care of who?
My nephew Wen Shaoqing.
It’s your nephew?
You should say it earlier.
Go. Hurry up.
Don’t miss the life-saving rescue.
Go. Go.
So you’re talking about Jiang…?
Nonsense.
Hello.
Rong.
Answer me.
Is Wen Shaoqing ill?
Yes.
What?
Great.
Great?
No. No.
That’s not what I mean.
I mean that your boyfriend
does me a huge favor.
He proves a very important thing for me.
What is it?
Wen Rang didn’t lie to me.
I’ll hang up now.
Glad that he’s not seeing Jiang Yao.
You have a new order.
It’s a big one.
Burang Barbeque
These paintings will be
on display next week.
It will be transported by sea.
Keep it monitored.
And one art installation hasn’t arrived.
It’s still on the sea.
Okay.
Global Original Art
Excuse me, the takeout is here.
I’m sorry.
The rain is too heavy.
I spent a little longer on the road.
Take it to the office.
You’re the one who ordered the takeout?
Yeah, it’s me.
You asked me to support
your restaurant, didn’t you?
Thanks.
Your hair is wet.
Let me get you a towel.
There’s no need for that.
I’ve delivered the takeout.
I’ll go back now.
Let’s talk about Wen Rang.
This is amazing.
My place isn’t bad, right?
Not bad.
My family is in
the antique art business.
So we’re somehow
in the same industry.
Hurry up.
Dry your hair.
Thanks.
Yesterday, I was like an old friend.
Now I’m an enemy?
It’s different now.
Because of Wen Rang?
He said he has a girlfriend.
Do you know who she is?
It’s…
It’s me.
What?
You don’t believe me?
Yesterday, I had dinner
with him and his parents at their house.
His dad really likes me.
But I remember that
his dad seldom asks
about his relationships.
People change.
His parents are older now.
They want their son to
get married sooner.
That’s natural.
Wen Rang has changed too.
No one will stay the same forever.
Have you been with him for long?
Yes.
I’m friends with his nephew
Wen Shaoqing too.
I even introduced my bestie to him.
Now, the four of us
visit the elders
together at festivals.
And we plan to hold weddings
together in the future.
It seems that I came back too late.
Yes, you’re late.
But it’s fine.
You can move forward.
You’re an extraordinary person.
You don’t have to look back.
I’m just being a bit reminiscent.
Does he still celebrate June 8?
Sure.
Every year, he books restaurant
and takes me to fine-dining.
It’s a special day after all.
Why are you laughing?
June 8 is the day
I left him without notice.
Then I must have mistaken the date.
In short, don’t try to win him back.
He won’t get back with you.
I came back this time
to hear it from him.
He doesn’t want to see you.
So,
you can ask him out.
You’re his girlfriend.
He will come if you ask him to.
But it’s raining heavily outside today.
So I have to keep pursuing him.
Wait a second.
Come on.
Eat something before you sleep.
How’s the taste?
Not bad.
Years of experience as a cook pays off.
Not bad?
You’re such a picky eater.
How dare you be so picky
when your girlfriend has left you?
You sound like you haven’t been
abandoned by your girlfriend.
What’s wrong?
I haven’t seen you like this
for a long time.
She’s back.
Who?
Jiang Yao?
You’re not considering
getting back with her, are you?
No.
No wonder!
Her name is so fitting.
She’s like the relentless wind that
stirs up everything.
Jiang Yao.
You’re still so mean
when you’re having a fever.
Doctors will shake their heads at you.
What do you mean?
You’re helpless.
Will you eat it or not?
I’ll take it away if you don’t.
How about Zhou Chengcheng?
I refused her.
This is going to be fun.
A girl you can’t let go of.
A girl who can’t let go of you.
It’s an equilateral triangle.
The structure is pretty stable.
What happened?
You’re a Nobel prize winner in math now?
Don’t try to shift the subject.
Who will you choose between them?
I choose you.
Zhou Chengcheng
Hello.
Wen Rang.
I was riding my e-bike.
And I was hit.
Were you injured?
Wait a second.
What are you doing in the pouring rain?
I’ll text you the address.
Can you come and pick me up?
I have something to attend to.
Have to go.
Lend me your car.
The key is at the entryway.
Get it yourself.
You just said you would choose me.
Zhou Chengcheng.
I’m here.
Are you injured?
You can’t even ride the bike properly,
let alone an e-bike.
I’m fine.
Wen Rang.
It’s me who want to see you.
I didn’t mean to do this.
I told her you’d not get back with her.
She didn’t believe me.
So you lied to me
and made me come all the way
just to answer such a trivial question?
If this is really a trivial question,
then answer me honestly.
Tell me that you don’t like me,
that you don’t care about me,
or don't want to see me anymore.
Tell me.
Jiang Yao.
This is not ten years ago
when I gave
every answer you wanted.
So you’ll not give me the answer.
You haven’t changed a bit.
You still like this game.
You threw a bait in the ocean
and waited for me to take it.
You used your own name
to buy my books
because you want me to look for you.
You’re so sure that I will.
You want this sense of accomplishment.
You don’t have to look for me.
But you still did.
What does that say?
It means that there’s still a place
for me in your heart.
That’s the answer I want.
What’s wrong with you?
You just can’t listen to people.
Why are you so narcissistic?
Why do you think
he still cares about you?
Because he wrote books
and he’s never dated anyone
since he broke up with you?
Your words just
further proved what I think.
Come out.
Don’t you know that you give her hope?
I’m such an idiot.
I got all the speeding tickets
rushing over not just to be the prize
of your bet.
That’s not what I mean.
You know it.
I don’t want you to get hurt anymore.
Can’t you make it clear to her?
I’m in a bad mood now.
I can’t sort things out with her.
If you’re unwilling to say it
to her face,
you can talk to her on phone,
or send her a WeChat message.
You can always make
things clear if you want to.
You can’t say it to her face,
or you just don’t want to?
You’re hesitant.
Yes.
I am hesitant.
I am hesitant. So what?
That was ten years of my time,
not your past,
nor the past of anyone else.
Don’t I have my right to be hesitant?
Who are you to me?
Sandman Space
Do you need refill?
The kitchen will close soon.
No, thank you.
Okay.
Let’s go.
They’re late for over an hour.
They probably won’t come.
I’ll wait for a bit longer.
Don’t have too much hope.
This case is at the center of
media attention right now.
The victims don’t want to subject
themselves to public debate.
Few will be willing to testify in court.
I know.
That’s why I need to wait a bit longer.
Why are you so stubborn?
Mr. Shangguan, do you know?
Some media said that
the victims got what they deserve,
that if they were not greedy,
they wouldn’t have fallen for the trap.
Zhang was deceived
because she wanted to buy meds
for her mom.
Is it wrong to be poor?
The scammers deliberately
chose the poor, young interns,
because they knew those people
value their future more than the others.
They’ll do their best
to pay off the debt.
They were already deceived.
And they also have to be accused
by the public?
Mr. Shangguan.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Something came up to me.
What is it?
When I was in graduate school,
I had four part-time jobs a week
to support my family.
There used to be a grocery market
behind the house I rent.
I used to study all night till 4 AM,
and I’d hear truck driving out, warning,
“Beware! I’m backing up.
Beware! I’m backing up.”
Mr. Shangguan.
I’ve always wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
Why were you willing to
recommend me to Daren Law Firm
as an intern?
At that time...
Miss Cong.
We’re so sorry.
We’re late.
They said that they trust you.
And we want to file a joinder.
Thank you so much for
coming to see us tonight.
Thanks for your trust.
But now I need you to tell us
every detail of your case,
as detailed as possible.
Tell us every detail accurately.
The thing is this.
That day,
I was playing video games in my dorm.
And my friend rushed in.
He told me that
he lost his mobile phone
and his ID card.
Sandman Space
Let’s call it a day.
Thank you.
Let’s keep in touch.
Thank you, Mr. Shangguan.
Thank you, Miss Cong.
Thank you.
Be careful on your way home.
Okay.
Bye.
It’s unexpected that they all signed it.
It’s half past 9 now.
Xiong Jingjing
Let me give you a ride home.
Excuse me.
Let me answer this call.
Sure.
Hello.
Has Mr. Shangguan had lunch?
How about any snacks?
His stomach has just recovered a bit.
He needs to have small meals frequently.
Xiong Jingjing.
I’m not your pigeon.
Relaying messages for you isn’t my job.
Why don’t you just call him yourself?
Because you said that
I shouldn’t be too annoying.
So you annoy me instead.
Are we good friends?
Can you help me buy some porridge
for Mr. Shangguan?
No, I won’t.
Fine.
Then I’ll call your doctor boyfriend.
Stop bluffing.
13564628...
Where did you get that from?
Are you buying or not?
Fine.
Thank you, Miss Cong.
You’re the best.
Mr. Shangguan.
Can you wait for me a bit longer?
Don’t drink too much coffee.
It’s not good to your stomach.
Have some porridge.
Your scarf is stained.
It’s fine.
I’ll take the coffee.
Let me give you a ride home.
No, thank you.
The taxi I called has arrived.
Oh.
Mr. Shangguan.
May I take a day off tomorrow?
You’ve been working
really hard recently.
Take a day off.
Thank you.
Please hold on.
The subscriber you dialed is busy now.
Hello.
I was just about to call you.
How’s Wen Shaoqing doing?
He took some pills and went to bed.
He’s fine.
Don’t worry.
Great.
Thank you so much.
Well.
Can you give Zhou Chengcheng a call?
What happened to her?
Nothing.
She didn’t come back
to her restaurant tonight.
I’m worried about her safety.
I’ll hang up now.
I am hesitant. So what?
That was ten years of my time,
not your past,
nor the past of anyone else.
Don’t I have my right to be hesitant?
Who are you to me?
Husband
Hello.
What?
You miss me?
Yes.
I miss you.
Where are you?
I’m on my way home.
What’s up?
You didn’t argue with Wen Rang, did you?
Argue?
Why should I argue with him?
I’m not his girlfriend.
He just called me.
He said he’s worried about you.
Maybe he said that merely to be humane.
I’m home.
I’ll hang up now.
Bye.
However late it is,
I’ll come home and make soup for you.
Is that okay with you?
Chicken soup?
Chicken soup it is then.
Boss.
Have some water.
As the saying goes,
the owl doesn’t come into one’s house
for no reason.
I finally have a day off.
You don’t hide from me.
Instead, you knock on my door.
There’s something fishy.
You got me wrong.
The colleagues say you’re built of iron.
It’s rare that you’re sick.
So I’m sent here to solace you.
This is our gift to you.
Why does this look familiar?
This was your gift to me.
So you give back what I gave you
when I’m ill?
What’s wrong with you?
I have to be honest.
Today, we had a dissertation seminar.
When you were not around,
we recommended you as the participant.
I’m just here to inform you.
We don’t punish someone who confesses.
I’ll get the door.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Boss.
You have a package.
I’ll open it for you.
Okay.
The stench of romance.
You give my cousin luxury products.
But you gave me natural science stuff.
You’re so miserly.
What is it?
The scarf you’ll give my cousin.
Scarf?
I didn’t buy scarf for her.
Boss.
I don’t have a scarf as well.
Thank you.
Shangguan Yi.
Who is this person?
The brother of Shangguan Wan’er.
New champion of Arena of Valor?
Open the door.
Wen Shaoqing.
Boss.
I suddenly...
I suddenly want to study.
I’ll go read books in your study.
Open the door.
It’s so hot.
Listen.
I’m sure the soup is as good as yours.
It’s been stewed all night.
I banged on the grocery store’s door
for half an hour last night
to wake up the store owner.
So he could sell me a Luhua chicken.
When did you come home?
Around 11 or 12 in the evening.
What?
Mr. Shangguan had you
work overtime with him?
I forced him to work overtime.
Hurry up.
Try the soup.
Come on.
I don’t want to drink it.
Are you still ill?
You have no appetite?
Mr. Shangguan
sent his gift to the wrong address.
I signed it for you.
It’s the scarf.
Put it aside for now.
The soup will be less palatable
when it’s cold.
Why would he give you a scarf?
I stained mine when
I bought him porridge last night.
He bought me a new one instead.
You bought him porridge?
Yes.
What’s wrong with that?
Why porridge?
Yes.
His stomach hasn’t fully recovered.
So he has to drink porridge.
I can’t buy barbeque for him.
It’s fine if you buy him
plain noodles or gastric powder.
But you can’t buy porridge for him.
What’s wrong with you?
If you don’t like the fact
that he bought me a scarf,
I can return it.
But I’ve been cooking this soup
all night.
You can’t just decline it
without a reason.
Why are you being so mean?
Is it because of the gift,
or the porridge?
Or are you angry
that I often bail on you?
I had a hard time learning
to write the character, heart, as a kid.
In a character
with “heart” at the bottom,
make it shorter
and a little slant.
But I just couldn’t do it,
to make it shorter and tilt right,
I couldn’t write the character perfectly
because I cared too much about it.
Isn’t it the same with romance?
The one who falls in love first
is always at disadvantage.
You don’t trust me at all.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪