[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 18]
Although I'm
the master of Artefact Forging Sect,
I can't decide for the entire Sect.
Whether we fight or surrender,
you decide.
Those who want to surrender,
stay where you are.
Those who'd fight till the end,
please step forward.
Disciples who want to surrender
may leave.
Others are forbidden to stop them.
And if you won't surrender, let's fight!
I'm the master of the Sect,
but I don't have what it takes
to protect all of you.
Fortunately, Qin Lie is one of us.
He's extremely talented.
He has lighted 11 Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Besides being brave and smart,
he has the help from the strong one.
I hereby announce
that I, Ying Xing Ran,
will hand over the position of master
to Qin Lie.
-We'll never surrender!
I'm sorry, everyone.
I kept you waited.
It takes time to put the clothes on.
Greetings, Master Xie.
Skip the formalities. Hey, you.
What have you been eating in secret?
It's all thanks to you.
The master of Eight Extremes Temple
Sanctuary personally joins the war.
It's worth the wait.
My, my. Song.
I love talking to you the most.
So?
Are the Artefact Forging guys
defeated?
They're still alive
but they won't surrender.
Why aren't we attacking
and eliminating them yet?
Never mind.
Let's wait till tomorrow morning.
It's okay.
Just attack.
We wait.
We attack.
Fine.
Your life is miserable enough
after losing your wife.
I'll let you make the call this time.
Your life is miserable too
as you have lost your daughter.
Fine.
Let's wait.
He sure knows
when to step down.
Yeah, what a cunning old man.
Qin Lie,
those who would fight are waiting.
Do you dare take up the position
and be the master?
As a newly joined disciple,
I'm surprised to become the master
all of a sudden.
Cut the crap, kid.
Come on, do you dare or do you not?
But if you dare say no...
There's no need to threaten me.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Guys,
I'll be the master for now.
After the problem is resolved,
anyone
can take this seat.
That is a dream position to many people.
Stop pretending.
Du Shao Yang,
becoming the master
of Artefact Forging Sect
doesn't mean one has reached
the highest and furthest place.
You're right, Master.
Looks like we can't be friends
no matter what.
Who was it that told me
that he'll never be my friend?
If you're going to catch up,
move aside!
Dawn is coming soon, Master.
Please decide what we will do.
Blood Progenitor.
The Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Spiritual Lines Pillars?
Yes.
It has been binding me for a millennium.
With its great power,
of course it can bind others too.
Since you've comprehended all Pillars,
you'll be able to do that.
You want me
to create a binding formation
using the 12 Pillars?
Exactly.
But you're unable to do that yet.
In order to create
an ancient formation with the Pillars,
one needs to at least achieve
Fragmentation Realm
before he can get started.
But you're a useless junk.
Is there anything else we can do?
Yes.
Fight with full force.
Fight with full force?
You're scared?
I'd rather fight hard using wisdom
than die because of my stupidity.
Everyone, if we're going to fight,
we need a plan.
If we're meant to die on the battlefield,
let's make our death worth it.
I have an idea.
Tell me the ingredients to make
Terminator Profound Bomb.
I need one day.
Please buy me the time.
Where's Song Ting Yu?
She left.
Left?
Why would she stay?
To be your hostage?
You captured Song Ting Yu
to help her escape?
Yes.
And it's your and Song Ting Yu's plan
to make me the master?
Yes. So?
Ying Xing Ran will surrender.
Going against him
will make you a traitor.
And that gives everyone in the world
the reasons to kill you.
It's better if you're the master.
That was my idea.
Women,
can you tell me your plan
to my face next time?
We've had the plan
for negotiation,
but you men were scheming against us.
That's enough!
It's ridiculous to fight about genders
when the sect is facing a war.
Master Qin,
I heard that in order to buy
Master Mo a day,
you've sent someone to Song Yu,
pretending that we're trying our best
to persuade everyone
to submit to Profound Heaven Alliance.
One day is a short time.
And the Sect's future is at stake.
Since you're busy, Master Qin,
why don't you go and handle
the sect's affairs first?
Shao Yang should stay here.
He and I need to talk.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt a woman.
The resentment between men
shouldn't involve their families.
Don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
Furthermore,
I trust Saintess Xie.
I know that you're unhappy.
But we were comrades once,
and we're now facing the same enemy.
We still fight alongside each other.
I'll take a look out there.
What else do you want to say to me?
Words of apology?
Why should I apologize?
Because I let another man
leads my own man temporarily?
Shao Yang,
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
I'm going out.
You guys work for a strategy inside,
while I'll make a plan outside.
What do you plan to do?
Don't ask me.
You can't help.
Yes, you're right.
I can't be of any help.
Shao Yang,
we've gone through a lot together.
You know the pain of losing your family.
But you're being sarcastic to me
over some disappointment?
I'm sorry, Si Qi.
I know you're not leaving
so that you can make a plan,
but because your father is here.
You're afraid that he'll find this out
and I'll be implicated.
You're imagining things.
I'm really going out
to see what I can do to help.
Will we
meet again?
Maybe we will.
It'll be dawn soon.
If both of us survive the night,
can we still see each other?
Maybe we can.
Why the uncertain answer?
Stop asking.
I'll be leaving
as soon as I'm done here.
Does that mean
we'll never meet again?
If we're still alive after tonight,
let's meet again.
Go.
Go now.
He's left.
Are you sure
the momentary happiness
worth
the pain of parting?
You're not coming with me?
I want to stay and protect Qin Lie.
So, you do like him.
This is the Profound Heaven Badge.
It'll take you to my father.
Stay alive. See you.
Be careful not to bump into your father.
Brother,
I can sneak into the Sect
and save Ting Yu.
Don't worry about her.
I'm not.
But I am.
If she can't even protect herself
and accomplish the mission
entrusted to her,
then she's not worthy of my daughter.
I'm worried about Xie Yi.
He's an unpredictable lunatic.
Greetings, Master Xie.
The Sect sent someone to talk to Song Yu.
They're asking for another day
to persuade their disciples.
Song Yu has agreed to that.
Song really cares about his reputation.
He'd say yes when someone begs him.
What an idiot.
What should we do, Master?
You have two hours.
After that,
I'll attack personally.
Terminator Profound Bomb
is a good stuff
from the Heavenly Calamity Continent.
It's very powerful.
I've never seen one.
When they're ready to be used,
you'll get to see it.
Promise?
Yes.
You're not wearing your armour.
What's the point of wearing it at home?
Furthermore, even without it,
I can still protect my home.
It doesn't matter if you fail.
The world is large.
Be it in the clouds or on the cliff,
where there are you, there is home.
However, we have our responsibilities.
I wonder
when can we let go of the burden
and travel the Spirit Realm happily.
The rumoured land
with Central Golden Holy Light
where the Holy Lights of Supreme Lords
are shining down.
When can we see that?
As long as both of us are alive,
there's no rush.
Aren't you going on patrol?
The Sect
is well guarded by Bloody Spear Guard.
We're counting on you to win the war.
I'll guard you.
Rong'er,
I'm hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Braised meat.
Okay, I'll make braised meat.
We can have meat after the war.
Okay.
[Ling Ye Palace]
Stay there.
Tang Si Qi wishes to meet Master Song.
Jing Xuan?
It's me, Uncle Song.
Your father is unpredictable.
And you're unruly since young.
Regarding you faking your death,
whether it's your father's order
or your own idea,
it doesn't surprise me.
You've misunderstood, Uncle.
It's just because
I yearned for the freedom of an armourer.
My father didn't give that order.
Stand up and talk.
Yes, Uncle.
Is this from Ting Yu?
Yes.
She's still in the Sect,
carrying out the mission you gave her
to bring Qin Lie here to you.
And why are you here?
I heard that you and my father
plan to attack the Sect.
Ting Yu and I dare not stop you.
But I'm worried.
About what?
Seven hundred years ago,
the abbot has warned us
not to attack the Sect.
That is a 700-year-old story.
Chilan Continent
was having a civil war back then.
A high-ranking abbot
stopped the human race
from killing each other
with his own power.
All humans feared and respected him.
Before he left, he said that
no matter what happened
the Artefact Forging Sect
shall not be touched.
Then, do you know
why he protected the Sect?
He didn't say anything about that.
He didn't say the reason,
but what about the consequence?
There's no consequence?
The abbot's words
must have another meaning.
Aren't you worried about the consequences?
Before I allowed the five great sects
to attack the Sect,
the abbot's words came to my mind.
And I tried to contact him using
like our predecessors did,
but to no avail.
Maybe
it was just something he blurted out.
He might have forgotten
about Chilan Continent.
Why would an abbot blurt something out?
Please try again, Uncle.
Since it didn't work,
I won't try again.
Let me try.
You do love
the Sect very much, huh?
I'm just worried
that the consequence is unbearable.
The Saintess of Eight Extremes
Temple Sanctuary is a smart girl.
I don't think
it's as simple as this.
I don't want the people to suffer anymore.
Even if hope is faint,
I'll still do my best and give it a try.
Please be like that too, Uncle.
Okay.
You may try.
But until you get in touch with the abbot,
I won't stop the attack.
Thank you, Uncle.
Does your father know
that you're still alive?
That depends on you.
The Artefact Forging Sect
is on the verge of destruction.
Please come forth, Abbot.
Song Ting Yu?
Didn't you escape?
This is not the time to argue.
Elder Mo Hai might be in danger.
Why?
My father will give you another day
as promised.
But Xie Yi is a lunatic.
He won't wait any longer,
let alone one whole day.
He'll attack before my father does.
What will he do?
Of all the people in the Sect,
he fears only Elder Mo Hai.
If he's making a move,
Elder Mo Hai will be the target.
Commander Feng is with him.
That's why Zhan Tian Yi will come.
He's the only one who matches Feng Rong.
I can't show myself.
You're their only hope.
Okay, I'll go now.
Rong'er!
Master Mo Hai.
What a loyal and loving wife you have.
You two really make a perfect match.
Don't mind me.
Focus on forging!
Fine, then.
A Manifestation Realm achiever?
I'll settle you first, kid.
Mo Hai,
since you won't listen to me,
don't blame me, then.
Zhan Tian Yi,
let her go
and take the Terminator Profound Bomb,
or get bombed into pieces!
Fine.
Okay!
Take it.
The Terminator Profound Bomb.
What a fancy finding.
Rong'er.
Mo Hai.
In the future,
take good care of yourself.
Don't be too obsessed with forging.
Don't forget to eat.
Also,
remember to cultivate.
Otherwise,
you'll grow old.
Anything unusual?
No.
Here I am!
Xie Yi?
Xie Yi's here.
The lunatic has finally come.
Qin Lie.
Wait for me.
You broke your promise, Xie Yi!
I'm not here to talk,
but to kill.
Formation!
Palm of Great God!
Again!
Essence of Frost!
Not bad, kid.
You've got skills.
Let's see how long you can hold on.
Master Lang Xie,
get him to Spiritual Lines Hall.
You want to bind him
with the Pillars' formation?
But the Blood Progenitor said you can't.
I have no choice,
but to go all out!
Okay.
If I'm going to die either way,
let's give it a go!
If I manage to
create the binding formation
with the 12 Pillars,
you must leave the plaza at once.
Retreat to the plaza!
Yes, sir!
Ouch, it hurts.
Don't go.
Fine, run faster.
I'm catching up.
Hurry up, Qin Lie!
Help me, Grandpa.
So, these are the Spiritual Lines Pillars?
What's he doing?
Netherworld's demon aura?
Hold your breath and leave the plaza.
Qin Lie, this is a nether passageway.
Opening it up
and releasing the Dark Nether Race
will endanger the Chilan human race.
Leave now!
I'm at my limit.
-Let's go.
Hurry.
Why is there Netherworld demon aura here?
Retreat.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Leave me. Run!
Come on.
Let's go.
Qin Lie!
Flowing Cloud Rainbow Butterfly.
Yu Shi!
Qin Lie, take the Demon Cleansing Pill!
Demon aura from Netherworld?
Why is the demon aura here?
Use Demon Cleansing Pill
to purify it now.
What's happening out there?
Why is there demon aura?
Xie Yi attacked us.
Qin Lie wanted to fight him using
the 12 Pillars formation.
But who knew, under the Hall
was a nether passageway.
As it opened,
the demon aura and
countless nether beasts roared up.
What?
There's a nether passageway
under the Spiritual Lines Hall?
So, the 12 Pillars were actually
used to seal off the nether passageway.
How is everyone doing?
I already asked them to retreat,
and they're given Demon Cleansing Pills.
With Demon Cleansing Pills
made from Demon Purifying Grass,
our disciples are fine for now.
But Purple Mist Sea is very far from here.
Without anyone guarding there
or Demon Purifying Grass,
and there's only that many Pills we have,
I'm afraid that
the areas around here
will be tarnished
by demon aura in a few days.
The Dark Nether Race's troop
may invade us.
The five great sects,
Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple Sanctuary,
you caused this calamity.
If I'm lucky enough to survive this,
I'll never for give you all!
Qin Lie? It's him again!
Why did he remove
the Pillars all of a sudden?
It's all his fault.
Where's Qin Lie now?
The Hall went into chaos.
Qin Lie and Saintess Song
as well as Ling Yu Shi
dropped into the nether passageway
and went missing.
There's a total of
12 Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Since establishment,
Qin Lie's the only one
who could comprehend all of them.
If he died just like that...
So what if he dies?
He caused all the troubles.
I won't be satisfied
no matter how many times he dies.
Knock it off!
Everything Qin Lie did
was for the sake of our sect.
No wonder the abbot warned everyone
not to attack the Sect 700 years ago.
It turned out that he knew
the Spiritual Lines Hall
was sealing the nether passageway off.
Why didn't I think of that?
Even if you did,
who would believe you?
So, are we going to fight or not now?
We need the master's order.
Qin Lie...
Qin Lie brought the disaster upon us.
Will he have the nerve to be the master?
Please give us order, Master.
Where are Elder Mo and Commander Feng?
Feng Rong...
It was Zhan Tian Yi.
I'll kill him!
No need.
He's being bombed into pieces.
And the five great sects' men
have all absorbed the demon aura.
They're having a hard time themselves.