[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 17]
You are the saintess of the
Eight Extremes Temple,
and they're your subordinates.
How could you kill them so happily?
Didn't you kill Di Shi Jiu, too?
But that was to save you.
You women are so annoying.
Still bickering at a time like this.
She started it.
Things aren't looking too good.
At this rate,
you'll be exposed as the saintess.
Then
let's see how you will protect
your little boyfriend.
We'll discuss strategy later.
Meet me by the Blood Pool.
Okay.
Weren't you leaving?
Why are you back?
I saw the Five Great Sect's
messenger spirit bird on the way
and felt something was amiss,
so I came back.
Little did I expect
things would become like this.
If this ruckus goes on,
our fathers might join the fray
and draw swords against each other.
The Artefact Forging Sect will be doomed.
No.
The Artefact Forging Sect
is my second home.
In my heart,
the sect is far more important than
the Eight Extremes Temple.
I won't allow anyone to desecrate
the sect.
The sect may not be the most
agreeable bunch,
but they're peaceful.
Besides, Master Mo Hai
has treated me kindly.
I don't want bad things to happen
to the sect.
Master, we've dealt with the
Shadow Tower assassin accordingly.
Di Shi Jiu has been
brought to justice, too.
Good.
My lord,
leave this matter to me.
The Five Great Sects have always
stayed in their respective domains
and lived in harmony.
Now that Yuan Tian Ya's son is dead,
the five sects may seek
recompense from the Artefact Forging Sect.
I think
they're only using you as an excuse.
Their real target is the
Artefact Forging Sect.
No need to tell me.
I know I'm an excuse for them.
Commander Feng once told me,
700 years ago,
A powerful abbot
warned the leaders
of the Chilan Continent
not to cross the Artefact Forging Sect.
Hence, they never dared to transgress.
What makes the Artefact Forging Fact
so special?
Nobody knows.
It's not just recently
that the Five Great Sects
set their sights
on the Artefact Forging Sect.
But why do they strike now,
of all times?
700 years have passed,
but that abbot still has yet to show up.
It's bound to give somebody ideas.
The Five Great Sects is divided
into two factions.
Without the Profound Heaven Alliance
and the Eight Extremes Temple's approval,
who'd dare unleash such a bloodbath?
I'm going to ask outright.
Are you two spies?
Tang Si Qi definitely isn't.
As for Saintess Song,
I can't be too sure.
If I were a spy,
I could've whipped out
the Profound Heaven Seal,
and none of you could stop me.
The Artefact Forging Sect may have
the Bloody Spear
and generations worth of magical items.
But if the Five Great Sects team up
and fight us head-on,
we may very well perish.
Since the Five Great Sects
have the guts to attack,
they must've come prepared.
Armoury City,
Firetop Mountain and other escape routes
have probably been sealed off.
We can't fight, we can't escape.
What should we do?
If we can't fight,
we'll settle for a truce.
We'll lure the Five Great Sects'
kingpins over,
and use them as bargaining chips.
But we can't let Ying Xing Ran go.
Everyone knows
the Master is shifty and corrupt.
So I say we let the Chief Elder
negotiate the deal.
The Chief Elder is a coward.
He'll give the leaders
of the Five Great Sects
a sense of security.
This plan couldn't be easier.
Du Shao Yang and Qin Lie are so smart.
Nothing can go wrong.
As long as they follow the plan...
They won't.
Why not?
Because they're delinquents.
At least
Qin Lie isn't.
I don't believe you.
How about a bet, then?
Fine, I'll bet.
One stone coin, what do you say?
Alright. I'll wager for her, too.
I have money.
Money's beside the point.
I'll win for sure.
An armistice?
Are you sure?
We may as well surrender.
What do you propose?
What do you think?
Kill them all.
Forget about their plans.
Listen to them
or not listen to them, who cares?
Ying Xing Ran, we,
the Five Great Sects stand before you.
We have no time to chit-chat.
You have one hour
to submit the surrender document,
or else
the Artefact Forging Sect gets decimated.
Kill them! Kill them!
Master,
the Five Great Sects have gathered
at our doorstep.
The master of Cloud Sky Mountain,
Wu Tuo, has spoken.
They're awaiting a written surrender.
We have an hour to comply.
He's a jinx. A jinx!
Master, we can't let the sect's
thousands of years of accomplishments
go down the drain
just because of Qin Bing.
11 Spiritual Lines Pillars.
In the history of the sect,
no one was able to
master so many Spiritual Lines Pillars.
Qin Bing is the future
of the Artefact Forging Sect.
If I simply give him over,
how can I face
our ancestors?
He may be a genius,
but not a blessed genius.
The heavens disdain his talent.
The gods will his death.
Master, cut him off
before it's too late!
Call him a blessed genius
or a cursed genius,
Qin Bing's fate is sealed.
Since it's the will of heaven,
Qin Bing's life or death
isn't up to us.
Master,
hand Qin Bing over.
Qin Bing,
you're only one life, after all.
The sect must come first.
At this point,
I have no choice but to...
Master,
how can you be so cruel?
Lang Xie,
seize Qing Bin.
As you wish.
We did it.
Shao Yang said they did it.
I told you they'd listen to us.
You speak too soon.
It's not over yet.
That's it. We're going in.
Pass the order.
Attack the Artefact Forging Sect!
Masters of the Five Great Sects,
you've come a long way.
Apologies for the lack of hospitality.
What a crowd.
Is there a wedding?
There sure isn't one in our sect.
Not weddings,
but funerals.
Are you here to surrender?
Not a surrender.
An armistice.
If you want to beg for mercy,
just say so.
They have brains, or rather,
backbone.
But today,
we have your city surrounded.
On what grounds do you demand
an armistice?
We're a long-standing sect.
And with that abbot's warning
700 years ago,
I must admit we've grown prideful
and careless.
Your presence here today
is indeed a rude awakening for us.
I apologise for any disrespect.
Why don't we sit down and talk?
Why cross swords?
We're all Chilan people, after all.
We should unite.
That's correct.
Trying to lord it over us
with a 700-year-old story?
Very smart.
Too bad we're not buying it.
If you defeat us,
we'll sit down and talk.
If you lose,
you'll kneel before us.
You act barbarously, raising your army
to intimidate us.
I admit, we're no match for you.
But does that mean we must
incinerate the jade with the rocks?
If we call a truce,
you'll get what you want.
If we don't,
you'll get nothing.
Master Mo Hai,
we should be sincere during peace talks.
We can have backbone,
but we can't be arrogant.
That is true, Chief Elder.
At first, it was only a tiff
with the Palace of Hell.
Who knew everyone would join the fray?
Isn't it because
you want to destroy our sect,
steal our magical items
and enslave our armourers
to your cause?
Nonsense.
Let's not pretend anymore.
Armourers require morale.
If you enslave them and take away
their freedom,
their morale will be gone.
Without morale, what can they produce?
You'll end up with a bunch of useless men.
Too expensive to be killed,
too worthless to be kept.
Wouldn't that be a dilemma?
Master Yuan,
this whole thing started with
the Palace of Hell.
Say something.
Negotiate?
Or fight?
How do you intend to talk?
Go inside, sit down
and negotiate calmly.
Why don't Ying Xing Ran
come out himself?
We may be sincere in our negotiation,
but we can't let our guard down, can we?
I don't trust Ying Xing Ran.
Even less so Mo Hai.
Exactly.
What do you say, Chief Elder?
We're sincere about this.
You won't let your guard down,
neither will we.
Send the Assistant Master instead.
At this time,
according to our plan,
Mo Hai and Chief Elder
should have engaged the Five Great Sects.
The five masters aren't easily fooled.
But for Master Mo Hai,
luring five Assistant Masters
to become hostages
should be a cinch.
We don't want the Assistant Masters.
We want the Masters.
Mo Hai, what are you up to?
Chief Elder,
I was thinking,
this negotiation concerns the fates
of both parties
for at least the next hundred years.
It's a monumental decision.
Can five Assistant Masters
make the call?
Yes.
They will mediate between us.
In that case,
how long will it take to reach
an understanding?
Three days? Five days?
Three months? Five months?
Tell you what,
since the Chief Elder
is on speaking terms
with the Five Great Sects,
he will choose a trustworthy candidate
to participate in the talks.
Master Yu.
Okay. Then Master Yu
will come in
on the Five Great Sects' behalf
and decide on the power-split
for the next hundred years.
Hold on.
Why him?
Why not me?
This is a big matter
concerning everyone's interests
for hundreds of years to come.
How can you alone decide?
Exactly.
If you go in and negotiate,
and claim all the advantages,
what will be left for us?
At the end,
you're just scared I'll short-change you.
You mean
you won't?
We've all been alive
for over a thousand years.
We're no fools.
If it were me,
I'd do what's best for my faction, too.
That's right.
If you're going,
-we're going.
-After you.
Qin Bing, why are you here?
Who let you out?
Qin Lie!
Master Yuan, you got the wrong guy.
He's Qin Bing.
I get it.
You're both Qin Lie and Qin Bing!
Qin Lie?
The man who killed Master Du
of Xingyun Pavilion?
How could you give him refuge?
I...
What are you waiting for?
Blood Progenitor.
What's going on here?
I knew it. An ambush.
Are you Qin Bing or Qin Lie?
Qin Lie.
You killed the master of Xingyun Pavilion?
Du Hai Tian set up the Ling family
during the battle of Purple Mist Sea.
No one sought justice.
I killed Du Hai Tian to avenge
the Ling family,
yet became every faction's fugitive.
Is there justice in Chilan Continent?
Du Shao Yang, tell us.
Was the Ling family massacre
a set-up by your father?
If Qin Lie is slandering him,
we'll punish him accordingly.
Alright. We'll come back to it later.
Qin Lie,
who is this man?
And what are you plotting?
There is no plot.
I was outnumbered,
so I used my wits
to capture the five masters
in order to force a retreat.
Master,
me and Qin Bing...
I mean Qin Lie,
planned this.
If anyone were to be blamed,
let it be me.
I was part of it, too.
I should take responsibility, too.
And us.
Why didn't you discuss with us
instead of feigning armistice?
There was no time.
We were worried we might not
convince you and Chief Elder.
That's why we resorted to this.
You people
have committed treason, then?
Not treason,
but protecting the lives
of the Five Great Sects
by unconventional means.
Qin Lie,
you said you could
use the power
of the Spiritual Lines Pillars
to overmaster the Five Great Sects.
We trusted you.
But you never mentioned this man.
May I ask who you are?
The spiritual energy emanating
from your body
tells me you're a Bloody Spear.
What is the Bloody Spear?
They call themselves a faction?
Kid,
don't you point at me.
I'm your ancestor, the Blood Ancestor.
Blood Ancestor?
That's right.
They call me the Blood Progenitor.
10,000 years ago,
I was the master of the Blood Fiend Sect
that ruled Heaven Calamity Continent.
All the Blood Fiend Spirit Arts
were created by me.
If I'm not mistaken,
your so-called Bloody Spear
is an illegitimate offshoot
founded by a heretic
of the Blood Fiend Sect.
Based on seniority,
shouldn't you address me as your superior?
But
why are you trapped
in the Spiritual Lines Pillar?
1,000 years ago,
the Blood Progenitor was betrayed
and banished inside
the Spiritual Lines Pillar.
The 12 Spiritual Lines Pillar
fell into the hands
of the Heavenly Armament Sect,
and was later stolen by a defector,
who brought it to Chilan Continent
and founded the Artefact Forging Sect.
When I tapped into the pillars,
I felt the Blood Progenitor's presence
and struck a deal with him.
You want to get out?
Name your terms.
Fend off my enemies,
and I'll release you.
You said you were betrayed.
By whom?
It happened 1,000 years ago.
Even if I tell you, would you know
who he is?
By the way,
kid,
by the tone of your voice,
it sounded as if you were going
to punish Qin Lie?
If anyone lays a finger on him,
I'll kill him.
Qin Lie,
you created this mess.
How do you intend to clean it up?
That depends
on the Five Great Masters.
Master.
What is it again?
It's...
I know.
Qin Bing.
Yi Yuan,
his real name is Qin Lie.
I don't care.
Just spare my father.
You told him everything?
Get up.
Not until you promise me.
If they belay the siege,
I won't hurt them.
Otherwise,
I can only promise
to spare your father's life.
But first,
I need to borrow his fingerprint.
I'll do it instead.
Is that okay?
Greetings, Masters.
Qin Lie.
Where's Yu Shi?
What have you done to her?
She's alive and well.
Recall your troops.
And our master
will have the Eight Extremes Temple
and Profound Heaven Alliance
redress the scales.
You think we would attack Firetop Mountain
without their approval?
I guessed as much.
Then I'd like to invite Master Song
of the Profound Heaven Alliance
and Master Xie
of the Eight Extremes Temple
to delegate with us,
so that you may recall your troops.
Dream on!
Shao Yang.
He's tough.
Too bad he's a scoundrel.
Lord Lang Xie,
free Jiu Liu Yu and Yu Dai.
Let them show their people
their fingers.
If they don't retreat, next time,
it'll be their heads.
Why them?
Yi Yuan is Master Yu's son.
He didn't betray the sect.
I promised him
I'll spare his father's life.
As for Jiu Liu Yu,
she's outlived her time.
You sound so righteous.
At the end, it's because that old granny
was your good friend's master.
What if she was?
If you were my friend's master,
I'd let you off, too.
This is...
Those fiends.
Let's get them!
-Get them!
No.
Don't.
They're still inside.
The armistice fell through.
What happened? What went wrong?
Qin Lie and Du Shao Yang got too ambitious
and asked for the Masters instead
of the Assistant Masters.
They even ordered their fingers cut off
and forced them to draw back.
They actually went against our plan.
Men who don't listen to orders
are real men.
Your man...
Your men gave the orders,
my man carried it out.
Can you get your head together?
The Profound Heaven Alliance
and the Eight Extremes Temple
could strike any moment.
Then we'll see how you and your man die.
What's so bad about dying?
Dying with the man you love
is nothing to be afraid of.
You dying in your lover's arms
is one thing.
But
if you expect the entire sect
and myself to go down with you,
think again.
What do you propose, then?
You're the genius here. You tell me.
I may be good at fighting,
but when it comes to strategy,
you're better.
You come up with the plan.
Make Qin Lie the master
of the Artefact Forging Sect.
Qin Lie is too headstrong.
If this carries on,
both parties will perish.
Only by making him the sect master
will his thinking change
to fit his new role
and responsibilities.
He'll think of the greater good
instead of being impulsive.
Only then will the situation be remedied.
Du Shao Yang,
some nerve you have!
Si Qi.
Cut it out.
Everyone's looking. Let go.
Get it out of your system.
Then we can focus on the real issue.
You've lost.
Take it.
You girls
were betting on me?
So, did you win?
Of course.
Extra dinner tonight.
Great.
The Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple
have deployed.
By order of the Profound Heaven
Alliance's Master
[Zhan Tian Yi, Song Si Yuan]
and the Eight Extremes Temple's Master,
we beseech you, Ying Xing Ran,
to release
the three masters and surrender
by daybreak.
If you disobey,
you will be killed.
Are you happy now?
How would I know they'd arrive so soon?
We still have three masters.
To our father,
their lives are worth nothing.
What about Saintess Song's life?
Qin Lie,
what are you planning to do?
You could've stayed out of this,
yet you came back.
You said you'd take me to your father.
This unholy battle
wouldn't have happened
without his consent.
What is your motive?
I did lie to you.
The Five Great Sects was primed
for an assault.
When I saw the messenger spirit bird,
I knew they'd strike.
I didn't want you to die,
so I tried to persuade you to leave.
Why?
You fell in love with me?
You're shameless.
If you don't want to tell me, fine.
You're full of lies anyway.
I wouldn't believe anything you say.
When you tried to help
the Artefact Forging Sect,
I kept my peace.
But things are different now.
Do you think I should release you
and have another enemy,
or use you as hostage
to force back the
Profound Heaven Alliance?
Xie Jing Xuan!
I've cut off ties with the Eight Extremes,
you guys know that.
I've been meaning to take her
as hostage.
Go now.
Before Ying Xing Ruan
and those spineless oafs
surrender our sect on a silver platter.
I believe her.
Go.
Let's go.
Wait.
Qin Lie, back in Qisha Valley,
my master told me
in the ranks of the Artefact Forging Sect,
Master Mo Hai is the most respected.
What does that mean?
Those who follow Master Mo Hai
all value freedom.
Which means they'd rather take up arms
than to submit.
Why haven't you freed her?
You're smarter than you look.
You saw right through it.
Although we've been fighting for decades,
we were still childhood friends.
Not even Shao Yang saw through me,
but you did.
Since you wanted to play,
I played along.
I only resorted to such tactics
so they'd leave.
How could I let you fight
among yourselves?
When did those two
become so ballsy?
Striking me out of the blue.
You're smart.
Very smart.
If Qin Lie becomes the master,
the sect will protect him.
I did it out of personal interest,
but also for the greater good.
Besides,
you two agreed to it.
So where should we start?
Ying Xing Ran and Cheng Ping, naturally.
So it's my time to shine?
Why are you two
back this late?
On our way back,
we saw the Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple
in the sky, demanding a surrender.
So we went to a quiet place
to recalibrate calmly.
Have you come up with a plan?
That depends on whether you wish
to fight or yield.
At this time,
you have the gall to push
the responsibility to Master?
This is all your fault.
It's no secret that the Five Great Sects
have been eyeing our sect.
I'm only an excuse to initiate war.
Do you really think
killing me would make them retreat?
If it weren't for our retaliation plan,
this sect would've long
become their back garden.
What's there to die
for the sake of the sect?
Are you scared of dying?
And you're not?
You'd be nowhere
without the Blood Progenitor,
what with your half-baked cultivation...
Chief Elder,
on the grounds of your seniority,
I won't argue with you.
But don't think my patience is infinite.
Qin Lie!
I'm obligated to our ancestors
to ensure this sect's survival.
I've always been impartial.
When you lit up the
11 Spiritual Lines Pillars,
I saw you as a rare talent.
That is why I've tolerated
your shenanigans.
But today,
you've overstepped your bounds!
Master,
I don't know what boundaries are.
All I know is,
Xingyun Pavilion killed Ling Borough.
I sought justice,
but was unjustly demonised.
The Five Great Sects declared war
against this sect
for immoral reasons.
Against such injustice,
one either dies a hero
or lives as a coward.
You're the one who's
indecisive and weak...
Insolence!
Take Qin Lie away.
What's the matter?
Are all of you going to disobey me?
May I ask,
do you mean to surrender
by seizing Qin Lie?
I'm only surrendering
because I have no choice.
It's for the good of the sect.
Can you really speak for the entire sect?
Can you?
Well said!
Chief Elder,
can you speak for the sect?
Master Mo Hai, can you?
I can't.
Since no one can speak for the sect,
why not let all the disciples speak
for themselves?
Mo Hai.
This is an outrage.
It's an outrage indeed.
Such blatant coercion.
Is there no respect for rules
in this sect?
Master, this is important.
You should be trying to figure out
a solution.
Master, you finally got fired up?
Master, you ought to be fired up.
To think a small fry like Qin Lie
would disrespect you.
How are you supposed to secure
your seat as the sect master?
Forget about the seat.
Master, at this stage,
things have gotten beyond control.
If the ruckus continues,
there will be chaos inside and out.
As the sect master,
you won't escape blame.
Why not let Qin Lie take the brunt?
Why do you mean?
That's right!
Make Qin Lie the scapegoat.
Once the dust has settled,
you'll pick up the pieces.
The seat of the sect leader
will still belong to you.
Your wisdom knows no limit, Chief Elder.
Round up the disciples.
Everyone,
today,
our sect's survival
hangs on the balance.
The Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple have spoken.
If we don't surrender by daybreak,
they'll slaughter every one of us.
I thought
I could provide a safe haven for you
to pursue the craft of armoury.
But in the end,
we were unable to evade our predators.
Though I'm the master of the
Artefact Forging Sect,
I can't speak for every disciple.
Should we fight or yield?
Please decide for yourselves.