ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Damn it.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
-Son, you're here.
-Hi.
EPISODE 1
Do the cameras make you nervous?
They're blinding, that's all.
How silly of you.
That's Yook Ji-woo's son.
He's on the national team.
Where is her assemblyman husband?
Isn't he more well-known?
Someone younger
always makes better company.
He's handsome too.
We love you!
Finally, it's over. Good job.
Ji-woo, you need to get going.
The visual radio show is next,
so keep that on.
A visual radio show?
Only for the best, Ji-woo.
By the way, these are from your fans.
Son, what do you have planned next?
I'm meeting up with some colleagues
by the theater.
We'll head there together, then.
It's on the way.
What do you say about joining me
for the visual radio show?
No, thanks.
Joining us today in Annam
is Yook Ji-woo, the Queen of Cannes.
Hello.
Hi.
Will we be able to see you
promoting a new movie next year?
I'm not sure,
but I'd be grateful for the invite.
I'd appreciate the interest
of those in the film industry.
Now, who was the young man
you stepped on stage with?
The partner of your next film?
He's the man
I love the most in this world.
Maybe I do because he resembles me.
Could you tell us about your new project?
Many are looking forward to it.
We haven't begun filming,
so I can't mention anything in detail.
It's one of those ordinary love stories
where one can be…
a nutjob,
a loser,
a psychopath…
Wait. I know this voice.
She's Yook…
Yook…
…a piece of trash,
or someone's first love.
I really wanted to be there.
Please look forward to it.
-That was nicely put.
-Excuse me, but what's going on here?
It's an event held by the festival.
Actually, it's already my third time.
-The woman inside…
-It's Yook Ji-woo.
You're still one of Korea's finest
-female actors.
-No way!
What's your key to success?
-I have to thank my family and my husband…
-Ji-woo…
-…who have been my biggest supporters.
-Not now.
My husband…
-Hey, May.
-The movie will start soon.
When will you be here?
Are you even coming?
I won't make it.
Why not?
Did something happen?
Were you in an accident?
You can say that.
I made it to the theater,
but guess who I saw.
Yook Ji-woo is before my very eyes.
Can you believe it?
I wanted to catch the first run,
but I'll pass.
Luck won't ever find me like this again.
It sure is your lucky day.
I'll send you a photo
of the closing credits, then.
-Sure. I'll hang up, then.
-I'm always trying my best.
I see.
-What do you typically do…
-May I sit with you?
-…for a workout?
-My regular exercise routine?
I walk 10,000 steps in the morning.
-How you stay fit is admirable.
-Ji-woo!
Wait, what's that?
-"Ji-woo, your skin is as fair as milk."
-She saw my message!
"I'm talking about your skin."
-Yes, your skin.
-I'm flattered.
You, over there, with the fair skin.
I appreciate it.
-You're the best.
-Ji-woo!
How sweet!
Should we eat first
or watch the movie first?
Why don't we eat first?
-I'm starving.
-Sure.
Did you see Choi Tae-ri earlier?
How can one even look like that?
I know. She is drop-dead gorgeous.
If I had known this was held
near the training center,
-I would have come every year.
-Exactly.
Could I perhaps get a ticket?
There's a movie I want to see.
You always complain
about not having money.
You never even buy us drinks.
I'm sorry.
If I win the prize next time, I'll--
I'll get the ticket for you.
There you are. You come waltzing in
bragging about your money.
Seon-gyeom,
you looked great on stage earlier.
I nearly asked you out.
-I'll get my ticket, then.
-Mine too.
Sure.
Why yours too?
Because you're rich.
You and Yook Ji-woo…
The photo of you and your mom
was uploaded.
My mom wanted to take one with me.
Then go to a photo studio.
Why let it get plastered online?
What an AS.
-What?
-"An AS"?
-What about it?
What does it mean?
Look it up online.
Why be proud of being ignorant?
I almost let you know.
Can I get two tickets
for Gone is the Night?
-I mean, three.
-Just a second.
Sure.
Seung-woo's need for speed was
what pulled the trigger on Yoon-sun.
What did you think?
-It was good, right?
-Right.
Did you enjoy meeting Yook Ji-woo?
If this were a dream, I'd stay in it.
You did a good job on the translation
despite the lack of time for spotting.
Spotting for a film festival movie?
I could barely keep up with the deadline.
I worked my ass off
to have this shipped abroad,
so I'm the one to credit if that happens.
You're only good for Sundance though.
-Here.
-Is this it?
-Thank you.
-Could we get your autograph?
Sure.
You work hard. I give you that.
Translating film festival movies
every year from Korean to English?
Well, the reward is more exhilarating.
I do it all for this single line.
Oh Mi-joo?
It really is you.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
-It's good to see you.
-Really?
I doubt it'd be good
considering how we broke up.
Exactly how did we break up?
Like a scene from a movie.
Long time no see, May.
-I heard you became a film distributor.
-Right. Hi, there.
You've come a long way
to be translating for my movie.
Congratulations.
I kept it as professional as possible.
For someone
who claims to be a professional,
you truncated the male
protagonist's monologue too much.
Did you even get it right?
I kept it short to not ruin the scene.
The meaning was well conveyed.
It's not always good
to have long subtitles.
They ruin the immersion.
-Director Han.
-Yes.
You did a good job.
We'll talk more at dinner.
May, I'll see you later too.
Lucky bastard. I'm so jealous.
Unfortunately,
I can't go with you because
I have to be at a different event.
I'll manage on my own.
You saying that is most terrifying.
-How about a few drinks?
-Is there a pub?
Soju, here we come.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
-Hi, guys.
-It's us.
I thought you guys went back
to the training center.
How can we miss dinner
when Seon-gyeom's buying?
This looks great.
Set the table properly.
I'm sorry.
Here.
Cheers!
Director Han, I enjoyed the movie.
It was great.
-Thanks for saying so.
-Congratulations.
I have a good feeling about this,
you know.
Off to Cannes with you.
Thanks again.
I knew Seok-won would make it.
No other young director
is as well-known as he is.
All tickets for his movie were sold out.
-I know!
-When will our food be out?
It's on its way.
Mi-joo, I heard you were translating
the guest interview too.
-Really?
-Well, yes.
I can easily go from
translator to interpreter.
I guess I'm a genius.
-That's so cool.
-Awesome.
All I did was follow
your guidance, Professor.
Isn't he handsome?
He scolded me often,
and one time I ended up crying.
Professor Hwang
mentioned you a lot, Mi-joo.
Out of all his students,
you translate the best.
You guys must be close.
I guess we are.
We're so close that I did everything
that required translation for him.
We're so close that he hardly paid me.
Mi-joo, there you are.
You should get over here. Come on.
-What about us?
-All right.
Sure, you guys can join too.
I'll make room for you both.
-One more.
-Over here.
Mi-joo, it's been a while.
-Here.
-Right.
Thank you for giving me a shot with this.
The head programmer and I
graduated together.
It was him who recommended you.
Since we're alumni, it could
add weight to the university name.
Yes, I know him too.
I volunteered
at the festival for a few years.
I translated urgent projects for him,
so I guess he liked it.
Right. Well, I was against it.
I see. You were against it.
My glass is empty.
You'll get sick if you drink
on an empty stomach.
Are you looking after him
now that he's a successful director?
-Who, me?
-Aren't you?
Our university hasn't seen
a late bloomer in years.
-I'll make sure to write a rave review.
-Thank you, Professor.
Are your glasses full?
Let's drink.
Wait.
I see that your glass is empty.
All right, then. Cheers for Han Seok-won!
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
-Nicely done.
Can I get another bottle of soju?
SEARCH: AS
ATTENTION-SEEKING
BEHAVIOR EXHIBITED BY PEOPLE
WHO WANT TO BE AT THE CENTER OF ATTENTION
"Attention-seeking"?
"Attention-seeker."
What?
Eat.
My research paper…
should be read by all aspiring directors.
Of course.
Movies by Andrei Tarkovsky
such as The Sacrifice and Stalker
depict the beauty of long takes.
The long takes and the mise-en-scène…
Boy, do I want to go home.
What did you just say?
Professor, your glass is empty. Let me--
No. Mi-joo should be the one
to fill my glass.
Professor, we should call it a night.
You seem tired and--
You're the one who's tired
because you got older.
Let's order more or head to another bar.
-Professor, are you all right?
-You can barely stand.
What? I can barely get it up?
I was just worried because
you can barely keep yourself upright.
How dare you!
Professor, what's wrong?
-Mi-joo, are you okay?
-I can take care of myself.
Female translators need a reality check.
Just because you're pretty…
Pretty faces may be good to look at,
but it's not enough
to excuse that attitude of yours.
What the hell?
Apologize, Professor.
If you do, I'll let it slide.
You think you're something now,
don't you? An apology?
Doing well in your field
doesn't give you the right
to disrespect me!
Fine. Then let me ask you this instead.
What has my pretty face
got to do with my translations?
Do the movies you watch
show the face of the translator on screen?
-That's never been the case for me.
-What?
Pretty faces are good to look at?
Do you even know what you're saying?
A comment like that in this day and age?
You must be from
a different era, Professor.
Are you from the Joseon era?
Are you a time traveler?
Who is your current King, then?
King Sejong? King Cheoljong?
Why you…
Professor, please. Professor--
Just let him go. He wants you to let go.
You're abusing the elderly.
Mi-joo, that's enough!
Get off me.
I graduated and am no longer your student.
I'm now a member of society
who has civil rights.
Is being a woman
reason enough for you to insult me
with sexist comments?
You're the one who humiliated me first.
You said I couldn't get it up.
What do you mean
I can't get it up?
Is that what you thought I meant?
How can this happen to me?
Excuse me, Doctor
-She said I couldn't get it up
-What? Hey!
-She said I couldn't keep it up!
-What?
-What the…
-Let go of me.
Who do you think you're talking to?
A wig?
-You, Oh Mi-joo!
-Professor.
-You asked for it!
-She didn't mean it.
-Professor.
-Likewise.
-What?
-You'll regret what you said to me today.
What the…
You, Oh Mi-joo, get back here!
-Professor, please calm down.
-Get off me!
Let me apologize instead.
-Please.
-Oh Mi-joo!
I shouldn't throw away garbage
on the street.
Hold on for a while.
About a year ago--
Ouch.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
-That's a lighter.
-I didn't ask.
You're right.
Just forget you saw this.
Mi-joo!
Oh Mi-joo!
Gosh. Just a second.
Sorry. Just spare me three minutes.
-Let's go.
-No, I don't want to go.
Mi-joo, come on. Let's go already.
-Just this once.
-Come on.
-No, I'm not going.
-What's with you?
-Are you really going to make me do this?
He was drunk. He just said whatever.
So what? I'm not going. Let me go.
-Come on.
-Gosh, you're hurting me!
My goodness.
Is this real?
Does this shoot real bullets?
What if it does?
I thought maybe I could make him
let go of your hand.
Do you know him?
I don't quite get it.
Are you helping me right now?
You fell because of me.
That's why he was able to catch you.
And three minutes isn't over yet.
I get that you're trying to help,
but why the gun?
Is it real?
I thought he'd at least
let go of your hand
or put his hands up in the air.
I guess I was wrong.
That only happens in movies.
-You look a little crazy.
-Exactly.
Who is this crazy man?
Or he might just leave thinking I'm crazy.
What?
Oh, my gosh!
Gosh, that totally startled me.
My goodness.
Get up.
-You should go.
-Okay.
My gosh, where did she go?
MAY 5, 2019
COLANGELO
Get ready.
-Thanks.
-I'll see you.
Is the sports news shoot this week?
Didn't they ask you for an interview?
Seon-gyeom,
are you doing an interview or not?
I already declined.
Why did you decline? Even I'm doing it.
You have the best record in Korea.
But I'm nothing. That's why.
If you call yourself that,
what does that make the others?
Are you trying to be humble or what?
Is that a compliment?
You have a weird way
of complimenting people.
Why would I compliment you?
Are you on drugs? Are you nuts?
Yeong-il, you really know
how to speak your mind.
The reporters will love
that attitude of yours.
Keep it up.
Good luck with the interview.
Gosh, that annoying punk.
He always thinks he's different and smart.
Seon-gyeom is always annoying.
Exactly. It's nothing new.
Hey, Gyu-deok.
-Yes?
-Seon-gyeom is my friend, not yours.
-Respect your seniors.
-Yes, sir.
See you guys.
-Bye.
I guess the guys
talked behind my back again.
Well, the thing is…
Yeong-il seems to keep you in check
even though he's the best athlete.
I mean, you're a really nice guy.
That's why he's always number one.
Then why do all the other guys
hate you so much?
You're tearing me down
with a smile on your face.
Me?
I think my personality
is changing a little.
Maybe it's because
I'm always thinking about
reducing my record time.
It's also difficult
how everyone's so strict.
Maybe I'm not used to the place yet.
Don't blame yourself.
Blame the ones
who made you become like that.
Does that include you?
Of course.
I'm sure I also played a part.
Seon-gyeom.
I got this for you.
You bought the movie tickets.
-Did you like it?
-No, not really.
I understand.
-You're so handsome.
-Gosh, thank you.
-I enjoyed your movie.
-Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Did you get home safely that night?
It was the worst day ever.
I ran into my ex-boyfriend
and lost my gun.
You're talking like a total stranger.
That's making my heart flutter.
Are you kidding me?
Can I punch you real hard?
-I thought you went back to Seoul.
-Why would I?
I have to provide the interpretation
for your interview.
-Don't ruin my excitement.
-You don't need to be excited.
Professor Hwang will be taking your place.
What?
Professor Hwang, I noticed you forgot
to take your wig.
I took it home
and washed it nice and clean.
My dear Professor Hwang.
Are you there?
Professor Hwang?
I really wanted to be an interpreter
for that movie.
Keep this up and I'll kill you.
Get the facts straight.
You're the one who took my wig.
-My goodness, hello.
-Wait inside, honey.
Hello, ma'am.
I heard you decided to interpret
Director Han's interview yourself.
Yes, he's doing well.
They call him the next Bong Joon-ho.
Did you watch Gone is the Night?
It was released yesterday.
Yes, I watched it.
You only saw it once?
It's a nonlinear movie,
and it's complicated
with a lot of metaphors.
And Director Han goes back and forth
when he speaks,
so it'll take some effort
to interpret what he says.
I understand you took the job from me
out of spite,
but think of the foreign audiences.
This is all on me.
Once I finish interpreting the interview,
I'll apologize to you--
I'll let you do it if you turn back time.
-What?
-You asked me if I'm a time traveler.
Why don't you go ahead
and turn back time yourself?
If you can, do it here and now.
Turn this back.
Back to when you used to have hair?
My gosh, you're unbelievable.
No, wait.
Professor Hwang, that's not what I meant.
These days,
people shave their heads for fashion.
So just be proud of yourself.
-This is my honest opinion.
-That's the problem!
Why are you angry at my sincerity?
Go! Get lost, you psychopath!
I will never forgive you!
My goodness.
I hung it on the doorknob, sir.
My gosh.
Did you go there to apologize
or to get on his nerves?
Don't ask. He got angry about
his bald head and told me to get lost.
-He even called me a psychopath.
-With his wig back on?
I'm not in the mood to joke around.
It's only getting colder,
and wigs keep getting more expensive.
Did you know? Wearing a hat
increases your body temperature by 1°C.
Just worry about
our heating bills for this winter.
Aren't you worried about polar bears?
I just don't get it.
I'm not the reason he went bald.
If you think of his wig as his hair,
you did make him go bald.
May.
Life is so hard.
-All of a sudden?
-Yes, it comes suddenly.
Just forget about it.
Let's go watch a movie.
We already booked a hotel.
I must have been
out of my mind that night.
And how am I going to find my gun?
Yes, that gun. Didn't you get it
autographed at a film festival?
Who was it again? Col…
-Cola.
-My gosh, May.
I told you so many times.
It's Michelle Colangelo.
Do you think I should have bought him
some red ginseng?
You went there empty-handed?
Get lost, you fool.
Seon-gyeom,
it took you exactly ten seconds.
It's your best time. Good job.
That was close. You could have
reduced it to nine seconds.
It took a while to get this far.
Keep it up until the competition.
Great job.
Why are your records getting worse?
Do you do martial arts?
Are you a bodybuilder?
You guys are bulking up
front, back, and sideways.
How will you run with that body?
You guys are huge.
Do a proper job, okay?
Stop slacking off and run!
Watch Seon-gyeom and learn.
-Yes, sir.
-Got it, sir.
Okay, go. Keep it up there. Good.
Woo-sik.
What's that on your face?
I fell while taking a shower.
I figured it might hurt if I sweat.
This is your first year.
You need to be on your toes.
I'm sorry, sir. I'll be more careful.
Watch out, okay? Now go ahead.
Okay.
That's right. One more time.
Keep it up there. Just one more.
Okay, good job.
Woo-sik.
I thought about something.
Would you like to hear me out?
Our coach is extra careful
with all the athletes.
Yeong-il only cares about himself.
And you're a complete stranger
to athletes who play other sports.
And you don't seem like the type
who enjoys hurting yourself.
You went to high school with
Park Gyu-deok and Kim Gi-beom,
and I think they've been doing this
since then.
-What do you think?
-It's nothing like that.
What is it, then?
I mean, at least lie about it.
I…
I lacked discipline.
That's why they did this to me.
You're actually going to lie?
It's not a lie. I'm really okay.
-Really?
-Yes.
You're okay with getting beaten up
for no reason?
And even if you did do something wrong,
are you really okay with
getting beaten up?
Can't you just ignore what you saw?
I don't want to cause a fuss
over nothing. I'll do better.
Let me tell you what it is
that you need to do.
Get a doctor's certificate.
This…
Take photos of this.
Take photos of all those bruises.
You never know what might happen.
Make sure you take photos, okay?
Even your back.
Hello, ma'am. I'm Oh Mi-joo,
Professor Hwang's pupil.
Is Professor Hwang inside?
Just a second.
What if he refuses to meet us?
If you feel uneasy about meeting him,
I could go in by myself.
You could've said that earlier.
Are you still there?
He asked me to say he's not here.
-Seriously?
-What's with this lady?
Ma'am, we bought some red ginseng for him.
Could you at least take this for him?
He says he can. Just a second.
That scrooge.
He must want the red ginseng.
May, long time no see.
So you quit translating
and became a film distributor?
I heard you're doing great.
-It's all thanks to me.
-You're still arrogant.
That's why I started my own business
instead of working for someone else.
It's because you lack social skills.
I'm about ten years your senior.
If you started a new career,
you should have reached out to me
with some job offers.
Gosh, you really have no respect at all.
When you make bone broth,
you need to have bones.
It takes an effort.
Why would I respect you
and reach out to you
when you taught me nothing?
Then why are you here?
You should've come to my funeral instead.
Sir!
You startled me.
A funeral? You should live a long life.
Don't even say that.
I was out of my mind that day.
The same goes for the day after.
Will you please let me interpret
for the remaining interview?
It's really important for my career.
-You want to be an interpreter that badly?
-Yes.
I promise I'll do my best.
Professor Hwang.
How long will it take to find me
an interpreter who can work for a week?
Sir.
I asked for someone who could follow
my son during his training
and help him speak
with the foreign reporters.
Did I ask for too much?
I had been looking around for the best
since he's a national athlete.
In that case,
I'd prefer someone who's poor.
They won't cause a mess later on
since they need the money.
I've found someone
who fits that condition.
Okay. Goodbye, Assemblyman Ki.
"Part-time interpreter," my ass.
Does he think you're still his student?
And what? You'll do it pro bono?
He's going to take
your pay and your commission for himself.
I'm really fine.
It's much easier than turning back time.
When will I ever get to interpret
for a national athlete?
This will be a stepping stone
for my career.
That cheap bastard.
He's so pathetic.
-Let's not age like him.
-Of course not.
Why hasn't the Grim Reaper taken him yet?
He must be busy.
May, go home first.
I need to practice my shooting.
Damn it.
Furry, I thought
you went to a film festival?
I'm there now.
But you're at a net cafe.
I couldn't sleep.
I lost my gun IRL.
No way. Did you find it?
No, I think someone just like me
farmed it.
I have a limited edition Ruger.
Care to buy it?
I'll sell it for cheap.
No way. Seriously?
Can we meet in Seoul?
FURRY KIM: OKAY!
It's so difficult
to live humanely.
SEJONG CULTURE AWARDS
YOOK JI-WOO
LTGA FAIR PLAY CHAMPIONSHIP
KI EUN-BI
PLEASE DELIVER TO KI SEON-GYEOM
YOOK JI-WOO'S MANAGER
MY PRETTY SISTER
What is this?
You changed your name on my phone?
Did you finally notice?
I changed it a while ago.
I guess it was futile.
What do you want?
What if I just called?
Apparently, siblings don't call each other
for no reason.
Did you make friends?
Where did you hear that?
Are you coming to the family gathering
next week?
There will be reporters there.
You better come.
Of course.
They even sent me clothes
in case I was going to go naked.
They're from Mom's manager.
-In case I threw it away last time?
-Did you?
-Not yet.
-Then take this instead.
I've changed the design.
Isn't it pretty?
This way.
I'll go with her.
What is all this?
Camping equipment. I go camping
with my kids on the weekends.
What a nice mom.
That's my hobby.
How was Palm Springs?
Dan-ah put in so much effort
to find the best hotel.
Thanks to her, it was nice,
but I felt burdened.
She probably spent a few hundred
million won on me in the past year.
Can she do that
when I belong to another agency?
Everyone knows that you became an FA
at the beginning of this year.
I'll be renewing my contract
since my father's close with them.
To them, an agency
is just a way to show off
without spending a lot of money.
The wealthy create golf clubs,
give sponsorships,
and create agencies as well.
And is yours any different?
Pretending to be so
helps us to be competitive.
You know you will be doing a photo shoot
with your brother, right?
Dan-ah prepared a lot for it so that
you could wear her company's clothes.
I'm escorting you today
so that you'll agree to do it.
I'm not a part of your agency,
so focus on Seon-gyeom instead.
Hi, I'm done swimming.
Could you give me a cup of hot coffee?
I knew it.
Eun-bi loves her brother so much.
Should I drop you off at home?
I'm not sure.
Do Seon-gyeom and I even have a home?
Of course you do.
Don't you live in Cheongun-dong?
It's not a home if it's vacant.
Seon-gyeom lived there alone
when he was little.
It's empty now that he's gone.
Please take me to a hotel.
No one's here.
My god, he looks so suspicious.
You're Angelic Smile, right?
I'm Furry Kim.
You're a woman?
Is that why you were never on voice chat?
It's all because of people like you.
May I see the goods?
Pay me first.
-I should see it first.
-Gosh, this is annoying.
Just pay me first.
You're so weird.
Let's do it simultaneously to be fair.
Gosh.
Do you think I brought a brick
or something?
This is awesome.
-Let me show you.
-No, I know.
Let me see it.
The reloading is a bit different.
Damn it.
-Hey!
-Move.
You asshole!
-Gosh. She's almost caught up.
-I'll kill you.
Hey! Stop right there!
Damn it.
Hey!
You bastard!
I'm going to kill him. Stop right there!
-Come here!
-Damn it.
You're dead.
I'm on my way, ma'am.
I'm almost there.
Apparently, today was my first leave
this year.
I didn't know.
I was going to rest,
but today was the only day
you were available.
I'm the one dying to see you,
but could you hurry?
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Sadly, I have nothing to throw at you.
Thief!
Is something going on?
Move aside!
Damn it!
-I'm hanging up.
-Come on!
What? Did he hang up on me?
Can I borrow that?
Will it work?
I'll have to try.
-The number you have dialed cannot be…
-What?
Did he reject my call?
-The number you have dialed cannot be…
-Is he playing hard to get?
Gosh.
I was so worried this would break.
You asshole.
Hello, sir. I caught a thief red-handed.
I'm in the middle of Jinguk Park.
-What's going on?
-Please hurry.
I'm going to kill this bastard.
How dare you scam a fellow gun nut?
I ought to teach you a lesson.
I will shoot you. Okay?
I will. I'm going to become
a killer today.
You son of a bitch, wake up!
Did you throw that?
No, of course not.
Well, it's mine, but…
He's the one who threw it.
Thank you for helping me.
Can you pretend it didn't happen?
I could get myself in a pickle
depending on
whether I was involved
directly or indirectly.
It's true that I didn't see you
throw that.
That's a relief.
Is that okay?
It's fine if it didn't break.
It's honey water.
I'm glad.
Then I don't need to compensate
for any damages, right?
I should get going, then.
We received a report.
Don't move.
Put the gun down!
This is fake.
It's fake.
I already knew that.
It's not real.
Help me.
Gosh, this really is intricate.
-It looks so real.
-Right?
There aren't many with such high quality.
I finally managed to get that,
but while I was looking at it,
he snatched it away and ran.
My heart broke.
I understand how you feel
and what went down at that park.
Please fill in this report.
Both of you.
That was a good throw.
I thought you didn't see me throwing.
STATEMENT
KI SEON-GYEOM
Right. I bet you threw well.
Thanks to you, I got my gun back.
-Are you sure it's fake?
-Of course.
Guns are illegal in Korea.
There are many perverts
who like to go against the law.
I'm not a pervert.
I didn't say you were.
Does that mean you sprinted
that distance for a fake gun?
Are you interrogating me?
Are you a cop?
Is that why you looked calm
when you first saw my gun?
I'm rarely startled.
And it obviously looked fake.
It was expensive
because it looked so real.
Are you a firearms expert or something?
I've come across many of them
due to my job.
Well, what's your job?
Are you John Wick or something?
-Who is that?
-Do you not know him?
No.
I see.
But why a pervert?
-Me?
-No.
Me.
Are you a pervert?
No. What I mean is…
When we were talking about guns
being illegal.
Forget it.
He must think I'm a joke.
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached.
He's still not picking up, is he?
Sir, buy me an ashtray.
Get me one of those thick, glass ones.
-Ma'am, before that--
-Why isn't Seon-gyeom picking up?
-The meeting will begin soon.
-He probably can't
since he's in police custody.
I see. He's in police custody.
Wait, where is he? How do you know this?
I witnessed it by coincidence. And--
Dan-ah!
Why is he here?
Your brother's here.
I told you to lock the door.
Did you swim again? I love this robe.
Wasn't he supposed to fly in tomorrow?
If I had stayed in Osaka until tomorrow,
you'd be working.
What's wrong with working?
Check if any of his fans
followed him here.
If there are any,
be kind and send them away.
Yes, ma'am.
Why do your fans like you?
To each to their own, right?
You should respect them.
-Then why do you like me?
-Because you're my sister, my family.
Then why do you dislike me?
-It's the same reason as yours.
-What?
Because you're my brother, my family.
Stop liking me. You're only bothering me.
Also, stop coming here.
Can I still come if I stop bothering you?
Why are you begging me?
Your fans just see you breathing,
and they go berserk.
Do you have that much free time?
Don't beg me for affection.
Didn't you--
Didn't you become an idol
to stop doing that?
I'm so upset.
Dan-ah, you're so annoying.
I rushed over here so you could eat this
while it was still fresh.
Have it if you want. See if I care!
Should I clean that up?
I just don't get why he's so dramatic
when we're only half-related.
Is he just good-natured
or downright crazy?
Does he even know
how precious time is for me?
We should reschedule Seon-gyeom's meeting.
Do you know why he's at the station?
It was related to some civilians.
I guess he didn't know
that athletes shouldn't get involved.
I should have told him.
I'll take care of it.
I trust the assemblyman. Right.
Did you look into it?
About the interpreter Assemblyman Ki
hired instead of me?
Goodness, it's already nighttime.
What will you do about the meeting?
I'm not sure.
Today may be the last time
you get to see me.
The president wasted her leave
because of me.
You must be famished.
I'm so grateful and sorry.
Maybe I could treat you--
I'm not hungry.
Then when do you think you will be?
You can give me your number
or your business card…
I'm not making a move on you.
You can say no if you want.
It's not because
I'm kind of unemployed and bored.
It's just because I feel bad
for what happened.
Since you're just staring at me,
I can't help but keep spewing nonsense.
This was how you stared at me
back at the park.
We're outside a police station
thanks to that,
and the president is going to kill me.
You were the only familiar face
in the crowd.
Is there a way I could save you?
Give me your number.
-Should I call you when I'm hungry?
-Sure.
Are you unemployed?
Not entirely. It's just temporary.
You're unemployed
if you're not working at the moment.
Here you go.
WHEN HUNGRY, BANG
"Bang"?
"Bang!"
Just give me a call and I'll be there
like a bullet so we can eat.
So about that gun…
Is it even worth owning when it's fake?
It doesn't have to be real
to be worth something.
So what if it's fake?
I got it because I wanted one.
Why did you help me? Twice at that.
Well, I just did.
You must have a reason for helping me.
I don't.
You also got that fake gun for no reason.
I guess we're the same, then.
What's John Wick's profession?
John Wick.
What is his profession?
A killer?
Going on a business trip again?
Yes, for a film market.
Do you want anything from duty-free?
Ammunition.
Will that be tax-free?
Did you take care of everything?
May, do you believe in fate?
I do, only if he's handsome.
Forget it, then.
Sure.
I don't know this number.
Could it be…
Hello?
Sorry? Who is this?
What? No way.
He's a model?
I guess he's not available.
Ever since they got a new chef,
they don't taste as good.
You're right.
I hate it when I get full
after a horrible meal.
This is what I get for hard work?
Excuse me.
How may I help you?
I was told to come here
to interpret for the off-season training.
Are you Ms. Oh Mi-ja,
the assemblyman's special interpreter?
It's Oh Mi-joo.
I don't know about special,
but I came because my professor's wig--
I mean, my professor introduced me.
Are you rich?
Not that I know of.
I thought maybe you bought your way in.
I know that Professor Hwang Guk-geon,
who recommended you,
is the assemblyman's gofer
and crazy about money.
Does that make you a gofer's gofer?
Was this week-long interpretation job
worth soliciting for?
It definitely wasn't a job
that you could beg for and get
without executive consent.
I didn't beg for anything.
-You must be an executive, then.
-I am.
As you can see,
I own the athlete
you may be interpreting for.
Shall we grab a coffee nearby?
I haven't had one after my meal.
-You can work.
-Yes, ma'am.
I thought you had called me over to say hi
since we'd be
temporarily working together.
But it seems like you just want
to vent on me.
I'm upset because some politician
hired you behind my back.
I wanted to check if you were like him,
but I don't think you are for now.
I don't feel that great either,
because I'm starting to think
I really am the gofer's gofer.
If you're upset with some politician
and not me,
I'd appreciate it
if you could vent on him instead.
You're right. I'll do that.
Are we done, then?
Don't burden yourself with this job.
Our agency also has interpreters.
They're very competent.
You're going to fire me? Again? Why?
I'm not sure about "again."
But it's because we don't need you.
No, if I get fired,
I'd have to force myself to apologize
and suck up to him.
I'd rather die than do that.
Why would I care?
I have to do this job no matter what.
I can assure you that
I'll be the best temporary interpreter.
You've become
a completely different person.
Don't tell me you're going to
start begging on your knees.
What? Aren't you going to kneel?
Sorry?
Is it because it's grass?
Fine, you can do it.
If you want to, you should.
What a crazy--
Crazy?
I'm crazily thankful.
I see.
Yes?
So the athlete I'll be working with is…
Yes, that one.
I guess it's fate.
-Who is she?
-That's what I want to ask.
Who are you?
Most people know his face
even if they don't know his name.
He's Ki Seon-gyeom,
a national track and field athlete.
You can introduce yourself.
Is this our third time?
It's the fourth.
"I'm talking about your skin."
-I'm flattered.
-You, over there, with the fair skin.
Thank you.
Her shoelaces are untied.
-She's going to trip and fall.
-How sweet!
I love you.
Today, your shoes
don't have any shoelaces.
Yes. What?
Why are you here today?
Is this another deal you're making?
No. What do you take me for?
You're the Deal Killer.
I'm Oh Mi-joo, and I'll be your gofer.
I'll also be your interpreter.
Shall we shake hands
to formally introduce ourselves?
Bang!
I have your lighter.
Are you really insane?
I'm not insane.
I'm Ki Seon-gyeom.
Have you become more motivated
now that you'll retire soon?
I assaulted someone, Coach.
-What?
-Did you say you assaulted them?
-What's wrong with your face?
-That drawing tube…
-We've met before, right?
-I'm Lee Yeong-hwa.
He drew all the paintings here.
Sell this to me.
-"Choi Tae-ri"?
-A love scandal?
I'm so proud of you.
Can you not tell anyone that you went
to the station because of me?
Ms. Gofer. I mean, Ms. Oh.
Ms. Oh, are you sleeping?
-Then would you like to watch my movie?
-Just the two of us?
Do you drink?
You're wasted. You're an LW, aren't you?
A lousy woman?
Are you flirting with me?
Keep this up, and I might end up
making a mistake.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim