ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Seon-gyeom, where are you going?
-Hey!
-What's with him?
Mr. Ki, are you feeling unwell?
Is this about the scandal?
Is the rumor true?
Why didn't you run?
Because I couldn't.
I assaulted
my juniors.
An assault?
Did he just admit to it?
-Did you get that?
-My gosh.
Aren't you going to translate that?
He must be insane.
What?
-No way.
-Seriously?
Get his photo.
EPISODE 4
We'll release a separate statement.
That's it for today. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
The reporters aren't following.
They're probably in a tight spot.
There are major political figures
present here
so they must be confused.
Aren't you scared?
I've made my move.
All I can do now is to wait
and see how things turn out.
I guess raising children is hard
for every family, Assemblyman Ki.
This must be due to
my lack of conversation with him.
I'll excuse myself.
If this were an official race,
he'd be disqualified
for not running.
It wouldn't be a DQ, but a DNF.
Know your facts before babbling.
D what?
He wouldn't be disqualified,
this isn't against the rules.
He just didn't finish.
Even while making a mess,
he still didn't break the rules.
Damn bastard.
Ms. Seo, are you all right?
Go and dump water on the reporters
and any electronic devices they have.
Was that too tacky?
Oh, dear.
You're Kim Woo-sik, right?
Are you perhaps the fellow runner
who Ki Seon-gyeom was referring to?
Was it Ki Seon-gyeom who assaulted you?
No, Seon-gyeom wouldn't do that to me.
You're the only runner
who's injured though.
Is it retaliation you're worried about?
No.
That's not it.
-You see--
-Coming through.
Woo-sik.
-Come on.
-Coach.
-Let's go.
-Woo-sik, come on.
-Come on.
-Wait for me inside.
-Mr. Kim?
-Mr. Kim, wait.
-Excuse me.
-What were you about to say?
You should talk to the head coach.
Hey, keep your mouth shut.
Can't you see you ruined practice?
What's this about Mr. Ki's assault?
It wasn't an assault, but his way
of keeping his juniors in line.
Meanwhile, Woo-sik was injured
during practice,
so please don't jump to any conclusions.
Seon-gyeom has trained
with this team for a few years now
and they're all on good terms.
It seems like Seon-gyeom
has been stressed out
with his relationship problems,
and that must have led him to act out.
At least two people will kill me, right?
Three, including Professor Hwang.
Don't worry too much.
It's me on the chopping block anyway.
At least I won't be lonely
on my way to hell.
Miss!
Miss, do you really think I hired you
just as an interpreter?
Why did you do something
you weren't told to do?
I did what was asked of me.
Didn't you hire me to be
my client's ears and voice?
What?
You insolent wench, how dare you--
Let's not kill the messenger.
And you dare call yourself my son?
How could you do something so stupid?
I told you that your flaws reflect on me!
Why are you pissed off
over a minor beating?
It's not like you used drugs for
leisure or performance-enhancement.
You only roughed up some kids!
What did you just say?
It's not like you'd lose the election
over a minor scuffle.
If that were true,
you wouldn't be in your fourth term.
What is your problem?
You've never been like this before.
You're the one who added fuel to the fire.
I let you become a runner
even though it was a waste of time.
So what about your life
are you complaining about?
You say that like my life
has been mine to live.
What?
That time when I had surgery
when I was a javelin thrower.
Do you remember the first thing
you said to me on that day?
"Your shoulder is wasted now
and is of no use."
Your shoulder is wasted now
and is of no use.
Your legs are still healthy enough,
so why not try soccer instead?
God blessed you with an opportunity
before it was too late.
Use this chance
to finally fulfill your dream.
I've never wanted to play soccer
or become a national athlete.
Just how much do you love me
to dream and plan my future?
What did you just say? You darn brat…
What if I injure my leg?
What use will you have for me then?
Will you marry me off to a family
who'll secure your political career?
You…
-Are you talking about me right now?
-Is that what I was doing?
Damn you.
You ungrateful brat.
Do you not know how much I love you?
Unwanted love
is the same as violence.
Suck it up!
That's the love I have for you.
Now, get lost.
I don't want to see your face,
so get lost!
Mr. Ki, are you all right?
My gosh.
What's with your face?
Did someone hit you?
The photo shoot is still on, right?
It won't be revealed domestically anyway.
It's for the States and China.
And people there won't care
even if it's murder I committed.
Isn't that what I should say?
Keep going if you're not finished.
That means my photo shoot
will go on as scheduled, right?
What matters anyway
is whose clothes I'm wearing.
Your sister's on standby,
so I need to head there.
I'm saying I'm busy.
But you pulling the trigger like this
finally made me understand your mood.
Don't do anything
until I come up with a solution.
Cleaning up the mess
is easier than reversing time.
Get some fresh air
and be on set in the evening.
Got it.
Am I the only one here
who isn't following this development?
Follow me and I'll explain.
I never said to take
your interpreter with you.
She's my interpreter.
How can I go to places
sans my ears and voice?
You say that as if you're in Hawaii,
not Jeju.
Jeez, I sure am popular today.
This must be the time
to take it out on the one who deserves it.
We should talk, Assemblyman Ki.
So it's my dad who hired you.
No wonder why Ms. Seo wasn't pleased.
Well, it's quite a long story,
but it's not like what you think.
Ms. Seo and I wouldn't have
gotten along anyway.
We just don't click.
Let's head to the resort first.
My rental car is there.
Are you really going out to cool down?
I guess I should start listening
to Ms. Seo, right?
I really don't follow.
I know that my son
has been giving you a hassle.
That's rich considering
how you thrust someone you hired my way.
It was an unpleasant experience, sir.
Bring back that interpreter.
Will you be taking it out on her instead
since you can't hit
your beloved son anymore?
I have a right to reprimand her.
I even gave her some pocket money
so that she'd do right by Seon-gyeom.
If chump change can get you that right,
I'd throw around cash myself.
I haven't said anything while you
seduced my children for your pet project.
Besides, my son wouldn't have come here
had I not told him to.
-Proud, are you?
-You might not have been able to use him
for your clothing business.
But you use him for your campaign.
Ms. Seo,
watch what you're saying.
You hired someone on your own
because you wanted to keep me in check.
Now look where that got you.
She translated every last detail
-that she didn't have to--
-That interpreter
-isn't one of my people.
-Well, she surely isn't mine.
Is she with your son then
since that's who she translates for?
Let's solve this with money
and keep it simple.
Don't you see where that got you?
Your son has quite the temper, doesn't he?
I'll take care of this
as nicely as possible.
An assault charge
doesn't do me any favors either.
I'm a hopeful candidate in
the next presidential election.
He can't be dismissed from the team
until I announce my candidacy.
A dismissal instead of retirement--
Just watch your approval rating
and stay out of my way.
That damn girl…
I'm sorry, but I can't speak English.
He wants an interview with you.
Sorry?
You're Kim Woo-sik, right?
Yes, that's me. May I ask who you are?
Ms. Seo would like to see you.
Please follow me.
Where's woo-sik?
I told him to get some rest.
Are there any articles?
A few,
and most of them are about the assault.
Ki Seon-gyeom, that fool…
You idiots!
Reckless brats.
Ki Seon-gyeom…
He really grew some balls, didn't he?
This wasn't what I meant
when I said it though.
Why did he hit you though?
I still can't believe this.
He's more like the kind
to beat up a senior, not a junior.
What are you going to do about this mess?
-Who do I need to strangle?
-Jeong-do.
We didn't know this would happen.
Let's go outside and--
Jeong-do?
Why are you addressing me as your peer
when I quit sports years ago?
Address me properly!
Assemblyman Ki, please calm down.
As the head coach,
you should've taught these boys well.
How can he hit someone out of the blue
and then openly confess it?
You…
and you two!
I'll keep my eyes on you. Got it?
Yes, sir.
That son of a bitch.
How embarrassing.
-Coach?
-Later, coach.
He's nothing like Seon-gyeom, isn't he?
Maybe he's adopted.
Do you have Kim Woo-sik isolated?
Yes.
Good.
And the reporters?
How long until this blows over?
About an hour.
You said 30 minutes not long ago.
Come in.
I bought you some time
for your treatment session.
As if I have the time.
I'll get it once I'm done.
I'm trying my hardest
not to take you to the hospital.
If you want to have the meeting
with a needle in your arm, be my guest.
As if I'd want to humiliate myself
by announcing my illness.
It's why I'm doing this.
This way, please.
Ms. Seo.
Damn it.
Don't be so dramatic.
This will hardly kill me.
PRESIDENT SEO DAN-AH
-The number you have dialed
-Dan-ah, are you ignoring my calls?
-cannot be reached at the moment.
-Having fun in Jeju, are you?
What's this?
Is this a painting?
What's that?
PRESIDENT SEO DAN-AH
She told me to give this to you.
She said she'll give you feedback
on your painting.
I didn't think an agency president
would like amateur paintings.
Hey, bike owner!
Who are you?
-Me?
-Who else is around?
There are lots of people.
Why were you looking over there?
How did you know?
Because I've been watching you.
-Why were you watching me?
-Because you were.
-You're awfully rude.
-I'm always like this.
-You can do the same.
-That's what I'm doing.
Good for you.
Why were you looking at
the president's office? Who are you?
Then what about you?
I'm Seo Tae-woong.
Seo Tae-woong?
Then I'm Kang Baek-ho.
Okay, Kang Baek-ho.
Are you affiliated with this agency?
You look new.
-What do you play?
-Does it look like I play basketball?
I'm asking if you're
one of Dan-ah's athletes.
Gosh, what's with that weirdo?
-What is he saying?
-Hey.
-He's so loud.
-Hey!
I'm not done talking to you!
Kang Baek-ho!
LEE YEONG-HWA
My gosh, who is that jerk?
Dan-ah is already too focused
on Ki Seon-gyeom.
Mr. Ki, are you really here
to get some air?
We're at Jeju Island,
so it's really windy.
You seem too fine,
and it's starting to scare me.
I'm scared you might jump in,
so please take a few steps back.
My gosh.
I haven't seen the sea in a while.
I totally acted out today.
Just for your information,
it means I behaved really badly.
I'm sorry for making you act out.
My gosh.
I'm…
hungry.
That was out of the blue.
I tried changing the subject.
Was it awkward?
Yes.
It was, wasn't it?
"When hungry, bang." Should we go eat?
We're at Jeju Island,
so let's eat abalones.
Sure.
Okay.
That was pretty smooth.
All I did was act out today,
but wasn't it a huge issue for you?
What are you going to do?
I won't be able to do much.
I'll either get kicked out or suspended,
and I'll have to pay a fine
after I get fired from all the campaigns.
Then I'll have to leave
the training center.
I also need to think about what I can do.
-You talk as if it's not a big deal.
-It's not a big deal to you.
Thank god you're rich.
Thank god you think that way.
Does that mean
you're no longer a national athlete?
I won't be able to run
as an athlete at all.
So now I'm just Ki Seon-gyeom.
Aren't you scared
that you won't be able to run again?
I should bear with it.
Oh, right.
I did make a promise.
-A promise?
-Yes.
I promised to coach
the track and field team after I retire.
The track and field team
of the school you graduated?
No, it's this Christian school.
My dad is a Christian.
Oh, he's a Christian?
I went to do volunteer work with him,
and I couldn't refuse. They were so cute.
I guess those kids make you smile
just by thinking about them.
Yes.
They're going to be really upset at me
for not keeping my promise.
That's all I'm scared of.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
Gosh, that's hot.
Thank you for the meal.
By the way,
your parents must be pretty strict.
Did you think we'd be a happy family?
It's just that you look so perfect.
And you grew up so well.
Don't you think you're overestimating me?
You're the one
who's too harsh on yourself.
You should be more confident.
It's natural I grew up like this.
The world was fairly nice to me.
So I grew up thinking
I should also be nice to the world.
"Nice"?
That's not what I saw today.
The world was pretty harsh on you.
That's why I said "fairly."
It would have been nice
if I grew up with that kind of mindset.
I don't know what kind of mindset you had
while growing up,
but you turned out nicely.
You're starting to make me get curious.
Curious of what?
You're risking your entire career
just to help out a junior,
so I wonder what you'd be like
once you fall in love.
You seem to want to know a lot about me.
I know, right?
I wonder why I'm so curious.
Is there anything
you want to know about me?
Forget it.
From time to time, I do think of that day
when I saw you run.
I don't run unless I have a race
or I need to train
because I don't want to hurt my muscles.
So I try not to get myself
in urgent situations.
But you ran really fast that day.
You almost set a record.
That's because you were waiting for me.
As if.
Am I counting chickens or abalones?
They're abalones.
You didn't have to answer that.
I was talking to myself.
I see.
You talk to yourself out loud?
Are the articles out?
Well, the articles are a little…
This isn't right.
They're too exaggerated and blunt,
aren't they?
Are you used to it?
This is way worse than the recent scandal.
What does it say?
They're just making assumptions
or condemning you.
"The track and field team announces
that the assault was just
a minor incident."
"Many claim they saw Ki Seon-gyeom
disciplining his juniors.
Hasn't made any noticeable progress
after the Asian Games.
Assumed to have broken up
with Choi Tae-ri.
Did he take out his stress
on his juniors?"
What is all this nonsense?
"Hierarchy in sports is a real problem."
This is the only normal one.
-They say you should just go to the army.
-I already went.
All the articles are
mentioning Choi Tae-ri.
So your name might end up
all over the portal site.
The articles are pretty high up
on the list.
-Gosh, this is making me angry.
-Don't be so angry.
I wouldn't be so angry
if you were angry about it too.
-At least get frustrated about it.
-I'm just a jerk who beat people up.
What? You're empathic
when it comes to others,
but when it comes to you, you don't care.
Do you have no love for yourself?
Didn't you learn to love yourself
in school?
I was busy training, so I skipped classes.
Okay, whatever. Just focus on driving.
Couldn't they put up
more streetlights here?
It's so dark. I can't see anything.
Do they want people to die here?
-I think I know this place.
-What?
-It's the road to the afterlife.
-Hey.
Sorry.
Hello.
NATIONAL ATHLETE, KI SEON-GYEOM,
CAUSES TROUBLE DURING OFF-SEASON TRAINING
KI SEON-GYEOM HAS CONFESSED
TO ASSAULTING HIS JUNIORS
JUST GO TO THE ARMY
NO WONDER CHOI TAE-RI DUMPED HIM
You can stop working for Mr. Ki.
Just head back to Seoul.
Assemblyman Ki is very upset.
I know I'm here as a part-timer,
but my job isn't done yet.
Will I get in trouble
if I insist on finishing my job?
I was given orders, and I'm just here
to relay the message. Bye then.
Wait.
I'd like to give this back.
He can pay me for my work instead
by wiring it to my account.
It sounds like
you're returning this so you can stay.
Is that correct?
I can't take it because I didn't do
what he asked me to do.
I relayed the message, so my job is done.
It's going to take a while to get ready.
You can take a break.
-Okay.
-You're too handsome to be an athlete.
-You read the articles, right?
-I heard about them on my way here.
Do you think the issue you've caused
will manage to change
the rotten hierarchy system?
It would have been a start
if I had gotten punished properly.
I thought people would naturally realize
that it's wrong to use your authority
to bully your juniors,
and that you get punished
if you do something wrong.
I had no idea
grownups would just cover it up.
You talk so eloquently.
Give Woo-sik some tips
on how to do an interview.
I have a foreign reporter waiting.
He has 30 minutes.
Kim Woo-sik is waiting somewhere safe.
Woo-sik?
-Can you really help?
-Yes, if that's what you want.
Tell me what you want.
It might be different from what I want.
I want
the men who hit me to be punished.
-Okay.
-Seon-gyeom never mentioned me
because he was worried
I might get in trouble.
And because of that,
people think he's garbage.
I'm glad you at least know
how much you ruined his reputation.
If this goes public,
you might be outcast as a whistle-blower.
You having told your story
will be more upsetting
to the higher-ups
than the fact that you're a victim.
I know. I don't care as long as I can help
Seon-gyeom clear his name.
Clear his name?
He still hit people,
so he'll still be criticized for that.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Just don't think of it that way.
Seon-gyeom didn't do anything
to disgrace himself, okay?
Okay.
It looks like Seon-gyeom cares
a lot about you.
I bet Seon-gyeom has a lot of respect
-for you.
-Do you think so?
He respects me?
Are you sure?
You're about to get bashed by the public,
so let's do all that we can
to bring that down a notch.
That's my solution.
-Do you like it?
-What does that even matter?
I'm hoping you'd cut me some slack.
What you did earlier
was your way of messing with those
who insisted on keeping things quiet.
Don't hate me
as much as you hate the others.
I don't want to be one of them.
I never thought of you that way.
But if it's a foreign reporter,
we'd need an interpreter.
Your interpreter can do the job.
But she might not be able to do it
because of what she took.
You have ten minutes.
Get ready and meet me in the meeting room.
Why do people hate me so much
when I'm so considerate?
I think I'm pretty nice.
Can we talk for a moment?
Woo-sik will tell them everything
in order to save my career.
But if he tells the reporter
that I did it to help him,
I'd like you to leave that out.
But isn't he doing this for you?
It'll be inevitable for him
to talk about you,
but you want me to leave that out?
Are you giving me orders
to make up things as I go?
I know what I'm doing right now
is an abuse of authority.
But I just don't want
to cause you any trouble,
so please understand.
Why are you worried about me
when you're the one in trouble?
My dad.
I'm his son,
so all I got was just a slap in the face.
But you…
You mean nothing to him,
so it's natural for me to worry.
You're so strange.
You worry about everyone else
but yourself.
Do you know what you seem like to me?
A person who's used to being hurt.
You got hurt so much
that you're just used to it now.
So now you don't even know
what's hurting you.
You shouldn't get involved in this.
-It's my business.
-It's mine too.
I'm the only interpreter here.
You told me you're used to being linked
with certain things, right?
Do you want to be referred to
as a piece of trash who beats people up
-until you get used to it?
-Yes, I should.
I already expected that much.
I never really cared
what others say about me.
You don't need to say anything about me.
It's not important.
What do you mean?
Your story is what matters the most to me.
Do you really want people to hate you?
Do you think the world is nice?
Then don't ever ask
for something like this again.
I won't do it.
Do you think you'll be fine
since you're rich?
Ms. Oh, the interview will begin soon.
Okay.
I'll interpret what I think is necessary.
You need to start
taking better care of yourself.
You were my interviewee until just now.
He says he was there at the track
when Ki Seon-gyeom refused to start
and confessed to assaulting
his own teammates.
And he wants to know if that was you.
No, Seon-gyeom would never do that to me.
The guys who hit me
were Park Gyu-deok and Kim Gi-beom.
Seon-gyeom was the only person
who told me it was wrong
to be beaten by someone
whatever that reason may be.
Thank you for today.
I'll treat you to a meal one day.
You did great, Woo-sik.
You did great.
I'll be off now. I have a flight to catch.
I'll see you next time.
I don't have a flight to catch.
I missed it ages ago.
It'll cost me so much
to buy a ticket at the airport.
Ms. Oh.
Let me give you a ride to the airport.
You should go and console Woo-sik.
It's hard to grab a cab here.
Just let me give you a ride.
I took care of the interview.
It wasn't because I felt a sense of duty.
I just wanted you to be seen
as a nice villain.
Wait.
This isn't about work.
I just have a question.
What is it?
Don't take this the wrong way.
I'm asking because I don't know.
Do you like me?
Everything you've said so far
seems to be hinting at that.
Am I mistaken?
Even if you didn't know, don't you think
asking me like this is wrong?
I like you.
This is how you confess
unless you wanted everything I said
to be a confession.
Did I give you the wrong idea?
If you were offended, I'm sorry.
I apologize.
You're so considerate
even at a time like this.
Not everything I said hinted at that.
But some of them could have.
You should fix that habit of grabbing
others whenever you want.
It's as if you want me
to take it the wrong way.
Okay. One more time.
Can you make it slightly darker?
Gosh, you look amazing.
Okay. She can change.
Let's have her in black this time.
Hey.
Why aren't you answering me?
-Have you gone deaf? Seon-gyeom.
-What? When did you come here?
You were so bold back there.
Are you scared now?
You're right.
I really am a lunatic, aren't I?
At least you know.
Right. I totally forgot about it.
I was too focused on elsewhere.
What's wrong with you?
Where's your interpreter?
She already left for Seoul.
I didn't need her for this shooting.
-What are you doing after this?
-Catching Ryan.
He'll be attending a race.
Is he sightseeing or running away from me?
If it's the former, let him sightsee.
If it's the latter, let him go.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
Do you know what love is?
If that's what it is, I'm not interested.
I feel the same way.
I go crazy whenever I'm in love.
So I try to steer away,
but it's impossible.
Leave if you're done.
It's obvious that you miss him.
Hey, for someone who grew up
in a pretty messed up family,
you turned out
quite nicely.
This is all because you didn't live
in the same house as us.
I'm sure it was tough for you.
I guess I'm just blessed overall.
I knew how to endure it.
Bye.
You're here already?
I am.
You're not all here yet. Drinking already?
People may think
you were on a business trip overseas.
Eat something too.
You're going to ruin your liver.
Do you want some kimchi?
Or we also have fish cakes.
Maybe some fish cake stew?
Stop pestering me!
One day, I'm going to have a heart attack.
I'm not one to pity others,
so why is he being so pitiable?
Whoever it is,
it's game over if you pity him.
Game over in many ways.
Right.
How was that musical?
Wasn't it good? You're doing it, right?
Damn it, I need to get my gun back.
Mi-joo. The musical. Are you in?
Am I talking to a wall?
Don't you pity me?
You shouldn't drink in your room.
Did you sleep well?
I may be the nonchalant type,
but wouldn't it still scare you if I did?
Why are you leaving so discreetly?
I want to lessen the burden for those
who are annoyed with me.
-What about you?
-I'm not planning to stay until the end.
I'll stay for a few more days.
My therapist is here as well.
If I were to leave by myself,
it'd seem like we left together.
Woo-sik, I gave it some thought.
You shouldn't follow my footsteps.
Good work yesterday.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Mr. Lee Yeong-hwa?
Ms. Seo Dan-ah wants to see you.
Who are you?
How did you know I was here?
It's a long, lame story.
First, let's go.
What? But, sir.
Sir.
Wait up.
What are you staring at?
Hello.
You shouldn't be in there, so get out.
One minute.
I found this in here.
How did that get in there?
Who told you to grab my hand?
Pardon? Weren't you helping me out?
No. I wanted you to give that back.
It's mine.
You have no manners, do you?
Take that hairpin out
right before you get out, okay?
Hey, you only get five minutes.
You have to join the others
before the immigration.
I know. I'm just going to say bye
to my sister.
God, you and your love for your sister.
Remember how you left Osaka by yourself
and caused a mess?
If you fly out by yourself again,
they'll say you fought with your members
and are being bullied.
I said I got it.
Did you buy the coffee?
By the way, when is Ms. Seo Dan-ah coming?
That's me.
What is that reaction?
I thought you had to be old
to be a president.
For ordinary people, yes.
You must be extraordinary.
Damn it.
Didn't you say I was rude?
You even broke my bracelet.
I accidentally stepped on it on my way up.
I'll compensate you.
Tell me how much it was.
How can you let me look for you?
I bought that painting ages ago.
I came to the front of your building once.
A guy came out back then
and mentioned your name.
-Oh, that bastard?
-"Bastard"?
It's one of his nasty hobbies,
so don't worry about him, kiddo.
"Kiddo"?
Aren't you still in school?
Maybe "bastard" is better.
About my bracelet…
Compensate me in another way.
All I have is this body.
-Guess that'll work since it's inside you.
-Inside me? Do you mean
my heart?
Forget it. Paint me a picture.
As for the paint, will Schmincke suffice?
No. I've never used that before
because they're too pricey.
Then this is your chance.
Monet and Picasso used them,
so why shouldn't you?
Once you're done with the draft,
confirm it with me. I'll give you a week.
Mr. Jeong will give you his business card.
Call him if you need me,
and you can wear this.
Is this how you normally talk?
-What?
-What if I refuse?
I thought it'd be entertaining
if you refused.
But now that it has happened,
I'm quite offended.
Why are you smiling?
I have a habit of smiling
and being friendly.
You should fix that. You could grow on me.
How much is the bracelet?
It looked quite expensive.
-It's around 500,000 won?
-How much?
How is…
Yes, it's around that much.
Take this. My arm's sore.
You haven't told me
what you thought about my work.
Oh, right.
How do you paint like that?
What kind of life did you live…
I wondered what you were made of
to have painted like that.
I eat a lot of rice burgers.
I go to exhibits and watch movies often.
And I'm not entirely sure
what I'm made of.
I've never checked inside.
I don't know either,
but your painting was dark and unsettling.
It was nice to meet you.
Please throw this away on your way out.
Hey, Kang Baek-ho.
-You again?
-No, it's you again.
What are you doing here?
Your hair's wet. Did you shower?
Why are you wearing this?
What's it to you?
You don't look like you deserve
a two million won robe.
What? Two million?
Hey, is Dan-ah your sponsor or something?
Is she?
-Why are you talking casually?
-You told me to.
-What an obnoxious brat.
-Takes one to know one.
-How old are you?
-I'm old enough.
What…
And how old is that?
God, you…
Hey, what's your relationship
with the president?
-You--
-Time's up.
We're outside right now.
People have noticed you, so let's just go.
He's impossible.
He picks fights with everyone.
I'm sorry. He means well.
Let me apologize instead.
If you want to sue him, you can call me.
Why should I call you when I'm suing him?
This is a weird neighborhood.
Wow, what an asshole.
Myung-su! How old is old enough?
All the athletes are complaining
to the association.
They will carry out an inspection
of the sports committee soon.
Since the public is outraged,
the association won't be able to
turn a blind eye.
I tried to stop that from happening
but I guess he will be punished.
It won't be a slap on the wrist.
They're discussing whether
to disqualify him or not.
Dan-ah rambled about solving this nicely,
so what the hell is she doing?
Let me talk to the parties involved.
Retiring is better
than being disqualified.
Yes, sir.
I raised him with love,
but it was all in vain.
Because of him, I have to bow down
and apologize to these people.
Hey, Seon-gyeom.
Do you seriously have an appetite?
I was hungry, so I stopped by.
Right. I almost forgot who you were.
You did something insane
after falling in love.
I read the article.
And I hear you volunteered
to leave this place.
Have you finally decided
to have a bit of fun?
Did Tae-ri dump you after a month
because you were no fun?
Were you too boring for her?
Stop calling me boring.
You have so much japchae.
Did you reject me when I asked you out
for pasta because you liked Korean food?
So that's why
you didn't want to go out with me.
You're so boring.
I was afraid of you.
Was I really that boring?
Yes. Totally.
Then why did you ask me out?
Because I wasn't aware of that.
I had such a huge crush on you.
The boxing match is around the corner.
You'll win, right?
I win at everything
as long as it's not with you.
You're right.
By the way,
why are you talking casually to me?
I'm a year older.
What? You're finally telling me that?
You should express and share
your feelings more with others.
Be honest and say what you like,
dislike, or what you crave.
You'll be more fun that way.
In that case,
I think I'm already doing it.
ANNAM TRAINING CENTER
When I first ran,
I was running away.
Hey! Ki Seon-gyeom!
I wanted to leave everything behind
and go far away.
When I had stopped,
I could only hear
my heart thumping loudly.
It felt like I had a world of my own
where only I could be heard.
That was the first time
I made a decision on my own.
Goodbye. I'm leaving now.
It's not uploaded yet.
When is it coming up?
KI SEON-GYEOM
ATHLETE
FATHER: KI JEONG-DO
MOTHER: YOOK JI-WOO
WILL THE TRACK AND FIELD STAR
BE DISQUALIFIED?
NATIONAL ATHLETE KICKED OUT
FROM THE TRAINING CENTER
KI SEON-GYEOM
Are you okay?
Can you give me back my gun?
Please call me.
I heard you received money
from Assemblyman Ki.
You really are the gofer's gofer.
Where did your manners go?
In the trash can?
Of course not.
When people meet,
don't they normally say hi?
That doesn't make
receiving bribes normal, does it?
Would you like to order?
One iced coffee, please. Thank you.
Sure.
Is that why you called me?
Give me your account number.
I should pay you.
What kind of employer asks for it
like this?
I don't know the rate these days.
I'll tell them to wire enough money.
No, don't. Professor Hwang is the one
who'll get the money.
I don't get a single penny.
Why did you take this job?
I doubt the assemblyman paid you
to do well.
-Because I pitied him.
-Who?
-My client.
-Seon-gyeom? Seriously?
-Yes.
-You pity him? Why? How?
Look at what you're doing.
I think it'd be better
if you pitied yourself instead.
Make sure he doesn't know about the bribe.
He hates that.
I didn't know you'd be this concerned
about your athlete.
I can't help it.
It's been ages since he liked someone.
And how do you know that?
I was the last person he liked.
I'm not interested in his love life.
He can tell me himself if he wants.
I don't think this is right.
You'll hear from him?
Have you two even met since then?
I really pity you.
Here's your drink.
If you're done toying with me,
I should go see him now.
I'm supposed to see him today.
Is that so?
Next time, let me know in advance
if you want to bicker.
I should prepare myself.
Thanks for the coffee.
Did you feel fine
during your time with him?
At times,
I feel like shit when I talk with him.
It really feels shitty
when he makes you feel like human garbage.
You're right. That's how I felt too.
-Right?
-But I realized
that it wasn't his fault.
That's true.
She's a smart one.
Damn it. She won this time.
But it's not good
to get your emotions involved.
Do you normally get so emotional with her?
No, not normally. But yesterday, I did.
If it's not normal, then why are you
emotionally involved?
-So you left the training center?
-How did you know?
I can look you up online.
You packed my lighter, right?
Give it back right now.
-Right now?
-Yes, now.
Right now is not the best time.
Would you have said the same
had it been Ms. Seo?
I might make a mistake
if I see you right now.
What mistake?
I'll go wherever you are,
so bring it outside.
Just one minute is fine.
I'm at a hotel.
Okay, text me the address.
Isn't it a bit weird
that you're at a hotel?
Why?
I sleep, eat,
drink coffee, and even work out here.
This is my home.
Well, that's exactly why it's weird.
How could you do all that at a hotel?
You're an odd one.
Text me the address.
Human garbage or not,
I definitely have a dirty mind.
It's a room.
Out of all the places you could stay at,
you chose a hotel room.
-Ms. Oh.
-I'm talking to you.
Did my father pay you?
Remember what I said?
That I might make a mistake?
So this is what you call a mistake.
You have such a noble character.
I thought you meant something else.
It's true. He paid me,
and I took it.
You can be disappointed in me.
Don't stop yourself.
Let's forget that there was anything
between us two.
I'll give it back if you say you won't.
He's so annoying.
He makes me feel like a loser.
Why here of all places?
This is where Seon-gyeom stays.
There's no way I'm going. No way.
Have you been painting?
So you can see me.
Why did you ignore me just now?
-Ms. Oh.
-What?
-Why are you…
-What are you doing here?
That movie was still showing.
-It was an excuse to make you stay.
-Same here.
Why did you have to let me
find out like this?
You have so much to learn.
Being unemployed will be boring.
Let me know if you get bored.
-If I do? Will you hang out with me?
-If I'm not busy.
What's wrong with you?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim