ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
She's my girlfriend.
Have you lost your mind?
I'm serious.
Are you insane? Seriously?
Seriously.
Oh, my gosh. My goodness.
Hello.
Did you call for a chauffeur service?
-Which one of you called?
-That guy.
-Over here.
-Okay.
Are you okay?
Did you take the photos?
She isn't a celebrity,
so stay quiet
if you don't want to get sued.
And I don't care about Ki Seon-gyeom.
He's not even my boyfriend.
Bye, guys.
You're up.
We live together.
We're not dating, we're friends.
So don't get the wrong idea.
My gosh. You were kind enough
to let me live with you.
Hello, I'm Ki Seon-gyeom.
I'm sorry this is how we had to meet,
but since I'm already here,
may I use your bathroom?
You must be pretty clean.
-Yes, kind of.
-What are you going to wash?
Your face? Hair? Body?
-Is there a limit?
-Make yourself at home
I'll give you a toothbrush. Wait a second.
Here. Eat this first.
-What is it?
-It's for your hangover.
Haven't you seen it before?
You should take it often.
You're too much of a lightweight.
Here. Take it.
I put new clothes there.
Feel free to wear them.
-Is this it?
-Yes.
You didn't have to do this. Thank you.
Your clothes are in the wash.
That's for men.
We purposely hang it out on the balcony
to keep us safe.
But no one's ever worn it though.
What's wrong? Is it too flashy?
I wasn't able to think that far.
I'm just surprised
people actually do that.
Thanks for letting me wear this.
Borrow it if you want.
Just make sure you return it.
No, I'm good. I'll return it right away.
Okay.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but your shoes were a mess too.
We also have a pair of men's shoes,
so you can wear them home.
-I'm not sure if they'll fit.
-My goodness, it's like he's Cinderella.
You know Cinderella, right?
Do you know the story or not?
Cinderella was bullied
By her sisters and stepmother
So you do know.
We won't bully you, so sit down.
There we go.
Isn't it "Stepmother and sisters"?
I think he's still drunk.
This is it.
This is the meal I owe you. Dig in.
I'll do the dishes.
-Okay.
-Thank you for the meal.
My mom makes really good short rib soup.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
By the way,
how did I end up coming here?
I don't see a home address
on his navigation history.
There's the training center, the agency…
-There's Seoul Hotel.
-A hotel?
Should I drive to Seoul Hotel?
My goodness.
The hotel sounds like the best option.
Just take us
to Hannam five-way intersection.
-Hannam five-way intersection?
-Yes.
Okay, you got it.
I'd punch him if I could.
Beginning navigation.
How do you feel? Do you feel better now?
Gosh, darn it.
That hurts.
My gosh. Wait.
Wait.
Oh, my goodness!
What's going on?
-Hey, May.
-What's that on your back?
You're unbelievable.
I found him on my way home.
Isn't he pretty?
Gosh, I'm cold.
I wanted to leave you behind,
but if you died,
I'd be summoned by the police.
So I carried you here on my back.
You didn't exactly carry him on your back.
To be more exact,
she dragged you here on her back.
Yes, it's always best to be exact.
So tell me.
When exactly did you black out?
I just remember paying.
I don't remember anything
after that.
That's where you blacked out?
You deserve a beating.
You promised yesterday.
Did I promise that yesterday?
So it wasn't a dream?
I guess not.
Hit me. You should've hit me
right after I kissed you.
We didn't kiss.
It was just a peck on the lips.
What's your lip balm?
It was delicious and moist.
-You talk like a guy.
-I need to check.
I just use whatever.
Birds of a feather flock together.
So it wasn't a dream.
I'll go on my own from here.
I'll be off now.
You look good in that outfit.
Thanks for the compliment.
I always wanted to buy a car
after I got myself a house.
But unfortunately,
I haven't bought a house yet.
I saw on the news
that a car driving 200km per hour
crashed into this car,
but the guy who drove this car
only ended up with bruises.
I also saw that news. It wasn't this car.
This obviously has a V8 engine.
I bet it drives really fast.
It's always been my dream
to drive a car like this.
And it just happens to be
right in front of me.
It has a V6 engine, not a V8.
I'm just asking for a ride.
Can't you do that for me?
Other couples share their cars
all the time.
You said so yourself that we're dating.
Then that would make me insane.
I need to go meet Ms. Seo.
Is that okay with you?
Yes, I'm fine. I'll just stay in the car.
-Is it a meeting?
-No, I need to apologize.
-"Apologize"?
-I got angry at her yesterday.
But it's not good
to get your emotions involved.
Do you normally get emotional with her?
No, not normally. But yesterday, I did.
Get in. Let's go for a ride.
Mr. Ki, what brings you here?
Is Ms. Seo inside?
She just went to the head office.
Should I leave her a memo?
I'll talk to her myself.
Mr. Ki.
Ms. Seo cares a lot about you.
I hope you know that.
I do.
Get in.
Did you meet Ms. Seo?
No, she seems busy.
Where to this time?
-The hospital.
-Why?
-Someone's hospitalized.
-I see.
I should get a stuffed doll
on my way there.
I know a great place for that.
-I'll take you there.
-Okay. Thanks.
-My gosh.
How long have you been driving?
You didn't know?
Is it your plan to steal my car?
You think my plan is merely
to steal your car?
Gosh, what's wrong with that jerk?
What's his problem?
You're at fault, you know.
-No, I'm not.
-My gosh.
You can't just deny it.
You have a driver's license, right?
Perfect.
Excellent.
Heads up.
The person at the hospital must be young.
Yes, I guess.
Don't people normally get patients
fruits or drinks?
I want to give him a friend.
It gets boring when you're alone.
If you talk to stuffed dolls,
they'll get possessed.
But why couldn't we just buy one instead?
Because it's more fun to win it.
Just a second.
I sent you the interview questions
for Mr. Ki's photoshoot.
Please look over them.
Mr. Jeong just gave me work.
I should go now.
Thanks for the stuffed doll
and for driving me.
But don't buy a car.
You're a terrible driver.
Does this mean
we're not going to talk about
what happened yesterday?
I got you that doll and drove you here
hoping we'd talk about it.
Why don't you hit me now?
I'll apologize if that's what you want.
You don't need to accept my apology
if you don't want to.
You can sue me too. I'll make sure
Ms. Seo doesn't call her lawyers.
If you want, you can do all of the above.
You left out the most important part.
I want to know why.
Why did you do that to me?
I wanted to avoid the situation.
-And you just happened to be there.
-What?
You talk as if you would have
done that to anyone.
I was too drunk yesterday.
I would have kissed whoever I was with.
If it really didn't matter to you,
why didn't you kiss Tae-ri's dad?
What?
Why did you kiss me if it didn't matter?
Is it because you're straight?
Don't get me wrong--
Hitting you sounds most appealing.
But I'll save it.
It's too crowded here,
and I'm a woman of culture.
Have fun visiting your friend.
Impressive. You pack a mean punch.
Hello.
Are you Woo-sik's friend?
Woo-sik and I train together.
My name is Ki Seon-gyeom.
You look so pretty.
I almost thought you were a woman.
-I'm a man.
-Go on inside.
I need to go to work now.
-You work?
-Yes.
It's nothing grand, but I clean buildings.
By the way,
did Woo-sik get hurt while training?
I keep asking him, but he won't tell me.
I'm asking because I'm worried.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I'm just grateful
that you came to visit him.
Thank you.
Seon-gyeom.
Are you that happy
that you don't have to train?
You're smiling ear to ear.
What are you wearing?
-And what's with that doll?
-It's yours.
Did you get this for me?
Let it keep you company.
-Your legs must hurt. Sit down.
-Okay.
I didn't know your grandmother
would be here.
I just met her out front.
-You didn't tell her anything, right?
-No.
How do you feel?
I'm sure you're still not okay.
It'll take a while to start running again
because of rehabilitation.
I guess you won't get to come
to the off-season training in Jeju.
That's the least of my worries right now.
What's going to happen to you?
They can go ahead and discipline me
or suspend me.
But it happened because of me,
so just tell them that--
Seriously.
If I do that,
people will think we're dating.
-It's not funny.
-I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm seriously worried.
Did you want to be a hero?
You talk as if I saved my country
or something
when I couldn't even save you.
You knew that already.
-Why did you even bother?
-Because you would have put up with it.
You finally became a national athlete,
so you wouldn't have wanted
to raise an issue.
You would have also been worried
about the repercussions.
On the other hand, I'll be retiring soon.
I don't mind getting kicked out.
I have a lot of money too.
You're annoying.
-Yes, joke around like that.
-I meant it.
I'll see you then.
Seon-gyeom.
I wasn't able to thank you properly
because things were so hectic.
But thank you so much.
Does this really look bad?
Your outfit doesn't matter.
I really am grateful.
Rest up. You're still injured,
so get some rest.
FAMILY GATHERING
TOMORROW 3 P.M.
Are they kidding me?
This is pretty much
an exclusive interview.
Hello, Mr. Jeong.
There's a small problem with
the interview questions you sent me.
Is it about the translation?
You just need to focus on
Mr. Ki's questions.
He's like a third wheel in this interview.
There's not much about him.
Yes.
Okay, I'll summarize the issues
and email them to you.
Okay. Bye.
I'm working so hard
for that annoying punk.
He wanted to come himself,
but his meeting hadn't ended
so I had to come instead.
He'll probably have a good excuse
even when he dies.
You'll be riding the same car
once his meeting ends.
Yes, I know.
We need to get out of the same car.
Drop me off at a beauty parlor.
I should make sure I look nice
for the photos.
It's the athlete who committed assault.
Do you stay here too?
-I live here.
-Still?
Then let me go with you.
I don't want to take the car
that Dad sent.
Who told you about me?
I know everything.
Are you really dating Choi Tae-ri?
Why didn't you invite me to meet her?
We're not dating.
I'm getting sick of this.
I'm sick of it too, you know.
Everyone I meet asks me about it.
But I thought you knew everything?
You're right.
How long are you staying this time?
Until I wrap up ad campaigns,
attend the events I'm invited to,
and catch that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch?
Ryan? He ran off again?
Ran off? Again?
One might get the wrong idea.
Are you even together?
We are if I say we are.
Ranking first in the world
gives me the authority.
A CLEAN ADMINISTRATION WITH KI JEONG-DO
I'm sick and tired of election periods.
He puts us on display
like animals at the zoo.
Can't he stop using us for his campaign?
Has he no shame?
There's no reason for him to stop
since it's the only reason we exist.
It's good to see you.
Dad!
-How is it that you always look good?
-You only see me when I'm dolled up.
I sent it home not knowing where you'd be.
I'm glad you found it.
My manager made the delivery,
but it was me who picked it out.
I know. It has you written all over it.
Hello.
Seon-gyeom, my goodness!
You've lost so much weight
since I last saw you.
I haven't lost any, actually.
That can't be true.
I can smell japchae.
Well, I heard you'd be here.
I know how much you like it.
Do you want to try it?
The punishment for
bringing home a guest unannounced
is to read a transcript?
It's more of an honor than a penalty.
This will be as big as La La Land.
But I hate musicals!
No one has hired you yet.
I'm just asking you to take a look.
You're not allowed to go home
until you do.
La La Land's box office score…
La La Land.
LA LA LAND
POPULAR SEARCH TERMS
ASSEMBLYMAN KI JEONG-DO
YOOK JI-WOO AND KI JEONG-DO'S
ANNIVERSARY GATHERING
NETIZENS THRILLED
BY THE AFFECTIONATE COUPLE
I'm used to this, so I'm fine.
If he's fine because he's used to it…
it must mean he wasn't at first.
Mr. Ki, are you sure
you're okay with this?
Why do you look like that in the photos?
I'd like you to answer.
How is this even flirting?
You weren't shy of smiling
when you were drunk.
Thank you, Lord,
for blessing us with today's meal.
Our whole family hasn't
gathered to eat in a while,
so let us enjoy this feast
and return safely home.
In the name of Jesus we pray,
amen.
You. What's with that
actress you're dating?
- We're not dating.
- How can you be silly enough
to let reporters catch you
with that tacky clown of an actress?
This tacky clown of an actress
is thrilled by the name-calling.
Why were you at the police station?
It's one of the last places
you should ever be spotted at.
Assemblyman Ki,
do you still keep tabs on Seon-gyeom?
People might think you actually love him.
Of course, I love him.
I'm his father, aren't I?
Why can't you be
even a fraction like your sister?
She's been a golfer her whole life
and always managed to win first place.
What about you though?
The best you can do is second place
and now you get in fights like a kid?
Be ashamed of yourself.
Dad, that's a weird way to put it.
Can he fight if he was a kid?
Did you come out on top?
Of course, he should have.
He's my son, isn't he?
Anyway,
what a proud moment
for a national athlete.
I see you've been patient.
You normally would have
given me an earful for every incident.
I was busy campaigning.
I'm a very busy man.
You sure do know a lot for a busy man.
I'll take care
of the disciplinary committee,
-so stay put.
-Are you going to pay them?
Why did you have to assault them?
I never asked for much.
You have everything.
All I wanted was for you
to stay on the national team.
Is that seriously so hard to do?
And why choose to be a runner?
I should have had you play soccer instead.
What's the use of a man with no ambition?
Isn't it better to not have any rather
than grinding yourself to have some?
Are you mocking me right now?
About the disciplinary committee…
Don't stop the disciplinary committee.
Let me get punished.
You darn punk!
You being disciplined
will put a dent in my political career!
Why must you be disciplined?
It's not like you used drugs for
leisure or performance-enhancement.
You only roughed up some kids!
Shall we go with the latter then?
It sounds more like a juicy story.
I'll go before I ruin lunch even more.
Happy anniversary.
What's his problem?
Couldn't you…
have done a better job raising him?
If that were my priority,
I would have become Mother of the Year,
not the Queen of Cannes.
A damn mess like always.
Seon-gyeom!
Hey, Seon-gyeom!
I was told to give this to you.
It's japchae.
-Eun-bi.
-Aren't you going to take it?
I'm sorry.
For not introducing me to your girlfriend?
I will next time.
Head back inside.
Park May, darn you.
You sure know how to pick a good movie.
What a way to end the movie.
Damn it. Damn this musical!
HAPPY PHARMACY
What's he eating?
Is he actually eating something?
What were you eating?
Japchae.
Why were you eating that out here
for everyone to see?
I was hungry. Were you out today?
I was at my roommate's office.
Did you come here to see me?
-Yes.
-For what reason?
I wasn't able to come up with one.
How about this?
You're here to return the clothes.
-That's right.
-As if.
I didn't hand them over in a lunchbox.
You should have called.
Maybe I should have.
But my phone's turned off.
Seriously.
Why have you turned ditzy overnight?
And what's with the wound on your face?
Hold on. I happen to have
an ointment with me.
Here.
Thanks.
I also have a plaster.
Not there. Here.
-Why are you always hurt?
-Beats me. Maybe I do seek attention.
I saw your photo.
It was taken at your house.
-I thought you didn't have one.
-I only do…
on days like this.
A home is where you come back to…
just like you did now.
-Did you just touch me?
-I didn't want to waste it.
-Why squeeze out so much?
-That usually happens with a new one.
It's my fault for having a cut too, right?
I bet it is.
About your home…
If you don't have one, why not
get yourself something similar instead?
It's what I did.
A place I can come back to.
When X is one, this will be A.
Then what do you need to solve this?
-Factorization and reduction of fractions.
-Right, then we get two.
Since the two equations must be equal,
So A is two, and number three
is the correct answer.
Got it? That's how you solve it.
An art student who's good at math?
You shouldn't exist.
A sports major who hasn't given up
on math. You shouldn't exist either.
Actually, no. I'm not giving up
so that I can fool Mom.
What's with that tone?
I can't tell if you're
being negative or not.
-Kids these days--
-Whatever.
Your mom doesn't know
you want to be an athlete, right?
I'd be dead if she did.
If it's her you want to fool,
you should study at home
and not at a coffee shop like this.
Mom's never home. Only her son is.
Why do you hate Ye-jun so much?
An only child wouldn't know.
Why must there be a reason?
I just don't get
why your smart brother can't tutor you.
Because he doesn't understand
why I can't solve this equation.
He doesn't get why my grades suck.
I mean…
Ye-jun, how can I solve this?
"The two real roots are alpha and beta…"
Minus five and minus three respectively.
Put that in the equation
to get the answer.
I want you to tell me
how to draw that conclusion.
This is the same as the earth being round.
Goh Ye-chan, get over her. It's urgent!
I'm not kidding.
Goh Ye-chan!
What?
-I have a question to ask.
-What is it?
How is it that you're so dumb?
Honestly, I'm curious.
-What the…
-Damn it.
Ye-chan, it's for real this time.
What now?
Turn off the light on your way out.
You!
So Ye-jun's to blame.
Anyway, let's get back to studying.
Are you seeing someone?
Why not ask about my first love too?
Yes, tell me.
Who, what, when, where, why, and how.
I know you're only trying
to get out of studying.
It worked until now.
Next question.
When was your first love?
It's never happened for me yet.
-Why not?
-Because it hasn't!
Anyway, next question. Please.
-Please.
-Please!
-Next question.
-Please tell me!
I don't have one!
It's the lookbook for the photo shoot
from the States.
You'll be in clothes by Seomyung Fashion.
The concept will be
the mix-and-match of high-end clothing…
Why are you glaring like that?
I see you're desperately trying
to win the chairman's favor.
I was just admiring your tenacity.
I'm desperately trying to get you
to wear our clothes.
Why can't you see that?
I don't like you.
I wonder if you're aware
of how cute you are when you're this way.
I'm telling you to stop using my brother.
How can I
when it leads to conversations with you
and ad campaigns?
It's like you're holding him hostage.
Then let's sign the contract.
That came out of the blue.
You're the one putting ideas in my head.
As if.
What will you do about
Seon-gyeom's assault?
He seems to have done it
knowing he'd be disciplined.
Oh, that.
Have you ever argued with your brother?
We've never spent enough time together
to do so.
-Did you two get into a fight?
-I'm not sure
if he got angry with me or I provoked him.
Seon-gyeom rarely gets angry.
If he did though,
then that'd be on you.
But I never do anything wrong.
I'd only do so
if I was treated the wrong way.
While we discuss who's at fault,
your father will have the issue dismissed.
I know this isn't right,
but I get why Dad would do that.
Seon-gyeom's my brother.
An assault on fellow athletes?
That could end his career.
Being in the States must have drained
all the Korean blood out of you.
An assault charge
isn't the end of the world,
especially in this country.
No one was injured severely
and it was over nothing anyway.
We were slacking off,
so Seon-gyeom only taught us a lesson.
By the sound of it,
it seems like a simple scuffle
between the athletes.
It wasn't even a scuffle.
Seon-gyeom was only setting us straight.
Calling this an assault
is embarrassing on our part.
We were out of line.
-I'm sorry, Seon-gyeom.
-I'm sorry.
Why make a big fuss over
what is only a simple argument?
It was an assault,
and I'll be punished for it.
Punished for what?
There's no victim here.
They're not saying
that you assaulted them,
so why call it one yourself?
Seon-gyeom, isn't it odd for this case
to only have an offender and no victim?
Just be careful from now on.
I'm sure Seon-gyeom
is sorry for his actions,
so let's not make a big deal out of this.
Make good when you can, then.
We should end the session.
-Sure thing.
-This concludes the hearing.
Is this all that we're discussing?
Must there be more?
We should wrap this up.
Has this been the story
for all disciplinary hearings?
Full of happy endings
with no offenders or victims?
Watch your mouth.
Can't you see that you're
muddying up clear water?
There has rarely been
a hearing for track athletes!
Talking of rare sights,
will you call it an assault
if I beat them right now?
What?
I doubt it, right?
There's no way.
-I bet you're exhausted.
-Right.
I made reservations at a restaurant.
Go and eat.
Coach.
What did you do with
what Woo-sik gave you?
Didn't you hand it in?
Seon-gyeom, coach will come by soon.
I'll hand him
all the evidence of the assault.
It'll help you get a lesser punishment.
Don't worry about me.
Are you sure about this?
You know, it's been great
to be hospitalized.
I don't get beat up in here.
I would like to think
that I could change something
with my courage. That's all.
It was nothing.
There was no use submitting it.
Who are you to decide that?
Did you also tell them to say the things
back there?
Hey, it's all over.
Don't cause another issue.
-Sir--
-This wouldn't have happened
if you had talked it out
from the very beginning.
Are you saying it was wrong of me
to speak up from the get-go?
Because you've brought them here?
How dare you talk like that to me?
Are you just going to feign ignorance?
-Aren't you embarrassed?
-You punk!
Sir, we're at the association building.
-Please don't.
-Let me go, you bastard!
You must think you're entitled
because of your dad.
I wouldn't have been able to do this
if that was the case.
Seon-gyeom, that's enough!
You're going to pay for this.
Sir, you should go. Please.
Discipline him properly.
Go on your way. Look natural.
Sir!
Hey, let's go.
You're sorry for being rash?
You can say the same thing
to Woo-sik too, right?
Oddly, I don't feel bad for him.
Did he ever do you wrong?
If that concerns you so much,
I'll give it a thought.
So quit being hypocritical.
Thanks to your dad,
you can get away with anything.
-Let's just go.
-Let go, damn it.
Am I wrong? Why do you act so noble?
What's so different about us?
You're right.
No, I'm worse.
Because I gave him hope.
Where did you get this?
He's my buddy now.
Why does he look this way, though?
Are you Ms. Oh Mi-joo?
-Yes.
-You can wait with me.
-He'll be out soon.
-Okay.
It's an honor to meet you.
Why did you want to see me?
I just wanted to say hi
since you're looking after my son.
He's lucky to have you as his father.
This is only a week-long job,
yet you're taking an interest.
And yet, I feel sad
since he doesn't appreciate me.
Am I just a foolish dad?
To tell you the truth,
Seon-gyeom got himself in a pickle.
Just like his dad,
he could be difficult to deal with.
He can be unpredictable when he's upset.
I'd like you to keep him under control.
As an interpreter, I'm sure you know
how to sugarcoat everything.
Pardon?
I'd like you to report
on everything that he does.
You'll be following him around
as his interpreter.
I trust that you won't have
other intentions
such as chatting him up.
Here. Take it.
I've seen this situation before.
-What is this?
-How should I put it?
For your expenses?
Are you paying me
with the citizens' hard-earned money?
Wouldn't they think this is a moral deed
if I were to give alms with their money?
Professor Hwang told me
that you grew up well
despite your adverse upbringing.
If you're uncomfortable with this,
let's just say
that I'm giving you some allowance
in your parents' stead.
Why would you replace my parents?
It's not your fault that they passed away.
Then we can just say
that it's condolence money.
Sir, the intermission is almost over.
The mayor is already seated.
Okay.
I'll see you on Jeju Island,
Ms. Interpreter.
I trust that you'll do well.
I should still be sleeping at this hour.
I really don't want to go.
-Ms. Oh!
-Yes?
Hello, Ms. Ki Eun-bi.
Get in. We're going the same way.
Right. How did you know me?
Of course, I didn't.
He recognized you.
Ms. Seo will arrive tomorrow.
We don't need to wear her clothes today.
Let me make a call.
What's going on?
With your interpreter.
She interprets for me.
Being the best in something
is actually quite boring.
At times, people need
something to look up to.
I have to look into the mirror.
Can we skip this one? It's boring.
Because I'm Korean.
Yes, I'm fluent in English.
But many athletes are more fluent
than I am.
I'm still the best golfer out there.
Why use English
when the number-one golfer is Korean?
It's a chance to let everyone hear Korean.
That's commendable reasoning.
I'm sorry, but please excuse me
for a minute.
She's so cool.
Do you even understand her?
You should treat her well.
She's looking out for you.
-I'll leave.
-Okay.
Mr. Ki, I'm Reporter Yoo A-in
from Sports Tomorrow.
I came here today
since you'd be busy training tomorrow.
-Do you have some time?
-I'm sorry.
I'm a big fan.
Did you read the article
about the scandal?
I wrote that.
Is it true that you assaulted
a fellow athlete?
Everyone's sweeping it under the rug.
But you see, I have great interest in you.
I just want to check the facts.
-Can you make some time?
-I'm sorry.
Gosh.
Damn it.
I love him so much.
What's so great about him?
Make sure you take
good photos of him tomorrow.
That way,
our article will get many clicks.
Got it.
I can't blame Seon-gyeom
for his father's rude behavior.
I feel so uncomfortable around him.
Excuse me. Could you tell me
where Assemblyman Ki Jeong-do's room is?
I'm sorry. I'm afraid we can't.
You see, he had hired me
as an interpreter.
I have something to give back to him.
Is it not possible?
I'm sorry.
No, I understand. I'm sorry.
He's not here yet. He'll arrive tomorrow.
Ms. Ki.
I didn't know that.
By the way, why do you have his belonging?
Well…
Oh, that was an invasion of privacy.
I'm sorry.
I just saw you and wanted to say hi.
Seon-gyeom found himself
a good interpreter.
No, I'm not a good interpreter.
I should get going then. Goodbye.
Ms. Oh--
Who are you?
Ms. Oh.
What was that?
Are you crying?
You startled me.
Well,
I'm truly sorry about this.
I thought you were just
out for a jog like me. Anyway…
I think I know
what went through your mind,
so I'm really sorry about that.
Why would you run late at night
like some lunatic?
You're right.
I must be insane. I had trouble digesting.
Why? That was some good food.
I had a lot on my mind.
I couldn't do anything.
So if I were to go by the book,
I shouldn't have been here.
But you have a tight schedule.
A photo shoot, an interview,
and the training.
I need to run a bit more.
Could you wait for me?
Try to calm down in the meantime.
How are you feeling?
Have you calmed down a bit?
Let's stay here a bit more.
Sure. Let's do that.
Had I had a gun,
I would have shot you in the head.
I'm sorry again.
Does that mean that lighter
was for self-defense?
Something like that.
Did you bring it with you?
It's at the training center.
-What?
-But I can't go there.
Why not?
Because I assaulted my juniors.
We should walk now, right?
Let's go.
The association rewards its athletes
whenever they set a new record.
But let's be honest.
That doesn't happen very often.
However,
there are countless athletes
who strive for that reward.
Woo-sik is one of them.
One day, he asked me a question.
"Why do you run?"
To him, I was an inspiration.
But I couldn't give him an answer.
"Could there be a reason?
I'm just running."
It could be because it's your job.
You need to make a living.
I've never worried about making money,
so I don't think that's it.
So this is how they felt.
You do sound quite obnoxious.
I couldn't answer that question,
but I think I wanted to tell him this.
"I was punished,
so those who assaulted you
will get punished as well."
You know, that's a given.
But I couldn't do it.
Gosh.
The race only lasts ten seconds.
I wonder if striving that hard
for those ten seconds is worthwhile.
You see,
I'd run like nothing happened
even if I had a rough day.
I just forget about the past
and start the day afresh.
That was how I lived my entire life.
But this time around,
I don't think I should do that.
I don't want to.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
You don't always have
to overcome everything.
You can rest on the weekends.
So if you don't want to do something,
just don't.
I mean it.
But then again, I can't speak for myself
since I came here
even though I didn't want to.
I'm actually a loser.
You didn't want to do this.
Not because of you.
I was happy to see you.
I still am.
This is for tomorrow.
We're finally shaking hands.
You're right.
I hope we get along.
Likewise.
You didn't get a convertible?
It's Jeju Island.
It's quite windy here.
Were you worried that I'd get hurt?
Yes.
Those sunglasses really make you look
like a gangster.
Why are you here?
I thought you were rehabilitating.
I just came to watch.
The coach was considerate.
He invited me for some fresh air.
Considerate?
He brought me along with him
when I couldn't even run.
I'm grateful for that.
By the way,
about the disciplinary committee…
Seeing how everyone's here,
no one was punished, were they?
I'm still happy.
Right. I am sad that I can't run with you,
but when will we ever visit
Jeju Island again?
I'm relieved that you're okay.
I don't regret anything.
I don't resent anyone either.
Those two didn't get punished.
That means
they didn't do anything wrong officially.
Then
I should forgive them…
since they're innocent.
Can you forgive them?
No?
Then don't.
You have the right to do that.
Thank you. Look at the cameras.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
Executive Director Seo,
thank you for all your hard work.
It's all because Director Seo
didn't do his job. Thanks.
Did you have to put it that way?
You know how to make me feel shitty.
Since you're all here,
shall we get some fresh air?
The national track and field will begin
their off-season training today.
Wouldn't it be a beautiful sight
if we cheered for them?
You're the only one who makes me wait.
Is that a hobby of yours?
Is that not funny? It is for me.
Eun-bi's solo shoot will begin soon.
Join her after your training.
The foreign press will be there,
so make sure you smile.
Since when were they so interested in us?
Don't you know? It's because of you.
You did well in Doha,
and you're the face of track and field.
-You're handsome--
-Most importantly,
you want to dress me up.
That's only because of your fame.
It pays off well.
I heard you stopped by. What for?
I felt bad about getting upset with you.
Was that junior you mentioned Kim Woo-sik?
His leg looked badly injured.
Are you still angry?
I'm no longer upset with you. No, wait.
I was never upset with you.
Should I be happy to hear that?
But I'm still going to be upset with them.
I'm going to stay upset.
And I'll continue being mad.
Gosh, it's been ages.
I'll take a photo now.
Go!
Good work.
Sir, here.
I thought
there would just be more reporters.
Are we some monkeys in a zoo or what?
-He broke his previous record.
-Really? What's your record?
Right now, it's about 10.25 seconds.
-That's nice.
-He used to be faster, though.
All right, then. Goodbye.
No, right?
-What do you mean?
-Did you bribe them?
Tell me you didn't.
Don't act so naive.
It was nothing.
Don't cause a mess.
There are many people watching today.
-Answer me.
-That's why
you shouldn't have allowed me
to come here.
I gave you a chance.
What's on his mind?
Yesterday
and today.
He seems to be all alone on the tracks.
But then, he seems to have it all.
Even when he's not running, he seems
to be doing so with all his might.
All right, get in position.
In track and field, one must begin.
Get ready.
At the start line…
Set!
an athlete can make a decision
whether to run until the finish line
or not run at all.
I chose…
not to run.
However, I still couldn't answer
why I ran in the first place.
Mr. Ki, are you feeling unwell?
Is this about the scandal?
Is the rumor true?
Why didn't you run?
Because I couldn't.
I assaulted
my juniors.
You seem too fine,
and it's starting to scare me.
I'm scared you might jump in,
so please take a few steps back.
I know this place.
It's the road to the afterlife.
-Hey.
-Miss!
Do you really think I hired you
just as an interpreter?
I heard you received money
from Assemblyman Ki.
You really are the gofer's gofer.
Was it Ki Seon-gyeom who assaulted you?
You seem to want to know a lot about me.
As if.
Paint me a picture.
What if I refuse?
-Ms. Oh.
-Are you giving me orders
to make things up as I go?
I never said to take
your interpreter with you.
-You don't need to say anything about me.
-What do you mean?
Your story is what matters the most to me.
Everything you've said so far
seems to be hinting at that.
I like you.
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park