ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
I'm not insane. I'm Ki Seon-gyeom.
I don't care who you are,
but I'm glad you still have it with you.
I'm glad you're glad.
Are you guys smoking buddies?
Are you smoking now?
-Would you be mad?
-No. Just avoid the newspaper.
For example, the police station.
How did that end?
I guess you could say
that justice was served.
Are you going to stand there
while we talk about such heinous topics?
No, I'll disappear now. You two can talk.
I had a fun time.
You call yourself a gofer,
which means you know your place.
Mr. Jeong will email Seon-gyeom's
schedule and information to you.
Okay.
Gosh, she's a psychopath.
She's not normal.
The Ki Seon-gyeom that I've just met?
CHOI TAE-RI AND KI SEON-GYEOM DATING
What's your deal with that gofer?
You guys seemed to have a story.
Don't hold your breath.
I'm just asking as an agent.
In that case, I'll have to say
that this is private.
And if I'm asking as the woman
you once liked?
Why would you ask me this now?
You should have asked back then.
Is that so? Then I should
ask about this now, right?
CHOI TAE-RI AND KI SEON-GYEOM DATING
Front page? A love scandal?
I'm so proud of you.
I bought a newspaper for the first time.
-Who is this?
-It's you.
-They say it's lovey-dovey.
-Not me.
"Choi Tae-ri"?
She's the famous actress
with whom you did a photo shoot.
Why can't you recognize her?
She's even met your mom.
I heard she debuted in a movie
that starred your mom.
She was her future mother-in-law.
It was fate.
You even walked down
the red carpet together.
Everyone's having a field day with it.
People are so sharp-eyed.
How did they recognize us?
Thanks to them,
guess what the most-searched phrase was.
"Choi Tae-ri's boyfriend".
Share your thoughts on that.
What's there to share?
I didn't win a medal.
You should be sad that they didn't get
a better photo.
Let me make this clear.
We're not lovey-dovey.
Aren't you Ki Seon-gyeom?
-Do you work out here?
-Who are you?
Are you asking me who I am?
Yes.
We met a few days ago. Don't you remember?
Is it because I changed my makeup style?
I'm sorry, but I don't remember you.
But then again, I had full makeup on
during that photo shoot.
But still, you're so mean.
It's anything but lovey-dovey.
In fact, she gave me a bruise.
Please give an official announcement
that we're not dating.
We can do that after launching
our photo shoot.
I invested a lot of money
into this photo shoot.
It'll attract more reporters,
and you'll be publicized. Awesome.
This is the official announcement.
Let me see.
Your skin is looking nice.
You don't need anything.
Just get a massage before the photo shoot.
If you're done checking my face,
I should get going.
I have training to do.
It's adorable how aloof he is.
Wait.
When was the fourth time?
I don't recall.
You won't remember even if I tell you.
Whatever. Give me my lighter.
It's precious to me.
So did you go?
-Go where?
-That night.
No, I don't want to go.
No, I'm not going to go. What's with you?
It didn't seem like dating violence,
so I was relieved.
-What?
-The lighter is at the training center.
It's a two-hour drive from here.
We're speaking the same language,
so why am I lost?
-Did you live abroad or something?
-No.
If it takes that long,
you can return it
when we meet again for work.
You said you were unemployed,
but you're an interpreter.
That's not my main job, though.
I'm not even getting paid for this gig.
It's like charity.
You must enjoy interpreting
if you're doing it for charity.
You do charity to own up to something.
I didn't want you to feel embarrassed.
I see.
What was that?
-That's me.
-Have you not seen that before?
No. I don't monitor myself.
Actually, I wanted to treat you
to an overdue meal
and ask you for a favor.
What is it?
Can you not tell anyone that you went
to the station because of me?
If that crazy bitch…
If your president finds out,
I might have to kneel.
She probably doesn't care about that
right now
because of the love scandal.
Also, you were the victim in the incident,
so you shouldn't have to kneel.
About that scandal…
I'm not dating that actress.
Are you getting to know each other?
Am I that charming?
Why would she want to get to know me
when we only met once.
I looked into it,
and Tae-ri vehemently denied it.
I could see how enraged she was
just by reading it.
So many articles were mocking you.
They call you Tae-ri's boyfriend
forgetting that you're a national athlete.
I just don't get it.
-What's wrong?
-Are you trying to get on my good side?
Yes. Will you keep it a secret?
Did I offend you?
It feels strange that you're defending me.
I'm used to this, so I'm fine.
I'm used to being linked
with other people's names.
To Tae-ri, I'm his boyfriend.
To you, I'm a lunatic.
I should get going.
I'll keep it a secret.
I'm not hungry right now,
and I should go before the rush hour.
Why are you in a hurry?
Can't you just stay for a meal?
It seems like you want to get rid of me
after the meal.
Then text me a few dates
when you're available.
I'll take a look and reply back.
-You're asking for my number?
-Yes.
Okay. I'll text you.
Okay.
What was that?
BACK SURGERY
20,000,000 WON!
YOU'RE REALLY NOT
YOU'RE REALLY STUBBORN
YOU REALLY ARE STUBBORN
You're really not going to give up,
are you?
This is Jeong Ji-hyun.
Here's Ki Seon-gyeom's schedule.
He's going to Jeju Island.
Jeju Island is nice.
I should finish this up.
Focus on work. You should finish it.
Why is he wearing earphones?
He doesn't want to talk, does he?
It's not like him to be on his phone.
He's bragging about dating, isn't he?
Choi Tae-ri denied it already.
That's what celebrities say all the time.
Ask him if they're really dating.
-I don't want to speak with him.
-Okay.
Gosh, Choi Tae-ri.
ON THE 11TH, ITAEWON STATION AT 1 P.M.
Su-gyeong, hi.
-Did she stay up?
-She had a meeting.
Gosh, good luck.
Hey.
What is this?
I saw you finished the Romanian movie.
It was uploaded.
I said you could take it slow.
The interpretation schedule came out.
I had to finish the movie
before preparing for it.
This is my first time doing sports.
-What's this? What are you looking at?
-The goods from the film market.
I found a pretty nice musical film.
They're going to suffer big time.
Don't you think you should give it a try
since you've already suffered once?
You've done a musical before.
Care to read the transcript?
You'll be crying a river.
Isn't this the client who wanted us
to sync the subs with the lip movements?
"Are these lyrics or sentences?
Am I translating or writing a poem?
Is it day or night?"
I was crying a river too.
-I'll pay you handsomely.
-Ten million?
Get lost.
Hold on.
Who is this?
On the 11th, Itaewon Station at 1 p.m.
On the 13th, City Hall Station at 1 p.m.
On the 19th, Gwanghwamun Station at 1 p.m.
If these don't work, I'll text you again.
This is so detailed.
What is it? Is something going on
between you and your handsome fate?
We're too different
for something to go on.
-As long as you're not pregnant.
-That should never happen.
We may never meet again after this gig.
I choose the second option.
Let's make it 4 p.m.
Let's rehearse as well.
Seon-gyeom.
The training will begin.
-What are you doing?
-Texting.
Are you really dating…
What?
It's nothing.
Okay.
You're going to pay for dating men
based on their looks.
-Didn't Seok-won teach you a lesson?
-Why would you bring him up?
-It wasn't because of his looks.
-What's worse
is that he received
the best picture award.
What?
What? It can't be.
BEST PICTURE AWARD
HAN SEOK-WON
He actually got it.
It has finally happened.
This world has gone insane.
He'll be invited
to an international film festival.
It suits the Cannes, right?
The projects I translated were nominated
but never awarded.
Could this be…
He better not accept it.
Does he think he's a big shot?
Is he Bong Joon-ho? My ass.
Who are you talking to?
I'm terrified right now.
Ki Seon-gyeom?
Why is he in a photo with Yook Ji-woo?
Do you know him?
The national track and field athlete?
Be more specific.
The scandal with Choi Tae-ri--
Right, her boyfriend.
-That's his name?
-Yes.
-What about him?
-Is he very famous?
He sure is.
His entire family is well known.
How could you not know this
as Yook Ji-woo's fan?
He's Yook Ji-woo and Ki Jeong-do's son,
and Ki Eun-bi's younger brother.
-Go!
-We only remember athletes
who come in first.
-That's it!
-But he's famous
despite being second place.
Go!
That's it!
Hey. Get ready.
-Get up, Gyu-deok. Get up.
-I'm dying.
Hurry up and move. Get in position.
That's good!
Seon-gyeom, you're doing well these days.
I love your vigor.
I wonder why.
Is this the power of love?
I want to beat you at least once
before I retire.
You want to beat me? You?
Every time.
Are you dying or what?
Have you become more motivated
now that you'll retire soon?
I've always been motivated.
You didn't look all that motivated.
I thought you've been a runner-up
because you wanted to.
I want to come in first place too.
I just don't say it out loud.
Why didn't I know?
You? Because you only watched her movies.
You're right.
I'm used to this, so I'm fine.
I'm used to being linked
with other people's names.
I didn't know he had such a story.
I feel even more distant,
not that we were ever close.
-What do you mean?
-I mean…
I've barely managed to become a translator
by building a career
through my work and studies.
Since I represent myself,
I'm striving to support just me.
But then, he has his own struggles too.
So? Are you jealous?
That he has a family?
His life is filled with everyone
around him but himself.
Whereas, I only have me.
NAME
KI SEON-GYEOM
Yes, Coach.
Right now?
Okay.
Drop this, and I'll kill you.
I told you to buy me cigarettes.
The convenience store nearby
didn't have your brand.
Then you should've gone
to another convenience store.
I couldn't smoke thanks to you,
you bastard.
Also, Seon-gyeom beat me during training.
Am I a joke to you?
Damn it.
Hey, are you okay?
-You son of a bitch.
-I'm sorry.
How dare you touch me?
Do you want to end up behind bars?
Do you have money? Connections?
Or parents like everyone else?
All you have are these two legs.
What an impudent asshole.
Do you think Seon-gyeom has your back?
Do you think you're like him
since you're close?
I thought I was him all this time.
What the hell are you saying?
Have you gone insane?
-Hey, that's enough.
-Let go of me.
-Hey, explain it to me.
-You beat me for no reason back in school.
But now you beat me
whenever he breaks his record,
looks down on you,
or takes care of his juniors.
That's why
I thought I was a stand-in
for Ki Seon-gyeom.
Since I can't touch him, I instead…
Is that it?
Why would I be scared of him?
But you are
since he has everything.
Hey, you better shut up.
You're going to die tonight.
Damn it.
Run your mouth off again.
You bastard.
Woo-sik.
Woo-sik, open your eyes.
Let me see you. Are you okay?
-Are you?
-Seon-gyeom.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
Hey. Get up.
You shouldn't move.
The doctor said you should stay still.
Are you okay?
Why am I here?
-I should tell the Coach--
-I'll tell him myself.
I'll do it.
-I'll tell him everything later.
-When?
When your tendons have ruptured?
You need to receive surgery
for your thigh.
-A surgery?
-Woo-sik.
Let me ask you one more time.
Are you really okay?
Don't worry about the bills.
Get all the treatment you need.
You need to recover first.
Ask them to do everything they can.
Bye.
Don't do it.
-Don't do it, Seon-gyeom.
-Don't do what?
I don't know. I'm just…
-I'm just scared.
-Of what?
I hit Gyu-deok.
It was an accident.
He may kill me.
Then
let's tell them I hit him.
What do you mean?
You're a rising star.
You should win the prize money
and the medal.
Don't worry about anything.
He should be the one who's worried.
Bye.
That useless bastard…
Can you be more gentle?
Are you okay?
Damn it.
-Have you gone insane?
-That hurts!
-What's this about?
-Woo-sik.
You're here pretending to be
national athletes
when you should be in prison.
Do you want to go to prison?
Damn it.
Watch what you say.
I'm having a shitty day as is.
From the look of things,
he was beaten more than once.
He deserved it.
Ever since we were students,
he never knew his place.
I was just disciplining him.
Can't you see what he's done to me?
You're not showing any remorse.
He also got beaten up because of you.
You took part in it.
Are you sure that I took part in it?
I'm asking you. Are you sure?
You spoiled him
by embracing every mistake he's made.
Get lost while I'm being nice.
Quit playing nice
and telling me to apologize.
Apologize?
I'm not here…
to play nice.
Damn it.
You bastard, are you crazy? Are you?
Come here.
-What's going on?
-What is it?
Hey, open the door!
-What is this?
-What's going on?
Who the hell is fighting?
They're not our team, right?
Could they be sprinters?
I saw Seon-gyeom entering.
-Ki Seon-gyeom?
-Yes.
-Darn it.
-Is he hurt?
-Hey.
-Open the door!
Hey!
How are you still bad at making coffee?
-Is it not tasty?
-It's terrible.
Well, that took a long time…
-What's with your face?
-I assaulted someone, Coach.
You assaulted someone? Where? Outside?
When? Who? A civilian?
I assaulted the national athletes
Gyu-deok and Gi-beom just now.
-What?
-Who?
Word will spread quickly
as many people were watching.
Let's be clear here.
Did you say you assaulted them,
not disciplined them?
I don't think it's discipline
if I hit them
because I wasn't happy with them.
So you assaulted them.
Why are you telling me right away?
There's something else.
Will you fix the problem if I tell you?
Don't make a big deal out of this, okay?
-It happens all the time.
-Were you aware of it?
Then we'll summon
the disciplinary committee.
The disciplinary committee?
Why would a smart kid like you
do such a dumb thing?
Don't you know that he brought
those kids here himself?
So what?
I'm sure you had your reasons
for disciplining them.
-I wasn't disciplining them.
-I know.
So you guys fought.
It was an assault.
It was a power trip on both ends.
Hey.
Choose your words carefully.
People will get the wrong idea.
I wouldn't want them to.
Aren't you going to become a coach
once you retire?
Aren't you?
This will forever remain on your record!
The international contest is next year.
What kind of bastard destroys
his own future with such a trivial issue?
This isn't trivial.
Hey, go back to Seoul
until we decide what to do with you.
Get lost. I don't want to see your face.
Seon-gyeom.
Apologize to him. Will you end your… Hey!
If this is the flexibility
you expect from my future,
I don't think I have a future
to begin with.
I wanted to be a leader with principles.
Why do you run?
How can you ask me that
with a straight face?
Are you not going to answer?
Then what about you?
Well… It's because of my grandmother.
But you were the reason I started running.
Now, it's your turn.
Why do you run?
You know your house is right there, right?
I'd be a terrible son
for coming home drunk at this hour.
Who did you drink with?
You wouldn't know.
Why did you skip church?
Your mom was worried.
I've quit being Christian
for three years now.
Quit? It's not like smoking.
-Are you going to sleep?
-Yes.
-I smell oil.
-I use cheap paint.
It's going to get worse.
Plug up your nose.
I'm off to deliver my work.
Have some honey water when you wake up.
DON'T TOUCH, JUST LOOK
Shouldn't you be at work at this hour?
-Bosses shouldn't slack off.
-Can't we hang up?
Is this plant on display for me?
You should clean it up.
You should clean yourself up as well.
Why not sleep or do something else?
Can you just not exist?
Take out the trash while you're there.
Hello? Dan-ah?
Hello?
Damn, she hung up on me.
Why should I clean this up?
Damn, that stings.
Thinking like a true elite.
So when does the resort open?
I'd like to be present.
To do what?
It's not like that.
I just want to be there.
Ki Seon-gyeom will be too.
He'll only be there for the photo shoot
and his off-season training.
The dates just happened to overlap.
On the exact day of
Seomyung Resort's opening ceremony?
That's why I'm not wanted.
The chairman and
the director will be there,
so it'd be uncomfortable.
Director Seo does hate me, right?
Well, President Seo hates you too.
Do you hate me as well?
Forget it. There's no need to answer that.
I'm sure there's a reason
why only my brother and sister are going.
Being born a bastard sucks.
You weren't invited because
you have nothing to do with the event.
Here.
Since it's been sterilized,
-I'll put this on.
-How considerate of you.
It's quite odd considering how you look.
A gangster.
You can keep that.
It completes your look.
Get me some hallabong, okay?
-Hi.
-Welcome.
-One Americano to go, please.
-Sure.
Here.
Ms. Gofer. I mean, Ms. Oh.
Ms. Oh, are you sleeping?
My gosh. Goodness, hello.
When did I fall asleep?
Do you live around here?
Your clothes say that you do.
Right.
Judging by your clothes,
you must live elsewhere.
I don't. Neither does Seon-gyeom.
Which has me wondering.
How did you get to know him?
Goodness. Doesn't everyone know who he is?
You didn't know his name or occupation.
Did you meet him at the police station?
Miss, your coffee is ready.
Your coffee is ready.
I'll be heading to the restroom.
I'll see you in Jeju then.
Make sure you're prepared.
Here you go.
Please enjoy.
This painting…
It's ridiculously crude.
The angle…
doesn't do the painting justice.
Miss, are you okay?
My goodness!
The painting must've still been wet.
Oh, dear.
I'm fine, but the painting isn't.
It seems like a collectible.
Please don't worry about it.
I got it cheap
from a friend who paints for fun.
Meanwhile, your jacket seems expensive.
Oh, dear.
How about this?
Sell this to me
for double the original price.
What?
BASTARD 2
I cut my finger
cleaning after a broken flowerpot.
Can my fans wish me a full recovery?
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
See? My fans are saying I'm kind.
They want to be my flowerpot.
-Ms. Noh, it's me.
-Hey.
Hi.
Let me see.
Ms. Noh, did you take down my painting?
-You must not have liked it.
-Oh, you see…
I gave it to someone else.
A customer of mine took a liking to it.
Really? Who?
Really? Who is it exactly?
I'm sorry, but your painting--
That drawing tube…
We've met before, right?
Did you throw that?
No, of course not.
It's mine, but…
You're the one with the gun, right?
-That's right.
-I see.
I guess you must have settled
seeing how you're here.
It feels like I've made it out of prison.
Yes, it's all been settled.
I see you're acquainted.
He drew all the paintings here.
Really? Are you a painter?
Actually, no. I'm still a student.
Whether I'll become one
is still uncertain.
I'm Lee Yeong-hwa.
These are the kinds of paintings I draw.
Good morning.
It's good to see you, Ms. Seo. Inside--
Mr. Jeong.
Why do you keep letting my brother in?
What's wrong with you?
You see, Ms. Seo,
I don't have the authority
to keep the chairman's son out.
I work for Seomyung Group.
How are you their employee
when I haven't taken over yet?
You work for me.
Even if I do take over the group,
you'll still work for me.
Get your priorities straight, Mr. Jeong.
Is it a plant this time?
He just lets anything in.
What's wrong with your face?
I hit someone yesterday.
You had that in you?
As per protocol, I'll be disciplined.
I'm sorry.
You're not the type
to act without a reason,
so I guess he had it coming.
You can't justify violence.
And yet you still struck him.
Tell me who, how and why.
-They were my junior athletes.
-Right.
And I did it to get revenge.
Revenge?
I thought revenge
only motivated characters in soap operas.
How corny.
Don't tell me you think this is funny.
Wait. Can't I find it funny?
Of course not.
This is about athletes using
violence to discipline their juniors.
The young athlete they went after
beat his senior athletes and won
first place in his tournament debut.
They beat him to the point
where he almost needed a tendon implant,
and you find that funny?
So you could have told them off,
but you hit them instead.
I figured I'd feel a lot better
to give them a taste of their own medicine
and be punished for it.
Incidents like this
make me wonder if you're my brother
instead of Tae-woong.
I, for one, agree with your methods.
Being reprimanded
will have companies
drop all their campaigns and sponsorships.
No company wants to be seen
as an advocate for violence.
I'll make sure
this doesn't hurt your business.
You'll be reimbursed
for any cancellation fees regarding
the campaign deals and sponsorships.
We can sue the association
if they reprimand you.
Seomyung will provide legal aid.
Why are you bringing up a lawsuit?
On what grounds?
That the reprimand is unfair and cruel.
We'll get people to pity you,
despite having committed an assault.
But I don't find it unfair.
Yes, you do. Wasn't it out of justice?
We can turn this around
and make you a hero.
-Are you serious?
-Would I be joking?
Yes, you should be.
How can I be a hero
for assaulting someone?
You said you wouldn't
let this hurt my business.
Mr. Jeong, Seon-gyeom injured his face.
Book a dermatologist.
The photo shoot will happen as planned.
I'm only a package deal
that comes with Eun-bi.
Just find someone better you can manage.
Look at the package deal talk.
Eun-bi won't wear my clothes
if it wasn't for you.
If I only needed someone to run,
I would've signed Kwon Yeong-il.
I almost forgot that this company
was founded for you to play dress-up.
And to expand your fashion business.
To put it correctly,
it's to have my athlete of choice
wear the sportswear I designed.
I couldn't care less about
what happens to you.
-I'm only here for my agent.
-I wasn't finished.
But I was.
Goodness.
Look who it is.
Waiting actually paid off.
Right?
I can't introduce myself
unless you ask me who I am.
Don't just stand there and blink.
-I'm not interested.
-I'm not selling anything!
That I didn't mean.
Anyway, let me introduce myself.
I'm Yoo Jae-gyu,
the head of Choi Tae-ri's agency.
Why can't I get in touch with your agent?
Seo Dan-ah, that woman,
has been leaving me hanging.
She's not "that woman."
She's President Seo Dan-ah.
I don't care if she's a rich girl
running an agency for fun.
When there's a mess--
I don't think I've ever seen anyone
who is as passionate as Ms. Seo
when it comes to work.
Let's stay on topic here--
But there was no topic.
Milk has been spilled,
and you're just here to vent on someone.
So you know.
And I thought all athletes were dumb.
Dumb people are biased like that.
Hey! You little…
I know that you're trying
to use Tae-ri as a stepping stone.
Dreaming big, are we?
We only met once.
I am not dating Ms. Choi.
Who are you to conclude
that there is no relationship?
You're a nobody!
Look here.
You may not know this industry,
but there's evidence
to prove you're in a relationship
while there's none to prove you're not.
So find a new gym
while I'm asking you nicely.
Tae-ri must work out there
to keep up appearances.
As if that would solve anything.
It would only trigger more rumors.
Besides…
What? What is it?
Isn't that your car?
My car?
Hey, hold on. You can't do that!
When it comes to rumors,
I don't believe a word you say.
I'll keep an eye on you!
You little… Hey, wait!
Take photos of me and not my car.
Which district office are you from?
I reported the illegal parking.
Serves him right for parking his car
outside my building.
I wasn't in a forgiving mood today.
-And Seon-gyeom?
-He probably went to train.
He doesn't know how to unwind,
but he stresses himself to help others.
He wouldn't have cared
if he was the one beaten up.
He should learn to take care of himself.
-Mr. Jeong.
-Yes?
I feel like I offered
the perfect solution to our problem,
but Seon-gyeom seemed upset.
What did I do wrong?
I honestly don't get it.
Well…
Maybe you're just different
in the way you act and think.
No two people are the same anyway.
It'd be much easier
if we were all the same.
What a nuisance.
WHEN HUNGRY, BANG
I've arrived,
but there's no need to hurry.
Where on earth are you?
Knock, knock, Mr. Ki.
Why aren't you answering?
Are you sick?
Were you in an accident or something?
This is bad.
Is this how you blow me off?
This isn't the way to treat someone
you'll be working with.
Being a national athlete
doesn't make you a king.
I should forgive him since I'm pretty
and kindhearted.
What else can I do?
What the hell?
He sure is fast.
Where are you?
You just ran past me.
Head back this way and--
Hello?
Damn him.
What the hell?
-You ran a little slower than earlier.
-What?
Is it because you knew I'd still be here?
If I ran too fast,
I figured I might run past you again.
I texted you the wrong date.
I meant the 18th, not the 13th.
I sensed something was off.
It's okay.
What matters is that you're here.
Are you sure you're okay?
Thanks to you, I was entertained.
You ran so fast
that I couldn't even stop you.
First, let's rehearse.
I won't miss a lot of things
if we rehearse beforehand.
Can we do something else?
Is it because you don't want to work?
Yes. Instead, I'll make up for being late.
You're awfully confident.
Then should we go eat something first?
-Are you hungry?
-No.
Me neither.
Then do you like movies?
-No.
-You don't like movies?
How could you hate movies?
I never said I hate them.
Then would you like to watch my movie?
-Your movie?
-Yes.
Well, sure.
-Just the two of us?
-Yes.
It premiers today, but today might be
my only chance to watch it.
I mean, in theaters.
It's an independent film.
Let's go.
Here are the emergency exits
and safety regulations
in case of an emergency.
For your safety…
Don't you feel safe
when you're sitting in a dark theater?
That's why I like theaters.
It seems more dangerous.
It's dark and scary.
It could be if you were alone.
But don't worry. From this moment on,
we'll all be in the dark.
TRANSLATION: OH MI-JOO
How was the movie?
It was boring.
I see.
You weren't even in the movie.
My name came out at the very end.
It said "Translated by Oh Mi-joo."
I see.
Not many people notice though.
No one waits until the end of the credits.
So in order to see you,
people have to wait until the end.
You're right.
I didn't mean
your translations were boring.
I never really enjoyed watching movies.
As you've noticed,
the movie is really difficult.
So I had a hard time translating it.
You need to understand it well
to translate it properly.
I know I'm exaggerating,
but I probably watched it about 100 times.
Depending on the emotions
and relations of the characters,
the translation changes.
Isn't that interesting?
Do you drink?
-What if I do?
-Would you like to go for one?
Do you know
what people call this kind of stuff?
-A date.
-No.
A business dinner.
Let's go.
I worked on my first foreign movie
and saw my name on the screen,
but because of the font,
it looked like it said Oh Ma-joo.
It was as if my name was "Homage."
But you said not a lot of people wait
until the end anyway.
You make it sound like
I'm an attention-seeker.
An "AS."
For some reason, I'm offended.
I guess you know what that means.
A fellow athlete called me an AS
for taking a photo with my mom
on the red carpet.
Right. Your mother is Yook Ji-woo,
isn't she?
I almost translated the movie
she once starred in.
I don't watch my mom's movies.
And when I was young,
I couldn't because it was R-rated.
I think I know which one it is.
One of her films is R-rated
because it's too gory.
How gory is it?
Ji-woo plays a very cold-hearted killer.
She catches the bad guys
and tortures them in all kinds of ways.
Later on, she plucks out their eyeballs,
stabs them, and skins them.
It was the first Korean movie
to skin humans like that.
Why would you watch that?
I just like movies.
Is that why you became a translator?
Well…
The first time I watched a movie
in a movie theater, there was this line
that consoled me a lot.
But if there were no subtitles,
I never would've known what that meant.
"I wonder who it is that lays a bridge
between the two different languages.
I'd also love to do that for a living."
That's what came to my mind.
So I just did my best
to become a translator,
and here I am.
It makes me feel really rich.
I have to understand a movie
from start to finish
to share it with the world.
And it makes me feel like
I'm holding on to something bountiful.
It makes me feel like I have a lot
and it makes me feel rich.
Here. I hope you become rich too. Cheers.
Here's your rolled omelet.
-Thank you.
Enjoy.
That day,
you threw that drawing tube very nicely.
Do you throw things a lot?
Do you have trouble
controlling your anger?
Before I became a sprinter,
I was a javelin thrower.
And I rarely end up in a situation
where I have to control my anger.
Well, you got hurt.
I can easily tell it was a fist-fight.
I'm sorry. I just told you
I rarely end up in a situation
where I have to control my anger,
but let's say I don't control my anger.
Seon-gyeom.
-Do people tell you you're weird?
-They tell me I'm annoying.
Why are you laughing?
It's just that
people tend to be intimidated
when someone like you are around.
What kind of person am I?
Well…
You're mentally strong.
But not with alcohol.
You haven't been drinking that much.
Why did you want to drink
when you're a lightweight?
The guy in the movie seemed happy
after drinking alcohol.
So I figured maybe I might feel the same.
I'm not a big drinker,
but I still wanted to drink.
You're not a big drinker,
but you still wanted to drink?
I don't know how that feels
because I can hold my liquor.
But why did you choose to sprint?
Because you run fast?
I came in last in my first race.
All they ever do is run,
so I'm sure it wasn't easy to beat them.
You must have felt down.
My first goal
was to run faster
than the guy right in front of me.
I tried my best and finally managed
to come in faster than him.
Then my next goal was to beat
the next guy in front of me.
I kept doing that one by one,
and after a while,
no one was in front of me.
That's how I graduated high school
with the fastest record.
I see.
How does it feel to run for a living?
You're just out of breath.
When you run,
you don't think about what's behind you.
The only thing that matters is
what's right in front of you.
Normally, it's the finish line.
But today, it was you.
If I timed myself today,
it might have been
a little over nine seconds.
Nine seconds? Is that good?
Gosh, of course. Totally.
What's wrong with you? My goodness.
-I'm okay.
-You're wasted.
You're an LW, aren't you?
An LW? What's that?
A lousy woman?
It means you're a lightweight.
My gosh.
Where are you going?
Where should I go?
Home, of course.
And tell me you know where you live.
Try to sober up a little.
I don't have a home.
Why are you flirting with me?
How is this even flirting?
I don't see how it isn't.
You keep smiling when you rarely smile.
You have a place to sleep, right?
I'll leave you to go on your own.
I'll do the same.
Keep this up and I might end up
making a mistake.
A mistake?
Something like this.
But…
I'm going to control myself
since we'll be meeting again.
I'll be off now.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Gosh, you seem really drunk. Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
He doesn't look okay.
Let's just go.
Why are you back?
Why are you smiling at me like that?
It makes me feel like I abandoned you.
Is that why you came back?
Let's say I felt a bit guilty.
How do you plan to go home?
My car is parked nearby.
I'll take my car.
It's late, so let me give you a ride.
No, it's okay.
Let me walk you to your car.
I don't want to go
to the police station again.
Come on.
About that line from the movie…
What was it?
"Why do we fall?
So we can learn to pick ourselves up."
You should also learn to pick yourself up.
Come on.
There we go.
Look. She's here.
They're still there?
Is she looking at us?
If Seon-gyeom is in his right mind,
he wouldn't be here.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Nice.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
My goodness.
What? What are you doing here?
Have you lost your mind?
I see.
You're not in your right mind.
It's an honor to see a famous movie star
like you here, Ms. Choi.
Thank you for the compliment,
but we shouldn't be meeting again.
-Especially not in front of my car.
-I see.
I'm sorry. I'm drunk.
Gosh, this is awkward.
I get that you want attention
because of the love scandal.
But I really don't find this amusing.
I'm already dating someone else,
so please don't do this again.
Tae-ri!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you going to say
it was a coincidence again?
-You said it's not true!
-I swear it was a coincidence.
We're not dating.
You always say that.
But this already proves you're lying.
Avoiding him will make it look
even more suspicious.
There you go again.
You already lied to me once!
-Who did I lie about?
-That guy!
What's his name? Lee Jae-hun!
-Gosh, they're so loud.
-Let's hear you explain.
I can't believe you said his name.
I'm not renewing our contract.
What does that have to do with this?
That's totally irrelevant.
Hey, you! I said I'd keep my eyes on you.
How dare you lie to me?
We're not dating.
As if! You're together right now!
Seon-gyeom.
What's going on?
Hey, you're Choi Tae-ri.
-Hello.
Gosh, you little jerk.
Are you cheating on her?
How dare you cheat on Tae-ri?
What's wrong with you?
Just stay out of it.
Are you my dad or what?
-Do you have no pride?
-We're not dating!
What's wrong with those people?
-What's going on?
-Let me talk. Hey.
Who are you? Are you a rookie actress?
What is he saying? They're so weird.
A rookie shouldn't be dating already!
Will you please believe me?
He's cheating on you with her!
About that mistake…
There are reporters over there!
Can I do it instead?
-I'm serious!
-What?
-Where are they?
-Over there!
You always lie!
She's my girlfriend.
Have you lost your mind?
I'm serious.
Are you insane? Seriously?
Seriously.
What's your lip balm?
It was delicious and moist.
-You said so yourself that we're dating.
-Then that would make me insane.
How can you let me look for you?
I bought that painting ages ago.
Don't stop the disciplinary committee.
Let me get punished.
You darn punk!
You're touching me.
Can you forgive them?
Are you just going to feign ignorance?
-You should be embarrassed.
-You punk!
Ms. Oh!
Are you still angry?
Don't do it if you don't want to.
You don't always have to
overcome everything.
That was so cool.
You should treat her well.
She's looking out for you.
Do you like me?
Subtitle translation by: Ja-won Lee