[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 12]
Gao Yu!
They said you flee before the battle.
What happened exactly?
The Lings weren't killed by
Horned Demon Race,
but Du Hai Tian instead.
What did you say?
Du Hai Tian used us
to bait Horned Demon Race,
and waited until both sides were injured
before he showed up
as a hero cleaning the mess.
I saw them checked on
every single Ling,
Those barely alive
were given a final blow.
What were you doing then?
Me?
In the beginning,
I fought desperately too.
Then, I smelled something fishy
and hid away in chaos.
Qin Lie,
call me coward all you want.
But if I died too,
no one would know the truth.
Why did he do that?
Du and Ling families
are already on bad terms.
Now,
you're the great
Soul Reaping beast killer.
And during the war at Purple Mist Sea,
you became close with Saintess Song,
outshining his son.
These are the reasons why.
This must be revenged.
That's for sure.
But with our current capabilities,
we still can't go against Du Hai Tian.
Don't be reckless.
Stay back and handle the funeral.
I'll bring Yu Shi back from Qisha Valley.
We'll make a plan then.
Comfort Yu Shi for me.
Brother Li!
Brother Li.
Yu Shi, someone from
Ling Borough came for you.
Where is he?
Gao Yu?
What brings you here?
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Master Yuan,
thanks for greeting me personally.
Du family has made a great contribution.
Of course I
should come and greet you myself.
Follow me.
Your son isn't with you?
I heard
Young Master Du was a great help
in the battle at Purple Mist Sea.
Even Master Mo Hai
of Artefact Forging Sect
speaks highly of him.
My son is quite capable,
but he's young and therefore, arrogant.
In the war with the evil tribe,
he actually made some mistakes.
I only scolded him a little,
but he decided to leave,
saying he's going on a travel
to gain experience.
His temperament
is definitely a joke to you.
It's okay.
Young people should get out there
to practise and see the world.
You're very decisive, Master Du,
like the way of great men.
While Young Master Du
is an outstanding young man
with great potential.
This war
cost us a lot.
And there are many things
to deal with after the war.
It's time to decide who will be
the real Master of Xingyun Pavilion.
I will do my best.
Regarding this,
I need to consider carefully.
Some things
just won't stop troubling me.
I
can share your problem.
Okay.
You've travelled far.
Take a good rest.
He's being hesitant
and acting mysterious.
Madam.
I heard your family is broken.
Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
The Terminator Profound Bomb
is not something ordinary.
Did you give it to me
intentionally or accidentally?
So what if it's
intentional or accidental?
Ever heard about Master Mo Hai?
He's a famous person.
He once said
that all magical weapons
must be paired with
suitable spiritual arrays.
You must know that.
Uncle Li,
please teach me.
You want to use the Terminator
Profound Bomb for killing purpose?
Yes.
Are you confident about that?
No.
Don't get yourself destroyed instead.
I can go down with him.
The second room inside is empty.
You can stay here.
Thank you, Uncle Li.
Yu Shi.
Father.
I'm back.
I am back.
Where's Xuan Xuan?
She went to look for Yu Xin.
Don't worry.
She promised me
to return to Ling Borough
whether she found him or not.
But it'll be too late.
She even missed the chance
to look at Father one last time.
Where's Qin Lie?
He...
He left.
What?
Where did he go?
I have no idea.
He brought Chief and the others back,
and left a letter behind.
He was gone the next day.
[The war is an eye-opener to me.]
[The Artefact Forging Sect
is too good to miss. From Qin Lie]
What did Qin Lie say?
Your man just abandoned you?
What does it say?
It says
that the war at Purple Mist Sea
was eye-opening to him,
and that the Artefact Forging Sect
is too precious
to give up.
He'll be back
when he's achieved something.
What is this?
Even if he despises Ling Borough,
he should at least wait
until the bodies are buried
and Yu Shi comes back.
Ling Ying.
We know Qin Lie
better than anybody else.
-But he...
-You're too ruthless for him
that he chose to leave with Saintess Song.
You're abandoned.
Yu Shi.
Don't go after her.
She has enough men following her around.
I want to stay alone.
Please leave.
Are you sure you can stay calm?
Ling Yu Shi, mind you,
I don't like you.
I don't care.
Leave.
A woman's heart
will eventually get hurt because of a man.
Even when hurt,
you must remain strong.
Live on like usual.
Do what you're supposed to do.
After that,
you'll feel different.
Different, how?
Shutting yourself in your room
can't change the fact
that he's not coming back.
The dead ones don't matter,
but what about those who stayed alive?
Are you going to take them
and die along with the others?
Fine.
I got it.
I'll go.
Failed again?
Never mind. That's perfectly normal.
Take your time.
Some things are harder to achieve
if you rush it.
Have a good rest
and think it over.
Maybe you can make it
when you change the way you think.
Thanks, Uncle Li.
I got it.
Okay.
May the deceased rest in peace.
And we should stay strong.
After we buried our family members,
will you come with me?
Where are we going?
There's a village
for the families of Qisha's disciples
outside the valley.
What are we going there for?
To be dependable to them?
We have to admit
that Ling Borough is gone.
It takes time
to decide where our future lies.
I must return there and cultivate
in order to cure my poison.
Will you revive Ling Borough
or go another path?
I'll go with you.
-I'll go with you too.
-Me too.
-We're going too.
-We'll go too.
Very well.
Tomorrow night
is the one day we'll see the moon
throughout the year.
It's been one year.
Even if things have changed,
we must never give up.
Tomorrow night,
entrust whatever wishes you have
to the moon,
Ask Her to witness our heart
and guide us out of the hardships.
-Okay.
What do you want?
Do you enjoy watching me sleep?
You did it?
Well yes, you made one.
But this Terminator Profound Bomb's power
is at a beginner's level.
If you're going to use it to fight,
make sure
to surprise and take your enemy down
with one blow.
If your first attempt fail,
the enemy will be prepared for it.
This will make it hard
for you to attack with it again.
Okay.
Master Du.
Is Master Yuan awake?
Yes.
But he's out.
How pretentious.
What is he trying to do?
Yes?
Someone gave the guard a letter.
It's for you.
[The evil tribe will come back.
Keep a low profile.]
[The evil tribe will come back.]
[Let's meet up at a restaurant
as the sun set.]
[Keep a low profile.]
[As the sun set today,]
[let's meet up
at a restaurant in the city.]
Du Hai Tian.
I'm challenging you.
So, the letter was from you.
For his own interest,
Du Hai Tian set up a trap
during the war at Purple Mist Sea
and killed the men of Ling Borough.
I, Qin Lie, am here today
to avenge my dead family!
A baseless accusation.
Our Ling brothers
died defending our land
and will go down history.
When you say that,
have you ever thought about them
or me?
You know what actually happened!
I'll say it again,
I'm challenging Acting Master Du.
Do you dare take it?
Is this kid out of his mind?
He's actually challenging Master Du,
the Manifestation Realm peak cultivator.
How reckless.
Fine.
I'll give you a chance.
The peak of Natal Opening Realm?
There is
a whole Realm difference between us.
It's not too late to feel regret.
You're overconfident.
I haven't lost.
You want to bring me down with you?
I'm experienced in fighting a war
and have seen all kinds of opponents.
Show me how long you can hold up.
I'm surprised
that you are still holding on.
However,
it feels really good to see
my enemy's life fade away
while he loses the ability to resist.
Do you know that?
I watched the Lings died
on the hill across.
One by one, Ling Cheng Ye and the others
were defeated and killed
-I'll kill you!
-by the Horned Demon Race,
and I was there watching.
A final attack before you die?
Let's end this here.
What? Du Hai Tian was killed by Qin Lie?
I heard Qin Lie blasted him to death
on the street.
Close all the city gates right away.
Send out all fighters in the Pavilion.
Kill Qin Lie
before dawn.
Yes, Master.
What?
He killed Du Hai Tian?
I've just received the news
that Xingyun Pavilion
has locked down the city.
Even Palace of Hell's commanders
outside the city
are put to work.
Qin Lie won't survive the night.
Should we tell the Lings?
Pretend you don't know about this.
We should avoid troubles.
Let's leave for Qisha Valley
tomorrow morning.
Is that true?
Rejoice.
Your man didn't abandon you.
He took revenge for you instead.
Where is he?
I told you everything I know.
It's up to you to decide what you'll do.
Remember,
Brother Li must not know
that I told you this.
[I'm too petty for them to care.]
[I'm going to the highest place where
they and I can see each other equally.]
Move. Move.
Take a look there.
Let me see.
[Only the moon understands
my troubled mind.]
[Even if I have to live
the life of a fugitive,]
[please let me find Qin Lie]
[and stay by his side no matter what.]
[I'm too petty for them to care.]
[I'm going to the highest place where
they and I can see each other equally.]
What are you doing here?
Only the moon understands
my troubled mind.
My mind is troubled too.
He didn't write that letter.
It was you.
That's right.
Qin Lie
is a dead man now.
Why look for him?
How do you know he's wanted?
You fought alongside him
at the Purple Mist Sea.
How come he knows Du Hai Tian
caused my father's death
but you don't?
I was the only one who knew that.
Why didn't you let me know?
So that you won't be sad.
That's why you didn't tell me
Qin Lie went
to seek revenge on Du Hai Tian.
So that you won't be worried.
You knew he'd do that,
but you didn't go with him
or stop him.
You're sending him to his death.
Qin Lie didn't know that Du Hai Tian
was the culprit behind the Lings' death.
I was the one who told him that.
You want him to die.
Why?
That's because
my sister is dead because of him.
I want to get revenge.
Yeah.
I'm jealous of him.
I want you.
Yeah.
All of them are the reasons why!
Gao Yu,
it's not too late
to do the right thing now.
Let's look for Qin Lie.
Sure.
After we get married,
we'll collect his dead body together.
Gao Yu, don't you dare.
Gao Yu, no!
Kid.
Your love spell
is finally removed completely.
Uncle Liang,
thank you for what you've done.
Ting Yu,
something happened during the time
you retreat to recuperate.
Qin Lie killed Du Hai Tian.
Yuan Tian Ya gave an order to kill him.
Do you
want to save him?
The love spell is removed.
I'll be fine.
Okay.
Stay out of it, then.
No, I want to find out what's happening.
He has something I want.
It's done.
This kid is insane.
He's alive even after
losing that amount of blood.
And look at this.
This scar...
Logically, getting hurt here
means instant death.
But he actually lived till today.
That's a seal.
A seal?
That's some advanced stuff.
Such a remarkable kid.
Is he worth
our saving?
Back then,
I was saved by his grandpa.
It's only right
for me to save him.
Yes, it is.
It really is.
Commander, this is it.
We're closed.
No one is welcomed.
There are consequences if you barge in.
Master.
Go in.
[Shop]
Could it be the Master of Frost?
Master of Frost...
I'd like to meet her.
We'll leave when he is awake.
Even if you're the Master of Frost,
you should be able
to distinguish between right and wrong.
-This man...
-You want revenge for your subordinate?
Bring it on.
After all, killing a commander or a master
makes no difference.
Uncle Li.
You came to.
Cut the crap. Here.
Put this on and let's go.
I'll take ten steps.
Retreat or I'll attack.
Come on.
What are you looking at?
Tonight is the only day
throughout the year
we can see the moon in Ling Borough.
You call this moon?
Sleep already.
There's a long journey ahead tomorrow.
How could he be so brazen?
I'll kill him for you.
Never mind.
I'll kill him myself.
[Hua Tian Qiong]
What's so interesting about books?
Yet, my son loves reading.
You really regard Hua Yu Xin as your son?
[Gong Mu Shan]
One visit to Ling Borough,
and I ended up losing my wife and son.
Fortunately,
your grandson isn't dead.
He escaped death for many times.
That's because he's capable.
I was hoping that
you'd protect him.
Well, I'd better not.
Come on, there are saintesses,
masters and spirit beasts around.
I'm not needed.
But, I still helped.
As a result,
I lost my son.
Yi Yuan,
the Young Master of Purple Mist City,
He's honest and kind.
It's because of this
that I took out
[Yi Yuan]
the honest and kind part from him
and made Hua Yu Xin
to be your grandson's company.
This pity kid Yi Yuan
is missing one spiritual piece,
making him
a lifeless man.
You've had your fun.
Give it back to him.
Fine.
Listen,
I actually prefer Qin Lie.
As for Gong Mu Lie...
Whenever I make a joke,
he sneers at me,
and I don't know what to do with that,
you know?
In fact, the human tribe is more likeable.
That's because you're an old rascal.
Both my Lie'ers are great.
Is that true?