[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 11]
Shao Yang.
What are you doing in my room?
I have something to ask you.
Last night, when I came here
to see the Saintess,
I noticed that something was wrong
between you and the Saintess.
What did you do last night?
The Saintess invited me over for dinner.
It seems that
something happened,
but I could be wrong.
Last night,
something did happen.
Saintess.
What happened last night?
We had dinner together last night.
Then, I noticed that
something was wrong with you.
You looked sluggish.
I realised we were surrounded by
the demon aura from the Netherworld.
The demon aura from the Netherworld?
I thought it was an ambush by
Horned Demon Tribe.
So I ran out to take a look.
However, there was nothing out there.
Then, I remembered
Horned Demon Tribe launched
a surprise attack last time.
Hence, the demon aura
is still lingering here.
I see.
Do you feel any different from last night?
The demon aura of the Netherworld
might lead to weird hallucinations.
No, I don't have it.
Are you sure?
As I said, I don't have it.
Last night,
I didn't even dream.
Since you were affected by the demon aura,
you better take a good rest.
Why did you come to see me last night?
Saintess, this way please.
We shall let Qin Lie take a rest.
Master, have you found any clue?
Judging from the ashes,
these death warriors of Shadow Tribe
have cultivated some unknown
cultivation methods.
They can recover on their own
for three times.
It means they have triple the power.
No wonder there were not many
from the Dark Nether Race the other day
but we just couldn't wipe them out.
Spread the order.
Double up the castle defending vanguard.
Make sure the patrol troops
extend to a hundred miles.
Guard the place strictly by placing
a sentry every 1000 steps.
Yes!
Master, Du Shao Yang has some ideas.
Saintess Song, sorry we're late.
Father.
Rumour has it that in recent years,
Master Mo Hai has been trying to invent
a divine artefact that can seal
the Netherworld passage.
If the divine artefact is invented,
the passage will be cut off.
It can comb out
the Dark Nether Race's wild scheme
to take over the human world.
Their target
is to kill Master Mo Hai.
Since Master Mo Hai is the target
of the Dark Nether Race,
I have an idea
to lure in the death warriors
of the Netherworld
and annihilate them.
However, the Vanguard Castle
is too close to the Netherworld.
Demon Purifying Grass
can't be planted there.
The demon aura of the Netherworld
is a big trouble.
Master, do you have any ideas?
It is not difficult.
Just cover up its real identity
with hallucination.
Then, cover up its smell
with magic tools.
It helps to prevent Demon Purifying Grass
from getting in contact with demon aura.
Great.
Since Demon Purifying Grass
can purify the demon aura
of the Netherworld,
the Dark Nether Race won't be
able to resurrect from death.
We can put them to death.
Though the Dark Nether Race is brave,
they are not silly.
The hallucination will break apart
as soon as the battle begins.
Once Demon Purifying Grass
reveals themselves,
the Dark Nether Race
will retreat after a short fight.
We won't be able to get the target
even if we set up the trap.
With all due respect,
I think Saintess' idea is not proper.
If the bait is alluring,
the target will fall into the trap.
Will you be the alluring bait, Master?
Why should I be afraid?
However, the Demon Purifying Grass
at the battlefront is not enough.
We need to find a place as soon
as possible to plant the sprouts.
The Ling Borough in the far North
is located at the hot-spring area.
They have been planting spiritual herbs
for generations.
Now, it's time for them to contribute
to the human world.
I, Hai Tian, volunteer to lead
the warriors of the North to put down
our enemies at the battle front.
I hope that I can get your permission,
Saintess Song.
Permission granted.
Thank you, Saintess.
You requested someone from the Ling Family
to send us Demon Purifying Grass.
I don't think it is so simple.
What do you mean?
I remember
when the troop was taking a break
nearby the Ling Family,
you left the troop alone
and met up with someone at Silent Abyss.
Lure everyone in the Ling Borough.
Make them protect the magical herb.
As for the rest,
I will make the arrangement on my own.
You met up with Ling Bo in secret.
I don't think it was for old time's sake.
So you thought
you have something against me?
No.
Ling Bo is the spy
that I planted in the Ling Borough.
He is open minded.
He is not as stubborn as
those elderly in the Ling Family.
As the Master of Xingyun Pavilion,
mastering the situation
in the Ling Borough
is a matter of duty.
I see.
As the Master of the North,
you have given much thought to it.
You are close to the Ling Family
since young.
They are family to you
but don't you forget,
you are part of Xingyun Pavilion.
Have you forgotten about
Huang'er's death?
Don't worry.
I know my position.
Master.
The person in charge of
Spiritual Herb Hall
went through the Spiritual Herb Recipe.
He said that some of
the Spiritual Herbs
[Fire crystal,
the beast core of icy python]
[sphere container, black ice jade]
are very rare and precious.
He will give them to me
only after you go through the list.
Destructive Thunder?
Yes.
Fire crystal,
the beast core of icy python,
sphere container, black ice jade.
Where did you get
the spiritual herb recipe?
I got it from an unremarkable
store in Icestone City.
The store owner gave it to me.
Master, the spiritual herbs...
These spiritual herbs
are not really precious.
You can have them.
However, Destructive Thunder
is quite powerful.
Do you have the confidence?
I will try my best.
When it comes to
artefact forging skill,
you have to do it slowly.
With your current artefact forging skill,
you might not be able to succeed once
in making Destructive Thunder
even if you try a hundred times.
Furthermore, the slightest oversight
-can bring...
-It will explode.
I know that.
However, the battle with the Netherworld
will begin anytime soon.
My cultivation is inferior to an armour.
I need a magic tool to protect myself
and kill the enemies.
Okay.
You can use one of
the Artefact Forging Halls.
Make sure you don't destroy
the Artefact Forging Furnace.
No, I won't destroy it.
The worst scenario is
it explodes and I hurt myself.
All right, you may leave now.
Is there anything else?
You are the best armourer
in Chilan Continent.
I would like to inquire about someone.
He is an armourer too.
His name is Qin Shan.
Qin Shan?
I have never heard about him before.
Who is he?
He is my grandpa.
When I was still a baby,
I lost both my parents.
My grandpa was the one who raised me up.
He suddenly went missing ten years ago.
How about this? When I am back to
Artefact Forging Sect,
I will ask around for you.
Thank you, Master.
Can you tell what is wrong with Yu Shi?
She is not at ease.
She is distracted by her own thoughts.
Water spirit constitution
is indeed not of the common sort.
Half of the fire poison in your body
has been removed.
With your talent,
if you bring Heavenly Water
Demon Spirit Record
to a higher level,
you can cultivate further
with the pure air
found at Evil Aura Valley.
It's possible to completely get rid of
the fire poison from your body.
Your cultivation will
improve drastically too.
You have given me a new life.
I will try my best to cultivate.
There is no end to the law of nature.
All of us are cultivators.
We go against the nature.
Only when you abandon
the impurity in your mind,
can you cultivate wholeheartedly.
Yu Shi, you are distracted.
The distracting thoughts
may bring repercussion.
I know that.
You may leave now.
Who is the stealthy person out there?
Saintess, what are you doing here?
I am the general of
the Purple Mist Sea Battlefield.
I can go wherever that I want.
How may I help you?
I heard that you are
forging Destructive Thunder.
I am here to check if you are still alive.
You seem to be really concerned about me.
I am not.
The Ling Family is here.
It was a long and harsh journey.
Here, I propose a toast.
Master Du.
There are 23 cultivators in total
in the Ling Family
regardless their age.
All of them are here.
Great.
With the arrival of the Ling Family,
the warriors of the North
have become even more powerful.
The mission to escort
the spiritual herbs
is utmost important among everything.
It determines whether we can win
in the battle against the Netherworld.
It is also a good chance
for both the families
to become famous and successful.
Master Du is right.
The warriors of the Ling Borough
are all strong and brave.
We can seize the chance to
build our reputation in Chilan Continent.
You just have to escort
the spiritual herbs
to the place as agreed.
Someone will come to your aid.
It is going to be a long journey.
Make sure you protect
the spiritual herbs well.
Don't make any mistake.
Sure.
Uncle Ling.
[Qin Lie]
What did Yu Shi say in the letter?
Yu Shi said that she is doing fine
at Evil Aura Valley.
Her cultivation is improving
at a tremendous pace.
The fire poison in her
will be resolved soon.
Uncle Ling, after all this over,
I want to meet up with Yu Shi.
Meet up with her?
What is wrong?
In the past, Yu Shi
always tried to get closer to you.
but you always
gave her the cold shoulder.
Everyone in the Long Borough knows that
she likes you.
Now, she has become the favourite disciple
at Evil Aura Valley.
Once the fire poison is gone,
she will have a bright future.
Finally you remember about her?
Uncle Ling.
I am not a snobbish person.
What kind of person are you?
Lad, you are not qualified
to meet up with her.
I...
Evil Aura Valley
is Black Iron Class.
The Valley Lord admire Yu Shi a lot.
Even the sect leader of
Artefact Forging Sect
likes Yu Shi after meeting her.
He chased after her like no tomorrow.
Think about it.
If he manages to get Yu Shi,
Artefact Forging Sect
will belong to Yu Shi soon.
How about you? What do you have?
No, I don't have anything.
I am glad that you know.
I am telling you
there is no guarantee that
Yu Shi will fall in love with
the sect leader of Artefact Forging Sect.
It won't take too long before
Yu Shi
goes beyond the achievement of
the Saintess of Profound Heaven Alliance.
When the time comes, no man
can impress her.
Uncle Ling.
That is too much.
Is it?
I think I have slightly exaggerated.
By the way,
just now Du Hai Tian
said that Master Mu Hai is here too.
You have become his assistant.
Did you inquire about your grandpa?
Master Mu Hai said that
he has never heard of my grandpa's news.
However, he promised that
he will ask around once he is back to
the Artefact Forging Sect.
That is for the best.
I really hope that
Qin Shan is sound and safe.
Uncle Ling.
Please tell me more stories about
my grandpa.
Again?
My goodness.
I travelled so far.
Now I have to tell you the story.
I have twisted and turned
and told you the story
for countless times.
Do you still want to listen to it?
I just want to listen it again.
I have been forging artefact lately.
While doing so,
I kept imagining how my grandpa would look
when he was forging artefact.
Uncle Ling, please tell me more about him.
Perhaps I can learn something from it.
Okay.
I shall tell you about it.
Listen.
Your grandpa is a great person.
All the elderly in the Ling Borough
witnessed that with our own eyes.
Demon Purifying Grass liquid.
You indeed live up to your name.
Saintess Song, I shall leave
the rest to you.
The moon declining sinks into
a heavy mist.
The cloud is surrounded by purple mist.
I am surprised that
the Purple Mist Sea is so beautiful.
Clearly, I am prettier than the scenery.
Are you now?
I didn't realize that.
In the past, whenever you saw me,
you would always ask who I am.
Today, you didn't ask the question.
You answered my question whenever I asked.
Your answer was different each time.
Today, if I ask you again,
you'd fool me
another random answer again, right?
So what if I do?
Are you not happy
and not willing to be fooled?
Who are you?
There are five branches
in the Dark Nether Race.
Though the Shadow Tribe
is not the strongest
but never underestimate them.
You have to be careful.
Don't worry.
Thanks for informing me that
their target is Mo Hai.
I haven't had the chance to thank you.
You rely on a woman to earn merits.
Don't you mind?
I do.
Of course I mind. Therefore,
I will return ten times the favour.
I will remember that.
You will be killed
if you go back on your own word.
However, with your wits and wisdom,
I guess you have found
the way to solve it.
Of course I have found the way
but I can't tell you.
If you know too much,
it is not good for you.
You...
Surprisingly you are so good
at playing mind games.
Not only I am good at playing mind games,
I have many magic tools
that can protect me.
I can give you one of them if you want.
Yes, of course.
Where did it go?
It is in your ear.
This earring
can help you to listen to every sound.
You will stay more vigilant
on the battlefield.
It is a tool to keep you alive.
[Seal]
Chief.
I have a hunch that something
is not right about this place.
The valley is so quiet.
What could be wrong?
Exactly.
I think
it is because you are too used
to suffer on the snow land.
Don't worry.
I believe that Master Du
has made the arrangement.
[The exit of the Netherworld]
We've failed again.
Escort Master Mo Hai.
It's the Horned Demon Tribe,
not the Shadow Tribe.
Since the main force of
the Dark Nether Race is here,
what are we waiting for? Go!
Father.
A troop of Horned Demon Tribe
is moving towards the direction
of the spiritual herbs.
I shall go and aid the Ling Family.
Why are you so impatient?
We can talk about it
after the Ling Family is wiped out.
Someone has to be punished
for the death of Huang'er.
Father!
When will that person come?
What is the Dark Nether Race doing here?
Stay calm. Protect the spiritual herbs.
Ling Bo, why hasn't the aid arrived?
I guess it will be here soon.
You guess?
We'll be killed before they arrive.
They are trying to
wipe out the Ling Family.
No way.
Master Du promised me.
They will be here soon.
Be prepared!
Go!
Shao Yang.
Bring people to the scene.
Start attacking only after
the Ling Family is wiped out.
Shao Yang?
Master.
Young Master has left.
What?
The Ling Family, stay out of the way!
The aid is here!
Bring them away.
Master.
Master Du.
Why did you...
Kill him.
As expected by Du Shao Yang,
the Horned Demon Tribe
was targeting Master Mu Hai.
In this battle, the human warriors
hit the Dark Nether Race hard.
I think we can live a peaceful life
for some time.
As long as Master Mo Hai
completes the seal
to keep the Netherworld apart,
the human world will be at peace forever.
Defender Xie.
Yes.
In this battle,
soldiers from different troops
suffered casualties.
Compensation and reward
must be given.
Much obliged.
Saintess, in the battle at
Evil Wind Valley Valley,
the Ling Family got wiped out.
Gao Yu's dead body couldn't be found.
I guess he must have ran away.
Sorry for my incompetence.
Please punish me.
Qin Lie.
I am sorry for your loss.
I had discussed with Defender Xie.
You are allowed to send them
back to the snow land
before coming back to
Purple Mist City again.
Then, we will go back to
Profound Heaven Alliance for ascribing.
Were you trying to seduce
Qin Lie with love spell
but accidentally got backfired
by the Realm of Serenity instead?
Why did you do that?
Qin Lie comes from an unknown origin.
However, he did many amazing things.
I just want to find out his ins and outs.
You could send someone to spy on him.
You didn't have to harm yourself.
I was thoughtless.
It must not be known by anyone,
especially your father.
Don't go back in a rush.
Get rid of the love spell soon.
[To my dear nephew, Qin Lie.]
[Battling the Netherworld is risky.]
[If I don't come back alive,]
[I should tell you the truth]
[about your grandpa]
[to avoid you from going in
the wrong direction]
[and miss out the truth.]
[Qin Shan is an expert
in forging artefact.]
[The Ling Family is indebted to him.]
[As I told you before,]
[Qin Shan and I used to
drink together very often.]
[It was a lie.]
[I said that to bring you some comfort]
[as you were hurt from losing
your loved ones.]
[One night before your grandpa
went missing,]
[he came to see me.]
[He mentioned that you used to be
violent when you were young.]
[When you were seven years old,
you lost your memories in a disaster.]
[Your grandpa knew that
the Ling Borough is a nice place.]
[Hence, he brought you there]
[hoping that you would learn from
the surrounding and be a better person.]
[I asked if he installed
the Soul Suppressing Orb]
[in your brain on purpose.]
[He didn't answer my question.]
[I observed his expression]
[but I couldn't find any clue.]
[The next day, your grandpa went missing.]
[We haven't heard from him to date.]
[I have a hunch that the trip
to Purple Mist Sea]
[would be dangerous.]
[Hence, I decided to tell you the truth.]
[I am afraid that if I die,]
[those lies that I said
would misguide you.]
[When you see this letter,
it means I am no longer here.]
[My dear nephew, Qin Lie,]
[I shall entrust Yu Shi to you.]
[Please take care.]
Qin Lie.
Though the shape
of the Destructive Thunder is there,
but without the Spiritual Array,
it can't be considered as
a magical weapon.
If you want it to go full force,
you need to carve spiritual marks on it.
If you have the heart,
after burying the Ling Family,
-you can follow me...
-Master.
Thank you, Master.
I will bear your advice in mind.
I am not in a good mood.
Please forgive me.
Let's go home.
Stop.
Take a break.
Come with me.
I name you Shao Yang
with the hope that you will become famous
at a young age.
However, you are so disappointing.
Father.
The Ling Family don't deserve
to be wiped out.
Furthermore, stepmother’s death was...
You are siding the outsiders
and have ruined my plan.
Father.
I know that
eagles don't catch flies.
However, the Ling Family is just a dust.
Is it really necessary?
Do you know why are you a failure?
That is because you hesitate.
You have never demanded me
to spare none of them.
How dare you go against me?
I am going to take away your cultivation
so that you can reflect upon yourself.
When you learn your mistake,
you can start cultivating all over again.
Take away my cultivation?
I would rather you kill me then.
Who are you?
You might have a shock
if you knew my identity.
I don't care who you are.
This is my family affair.
Stay out of it.
If you are not his father,
you would have died long time ago.