Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
I...
got suspended.
They're not going to
pay me during my suspension,
and I'm probably going to get sued.
Everything is so messed up.
You said before
you'll run away with me
whenever I want.
I want to
go on a trip with you.
Right now.
Let's go.
CHAPTER 9
KING DONKEY EARS
Where should we go?
Don't you think it'd be nice to go abroad?
South America and Europe both sound nice.
Let's go somewhere hotter than here.
How about Africa?
Serengeti, the wildlife refuge.
What do you think?
"What in the world have I done?"
Is that...
what you're thinking right now?
No, not at all.
You'd better not be thinking that.
You impressed me by punching that guy
and even asked me to take you on a trip.
Don't tell me
you're starting to regret it.
No, of course not.
I'm not regretting it.
Then let's go to Serengeti.
I don't have a passport.
Are you from outer space?
-Who doesn't have a passport these days?
-Me. I don't.
-We can go to Jeju Island.
-We won't be able to return today.
"Return today"? Are you joking?
Last time, you offered to take me
to a mountain or a field.
That won't take more than a day.
Okay, fine.
Then for one night--
If we're spending the night,
let's take Sang-tae.
-What are you doing?
-Think carefully before you answer.
Stop the car.
Do you want to go for a day
or spend the night with me?
Stop the car!
Do you want to spend the night with me
or die with me?
Ko Mun-yeong!
Are you nuts? Why would you risk your life
to joke around?
Who says I'm joking around?
Please. At least count to three
before you do anything impulsive.
Did you count to three
before you punched that guy?
Get out.
If I stay with you,
it'll make me
want to crash into something.
Damn it! Gang-tae, that darn asshole!
He wanted to go on a trip.
Is he teasing me or what?
Is he really teasing me?
What the heck? How dare he tease me?
How am I going to get back at him?
Hey, buddy.
You're so strange these days.
I didn't have lunch.
You always skip meals,
and you quit your job
like it's your hobby.
But you punched someone today
and got suspended.
I'm surprised you have an appetite.
This is good.
Buddy, you must be sick in the mind.
Let's go get a checkup.
-Do you also think I'm a little strange?
-Not just a little. Very.
-What's the matter with me, Jae-su?
-It's the lunatic virus.
-"A virus"?
-That day,
when Ko Mun-yeong
hurt your hand with a knife,
her lunatic virus must have
entered your blood vessels
and totally messed up your brain.
You almost convinced me.
I almost thought of writing a novel.
-Do you know the word for that in English?
-"In English"?
Gosh, do you think I'm dumb?
You want to know what it is in English?
My gosh, come on.
It's "Nobel" as in
Nobel Prize in Literature.
My goodness, I guess you didn't know.
Yes, novel. That's what I said.
Novel Prize in Literature.
My gosh, seriously.
Okay, fine. My pronunciation sucked.
I admit that, okay?
-Jae-su.
-Yes, I know.
Gosh, that's enough.
End of conversation. Just drop it.
I...
want to have fun.
Sure. Why not?
It's been a while.
Let's go for a ride on Alberto.
Where do you want to go?
-Serengeti.
-Sereng... What?
He's not that kind of person.
He's a very patient guy.
I can't believe he punched someone.
It's just like when you fart.
If you hold it in 99 times
and finally let it out,
it could kill people.
You... You have no manners.
Don't talk about farting
when we're eating.
It's making me lose my appetite.
I'm sorry. Sorry about that.
Eat... Eat your own side dishes.
But how did he end up punching someone?
Back in the days,
I also beat up guys who used to bully you.
He probably got angry for the same reason.
Back when I was young,
I had a crush on Sun-deok.
But I got rejected three times.
That's... That's quite a surprise.
But... But how did you reject him?
"I don't like you!
I really don't like you!"
That's how I rejected him.
He was very unusual
ever since he was young.
It was a 50-50 chance.
He was either a genius or an idiot,
so I just rejected him.
You regret it, don't you?
My goodness, how did you know?
I regret it very much.
Don't leave any food on your plate.
Did you see that?
She still has feelings for me.
Don't be delusional. Drink your soup.
Director.
I'm sorry for bothering you
during your meal.
But can you come with me for a moment?
What's going on?
-You can keep eating.
-Okay.
Why can't she get discharged?
We're not saying she can't get discharged.
-But there's a procedure--
-I don't care.
-Let's go.
-Please calm down.
-The director will be here--
-How do you expect us to calm down?
Her ex-husband...
We brought her to this hospital
so that jerk wouldn't find her.
But that lunatic managed to find her here.
You should just come with me
to the States.
You can get treated there.
No, I don't want to go.
Just go by yourself.
Stop complaining! Let's go!
If you must leave...
What? What do you want?
Our hospital administration
is handled over there.
You need to pay before you go.
-You need to pay.
-We'll pay, okay?
-Let's go, Mom.
-My goodness.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Hurry up. Come on.
Ms. Lee A-reum isn't ready
to get discharged.
Are you really going to let her leave?
What else can we do to stop her
from leaving?
Her family won't let her stay.
-Come here.
-What is it?
Be quiet.
Jeong-tae. Listen to me carefully.
I'm listening.
You see, A-reum...
What about her?
Well, the thing is, A-reum...
No! A-reum...
Hey, Jeong-tae.
You shouldn't let people find out
that you and A-reum are a couple.
So just try your best to hold it in.
-I'll try to find a way.
-Damn it.
Jeong-tae.
Tomorrow, someone who can help you
will show up from the west.
What? A ghost from the west?
Someone who can help him
will show up from the west.
A person. Not a ghost.
He snores, grinds his teeth, and farts.
He does it all simultaneously.
It's like a darn orchestra.
I bet every single hole
in Lee Sang-in's body opens up
when that guy goes to sleep.
My gosh, it's hilarious.
If you can't stand him,
you can sleep in our room.
-It's empty.
-Can I really do that?
-I also have a favor to ask you.
-"A favor"?
It's regarding Sang-tae.
Tomorrow, can you--
Sure.
-But I'm not done talking.
-There's no need to explain.
I'll help you out no matter what.
That's what you call loyalty.
Thanks.
Then who do you like more? Me or Sang-tae?
-Do I really need to answer that?
-What?
I'll see you.
I like you, too.
-"Those two guys are
-Those two guys are
-trying to take over our house.
-They're a pair of rascals."
-They're a pair of rascals.
I hate them.
I really hate Dooly and his friends.
It's not even their house,
but they do whatever they want.
I like Ko Gil-dong.
"Ko Gil-dong"?
He let those guys into his territory.
He's a nice guy.
-What do you think?
-I like him.
I... I also like Gil-dong.
This... This guy's name is Teary.
His real name is Ko Gil-dong.
His name is Teary. This right here
is actually a piece of thread,
but it's also a teardrop.
His name is Ko Gil-dong.
-Do you also like him?
-Yes.
Ko Gil-dong is a caregiver
for Dooly, Douner, and Ddochi.
I mean, he's their guardian,
and he gives them a place to sleep,
gives them food, and protects them.
Just for your information,
I'm Gang-tae's guardian.
And a guardian should be
dependable and trustworthy.
I'm an adult and his older brother.
That's who I am.
We really click, Sang-tae.
We're like best friends.
"Best friends"?
Best friends.
My gosh, we're best friends.
Yes, best friends.
Best friends.
Sang-tae, I'm home.
Can we talk?
Best friends.
Are we not going anywhere tomorrow?
Did you overreact like that earlier
to have fun for just one day?
One day is more than enough for me.
I dreamt of that day
my entire life.
You're so annoying.
So are we going tomorrow?
Sometimes,
you're like a tamer, not a caregiver.
"A tamer"?
I feel like you're taming me.
I think it's the opposite.
I keep doing things I wouldn't normally do
because of you.
Earlier,
I couldn't hear
or see anything.
I must have been out of my mind.
I really couldn't hold my anger.
No, you weren't out of your mind.
You were stunning.
Should we leave the house
tomorrow morning?
Yes, sure.
Good night.
I want to twist that deer's neck.
Shut up, you stupid deer!
Ju-ri.
Where are you going?
Seung-jae.
Have you ever been in a one-sided love?
No, I would never do something so dumb.
It's such a waste of time.
I know, right?
It's a waste of time.
You deserve way better.
-Do you know who I have a crush on?
-Mr. Moon Gang-tae.
I'm very slow when it comes to work.
But when it comes to love,
I'm very quick-witted.
Let's be honest and realistic.
You're a lot better than Mr. Moon.
He may be good-looking,
but he has absolutely nothing...
You're right.
He doesn't have anything to offer.
He really doesn't.
I must've thought
I could be the one to fill up
his empty life.
What's the matter with me?
I must be drunk.
Let's go inside after we finish this.
I personally think
you should be with a guy
who's older than you, and has a laid-back
and broad-minded personality,
with the characteristics of a businessman.
I'm sure you'll be able to find
a guy like that somewhere nearby.
She's finally doing her money's worth.
No, you weren't out of your mind.
You were stunning.
I must be out of my mind.
What?
No, it's nothing. Go back to bed.
-Go back to sleep.
-Okay.
If you're out of your mind,
you need to go to a hospital.
It means you're sick.
I must have been out of my mind.
I really couldn't hold my anger.
He shouldn't have held back
his desire either.
My gosh.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
DIRECTOR O'S MUSIC CLASS
-It's okay to not be okay
-It's okay
-It's okay to be sick at heart
-I'm really okay
-It's not because of the director
-It's not because of my medicine
-I'm okay because I'm strong
-I'm really okay
I love you guys.
THERAPY ROOM
It's sunny outside.
Why don't we go for a walk?
Sang-tae, I have plans today,
so I'm going to be a bit late.
So wait for me at Jae-su's.
I'll go pick you up in the evening.
"We really click, Sang-tae.
We're like best friends."
-What?
-Best friends.
Ms. Ko and I are best friends now.
That means we're buddies and besties.
It means we're really close.
Your best friend is Jae-su.
My best friend is Ms. Ko.
I also have a best friend now.
I have a best friend.
Don't you miss your daughter?
I heard her fairy tale class is
really fun.
Maybe I should watch her teach one day.
She's just like that woman.
-"That woman"?
-Everyone
got fooled by that woman.
She has the face of an angel.
But there lives a demon inside.
Everyone is good and bad.
We all live with both traits.
That woman is a monster.
She killed someone.
I'm telling you. She killed someone.
Where is that monster?
She's dead.
I killed her.
I'm sure
But she came back.
She came back to kill me.
She's going to kill me.
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
Ms. Park Ok-ran.
You're not allowed in here.
Why were you reading this
when I wasn't done reading it myself?
Well, I was just...
See?
It's because you touched something
that wasn't yours.
I hate it
when people do that.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay. It's just a paper cut.
-I'll give you a bandage.
-No, it's okay.
By the way, I noticed that
Mr. Joo Jeong-tae went outside today.
Wasn't it Mr. Kan Pil-ong's turn?
Yes.
But Director O signed a permit
for Mr. Joo Jeong-tae this morning.
I bet someone made a deal
behind the curtain.
"A deal"?
Are you ready?
I'm going in, okay?
Are you doing a circus show?
Are you running away?
I mean...
Can't you wear something comfortable?
I feel comfortable naked.
Don't you have anything normal?
-I don't want to look normal.
-Why not?
Because it's normal.
-At least wear comfortable shoes--
-What did you pack?
Are we evacuating?
Well, we might get hungry
when we're outside...
My goodness.
Did a patient call you or something?
I just thought we might need it
just in case...
Don't make it so obvious
that this your first time going somewhere.
You just need to take care of me.
-Don't pick up.
-Hello?
Who is that jerk?
Two club sandwiches, please.
You should eat it while it's warm.
You had something urgent to tell me?
I can't talk properly when I'm hungry.
Do you have plans?
Yes.
A date with Ms. Ko?
I told you already.
I'm amazing
when it comes to reading people's minds.
Then
can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
What's the psychology
behind people who overdress
and wear things that are way too fancy?
I'm guessing it's because
they want to show off, right?
It's the opposite.
They want to protect themselves.
They think they're too weak,
so they use clothes for protection.
It's like an armor.
So you should do a good job
of protecting her.
I'm talking about Ms. Ko.
My best friend...
When... When are we
going to have our meeting?
-Sang-tae.
-Yes?
What kind of women
did Gang-tae hang out with?
Nurses, patients,
teachers at my school, landlords...
No, I'm not talking about
those kinds of women.
-What kind of women does he like?
-He doesn't like women.
-Does he like men?
-He likes me.
"You're my favorite person
in the whole world, Sang-tae."
Gang-tae only hangs out with me.
No wonder he doesn't know how to have fun.
I should make sure he has a blast.
No. Mang-tae.
I gave you Mang-tae.
-What?
-You can play with Mang-tae.
Gang-tae will play with me.
And I... I will play with my best friend.
-Can't I play with Gang-tae?
-No, you can't.
Gang-tae can only have fun with me.
He's my little brother.
Do you also adore Gang-tae?
Yes, I really adore him.
He... He has beautiful eyes.
He has the most beautiful eyes ever.
Have you ever hated him?
I guess you have.
When did you hate Gang-tae?
Aren't you going to tell me?
Sang-tae.
Do you know the story called
King Donkey Ears?
Yes, the guy goes into the bamboo forest
and shouts,
"The king has donkey ears!"
Yes, that's right.
If you keep a secret to yourself,
you end up getting frustrated.
You need to tell someone
in order to relieve your stress.
When did you hate Gang-tae the most?
My phone is...
Hey, Jae-su.
I need to talk on the phone.
Maybe you were right about that.
You said that Ms. Ko's mother
may not be someone whom she misses
but someone whom she still fears.
It's just my guess.
We can't trust everything
that a dementia patient says,
but that doesn't mean we can entirely
rule out the possibility.
What if
the writer Do Hui-jae actually isn't dead?
What if she just disappeared?
Then we know one thing for sure.
She'll definitely come back
to see her husband and daughter.
Let's hope I'm worried for nothing,
but just in case,
I wanted to ask you
to protect Ms. Ko and be there for her.
"NONSTOP" BY OH MY GIRL
Your brother is very calculating.
What do you mean?
He's all about give and take.
He doesn't give away anything for free.
Isn't that why you guys are best friends?
Because you two are alike.
Aren't you scared of riding motorcycles?
No, it doesn't. Hand me the helmet.
It's so scary.
-Jeez.
-Super scary!
Wait up!
Isn't it so nice to be home for a change?
Ms. Kang will throw a samgyeopsal party
for you this evening.
Why are you following me, Jae-su?
To hang out with you.
So you want me to leave?
You're so mean.
I closed up the restaurant for the day
and drove Alberto
all the way up the mountain
in this heatwave just to pick you up.
Right. You did that, boss.
Yes! I am your boss.
What kind of part-timer wants to hang out
with his boss at his place?
What?
What's that?
Is Ms. Kang making kimchi already?
Kimchi is made in the winter.
November 7th is the first day of winter.
My, I feel so refreshed.
Gosh, our very own illustrator
Mr. Moon is here.
Hello! Mr. Lee Sang-in,
the CEO of SangSangESang Publishers.
-Hello.
-What on earth are you doing here
half-naked in broad daylight?
As you can see, I'm enjoying my vacation.
Usually, I book a resort overseas
every summer
and do nothing but read books
for about a month.
This was not planned, but I ended up
spending my summer like this here.
Mr. Moon, take a dip.
-It's so refreshing.
-No, I don't want to.
I don't like water. I hate water.
Jeez, why did you do that?
Wait, Sang-tae. Wait up!
Where are we headed?
You wanted to see
the mountains and fields.
Then I guess the mountains first?
Is this the deviation
you've been dreaming of?
Are we going to tie a rope
around our ankle and jump or something?
Shall we?
-Let's go.
-No.
Why not?
I'm scared.
-Why are you laughing?
-Well...
Hearing you say the word, "scared"--
You think it's funny?
Do you think it'll be fun
to cross this stupid bridge?
I just
wanted to come up high
and enjoy an open view.
I can't come here with Sang-tae.
I saw it, so it's all good now.
Let's go back down.
So you're saying
you can't hang out
with Sang-tae like this?
Okay, fine. Let's do this.
But carry me on your back.
Wait here. I'll be right back.
Hey! Carry me on your back!
I said, carry me!
Give me a piggyback ride!
Darn it. Crap.
Shit! It's shaky.
That's why it's called the Shaky Bridge.
Why is it freaking shaky?
Wait up.
Why don't you sing a song
if you're scared?
A song?
If I
Feel lonely
Stop.
Why?
You sound scary.
Do you have a death wish?
If I
Gosh, I'm hungry.
What will you feed me?
Since we're in the mountains...
How about raw squid?
-What?
-Well, let's see.
Is there a good restaurant nearby?
Go stand over there.
I'll take a picture of you.
You said you're hungry.
Come on.
-Hurry up.
-Smile.
I told you to smile, not cry.
Just take it, will you?
Strike a cool pose.
Enough. I don't want photos.
Okay. If it's embarrassing,
I'll take it with you.
Sit back down.
Sit down.
One, two, three.
Smile. Don't cry.
Hello?
We were told to expect someone
who can help us from the west.
It was true.
My gosh.
What is going...
Can you explain this?
Oh, what happened was...
You know, I'm supposed
to stay out overnight tomorrow.
Can Jeong-tae go instead? Joo Jeong-tae.
A-reum!
We just got into a taxi
and said we'd go as far as we could.
That's why we ended up here.
181,800 WON
CHEAP GUESTHOUSE
300M
We spent all the money we had
on the taxi ride,
so we couldn't pay for the room.
-We're totally broke.
-That's right.
How did you get my number?
This reads,
"Call in case of an emergency."
EMERGENCY CONTACTS
Out of everyone here,
you're the closest to me.
Spending time with a patient
outside the hospital--
It's not allowed.
I know that it's against the rules.
So just lend us some money
to pay for the room.
It was hard for me to get out for a night.
I'll stay here with A-reum
just for the night
and return to the hospital tomorrow.
They also accept credit cards.
No, I can't do that.
-Why not?
-Why can't you?
Strictly speaking, this is all your fault.
Patients can't date one another,
so you told me
to just hold back my feelings.
-So I listened to you and did just that.
-Right.
But when A-reum's ex-husband
slapped Ms. Ko in the face,
-what did you do?
-He didn't hold himself back.
Well, in that moment--
Because you punched him,
A-reum's parents came to see her
at the hospital,
and they discharged her.
That means we will have to
part ways tomorrow.
And you can't even pay
for us to stay here for a night?
This is so cruel.
Very cruel, indeed.
Apologize to them.
It looks like it was your fault.
I paid for the room next to theirs.
Hey.
I told you that we can't stay overnight.
My gosh, are you Cinderella or what?
Sleep here by yourself.
I bet they'll elope tomorrow.
The woman will move to the States soon,
and the man has to return
to the psychiatric hospital tomorrow.
I mean, look at those eyes.
Do you think they can be apart?
Your rationality can never win
against your desires.
Will you let the patient run away?
How irresponsible.
Or will you break them apart
despite knowing how in love they are?
That's so cruel.
Let's just stay with them here tonight.
That way, you can take him back
to the hospital tomorrow.
Right, Mr. Caregiver?
I've been
suspended from work,
so I refuse to work.
See? We're so screwed.
We'll be okay, A-reum.
All right.
Do you guys know
when Gang-tae will be here?
It'd be nice if he could join us.
-Well, he'll get here pretty late.
-Did he get a part-time job again?
No, he had to meet someone.
Who?
Oh, I'm sure he's out
meeting up with people he knows.
He has lots of time
now that he's been suspended,
-so he's probably out clearing his head.
-Gosh, that's good.
When will he get to take it easy
if not now?
My gosh,
you've been grilling meat nonstop.
Here, Ju-ri. Have some.
I'll eat it myself.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Even my arm is getting tired.
Don't be like that. Just eat this.
Here.
Why are you being like this, seriously?
Are you enjoying working with Ms. Ko?
We will work later.
"Later" means sometime before you die.
What? Before you die?
Jeez, so she's working on a book
that will be published posthumously?
Gosh, Mun-yeong...
Have you two gotten quite close?
Yes, we're best friends now.
Best friends don't keep secrets
from each other.
Then you should've brought her.
I told her I'd love
to invite her over for a meal one day.
She said no.
She went somewhere fun by herself.
I... I would've been happy
to hang out with her.
You didn't want to hang out with me.
You're really hurting my feelings,
Sang-tae.
That's very odd.
She wouldn't want to go out in this heat.
Maybe they went together.
Ms. Ko and Mr. Moon Gang-tae.
You sure work in publishing.
You're incredibly creative, Seung-jae.
Right? She really is.
Hey, maybe I should have you sign
a publishing contract as a writer.
Well, how about a beer for everyone?
I'd love that.
I'll go.
I'll give her a hand.
Mr. Lee, do you mind picking up
some coffee milk for me?
You crazy little brat...
They're probably together now, right?
Gang-tae and Mun-yeong.
Not sure.
And who cares?
I mean, you're with me now.
I'm beginning to understand
why Mun-yeong has stuck around you
for so long.
That's a compliment, right?
But to tell you the truth,
it's actually the other way around.
I'm the one that's sticking around her.
Why?
Well...
Because she cannot be left alone.
She's very lonely.
But she doesn't want anyone to know that,
so she pushes people away.
She's complicated.
I have to say, they're so alike.
Do you think that's why
they're attracted to each other?
Ju-ri.
There can be countless reasons
as to why we fall for someone.
For example, you might fall for
how pretty they look when they cry.
Or you might fall for them
when they get drunk and swear at you.
Or it might be when they
unexpectedly slap you in the face.
Mr. Moon must've also
found some kind of reason
to fall for Mun-yeong.
The owner of this guesthouse said
we can drink this.
She made this fruit marmalade herself.
You haven't called him yet?
Shall I call him?
No, don't.
I'll go call him now.
Hey.
Did you eat dinner?
Yes, we had samgyeopsal.
My gosh, you guys must've had a feast.
What are you up to now?
What are you up to?
What? Me?
Well, I'm...
I'm chatting with you on the phone.
When will you be back?
Oh, I'll be back very late.
Around midnight? Or around 1 or 2 a.m.?
No, I may have to sleep here tonight.
Don't wait for me.
Just go to bed, Sang-tae.
And make sure you close the window screens
before you go to bed.
Don't sleep on the floor.
Also, make sure the fan is rotating.
If you get bored
or can't fall asleep, call me.
You too.
Call me if you get bored.
Oh, I've seen that face on TV dramas.
What do you mean?
The face of a man
who is cheating on his wife.
I don't want to be a mistress.
I want to be a faithful wife.
But those two
can't be best friends, can they?
Sang-tae was happy
about being best friends with you.
Well...
I'm also fond of your brother.
He's cute.
There was something
my mom wished for her whole life.
Seeing Sang-tae with a friend.
A real friend who truly understands him.
Just one.
I had a friend like that
a long time ago as well.
A friend who understands me.
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
-Nam Ju-ri!
-Gosh!
-Look at that!
-Hilarious!
What an idiot.
That girl
-was afraid of her classmates.
-Nam Ju-ri is a crybaby
-Nam Ju-ri is an idiot
But those kids
were afraid of me.
Get lost.
Hey. Shall we
become friends?
I liked it because I was no longer bored.
And she liked it
because her classmates
no longer bullied her.
But the thing is...
Ready or not!
-Rock-paper-scissors! I won!
-She didn't want just one friend.
She wanted to be everyone's friend.
And I
-didn't like that.
-We won!
So?
Did you harass those kids?
Yes.
I thought she'd only be friends with me
if she became lonely again.
Let's do it together.
What do you think? Did I do a good job?
But I was wrong.
Don't... Don't come close.
Go away.
I said, go away!
Please.
Please go away.
A friend who truly understands you
does not exist.
You should reconcile with her.
I don't want to.
-Why not?
-Because I have a best friend now.
And I also have you.
Hey.
Your cheeks are...
Goodness.
-What's wrong?
-This is booze.
What?
No, the lady said
it's raspberry marmalade.
I guess she didn't put in enough sugar.
No, Jeong-tae!
I won't drink this.
You saw me spitting it out just now.
Hey.
Go sleep in the other room
and send Jeong-tae here.
Those lovebirds
have to part ways tomorrow,
so just leave them be.
Don't turn your back on me.
I see that you smile a lot like an idiot
when you're drunk.
I have fun
when I'm with you.
I keep on smiling.
This won't do.
What do you mean?
-Hey.
-What's the matter?
-Come here.
-Why are you being like this?
-Who's more in love?
-Calm down, please.
The one who's more patient.
-Ko Mun-yeong!
-Moon Gang-tae!
Why?
Because love is all about patience.
Okay, fine. Let go of me now.
I'll just go to sleep.
I said I'll go to sleep.
Please.
Stay still and just go to sleep.
Come on. Just sleep.
I heard you can fall asleep easily
when someone caresses your hair.
CHEAP GUESTHOUSE
I told you
that I can no longer
hold myself back.
I guess
I can't run away anymore.
Don't go. Don't leave me, Mom.
Gang-tae, I'm here.
I'm here. Don't leave me.
Moon Gang-tae!
Don't go.
Don't go...
MY BROTHER
The number you have dialed...
Moon Gang-tae!
Moon Gang-tae...
Where were you?
Well...
To get what I couldn't give you last time.
What?
Don't trample on them this time.
They're beautiful.
So are you.
Oh, you guys are still here.
The other couple
left early in the morning.
Pardon me?
Their shoes are still here though.
I have no idea.
Gang-tae.
With this, we can stay together for
a month without worrying about anything.
I thought we'd have to part ways
in the morning,
so I didn't get any sleep last night.
Who knew Ms. Ko would give us money
so that we could run away together?
Isn't she so cool?
-A-reum.
-What is it?
I really don't think
this is right.
What do you mean?
Running away like this
will turn our love into nothing
but a petty and cowardly act.
-What are you talking about?
-You see...
The truth is,
I still go crazy when I see alcohol.
Even last night,
I struggled to restrain myself.
Had you not been with me,
I would've drunk until I dropped.
I have not yet
recovered enough to take care of you
and be responsible for your happiness.
We can just try our best together.
No, I need to get through this on my own.
I will get through this.
I promise you that I'll fully recover
and come to you.
So please
wait for me. I won't take long.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Thanks so much, Gang-tae.
I owe you one.
Is he a fool?
Why let her go if he loves her?
Because he loves her a lot.
Sometimes, that's why
you must let someone go.
So they broke up
because they love each other?
That's complete bullshit.
I will never let you go.
Don't be so sure of it.
You never know what could happen.
I'll go check in on Sang-tae.
Be quick.
I'll kill you if you take too long.
Are you serious?
Mr. Moon and Ms. Ko came together?
Yes, he must've been
that special someone from the west.
Thanks to them, A-reum and I
made some unforgettable memories.
Really?
That means they're seeing each other.
Yes.
It might be fun to plan a double wedding
down the road.
-Would you officiate our wedding?
-My gosh.
-Me?
-Yes.
It's almost done.
Why didn't you pick up?
What?
Oh, my phone is dead.
You called?
Yes, 4 times. No, 9... It was 17 times.
Why? Did something happen?
Where have you been? Where...
I told you
that I had to go to Seoul to see someone.
By yourself?
Yes, by myself.
I can change the water for you.
No, one must take care of one's own tasks.
One must take care of one's own tasks.
Big news! You need to hear this.
Mr. O, please be quiet
when you're inside the hospital.
Gosh, whatever. That's not important now.
-Hey, follow me.
-Ms. Park.
I'm going to tell you something,
but you two must keep it to yourselves.
I'm starving. What's taking him so long?
Dr. Kwon, you're a psychiatrist,
so I can trust
that you're discreet, right?
Yes, sure.
What I'm about to tell you
must stay between us, okay?
Mr. Moon Gang-tae and Ms. Ko Mun-yeong
are getting married soon.
-What?
-Seriously, for real.
Apparently, Mr. Joo Jeong-tae
saw them on a trip together.
They even slept in the same room
at a guesthouse, so they're obviously...
My gosh, that looks amazing.
Did the three of you go on a trip
in a camping car?
No.
Then did you, by any chance,
run into Mr. Joo Jeong-tae
outside the hospital?
No, I ran into him
in front of the hospital.
You're lying.
I told you not to lie.
Sang-tae, what's the matter?
Who do you like more?
Me or Ms. Ko Mun-yeong?
Why do you ask?
Who do you like more?
Me or Ms. Ko Mun-yeong?
My gosh. He likes you more, of course.
I want you to answer my question.
Answer my question!
Of course,
I like you more.
No, that's a lie.
It's a lie. It's all a lie.
-No, I mean it.
-It's a lie.
I told you not to lie!
Don't lie to me! It's all a lie.
No.
Sang-tae.
I'm not lying.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
I won't do it again, okay?
"I want him to die.
My brother...
I just want my brother to die!
I just want my brother to die."
You said that.
You said you wanted me gone.
You said to Mom every day
that you wanted me to die.
That's why you pushed me into the river
that day.
I shouted for help.
I shouted... I kept crying for help,
but you ran away.
You left me alone in the water
and ran away.
You wanted me dead. Every single day...
I bet you wanted to kill me.
-No...
-Everyone.
Listen, everyone!
He's trying to kill his older brother!
-No.
-Everyone!
He's trying to kill his older brother!
No...
Listen, people! He is...
He's trying to kill his older brother!
No, that's not true.
No...
-No...
-Listen, people!
Everyone,
He's trying to kill his older brother!
-No...
-Everyone, listen.
-No.
-My brother...
Listen,
he's trying to kill his older brother!
No, that's not true.
Listen to me.
-Sang-tae, no.
-He's trying to kill his older brother!
It's not true.
No, that's not true.
No, Sang-tae. That's not true.
I'm not lying.
Sang-tae.
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
IT'S OKAY TO NOT BE OKAY
Why did you save me?
You should've just left me to die.
Try your best to stay strong. Who knows?
Sang-tae might be the one
to help you one day.
I...
had a dream.
What you just said
sounds like you
begging me to stop you.
I miss him.
It seems like you know
a lot about Do Hui-jae.
Should I just kill him?
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee