Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
To get what I couldn't give you last time.
My brother is already a handful.
I'm already having a hard time
bearing with him, so please...
Please stop stirring up my miserable life.
And get lost.
CHAPTER 11
THE UGLY DUCKLING
What about Ms. Park Ok-ran?
Where is she now?
What do we do? It looks like she escaped.
Call the police station nearby. Hurry.
-Come with me.
-Okay.
GANG-TAE
You obviously didn't get all dressed up
and come here at this late hour
just for a cup of tea.
What do you want?
Darn it.
How nice.
The smell of old books.
These flowers are dead.
You should toss out dead things.
Don't touch my stuff.
What brings you here?
I was worried
that you'd be lonely.
Ko Mun-yeong.
Mun-yeong.
Earlier today,
your father tried to kill me.
He called me
a monster.
He said all monsters must be killed.
He also said he should've killed
his daughter too that day.
He completely lashed out at me.
You didn't know, did you?
-So what?
-It's just too cruel.
He's a father.
On his daughter's birthday of all days...
Gosh.
How could he say such a thing?
So I thought I should come by
to make you feel better
and wish you a happy birthday.
It's lonely to spend a day like this
all by yourself.
-But why do you care?
-Because I'm a fan.
Your mother.
I'm a fan of hers.
This is pretty.
I clearly told you
not to touch my stuff.
We're alike.
I also
hate it when people touch my stuff.
Ko Mun-yeong!
Where...
Ko Mun-yeong.
Moon Gang-tae?
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
-That lady, Park Ok-ran--
-Where is she?
Where is she now?
-She left.
-When? Where did she go?
When did she leave?
Just now.
Did you
come here to catch that escaped patient?
Not because of me?
Not because you missed me?
So you obviously
put your brother before me,
and even that patient
is more important to you than I am.
Ko Mun-yeong.
He followed that patient here,
so why the hell did he hug me?
Please.
At least count to three
before you do anything impulsive.
-One.
-Oh, no.
Is your hand okay?
-Two.
-You're bleeding.
-My gosh.
-Three.
I'm returning it.
Get out.
Should I have just stabbed her with it
and kept her here?
Let's talk.
Why wrap that around my hand?
Did I say it hurt?
It's just a small cut on the palm.
It doesn't even hurt.
"What we have
is an ill-fated relationship.
Please stop stirring up my miserable life.
And get lost."
That nonsense you talked about
was much more...
It was
much more hurtful.
You said that I'm not an empty can.
Then why are you treating me like one?
I said today
is a very important day to me.
I told you that I didn't want to be alone!
When you can't control yourself,
count to three.
One.
Two.
-Three.
Happy birthday.
I missed you.
Why are you blushing?
I'm... I'm just hot.
It's so hot in here, isn't it?
Your face is all red too.
I'm not feeling well.
You're burning up.
Mr. Moon called.
It sounds like Ms. Park Ok-ran
stopped by Ms. Ko's place.
What? Why did she go there?
We'll have to find out.
Let the police know
where she was last seen.
Yes, sir. I'll also update you
as soon as we check the security footage.
She may come back late at night,
so stay here
and make rounds throughout the night.
-Yes, sir.
-Will do.
Is your head okay?
How could I be okay?
She hit my head with a stone.
This should be processed
as a workplace injury.
All right.
I'll help you file a claim
for the benefits
and also consider
terminating your employment.
-Wait.
-Get home safely, sir.
Get home safely.
Hot. It's hot.
Be careful when touching something hot.
Gosh, it's hot. Be careful.
You must be careful.
Hey, Sang-tae.
Hi, Jae-su.
What? Why are you eating so late?
Are you snacking?
I waited for Gang-tae
to have dinner with him,
but there's an emergency at the hospital.
He has to catch someone,
so he can't come home tonight.
He's been dispatched.
That's why I'm here on his behalf.
That looks good.
-Can I have a bite?
-Gosh, no way. This is mine.
One bite will turn
into two and three bites.
"He who will steal an egg
will steal an ox."
No way. This is all mine.
Oh, right.
I found this out front.
That's Mang-tae.
-Mang-tae?
-Yes.
You mean, as in Grandpa Mang-tae
from the book?
No, he's not a grandpa.
He's Gang-tae's little brother.
Sang-tae, Gang-tae, and Mang-tae.
We're
three brothers.
Goodness.
What the heck?
I can't believe you're calling
this ugly fabric doll your little brother.
I'm the one who's been
following you around for over ten years.
If you want to say you have two brothers,
include me.
Jae-su between Sang-tae and Gang-tae.
-Include Jae-su.
-No way, Jae-su.
You're not our brother.
We don't have the same surname
and we're not related.
You're not on our family register,
so we're basically strangers.
You're not our family. How dare you.
How dare you...
-Just include me!
-Gosh, no. Don't.
Don't do that when I'm eating hot food.
-Just include me, will you?
-No, Jae-su--
-No, Mang-tae! It's hot!
-Gosh!
Come. I filled the bathtub
with ice-cold water.
Ice-cold water? Why?
You need to bring your fever down.
I've seen it in movies.
Get undressed and go in the tub.
You want rose petals in the water?
No, it's okay. Just get me a wet towel.
That lady...
Did she escape the hospital?
Can I ask you
what she said to you?
She said she thought I'd be lonely
and came to wish me a happy birthday.
She also said she's my mom's fan.
What else?
She said she nearly died
at the hospital today.
Why did that happen?
Patients often get into a fight like that.
You don't need to worry about it.
This feels nice.
What feels nice?
I've never
had someone look after me
when I was sick.
Ju-ri!
Heading out to work?
I'm sorry.
I should've apologized to you sooner
for the trouble I caused you.
Gosh, we're no strangers.
We're like a family
living under the same roof.
Come on. Don't even worry about it.
Here.
-What is this?
-Money for a car wash.
Please accept it.
-So this is how it feels.
-Pardon?
Every time Mun-yeong
got herself in trouble in the past,
I gave people cash
disguised as a box of sweet drinks.
This is probably how they felt
upon receiving it.
You reap what you sow.
Let's go out for a meal with this money.
Then I'll call it even.
Damn it.
I thought you were gone.
Where would I go?
How's your fever?
-It's gone down.
-In just a day?
You little...
You were faking it, weren't you?
No.
It was lovesickness.
Let's talk.
What did you want to talk to me about?
It's about my brother.
Jeez, that brother of yours.
Sang-tae
has a traumatic memory.
A traumatic memory?
That's why we left Seongjin City
when we were little
and had to move as if we're running away
from something every spring.
All because of his traumatic memory.
My mom
was murdered.
And Sang-tae was the only witness
who saw her getting murdered.
The butterfly said it'd kill me as well
if I didn't keep my lips sealed.
It said it'd chase me down
and kill me!
We were scared, so we ran away.
I was only 12,
-and there was no adult
-Come on.
who could protect us.
That's when it began.
Every spring
when you start seeing butterflies,
Sang-tae
has nightmares about the night
when Mom was killed.
What? Butterflies...
No, those butterflies!
-What? What's going on?
-Butterflies!
-Goodness.
-What's the matter?
-Those butterflies...
-Sang-tae.
-Butterflies...
Gosh, those butterflies...
-Butterflies! Those butterflies!
-He says the butterflies will kill him.
They said they'll kill me. The butterflies
-will kill me!
-And that we must run far away.
They're coming to kill me!
He's been bearing that pain all on his own
for nearly 20 years now.
And that's why
he needs me.
But the thing is,
despite that,
I keep wanting to spend time with you.
You once said
that you don't care about destiny.
If someone shows up when you need them,
you call that destiny.
And I
need you.
I have to stay
by Sang-tae's side,
so you just
stay by my side.
Sure, why not?
SANG-TAE
It is a flower
-Hey.
-Did you eat?
I had rice
with kimchi soybean sprout soup.
Did you catch the culprit? The culprit.
She's a patient, not a culprit.
Yes, the patient. Did you catch her?
No, I couldn't find her.
Oh, no. Then what are you going to do?
You don't need to worry about that.
Don't eat dinner without me.
I'll try to be home early.
Okay.
He'll be home early today.
The test will be done in no time,
so don't worry about a thing.
I'll see you in a bit.
Get going.
See you later.
Oh, boy.
I hope his brain tumor hasn't come back.
I'm worried.
It's a miracle that he's managed to
survive in that state for almost 20 years.
What did the police say
about Ms. Park Ok-ran?
She was last caught on CCTV footage
by the exit of a hiking trail
in Mount Oji last night.
They have to investigate
to find out where she went.
Really? Then clean up her bed
and send her belongings to the police.
We have to admit a patient
on the waiting list.
Already? She may come back.
No, she won't be able to.
Hi.
Wait.
We have to clean up Park Ok-ran's bed
and collect her belongings.
-Already?
-Yes.
Ms. Park said we have to admit a patient
on the waiting list.
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
Is she not coming back?
Or can she not come back?
Even when dogs run away,
people at least pretend to look for them
for a few days.
The head nurse doesn't come across
like that, but she's heartless.
The police are looking for her.
I see.
NAME: PARK OK-RAN
Thank you.
You've changed.
-Pardon?
-Your smile.
It's pretty.
I heard Park Ok-ran
was an obscure stage actress in the past.
She had multiple plastic surgeries.
I heard it from Yoo Seon-hae,
who shares the room with her.
-Gosh, what is this?
-She said that woman had been
acting weird for a couple of months.
Apparently, she said
she had to practice acting
and kept snickering
while looking in the mirror.
She also kept memorizing something
all night.
Yoo Seon-hae said she seemed to think
that she was still an actress.
She was practicing acting?
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
I'm so glad I held myself back last night.
Damn it!
What? "Damn it"?
I see that you're beginning
to show your true colors.
I'm sorry, sir.
-Where did you sleep last night?
-Pardon me?
You looked depressed,
but you now look all happy.
I guess you slept somewhere else
last night.
Did you get some action
instead of looking for the patient?
No, sir. That's not what happened.
But why go there?
Well...
I was very worried and...
To wish her a happy birthday, perhaps?
No.
That's not why I went there. I just--
No, I'm talking about Ms. Park Ok-ran.
Why did she go there?
There's no way she escaped
just to wish Ms. Ko a happy birthday.
I hope that's the case though.
I hope Ms. Park went there
to wish her a happy birthday
and that
nothing will happen to us anymore.
I really hope so.
And that being said...
Sir.
Everything from here to here.
To go, please.
Everything?
Everything on that row, ma'am?
While you're getting that ready,
I'd like to speak with your part-timer.
Sang-tae.
I think Ms. Ko needs to talk to you
about something.
Hurry over here and have a seat.
Move back in.
We need to get some work done.
This drawing you gave me--
I didn't give it to you. I threw it out.
Right, this drawing you had tossed out
gave me an idea for my next book.
Amazing, right?
I'll tell you what I want to write about.
These three will set off on a long journey
to find something they lost.
Oh, that will be fun.
Right?
Best friends do think alike.
That looks fun. I want it.
He said he'd never draw butterflies.
He was stubborn about it,
so I sort of had a hunch,
but I didn't know
there was such a shocking story behind it.
But why are you telling me all this
out of the blue?
You said one must
face one's traumatic memories
to overcome them.
Please help Sang-tae
so that he can face his trauma.
Do you trust me?
Everyone in this field
says that I'm a quack,
not just a quirky weirdo.
If you're a quack,
my brother
will know right away.
Unilaterally terminating the contract
triples the penalty.
You know that, right?
The penalty?
That was not included in the contract.
What you see isn't everything.
When it comes to liability
for breach of contract,
a verbal agreement based on trust
is enough. It's a tacit rule.
-Your face tells me that you do.
-What?
No, I never received anything.
Not even the camping car.
I provided you with room and board.
Do you know how much that cost me?
Either compensate me threefold
or draw my illustrations.
-Your choice.
-My choice?
I need to double that, for Gang-tae.
Compensate me sixfold.
What? Sixfold?
Hey.
Ms. Ko Mun-yeong
is such a wonderful person.
What's gotten into you?
You know that I love people
who are generous and decisive.
You do?
Yes, she's totally my type.
Not romantically though.
I'm not saying I'm attracted to her.
You're my number one,
no matter what anyone says.
But how important am I to you?
You're my number three.
What on earth is she up to?
-Even if it blooms in the field
-You won't draw my illustrations
-It is a flower
-or pay the penalty.
-So what? You don't care?
-Hello, tree!
-Good morning!
-Forget the contract.
-It is a flower
-We're besties. You're my fan.
-A fan must stay loyal.
-It is a flower
-Sang-tae, a promise
isn't something you can take so lightly.
Do you hear me?
Damn it. Moon Sang-tae!
You can't have Gang-tae!
Never!
Gang-tae isn't some object
we can toss around.
That's right. He's my brother.
Exactly, he's just your brother.
-He's not yours.
-He's not yours either.
Gang-tae is mine.
Gang-tae belongs to Gang-tae.
No, he's mine. I'm his big brother.
I'm sick of that word, "brother"!
You're just a stranger to us. A stranger!
-"Brother"!
-Stranger!
-I'm so sick of that word.
-Stranger.
-Damn it.
-Gosh.
-They're fighting.
-Stop swearing.
-Old habits...
-Teacher, they're fighting!
-die hard.
-No, they're not fighting.
-Let's go.
-Hi. Hello!
Did you and that lady fight?
Yes. No, we didn't really fight.
Why did you two fight?
We didn't fight.
We just had disagreements.
I really did my best.
How?
I tried asking him nicely and
persuading him in an articulate manner.
More like threatening him, I'm sure.
-Did you guys talk on the phone?
-Must I ask him to know?
Then you probably also know
how I feel right now.
How do you feel?
"Please give me permission
to marry your daughter."
I can totally relate to men
who must beg their girlfriends' parents.
-Really?
-Yes, really.
But you know...
Without his permission,
we can't live together.
It took my friend, Jae-su,
about ten years
to become close to Sang-tae.
Ten years?
-Anyway, just wait.
-For ten years? Are you nuts?
No. I have to drop these off
at the nurses' station, so wait here.
That little...
Did it really take him ten years?
No, right? You were joking, right?
-Ten years, my foot.
-Right?
You already got on his bad side,
so it'll take longer.
I definitely cannot wait that long.
No way. I refuse!
For Sang-tae...
I'm his only family.
He's afraid
that you'd take me away from him
and that he'd be left alone.
-What do I do, then?
-We should earn his trust.
-What do you mean?
-You're not taking me away from him.
He now has one more person
who will stay by his side.
You're not a stranger.
You'll be one of us.
Earn his trust.
You will, right?
I'll try.
Also,
keep the door locked when you're alone.
Do not let strangers into the house.
Okay?
Okay, I won't.
Good girl.
My gosh, what's all this pizza for?
So? How's Mr. Ko doing?
The brain tumor has spread deep inside
the frontal lobe.
What did his doctor say?
Can he undergo surgery now?
No, he said it'll be pointless now.
My gosh, I feel so bad for Mr. Ko.
Oh, dear.
Where are you going?
I have plans. I'm leaving for the day.
Plans? With who?
You're taking the rest of the day off?
With Sang-in. I'll see you later.
Wait, just a second.
What? Gosh, no. I don't want that.
-Stay still, will you?
-No.
You're going on a date,
so you need
to put on some makeup at least.
You'll meet him barefaced?
Are you that confident?
Goodness.
-How do I look?
-You look so pretty.
It looks like spring flowers
have bloomed on your lips.
I'll see you at home.
Stay out as late as possible.
My gosh, you're wearing makeup.
I wear makeup every day.
Right. You look pretty every single day
with or without makeup.
Well, can I ask you something
about Mun-yeong?
Does she have any family members
other than her dad?
Any close relatives?
Had there been an adult
who could look after her,
she would've ended up quite differently.
Why do you ask?
Are Professor Ko's test results that bad?
Has his brain tumor come back?
It doesn't look like
he can undergo surgery again.
That's unfortunate.
I'll see how she's doing
and find the best time to tell her.
By any chance, did Gang-tae--
-Well, Ju-ri.
-Yes?
Enough about Moon Gang-tae
and Ko Mun-yeong.
Why don't we talk about Nam Ju-ri
and Lee Sang-in?
Let them have fun on their own.
There are so many things
I want to know about Nam Ju-ri.
Since when did pink lipstick
suit you so well?
And why do you turn into
a different person when you're drunk?
Oh, also...
Who taught you to swear like that?
I...
Back in middle school,
I see.
My dad taught me how to drink.
Then how much can you drink?
I must pay threefold.
No, I must pay six times the amount
to get Gang-tae out as well.
But all I have is...
-Sang-tae.
-Yes.
-It's hot. What are you doing in there?
Well...
-Did everything go well at the restaurant?
-Yes.
Oh, Jae-su gave me a tip
because we made a lot of money today.
He gave me 30,000 won.
Customers give you tips,
bosses give you bonuses.
Yes, I got 30,000 won as a bonus.
I see.
Someone must've bought a lot of pizza.
Yes...
Yes. Ms. Ko Mun-yeong. She's rich.
She's filthy rich.
Ms. Ko came to the pizzeria? Why?
She... She came to the pizzeria
to buy pizza.
She didn't come to the pizzeria
to buy potatoes.
Why would you ask something so obvious?
Why are you here?
He was worried about
leaving you here all by yourself,
so I was asked to stay here for a while.
Mr. Lee?
No, it was Mr. Moon Gang-tae.
Don't just stand there.
Come here and sit down.
Mr. Moon called and asked Mr. Lee
if it'd be okay for me to work here.
He said that?
Mr. Lee was also thrilled
that you're going to start
working on your next book.
So he wanted me to come here
and support you for the time being.
Is that so?
Feel free to let me know
if you need anything.
I don't really need anything.
But I do have a question.
Sure. Go ahead.
Someone visited me last night
saying she's a fan of my mother.
And it just so happened to be
my birthday.
Isn't that weird?
No, not at all.
Why?
Back when I used to be a fan of Tony,
an H.O.T member,
I congratulated all the birthdays
of his entire family.
I bought gifts and waited for him
in front of his accommodation,
and the managers got really angry at me.
And after the group disbanded,
I went around everywhere
to get a glimpse of them again.
Really?
But if you were an H.O.T fan,
how old are you?
Have a good night.
Are you sure you're younger than me?
-"I... I ate breakfast.
-I ate breakfast.
-Then I ate lunch.
-And I had a small dinner.
-So I was hungry at night.
-Why isn't there anything about me?
-Why isn't there anything about me?"
-What do you mean?
-Sang-tae.
Why does Gil-dong let them live with him
even though he's always
angry at them?
That's because he's their guardian.
He's an adult.
But they're not even his family.
That's right. They don't have the same
surname, aren't related to each other,
and they're not on the same family
register. So they're basically strangers.
If they're strangers,
why does he let them live with him?
Because he's their guardian.
He's an adult.
You're
an adult, right?
Moon Sang-tae, 35 years old.
Born in 1984, the year of the rat.
I'm younger than I look,
but I'm not a child.
Exactly. You're an adult.
An adult like Ko Gil-dong,
who can accept others as a family.
Yes.
Sang-tae, do you want to know something?
I'm also
trying really hard
to become an adult.
You... You can also become an adult.
You... You just need to try hard.
You just need to make an effort.
I'm guessing you'll be done by next week.
Yes, I'm... I'm almost done.
It'll be complete soon. I'll be done.
But...
By the way,
how much are you going to pay me?
How... How much do you think
you can pay me for this?
I want to get paid the day I finish this.
Oh, dear. I don't see any butterflies
in the flower garden.
I... I'm not going to draw
any butterflies.
I told you that I wanted the painting
to look exactly like the garden outside.
There are tons of butterflies outside,
but the mural has none.
That means it's not complete.
It means you're not done.
I... I don't like butterflies.
I... I don't want to draw butterflies.
Then forget it.
But you won't be getting paid.
I don't want an incomplete mural.
But... But my money...
But...
This... This is pretty much complete.
My money... Gosh.
Oh, no.
O Ji-wang is a con artist.
He's a liar. That's what he is.
He sounds nice and looks nice,
but he's a liar.
I... I can't trust anyone.
Did I keep you waiting?
Let's go.
Why did you bring all your paints?
You're not done with the mural.
I'm not going to do it.
Why not?
I... I just don't want to.
Why don't you want to?
You're almost done.
No, I don't want to. Forget it.
I... I don't want to draw butterflies.
I don't want to do that.
Sang-tae.
Can we talk?
Stop.
Sang-tae.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Get up.
Get up. Let's talk.
Let me go!
You're not going to draw the mural
or go to the hospital?
And why don't you ever want to see
Director O again?
Are you going to avoid answering me
and keep acting like a kid?
I thought you were an adult.
Come on. Get up.
I'm going to count to three.
One.
Two.
-Three.
-Director O is a con artist!
He's a liar! He... He's even worse
than people who do voice phishing.
He... He promised to pay me once I'm done.
So why... Why won't he pay me?
Gosh. Stop running away. I won't let you.
-No.
-Talk to me.
No, let me go.
Just talk to me, Sang-tae.
No, I'm going to go. Move.
Stop avoiding it
and tell me what happened.
Let me go!
Will you please just talk?
It hurts, right?
It hurts when someone hits you,
doesn't it?
You hurt me, too. Look at the bite mark.
You... You hit me?
You hit your big brother?
How dare you hit your big brother?
You hurt me, too.
It hurt like crazy
when you stabbed me on the head
with a pencil.
When you pushed me and made me hit
a desk, I couldn't even sleep at night.
Do you think I stay quiet
because I enjoy getting hurt?
I'm not going to hold it in anymore.
I'm done doing that!
When... When you need to control yourself,
count to three.
One, two, three.
No, you count!
Listen to your big brother!
Then act like one!
Wait... Sang-tae, I meant...
You... You yelled at me?
How... How dare you yell
at your big brother?
You... You dared to yell at me?
How dare you? How... How could you?
How could you do that to me?
How could you?
Stop!
Come over here!
Come here!
Hey!
Are you about to die soon or something?
Is that why you're acting out?
I didn't really mind it
when Sang-tae hit me.
But now that I've fought back...
What did I tell you?
It breaks your heart, doesn't it?
No.
I feel so relieved.
The lunatic virus
is surprisingly powerful.
You've changed so much.
Jae-su.
Who are you? Do I know you?
This is...
who I really am.
Moon Gang-tae
belongs to Moon Gang-tae.
It's going to sting.
Gang-tae isn't my brother anymore.
He's not my brother.
Yes, you're right.
He shouldn't have scratched you.
That's cheating.
I never took him as the type
to fight dirty like this.
He cheated.
I saw him earlier,
and he was a lot more injured.
He's not my little brother anymore.
We're strangers now.
We're strangers.
-You're strangers?
-Yes.
Then...
Mom, why don't you just adopt Gang-tae
as your son?
I'd love to do that.
Sang-tae, thank you.
I'll think of him as my son now.
No.
Never mind. We're strangers.
Are you sleeping?
Jae-su.
I know you are disappointed,
but try to understand.
Me and Sang-tae...
It's just been the two of us
for a long time.
We have to learn
to socialize with other people.
But why does it have to be
Ko Mun-yeong?
She's the loneliest person
I know.
I'm going to start with her.
Call me.
I'm bored.
I'm hungry.
Darn it.
Why does he read my messages
if he isn't going to reply?
Maybe I shouldn't have returned Mang-tae.
I told you not to open the door
for strangers.
You promised.
Why did you bring this?
What are you doing here?
You told me you're hungry.
Let's go outside.
Are you really not going to tell me?
What happened to your face?
I got into a fight.
With a patient?
-That will get me fired.
-Then who was it?
-What are you going to do?
-I'm going to beat them up.
My brother.
Sang-tae?
You beat him up?
No, we just had a fight.
He hit me a lot more than I did.
Didn't you say we need to let him know
that he'll be getting another friend?
But you just fought with him?
What are you going to do now?
I'm still thinking about it.
Weren't you the one who told me
to think before I act?
You told me it's not a bad thing
to stick to your instincts.
Just be honest with him.
-What do you mean?
-Tell him you like me
and that you can't live without me.
Ask for his understanding.
It's simple.
I...
like Ko Mun-yeong.
I wonder what he'll say
if I tell him that.
When will you stop
caring about your brother
and start caring about yourself?
Didn't you ever have a dream?
Something you wanted to do.
Well...
I had about three.
Two of them already came true.
What were they?
I wanted to go on a trip
instead of moving somewhere.
And?
I wanted to have a fight with my brother.
It's lame, isn't it?
But you see,
I had a blast.
I think...
I'm finally living a normal life.
What's the dream
that hasn't come true yet?
You came running to me today,
so I'll make it come true.
No.
It's too late now.
Why? What is it?
Going to school in a uniform.
-What is this?
-What's that?
Hey, get up.
Eat up.
My gosh, come on.
KO MUN-YEONG
What? Where are you going?
Where are you going? Gang-tae!
Where are you going?
Hey.
Hey... Excuse me. Hey.
Well...
-Well--
-Gang-tae!
Did you skip school today?
-Come here.
-No.
-I just skipped the self-study time.
-Same thing.
Why do you even bother wearing a uniform?
-Why are you not at work?
-You little punk.
What...
Gosh, you're so annoying.
Excuse me.
-Hey, you. The girl with short hair.
-Stop it.
My brother has something to say to you.
-Can you please spare him some time?
-Will you stop?
Stop it.
She's coming.
She's coming here.
Be a man. Impress her.
Hey.
I...
Well...
I know you.
I saw you at school.
She knows you.
Well...
Congratulations.
Good luck.
Sang-tae.
Yes?
I...
I like her so much.
I like her.
What?
"Happy."
He's happy.
Gang-tae is...
He's
happy.
Gang... Gang-tae
He's... He's happy.
Yes.
That's right.
My brother...
He's happy.
Gang-tae is happy.
I... I've never seen him like this.
This is the first time.
My goodness.
Hey, why do you look so tired?
Mr. Lee, I don't think
I'm fit for this house.
I have nightmares all night,
and I get the creeps.
My entire body aches--
My gosh, that's enough.
Where's Mun-yeong?
She's in her study.
Look at you
sitting in front of your laptop!
It's been so long.
What is it going to be about?
I couldn't sleep a wink last night
because I was so excited.
I bet it's going to be an amazing story.
Wait.
Let me get ready first.
I'm ready. Now, tell me. What is it?
Here.
Is this
supposed to be similar to Bumpety Boo?
I don't have the storyline yet.
-What's the title?
-Undecided.
-What's the underlying message?
-Unsure.
-When will it be ready?
-Someday.
-So that means you have nothing.
-Probably.
Who's going to be your illustrator?
My best friend.
Please make way.
SANG-TAE
-What's--
-Did you eat?
Did you eat?
I couldn't eat
because we had an emergency patient.
Are... Are you hungry?
Yes, I'm starving.
Come to the restaurant
We Are Family by 6 p.m.
Meet me at We Are Family.
Mun-yeong.
-Mun-yeong?
-I'm going to stick to this subject.
That's fine.
That's not what I was going to talk about.
About your father...
His brain tumor came back.
It's apparently inoperable.
There's nothing they can do to save him.
My dad died a long time ago
when I was 12.
He died already.
All that's left of him is his body.
Mun-yeong.
Your father's brain is damaged.
That is why his memory is all messed up.
His body and mind
isn't functioning together
so that's why he acts the way he does.
But even so,
he's still your one and only family.
"Family"?
I'm an orphan.
-Mun-yeong.
-Leave. I'm tired.
Where are you?
I'm hungry. Let's eat together.
Let me join. I want to go, too.
Where is that restaurant?
Why not? Why can't I go?
Wait.
The adult needs to eat first.
Then you can eat.
-Okay.
-Did you wipe your hands?
Did you? Here. Wipe your hands and eat.
ORDER
TOTAL: 26,400 WON
Was... Was it delicious?
Are you full?
Yes.
I'm really full.
My stomach might explode.
Your... Your stomach shouldn't explode.
If your stomach explodes, you'll die.
It... It's your allowance.
"Customers give you tips,
bosses give bonuses."
And older brothers give allowance.
Overspending is a sin.
Make sure you don't overspend.
I'll... I'll give you more if you run out.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
I... I won't overspend it.
ORDER
TOTAL: 46,200 WON
Buy me dinner, too.
Darn it.
My gosh.
Buy me dinner.
Pay for mine as well. Buy me dinner, too.
Darn it.
Why are you leaving me out?
Buy me dinner, too.
Excuse me.
How much does she need to pay?
Then give me an allowance.
No one gives me that kind of stuff,
and I don't have a family to eat with.
I'm really an orphan now.
Let's go home.
Sang-tae.
I want a big brother like you!
Come on, Gang-tae!
Ko Mun-yeong!
Ko Mun-yeong...
Mun-yeong, get over here!
Hurry... Hurry up, Mun-yeong.
Aren't you guys coming?
Ko Mun-yeong. Moon Gang-tae.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Hurry...
Sang-tae, do you know
the fairy tale called The Ugly Duckling?
Yes.
The... The other ducks are mean
to the ugly duckling.
They bully him
because he looks different from them.
So he gets really lonely
and leaves his family, right?
Mun-yeong, don't run down the stairs!
You'll get hurt! It's dangerous!
Stop running.
What do you think would've happened
if the mother duck gave lots of love
to the ugly duckling?
Then... Then it wouldn't have left.
If the adult embraces the kids,
the ducks and swans
can all get along
and live together just fine.
Hey, duck. Chickens.
Don't fight with each other, okay?
Sang-tae.
Are you an adult
who knows how to embrace others?
Yes.
I'm... I'm an adult. An adult.
I'm...
I'm an adult like Ko Gil-dong.
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
IT'S OKAY TO NOT BE OKAY
The family register isn't everything.
A family...
One, two, three.
You become a family
by taking a family portrait together.
GANG-TAE,
PHOTO STUDIO ADDRESS
I hate kids and animals.
Because they beg for love...
Let go. Let go of me.
It makes me grow fond of them.
What if the butterfly shows up again?
Don't let the past trap you.
If we get stuck, we just have to
open the door and leave.
-You won't be able to see the door.
-I was finally
starting to get the urge
to live like everyone else.
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee