Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
Are you sure I can trust you?
I also cut my brother's hair for him.
I'm the only one who can touch it.
The sea should be here. Hello!
He asked you to
cut his hair like that, right?
No.
I came up with that hairstyle.
I don't want a mushroom haircut.
It's too late.
I have the scissors.
Stay still if you want this to go well.
It's all done.
How do I look?
You look pretty.
I no longer need to listen to my mom
now that I cut off my leash.
So you wanted to escape from
your mother?
Yes.
Now, I'm free.
Congratulations.
Don't congratulate me.
I want a compliment.
Good for you. I'm so proud of you.
Now, let's go have fun wherever.
Whether it's to a mountain or a field.
Like the Cheerful Dog?
Yes, like the Cheerful Dog.
CHAPTER 8
BEAUTY AND THE BEAST
It is a flower
Even if it blooms in the field
They're all flowers
What... What happened to your long hair?
I cut it.
-What do you think?
-Long hair suits you better.
What do you mean?
She looks better with short hair.
No.
She looked 100 to 1,000 times better
when her long, black hair
used to come down
all the way to her waist.
Why did she cut it?
-Why did you do that? Why?
-Sang-tae.
Let me cut your hair today as well.
It's really long.
You gave me a haircut on Wednesday.
I only gave you a trim.
Let's cut off a bit more today.
Now, eat up.
Okay. You looked better with long hair.
Why did you do that?
You shouldn't have cut it off.
Why did you get such an ugly haircut?
Why did you just kick me?
-Me?
-Yes, that's right. You.
You just kicked me three times.
These darn quail eggs.
Here.
I want a rolled omelet.
-Here.
-You should do it yourself.
You're not a baby.
Your brother is so slow-witted.
You mean he's too honest.
Are you taking your brother's side?
Of course. We're brothers.
Hey.
Come home as soon as you finish work.
Come and spend time with me.
From now on,
you're in charge of cutting my hair.
Okay?
Why not just go to a hair salon?
I'm just like your brother.
I don't like it
when other people touch me.
But you're an exception.
Only you can touch me.
Do I really look pretty?
Yes.
You look pretty.
I agree.
I also think I'm really pretty.
What was that laugh for?
Don't fight with Sang-tae.
Make sure you get along.
I'll see you.
Come home quickly.
If you're late, I'll kill you.
-Hello.
KO MUN-YEONG'S FAIRY TALE CLASS
PUT ON PAUSE TEMPORARILY
Gosh, you scared me.
Do I look that bad?
I look like a zombie.
Did something happen at night?
Do you have a concealer?
-What's that?
-Maybe a cushion?
-The cushions are in the lounge.
-No, a cushion compact.
Forget it.
Did something happen with a patient?
Who was it?
Mr. Ko Dae-hwan.
Why? What happened?
He had a seizure last night again.
It was a complete nightmare.
He came out to the hallway
with his eyes rolling upwards.
Then he started foaming at the mouth
and had spasms.
I didn't get to sleep a wink.
Gosh, why does this happen
every time I'm on night duty?
Why?
My goodness.
Do you think he'll be okay?
I'm worried he might have
another brain tumor.
He kept talking gibberish all night.
Don't worry too much.
I bet you didn't get any sleep last night.
I was actually thinking about
skipping meditation class
and get some good sleep instead.
You should do that. Here.
Get some sleep.
Mr. Moon.
Mr. Ko drooled too much saliva.
Can you help him get changed?
Sure.
That woman...
sang
a song.
What song?
"Oh My Darling, Clementine."
I'm sure
she's dead.
But that woman
is here.
Who are you
talking about?
She's dead.
But she's here.
WHAT IS THE TRUTH BEHIND WRITER
KO MUN-YEONG'S DISAPPEARANCE?
KO MUN-YEONG IS LOOKING AFTER
HER SICK FATHER
IS SHE PLANNING TO RETIRE?
She's pretending to be a kind daughter.
I bet she doesn't even care.
She needs to become a better person first.
A fairy tale writer who cusses
doesn't deserve to write.
I really regret having read her books.
I want to gather these insects
and spray pesticide on them.
Darn it.
I used to have tons of fans.
Where in the world are they?
Actually, my fan is right here.
Don't forget to ventilate the room
after you spray pesticide.
But if you want to kill insects properly,
electric fly swatters are the best.
Sang-tae, why do you like my fairy tales?
Because you wrote them.
So you like me, not my fairy tales.
-Why do you like me?
-Because you're pretty.
What do you like about me?
Your hair. Your long hair.
Your long, black hair
that came all the way to your waist.
It was so pretty. Gosh.
-You cut it off. You shouldn't have.
-End of meeting.
We never started a meeting.
How can you end a meeting
when we never even started one?
You give me a headache.
-Let's have a meeting later.
-"Later?"
Later... Later.
You mean sometime before you die?
No, I need to get a camping car.
I need to receive a camping car.
Do you have what I asked you to look into?
I know you told me
this is all part of work,
but I felt so uneasy
about doing a background search.
Why?
You're good at doing that.
If you hadn't done a background search
on that caregiver for Mun-yeong--
Her name is Nam Ju-ri.
She's currently single.
She met Moon Gang-tae
when they worked together
at the same hospital a year ago.
They haven't known each other long.
Her father died due to an illness
when she was little.
Oh, dear.
And her mother used to cook
for construction workers.
My goodness, she had a tough life.
Right now, she's working as a cook
at OK Psychiatric Hospital.
And the daughter and mother
are living together
at a two-story house
with a mortgage to pay off.
The Moon brothers live
in the rooftop house.
And their friend who runs a pizza place
lives in the basement.
And apparently, the owner of the house
gives them meals for free.
They're practically lodgers.
Mr. Lee.
Do you like that nurse?
Hey, why are you so quick-witted
when it comes to stuff like this?
Why can't you be like this with work?
Hey.
Be honest with me.
About what?
Between me and that caregiver...
Who do you think is better?
For a romantic relationship?
I'm taller and bigger than him.
And think about
my social position and maturity.
Aren't I much better than him?
But you lack the most important trait.
What's that?
This. Your face.
My gosh. You little!
How do I look?
You look pretty.
I must be crazy.
Hey, can I talk to Ms. Park Ok-ran?
Yes, right now.
Come in.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
My goodness.
Hello, Ms. Park.
You can sit over here.
Stay.
Just stay.
My goodness, you look great these days.
I guess the medicine is working.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to ask you something.
By any chance,
did you happen to see Mr. Ko Dae-hwan
in the hallway last night
at around midnight?
I did
go to the bathroom at that hour.
But I didn't see him.
By any chance, did you sing a song
when you went to the bathroom?
A song?
What song?
Ever since he regained consciousness
he keeps saying the same thing.
What was it... You know...
Right!
"Oh My Darling, Clementine."
He keeps saying that he heard that song.
In a cavern, in a canyon,
Excavating for a mine
...sang a song.
Oh My Darling, Clementine.
Lived a miner
forty-niner,
-I'm not a ghost.
-"A ghost"?
Yoo Seon-hae,
that woman who used to be a shaman,
keeps talking nonsense.
She keeps saying a ghost shows up at night
and sings at the end of the hallway.
But
I'm not a ghost.
Of course you're not a ghost.
So you didn't sing that song?
No, I didn't.
Okay then.
Why are you smiling?
It's just that
no one's really paid attention to me
even though I've been here
for a few months.
But now, people are paying attention.
How interesting.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
You are lost and gone forever,
Dreadful sorry Clementine
It's that song.
Why do you think she lied?
I don't know.
But
why are you asking me?
Ms. Ko Mun-yeong
is Mr. Ko Dae-hwan's only guardian.
And right now, you're pretty much
Ms. Ko Mun-yeong's guardian.
So it's kind of your business as well.
I don't think it is.
Chew on this.
Chewing on something
helps you prevent dementia.
It seems like something strange
is happening at our hospital.
Let's keep this between you and me
for the time being.
And during that time,
I'd like you to keep a close eye
on Ms. Park Ok-ran.
You're teaming up with the most
powerful man in this hospital.
Are you just going to chew and ignore me?
What do you want?
KO MUN-YEONG'S FAIRY TALE CLASS
PUT ON PAUSE TEMPORARILY
-Where are you going?
-The Chinese restaurant and pizza place.
You're going to eat that much?
I'm having Chinese with Gang-tae,
and I work at the pizzeria.
"Gang-tae"? I want to go, too.
HARIMGAK
Here's your jjamppong.
This is that jjamppong.
It has mussels and chili pepper inside.
The broth tastes amazing.
Why would you come to a shabby place
like this to eat jjamppong?
Our mom used to bring us here often
because I loved the jjamppong here.
"I want to have it every day, Mom.
I want to eat it every day."
No wonder.
It seemed like a famous restaurant
with a long history.
Eat up.
Here. Eat up.
What about you, Mom?
I'm not hungry.
Is it good?
-Yes.
-Really?
It's spicy.
Holy shit! It's so damn spicy!
It's capsaicin.
Capsaicin can be very addictive.
It releases endorphin when you eat it
and helps you get rid of your stress.
But it hurts when you poop.
It hurts when you poop the next day.
Your butthole hurts so much.
It's... It's so spicy.
-So cold!
-Thank you.
-I'll bring this back.
-Here.
-I love it.
Sang-tae, you're getting wet.
It's... It's raining. Wasn't it delicious?
It's sunny, but it's raining.
It's raining.
-It's pouring. I love it.
-Slow down.
Capsaicin is really addictive.
Don't you think so?
We had a big meal.
-We did, didn't we?
-Yes.
I wonder why it's raining.
-Slow down.
-It's pouring.
-Let's slow down.
-Gosh, we had a really big meal.
It's pouring over here as well.
Let me join.
Capsaicin is really addictive.
Ms. Ko finished everything
because it was so yummy.
It will hurt when you poop.
Has it ever happened before?
It hurts a lot.
Let's have coffee together.
Go by yourself.
My lunch break is almost over.
It will only take ten minutes.
Two iced Americano coffee, please.
Okay.
I want it.
Excuse me.
Are you Ms. Ko Mun-yeong?
My goodness, it's you.
I can't believe I'm meeting you here.
This is amazing.
-Do you know me?
-Of course.
I've been your fan for a long time.
Just a second.
Here. This is my business card.
-By any chance, is he your boyfriend?
-No, he's just someone I know.
That's good to hear.
Have a seat.
Well then,
I guess I'll join you for a moment.
Last summer, our company was
in charge of planning
your art book event.
But I bet you don't remember.
Back then, I saw you from a distance.
I can't believe I'm seeing you here.
That's what you call destiny.
"Destiny"?
I'm hoping that destiny
will allow us to keep in touch.
If you ever have time,
we should meet up for a meal.
Sure.
Then here. Can you write down
your phone number for me?
Dear Daniel, I hope you buy me beef.
Mun-yeong will be waiting for your call.
Excuse me.
Sir.
-Yes?
-I'm sorry.
But can you take a photo of us together?
Oh, sure.
Click on the camera icon.
One, two...
About your hand on her waist...
You want his hand on my waist?
Here. Take the photo.
You're very nice to your fans.
According to Mr. Lee, I sell one more book
every time I smile at a fan.
You should be focusing on writing,
not marketing.
And why would you give him your number
when you don't even know him that well?
I couldn't help it. I like handsome stuff.
"Handsome"?
What's wrong?
Go home. I need to get going now.
Are you
jealous?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm late, thanks to you.
Handsome, my ass!
He's such a cheeseball.
How handsome.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
-What?
-What is it?
Do you know that man?
I don't want that.
No, please. No way.
You don't want that? So what?
It's my house.
I've been paying
half of the mortgage payments.
Don't you feel bad
for the situation he's in?
He doesn't know anyone in Seongjin City,
and he's broke
because his company went belly up.
Okay, but why do you have to help him?
Why do you care?
How can I not care?
He's the CEO of the publishing company
Sang-tae is signed with.
But we don't even have an empty room...
Mom.
Don't tell me you'll let him
move into the room on the roof.
Mom?
-Just split it, then.
-Split what?
You and Jae-su should
split your rooms in half.
Does she think my room is a chicken?
It's not like ordering
half and half chicken!
I have to share the room with the guy
from the publishing company?
I get that she wants more rent,
but she's abusing her power
as the landlady. Don't you agree?
Jeez, I heard he's moving in today.
I'm so upset.
Everyone around that woman,
Ko Mun-yeong, is such a pain in the butt!
Stop scratching. It'll bleed.
Sang-tae!
Are you mad at me?
I kept calling you,
but you didn't pick up.
I thought you were avoiding me
because you feel bad about slapping me--
Why does it have to be my place?
Because of you, I guess?
There's someone I like.
Yes, I know.
The unrequited love
you want to give up on.
But you know, Ju-ri...
Don't turn into a bitch.
Why can't it be me?
Why that bitch?
And I can
be a bitch too.
You're kind and sweet.
You should meet a guy
who will love you for who you are.
I'm not kind.
Well...
Most people who say that they're not kind
tend to be kind.
Gosh, whatever.
Both the nice girl and the bitch
are head over heels for the same guy.
Jeez, what? What's your problem?
You want me gone or what?
I heard you told her that
a copy of her book
will sell every time
she smiles at her fan.
An author only needs to write well.
She's not a celebrity.
Why must she be extra friendly
when it's not necessary?
Because of your third-rate sales tactics,
she's learned to call
just about anyone handsome
and make finger hearts all the time.
She lets a stranger
put his arm around her waist
and even goes out to eat
with a guy she doesn't know.
You forced her to smile so often
that she only raises
the corners of her mouth
and looks like the Joker when she smiles.
What the heck are you talking about now?
Do your job better!
Seriously.
What did I do so wrong?
A-reum.
A-reum?
Gosh, my feet fell asleep.
I'm so sorry.
That old man, Mr. Gan, kept pestering me
to play table tennis with him,
so I had to shake him off.
You must be exhausted.
How much longer do we have to meet up
in secret like this?
You know that patients are not allowed
to date one another.
There are eyes everywhere.
This linen room is the only safe place.
Those jerks.
Let's just try to make the most of it.
Why don't we just enjoy the thrill
until we're discharged?
I feel as though
we're in some tragic love story.
A-reum.
If you don't mind,
I want to kiss...
May I kiss you?
Oh, gosh.
Damn it. I'm sleepy.
Why do I have to change the sheets now?
I'm so annoyed.
She always works me like a dog
when I'm working overtime.
Park Haeng-ja, that old witch.
I'll do it later. Just take some rest.
Really?
Then can I nap here for just an hour?
But I can't help you
if Ms. Park finds out.
That's fine.
Oh, boy. I'm exhausted.
Be careful.
What the...
Just this one time. Please pretend you
didn't see anything just this once.
Gang-tae. Please, big brother.
From what I know, I'm younger than you.
Gang-tae, let us love. Please?
Get up.
You see, love is not a sin.
Patients are human too.
Right, it's not a sin.
But, it's against the rules.
I can't believe this.
Gosh, A-reum.
One of you
will probably be transferred.
Brother, please.
Do not tell your higher-ups.
Please, I beg you.
You should focus on your treatment
so that you can be discharged soon.
Once you leave here,
no one will try to break you two apart.
Damn it.
I'm home!
Hi, Sang-tae.
Gosh, I don't want to do this.
I'm bored.
Sang-tae.
Can't you knock? It's rude
to just barge in without knocking.
Hang out with me. Can you play poker?
-Oh, Mang-tae.
-No, poker.
Mang-tae is mine.
It's mine now. Gang-tae gave it to me.
No.
Mang-tae...
Gang-tae made it in May of 2007
and gave it to me.
He said Mang-tae would eat up
all my nightmares, so I--
I adopted Mang-tae in June of 2020,
so it's mine now.
No, that's not true.
I never gave him up for adoption, so how?
-Mang-tae is mine.
-No, it's mine.
No, Mang-tae is mine.
-No, Gang-tae gave it to me.
-Give it back.
-No, it's mine.
-It's Sang-tae's.
-No, it's mine!
-Give it back!
-It's mine.
-Please, give it back.
Mang-tae belongs to Sang-tae.
-No, it's mine.
-Mang-tae is mine!
-No! It's mine. Give it back!
-It's mine!
-Mang-tae is mine!
It's mine...
Sang-tae?
-Mang-tae is mine!
-No, Mang-tae is mine!
-I said, it's mine!
-Mang-tae is mine!
-It's mine.
-It's mine!
-Mang-tae is mine.
-I told you that it's mine!
-No! It's mine!
-It's mine!
-It's mine.
-Mang-tae is mine!
-No, it's mine!
-No, it's not!
-Who does Mang-tae belong to?
It's mine, right? You gave it to me.
We're three brothers.
Mang-tae, Gang-tae, and Sang-tae, right?
-Both of you.
-It's mine!
No, I told you that
Mang-tae is mine. Mine!
-No, it's mine!
-Mang-tae is mine.
-It's mine.
-Mang-tae is mine!
-Be quiet!
Both of you, give it back.
One.
Two.
Three.
Hey!
Go away! I hate you!
-I hate you.
-Hey!
I hate Ms. Ko Mun-yeong.
Ms. Ko Mun-yeong is vicious.
She's a real fighter.
Ko Mun-yeong...
You too. Give it back.
You gave it to me! You can't take it back!
I told you not to fight with Sang-tae.
Anyway, give it to me.
Give it back, now.
There!
You jerk! You petty asshole!
You petty bastard!
I can't believe that petty bastard!
Sang-tae, come out.
You should get changed.
If you don't want to come out,
just open the door.
You know that Mang-tae
can't catch the butterflies anyway.
Mang-tae can't catch the butterflies.
What did you say?
I can't really hear you.
He's of no use
if he can't catch the butterflies.
Exactly.
You shoved it into the drawer
and forgot about it,
so I gave it to Ms. Ko.
I'm sorry I didn't ask
for your permission first.
But when you don't need something,
it's nice to offer it
to someone who needs it.
"Offer"?
Yes, that's right.
But...
if I give all my stuff
to people who need them,
what about me?
What will I have left?
You will
always have me.
Forget Mang-tae. You have Gang-tae.
Ms. Ko is alone, so she needs Mang-tae.
Then will you let her have Mang-tae?
Yes, she can have him.
She can have Mang-tae, not Gang-tae.
Yes.
Yes, she can take him.
Hey.
I can't sleep because I'm fuming mad.
What did I do wrong?
Sang-tae said you could have him.
Mang-tae.
Mang-tae is all yours now.
Whatever. It was mine to begin with.
Try to stay calm
even when Sang-tae gets worked up.
-Don't give me orders.
-It's not an order.
I'm asking you for a favor.
But how can I suppress my anger
and stay calm?
Tell me. You're an expert at it.
I saw you do it
when I cut your hand with a knife.
Even when that man grabbed your brother
by the hair at the bookstore
and when your brother
beat the crap out of you on the floor.
You just kept it all inside
and let him beat you up.
How do you do that?
If I just suck it up,
nothing will happen.
If I let my emotions get the better of me
without thinking about the consequences,
Sang-tae and I wouldn't have
this kind of relationship.
Keeping it all inside and enduring it
is the only way
I can protect Sang-tae.
I think that's why we're meant to be.
You're patient,
and I'm volatile.
Like a bomb and its safety pin.
We go hand in hand.
We're meant to be together.
How many guys
do you think you're meant to be with?
What do you mean?
Why don't you go ask your "handsome" fan?
"Handsome"?
You mean, this pen?
What do you think?
Isn't it so handsome?
Just look at this shape. It's perfect.
But you know,
you're much more handsome
than this pen.
Gosh, what are you doing?
So don't be jealous.
What? I'm not jealous.
I'm sleepy.
Go upstairs and sleep.
I don't want to. Mang-tae is here.
Relax, will you?
By the way, did Director O call you?
About resuming your class.
He did.
I see.
They received many requests
from the patients.
I guess
they all liked your class.
My mustache!
Where did my mustache go?
Oh, that.
I shaved it off.
What?
Why?
Well...
Damn you!
How dare you touch my mustache?
You're partially responsible. Let go!
-You little...
-What?
Wait, hold on. No.
No. Please! No!
Ko Mun-yeong...
-You bitch.
-I can't focus because of him.
Seriously, what a pain in the butt!
You had gum stuck on it?
Yes, it was glued on it.
My goodness.
You look so handsome
without your mustache.
Jae-su, I'm glad you shaved it off.
Thank you so much, Jae-su.
My gosh.
Didn't he lash out at me
for shaving it off?
What are you doing, Seung-jae?
Good morning, Ju-ri.
Did I wake you up?
No.
Why are you cleaning out of the blue?
Oh, I figured I should do something
to help out
while staying here with you.
I'll be in charge of cleaning the room.
Just think that I'm invisible.
Don't mind me.
Ju-ri.
Do you notice anything different?
You looked better with a mustache.
Why did you shave?
Here, have some meat.
Sang-tae can be a handful,
but he can draw very well,
so please take good care of him.
Then I'll make sure
there's always meat on the table.
My gosh. Don't you worry, ma'am.
I have to say, this is a feast.
I don't even know what I should eat first.
The soup is too salty.
Eat up.
I must say, you're very impressive.
You're still young,
yet you have your own publishing company.
I run my own pizzeria
despite my young age--
Ms. Kang.
I know I'm only paying
200,000 won a month to stay here,
but I'll get back on my feet again soon
and make sure I repay your kindness
a thousandfold.
Then finish your food quickly.
Let's put it down in writing.
My gosh.
What is it now? Why are you in a bad mood?
Why did you ask Mr. Lee
what his parents do?
He'll stay with us for a while.
I can't even ask him about his family?
It bothers me
that you seem so intrigued by him.
Because he's interested in you.
How did you know?
When you get to my age, you'll understand.
There are some things
that you just know when you're older.
If you know that,
don't lead him on.
He's hardworking and cheerful.
He seems like a responsible guy.
So why not?
Mom, you know why I'm being like this.
Yes, I know. That's why I'm saying this.
That guy won't even reciprocate
my dear daughter's feelings.
I, too, hate him for that.
I hate him,
but I also feel bad for him.
However, you matter a lot more to me.
You told me to keep on chasing after him
even if he rejects me.
I'm worried that
you're going to follow him
to the edge of a cliff
if I let you continue to chase after him.
Hello.
Oh, that's your live-in cook.
The three of you came together?
Yes, I'm here to work on the mural.
Gang-tae has his day shift,
and Ms. Ko has her class.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
You got a haircut.
It looks nice.
He gave me a haircut.
You cut her hair?
Why did you do that?
She looks prettier with long hair.
Come over when you have some time.
I'll make some food for you.
I don't think
your daughter likes the idea.
She takes after me,
so she can't hide her feelings.
Don't worry.
Just come over and have some food.
You two can fight again
if you have any energy left.
Even better if you girls can make up
after the fight.
We have to go.
Do you like that two-faced girl?
What?
-Why did you cut Ms. Ko's hair? Why?
-Sang-tae, that's...
Or do you have a crush
on your live-in cook?
Stop talking nonsense.
Then why did you unlink my arm?
Why should I link arms with you?
Because we go hand in hand.
Let go.
The bomb needs its safety pin.
Let me... Let me join.
I want to link arms too.
-Okay?
-Look ahead of you,
or you'll trip and fall. Look ahead.
-Okay?
-Look ahead of you.
Look ahead of you,
or you'll trip and fall.
Gosh, I thought you'd be mad at me
and refuse to teach.
I was so worried yesterday.
Well, I heard the patients
miss my class like crazy.
Did Mr. Moon say that?
I guess he was too embarrassed
to tell you that he threatened me.
He threatened you?
He said I'd better resume
the fairy tale class,
or he wouldn't do anything
I tell him to do.
He glared at me and gave me an ultimatum.
Why did he do that?
I guess he wants to see you
even when he's working.
There's something I want to ask you.
Do you,
by any chance,
know our patient, Ms. Park Ok-ran?
Park Ok-ran?
Oh, her.
-You know her?
-Yes.
She's in my class.
What about her?
I was just wondering
if she was enjoying the class.
If you feel dizzy
or have trouble falling asleep
after taking the medication,
-Open your mouth, please.
-let us know.
Roll your tongue like this.
Thanks so much, brother.
For not telling Ms. Park.
I'm still undecided.
You see, A-reum and I
promised each other
that we'd wait until we get discharged.
We have to follow the rules, you know.
We'll focus on getting better so that
we can be discharged soon
and love each other
as much as we want
after we leave this place.
I'm glad to hear that.
Your determination is what matters.
But to be honest, it's hard.
Unlike you, I'm not that patient.
It'd be better if I never saw her.
I see her every day,
and it's really driving me crazy.
I tell myself to just never look at her.
But I keep thinking about her
even when I close my eyes.
Then when I see her,
I want to touch her.
Whenever I see her smile with another guy,
I get so pissed off.
Beauty and the Beast was written by
Jeanne-Marie Le Prince de Beaumont,
a French author in the Middle Ages.
It was only when the story
was adapted into an animated film
-that the image of...
-My head keeps saying I shouldn't,
but I can't stop looking at her.
-The story is said to teach us
-And my heart
-to never judge anyone
-can only follow my eyes.
by their looks alone.
It's really driving me crazy.
But that's just what adults
want to tell children
to discipline them.
Beauty and the Beast is a story
about Stockholm Syndrome.
The Beast lives alone
in the castle because of a curse.
He holds a lady named Belle hostage
in the castle
and grooms this victim of his.
That's what the story is about.
Isn't it about a kindhearted lady
being locked in a castle
instead of her father
and helping the Beast
remove the curse on him
because she falls in love with him?
The Beast is usually selfish
and harsh on Belle.
So doing something nice
once in a blue moon
and gazing at her
with a faint smile on his face
was enough to move the naive lady, Belle.
"Yes.
The Beast is lonely.
I should embrace him with my love.
Only I can change him."
But Belle was being delusional.
Correct.
No!
-A-reum!
-Beauty and the Beast
isn't some crude story
about the Beast grooming his victim.
-Then what is it?
-The Beast
turns into a prince
because of the power of Belle's true love.
Belle's love
calmed the Beast's violent nature.
That love
embraced his wounded soul.
The greatest thing anyone can do
as a human being.
It's...
pure love.
Hey, I'm about to puke.
The drugs must be wearing off.
Did you take your medication?
That love
embraced his wounded soul.
Love?
It is a flower
Oh, my.
This really is a work of art.
Hello!
Hello.
This mural totally
brightened up the space.
When did you learn to paint so well?
I was born with the talent.
It's a natural-born talent.
I never had to learn it.
-Oh, you were born with it.
-Yes.
My gosh, I really envy those
who can draw or paint well.
Yes.
May I paint a little flower right here?
No! Don't touch it.
Don't touch my brush.
Don't touch my mural.
Oh, okay. I won't touch it.
-Okay.
-I won't touch any of this.
It is a flower
Even if it blooms in the mountains
-It is a flower
-What are you listening to?
It is a flower
-"It's all Flowers"?
-Yes.
I love that song.
Even if it blooms in the mountains
-It is a flower
Even if it blooms in the field
-Even if it blooms in the field
-It is a flower
-That song, right?
-Yes.
When you're done with this,
would you like to come with me
to see some flowers?
Sure.
My gosh, this is incredible.
You're amazing.
Thank you.
Will Ms. Lee A-reum be okay?
She agreed to meet him.
Mr. O is in there with her,
so let's see how it goes.
I heard he used to hit her.
Why visit her when they're divorced?
He has no shame.
Anyway, Ms. Lee is too nice.
Why would she even see him?
They went to middle school together.
They've known each other
for more than half their lives
if we include the three years
they were married to one another.
I'm sure it's hard to just sever all ties.
This is why grooming is scary.
Ms. Ko was so right.
A-reum! Wait, A-reum!
A-reum.
Let go.
Don't visit me ever again.
I'm sorry for everything.
Let's start over.
I promise I'll be good to you.
I won't be fooled again.
Things are already over between us,
and I'll start afresh
when I leave this place.
A-reum.
Think about the times
when we were happy together.
If I... If I hit you again,
I'll cut my hand off. I really mean it.
There's someone I like.
What?
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm going to live with him
when I get discharged,
so just move on and live your life.
You're already seeing some bastard?
-You're hurting me. Let go!
-You piece of...
Oh, my.
I thought you were the trash can.
Ms. Ko!
I sure am at a psychiatric hospital.
It's full of crazy bitches.
Why don't you check yourself in too?
You crazy bastard.
Goodness...
Hey, get up.
I said, get up.
You're not going to get up?
Mr. Moon!
-Just a moment.
-No, no...
Gang-tae! Stop.
You know you shouldn't do this.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Enough. Stop.
No! Don't, Mr. Moon.
Please don't.
Please...
Don't hit him. No, no.
You shouldn't hit him.
Are you okay?
No.
It hurts.
What are you going to do?
Well, technically it is self-defense...
No, it isn't...
-It's excessive use of force--
-Whatever the reason,
a caregiver punched a visitor,
so he should be punished.
If A-reum hadn't stepped in,
it could have been much worse.
And it's not just about Mr. Moon
-but the honor of the hospital--
-You heard her, right?
Try to justify yourself.
I'm sorry. My brother...
I'm sorry. My brother... I'm sorry, I...
I'm the older brother
so I will give a good talking to him.
You should've tolerated.
Why did you do that?
Did you count to three
in your head or not?
You should've counted to three.
I will accept any punishment.
Whatever it may be.
Well, firing you may be going overboard.
But reprimanding you won't be enough.
I guess, I'll have to suspend you.
And you won't be paid
while you are suspended.
Yes.
Go pack your things.
Hey, are you on drugs? Or are you drunk?
Why did you punch him?
He's definitely going to sue you.
Why did you do that?
You are good at keeping it
all inside and enduring it.
Bye.
Gang-tae.
Are you really leaving? Just like that?
Can't you say you're sorry
and that it was a mistake?
It wasn't...
a mistake.
Mr. Moon.
You were so cool.
You rock!
Oh no. It's all because of that jerk.
Gang-tae, come back soon, okay?
We'll be waiting for you.
Mr. Moon...
Why is he smiling?
No, he isn't.
He got suspended.
He's probably close to crying.
No. I saw him smiling just now.
Okay, fine.
When it looks like you want to run away,
I'll run away with you
right there and then.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
I...
got suspended.
They're not going to
pay me during my suspension
and I'm probably going to get sued.
Everything is so messed up.
You said before
you'll run away with me
whenever I want.
I want to
go on a trip with you.
Right now.
Let's go.
SPECIAL THANKS TO CHOI DANIEL
FOR MAKING A GUEST APPEARANCE
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
I feel like you are taming me.
Ko Mun-yeong!
I must be out of my mind.
Is this the deviation
you've been dreaming of?
I can't come here with Sang-tae.
I keep doing things I wouldn't normally do
because of you.
Why aren't you picking up?
What if she isn't dead?
What if she just disappeared?
Who do you like more?
Me or Ms. Ko Mun-yeong?
I don't want you to spend your entire life
taking care of your brother.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi