Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
CHAPTER 12 :
ROMEO AND JULIET
Do you want some toast? I made them.
-What do you want on your toast?
-No, it's okay.
While my bestie burned
eight pieces of toast,
I did the laundry and cleaned the house.
What a morning!
On the other hand, you were fast asleep.
Why didn't you wake me?
I even slapped your face to wake you up,
but you kept sleeping
like the princess in Sleeping Beauty.
Princess.
If you want to wake a princess,
you need to kiss her.
I did.
By the way,
shouldn't we name the characters first?
-He’s a guy who has no sense of self.
-Okay.
She’s an emotionless princess
who is just like an empty can.
Okay.
-And he's--
-Those aren't names.
Gang-tae and Sang-tae are names.
But what you just said aren't names.
Today's my day off.
They don't need names. That's the trend.
"Trend"? What's that?
You don't need to know.
If you guys have time,
do you want to go for a ride later?
-Stop asking questions.
-I'm only asking because I'm curious.
Then don't be curious.
Mind your language to your older brother.
-I'm the boss at work.
-Don't abuse your power.
-You can eat all of this yourself.
-No, I can't. It tastes horrible.
-Let me know when you're done.
-Don't get on my nerves.
-What did I do to get on your nerves?
-I'll be in my room.
Are you asking for a fight?
Gang-tae told me that fighting is bad.
-He told us to hold our anger.
-I'm going, okay?
We're in a meeting now,
so try to think of their names.
-What are you doing?
-I'm getting ready to go to work.
Today's my day off.
So what?
Want to hang out?
Should we go for a ride on Alberto?
Did your number one and two,
Sang-tae and Ms. Ko, reject you?
Is that why you're asking me,
you're number three?
Are you upset again?
Gang-tae, want to know something?
What?
You're sly as a fox.
Whenever you need me,
you talk to me all serious
and get me all worried
by looking at me with your teary eyes.
But once you get what you need,
you just ignore me right away.
You selfish punk.
So do you not want to hang out?
-Do you like me better or Sang-tae?
-You.
Then is it me or Ko Mun-yeong?
-Come to my restaurant.
My gosh.
"Sly as a fox"?
Ms. Kang.
Here.
I heard you have weak knees
because you're always cooking standing up.
Ju-ri told me she's extremely worried.
Here.
When did I say that?
Don't forget to take one every day
for your health.
My goodness.
It's okay.
You should give it to your parents.
I already bought them a box.
It's inside the car trunk.
I'm going to give it to them today.
Really?
My goodness, then I guess
I should take one right now
to thank you for the kind gift.
Yes, of course.
You're way better than my daughter.
Let's see. There.
Are you off to see your parents?
Yes, something came up at home.
I should go to my room.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
It's nothing big.
It's just a monthly event.
"A monthly event"?
Yes, my dad broke three ribs
and got hospitalized.
My goodness. How? Is he okay?
I'm so sorry to hear that.
He's lying.
Mr. Lee's father is a liar.
He's just like his father
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree
My gosh, that darn brat needs to be quiet.
Did you really just lie to me?
The thing is,
whenever a cousin gets married,
my dad gets really jealous
and makes me visit him
by making up all sorts of stuff.
Going on a few blind dates
is the least I can do as his son.
So you're going on a blind date today?
Yes, I do it once a month.
That's why it's a monthly event.
-Drive safely.
-Okay.
Well, I'll call you.
He's going to call?
He's totally my type.
-Should I ask for his number?
-No, don't.
Look at him resting his chin on his hand.
-My gosh, this is crazy. Look at him.
-He's so handsome.
-Will you look at that face?
-My goodness.
My dear Ms. Ko.
Just like how ants are drawn to sweets,
lots of women are getting ready
to hit on my lonesome friend, Gang-tae.
So I ask of you to quickly visit
my pizzeria.
Damn, get out of the way.
I'm going to kill those darn ants. Move!
Here. You can try all our toppings
with this pizza.
Try the one with sweet pumpkin first.
It's sweet just like you.
It's good.
Want to know something?
When someone's in love,
the brain releases vitamins
and makes that person
seem more attractive.
It's "dopamine," not vitamin.
Are you showing off
that you work at a hospital?
We both didn't receive good education.
We're like two peas in a pot.
It's "pod," not pot.
-You should be careful.
-Of what?
-Of women.
-What?
Women who are eyeing you.
But you should be more careful
of the crazy woman who is after the women
who have their eyes on you.
What are you talking about?
Welcome.
We have tons of pizza boxes
ready for you today.
I'm already full.
How did you know I was here?
Weren't you in a meeting with Sang-tae?
How is that important
when you're here surrounded by ants
that are after you?
I shouldn't have prepared so many boxes.
Hurry up and finish your pizza
so we can get out of this ant nest.
I just started eating. Give me a minute.
Goodness.
OK VEGETABLE GARDEN
Hello. Hi.
Hello.
Hello, tree.
It's a beautiful morning, isn't it?
Oh, hello.
You guys might not look the same,
but you're all birds.
So don't fight, okay?
You guys are so adorable and kind.
I'll be off now.
Bye, tree.
He's here.
I thought he might not return
because he was upset with me.
Ms. Park.
You wanted to see me?
I wanted to ask you something.
Sure.
Why did you get rid of
Ms. Park Ok-ran's bed already?
-Because she can't come back.
-What do you mean?
Patients who run away
rarely come back on their own will.
And we have a long waiting list.
Let's not do the same
with Mr. Ko Dae-hwan's bed.
Don't call hospice either.
We should let him stay here.
Yes, I already told our staff to do that.
Gosh, that was fast.
But sir.
Why do you think
Mr. Ko Dae-hwan acted out
when he saw Ms. Park Ok-ran that day?
It's most likely that he had delusions.
I'm guessing he mistook her for his wife.
The writer, Do Hui-jae?
It seems like he hated his wife
-and feared her at the same time.
-Why?
Apparently, she killed someone.
Who did she kill?
Hello.
-Hey, Sang-tae.
-Good morning, Ms. Park.
-Hi. Sit here.
-Okay.
I'll leave you guys to talk.
-It's nice to see you.
-Yes.
-No!
-I want some, too.
I hate kids and animals.
-Why?
-They're unreasonable,
they whine all the time,
and they always beg for love.
That's why I like them.
They make me care for them
because they're unreasonable.
It's cute to see them whine.
And because they beg for love,
it makes me grow fond of them.
Just like you.
I will not have your kids.
Don't expect that from me.
I don't want to be jealous of my child.
Come here.
Closer.
Not everyone can be a mother, you know.
Gosh.
Darn, that punk.
-Wait.
-I want that one.
Min-jae, sit down. Come here and sit.
-There you go. Is it yummy?
-Yes.
You eat so well.
Are you still upset
that I refused to pay
for a mural with no butterflies?
A... A promise isn't something
you can take so lightly.
You need to keep your promise.
That's only the right thing to do.
I just want you to stop
running away from butterflies.
Since you've always been running away,
Gang-tae had to go through tough times.
But... Butterflies...
I'm scared of them.
I don't like butterflies.
Let me tell you something interesting.
Sure.
In ancient Greek,
the word butterfly is psyche.
Psyche?
Do you know what they symbolized?
-They were a symbol of "cure."
-"Cure."
Not all butterflies are scary.
There are many butterflies
that are good and can cure people.
So instead of being so impatient,
why don't we both try
and overcome the fear together?
"Cure."
If we keep trying,
there might be a butterfly
flying around in your mural one day.
Yes. Cure.
Cure.
Is your next book going to be based
on my brother's drawing?
Is it about kids going on a trip
in a camping car?
It's about us. The three of us.
Am I the guy with no sense of self?
And are you the emotionless princess?
Yes.
Then what about my brother?
He's a guy who's trapped inside a box.
What do they do on that trip?
They meet people who are weirder
and a lot more deficient than they are.
-What happens after that?
-That'd be a spoiler. No more.
-It sounds fun.
-Of course.
I'm the writer.
I hope it's going to be
a happy ending this time.
Me too.
By the way, where are we going?
To buy bread.
You burned it all this morning.
I see.
Look at all this stuff.
I've never been to a place like this.
I want this.
Just get one.
I thought about it, and I think
it'd be nice to have a son
who looks like you.
I don't think I'll get jealous.
Let's have a son.
You really need to stop
getting ahead of yourself.
Why? What's wrong? Let's have a son.
Let's have a son! I want a son!
Why won't you cooperate?
I want your cooperation!
-Gosh, be quiet.
-He must not want a baby.
I wonder why he doesn't want one.
I wonder why he won't cooperate.
He looks completely healthy.
Stop talking about having a baby.
Just go and get some milk.
-Ju-ri.
-Yes?
Did you hear?
Dr. Kwon is getting married soon.
He wasn't seeing anyone.
He's marrying the woman he met
on a blind date last month.
-That quickly?
-Come on.
When you're at his age,
you just get married
if everything seems okay.
Were you guys talking about me?
Then let me just cut to the chase.
Surprise.
Everything's proceeding so quickly.
My ideal type showed up on the blind date.
Should I leave Sang-tae's art supplies
in the study?
Let me go.
When are we going to start
using the same room?
Why would I do that?
I sleep with Sang-tae.
Let go of me.
I'm home.
Let go of me right now.
Sang-tae! We're over here!
Okay, fine. Let's hang out later.
In my room?
Yes, in your room.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll call you.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
We have the overall storyline.
I'll ask Mr. Moon about the illustrations.
I came up with a list of places
we can go for research.
It's near the art library.
Okay. Bye, Mr. Lee.
Was that Mr. Lee?
Yes.
Did he say anything in particular?
Like what?
No, never mind.
Mr. Lee's blind date
apparently looked like Song Hye-kyo.
His ideal type of woman
is someone who looks like her.
That guy falls in love so easily.
He really got lucky this time.
Butterfly is psyche,
and it symbolizes "cure."
Butterflies that cure are good.
-Did the director tell you that?
-Yes.
"Stop running away
and face the butterflies
so that Gang-tae won't have to go through
tough times anymore."
Do you really think you can do that?
Is... Is this expensive?
How... How much is all this?
Sell lots of books and pay me back.
I'm going to take a shower.
Psyche symbolizes "cure."
There are tons of good butterflies.
There are tons of them.
Psyche symbolizes "cure."
No.
I don't need a pillow.
I can lay on his arm.
You came running
without even drying your hair.
Come here and sit down.
You really don't listen.
This is a lot of alcohol.
My brother started getting counseling--
I forbid you to talk about your brother.
If you do, drink an entire glass.
Then you can't cuss.
Deal.
Shit, my damn head hurts like hell.
Why am I so freaking dizzy? Damn it.
Look at you swear.
You should go to bed.
I'm...
so happy.
I'm so happy that you and Sang-tae
live here with me now.
Good night.
I WILL COME FOR YOU SOON
No, I'm talking about Ms. Park Ok-ran.
Why did she go there?
There's no way she escaped
just to wish Ms. Ko a happy birthday.
The butterfly said it'd kill me as well.
It'll kill me!
Those butterflies!
They said they'll kill me.
The butterflies will kill me!
They're coming to kill me!
I WILL COME FOR YOU SOON
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
My gosh, I hope you spend
a longer time outside this time.
Don't come back in just a few hours.
Don't worry. I'll see you later.
-You should eat a lot of delicious stuff.
-Okay.
I bet he's just going to get on a bus
and come back after circling around a bit.
Yes, probably.
But how did he end up
doing something like that
when he can't even kill an ant?
-What do you mean?
-Mr. Kan told me everything.
He told me he killed so many people.
Is that why he went crazy?
He's such a weak and kind person.
It wasn't something he could handle.
Turn off the gas stove
to save money.
We need to save gas to save money.
I forgot.
Your... Your eyes are red.
Did... Did you not sleep well?
You have the eyes of a rabbit.
No, I slept well.
You have counseling today, right?
Yes... Yes, I have counseling.
I... I have counseling today.
Butterfly is psyche,
and it symbolizes "cure."
It symbolizes "cure"...
But I'm still scared of them.
What... What if the butterfly
appears again?
We'll... We'll have to move again.
Sang-tae.
Let's stop
running away.
But the butterflies...
You know that I'm good at fighting, right?
Yes, you're a great fighter.
You have a red belt in taekwondo.
You beat up all the kids who bullied me
with your kicks.
You're also good at using your nails.
So from now on, if you're scared,
just hide behind me.
But... But I'm your big brother.
I'm an adult.
If I hide behind my little brother,
that would make me... What's it called?
A scaredy-cat?
It's okay.
I've been hiding behind you all my life.
Behind me?
Hey, babe.
Grilled meat? Sounds great.
Tonight?
Why did he have to say he'll call?
I can't stop looking at my phone.
-Ms. Nam.
-Yes?
Mr. Ko is slowly starting to recover
his cognitive orientation.
-So take him for a short walk.
-Okay, ma'am.
Oh, right.
Is Mr. Moon working the day shift today?
Yes, he got here a few minutes ago.
I WILL COME FOR YOU SOON
Mr. Moon.
What? What is that?
Did you receive
a love letter or something?
-Come on. Show me.
-It's nothing.
What's the matter?
Oh, you see...
I went into room 201 while doing
my rounds earlier in the morning
and found a dangerous item in the room.
Gosh. I have to say,
Mr. O Cha-yong always does
such a clumsy job when he's checking
the patients' belongings, doesn't he?
I'm sorry.
I'll train him better.
Can you do another thorough check
on the rooms on the second floor, then?
-Sure, no problem.
-Here.
You must be getting tired.
Would you like to sit down for a moment?
Will I
die soon?
Have I been
punished enough?
"Years went by,
and the boy became an adult.
He no longer had nightmares.
But for some strange reason,
he wasn't happy at all.
One night--"
Headed to the hospital?
Yes. Hello!
Oh, you're wearing
something different today. Nice clothes.
-Yes, I am.
-You look very young today.
By the way, how old are you?
Me? I'm 70.
You're 70? You're older than me.
You're an adult.
I am an adult indeed.
Being an adult isn't always great.
Right, I agree.
-Oh, look!
-Do you want this?
Thank you.
Right, the mural.
It looks amazing.
It's amazing. It looks super cool.
But Director O Ji-wang wouldn't pay me
because I refused to draw butterflies.
He is not a man of his word.
Why can't you just draw some butterflies?
I'm scared of butterflies.
Why?
Do you have a bad memory
of butterflies or something?
Don't let the past trap you,
or you'll end up like me.
Look at me.
I can't go back out into the world.
I'll always be stuck in the hospital.
The past can trap me?
Yes.
Then I can just open the door and get out.
No, you can't.
You won't be able to see the door.
You can't get out
once you're trapped in the past.
Don't end up like me.
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
Do your ears hurt?
God, that sound...
-Is that sound bothering you?
-That sound...
This sound? This sound...
Sir! What's wrong?
Are you okay, sir?
It's okay. You're okay.
You're okay. It's all right.
Could you please call
OK Psychiatric Hospital right away?
You're okay. You're safe.
You're okay. It's all right.
You're okay. You're okay now.
Count to three in your head.
You're okay. It's all right.
You're safe, okay? Everything's okay now.
Director O.
Can you just kill me?
Don't you worry.
You'll die anyway.
All of us here, including myself,
will die eventually anyway.
Don't be so anxious.
It's okay. Try to relax.
-What's up?
-Well, this...
I'd like to
lend this book to him.
-Really?
-I'm not giving it to him though.
He can borrow it.
I paid a lot of money for it,
so it's mine.
Okay, he can borrow and read it.
Yes, I'm lending it to him.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
Come in.
I must say, he sure is your big brother.
Without Sang-tae's help, Mr. Kan
would've gotten in a dangerous situation.
I am your big brother.
Have a seat.
Good job.
Remember what you told me earlier?
-Can you also tell your brother?
-Sure.
What is it about?
Mr. Kan told me
that I shouldn't end up like him.
He said you can never get out
once you're trapped in the past
because you can't even see the door.
A trauma?
Yes.
He fought in the Vietnam War
when he was only 20.
It left him with traumatic memories.
There were a lot of kids.
Kids
with sparkling eyes.
They were adorable.
I just couldn't bring myself
to look at them,
so I...
closed my eyes.
Then I...
I killed all those innocent people.
I don't even know why I'm still alive.
You were just following an order.
You had no choice.
You're nothing more than a beast
if you blindly follow such orders.
A human being with a heart
would never do that.
I shouldn't even call myself human.
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
"So don't forget any of it.
Remember it all and overcome it.
If you don't overcome it,
you'll always be a kid
whose soul never grows."
I'm not a kid. I'm an adult.
Sang-tae.
Yes, I won't run away anymore.
I will not run away.
-My gosh.
-That's right.
You're incredibly brave, Sang-tae.
That's right.
Then would you be able to tell us
what you remember about that day?
Yes.
Well...
That day...
-I--
-Kitty!
That night...
Well...
SEONGJIN WELFARE CENTER
I have to work late from now on,
so you'll have to go home with Gang-tae.
Okay?
Look, it's a cat.
Kitty!
Sang-tae, get back here.
You shouldn't go in there.
Get back here, Sang-tae!
Fine. I'm leaving.
I'm leaving without you.
Bye.
Bye, Sang-tae!
Kitty.
Kitty?
I didn't get to say this earlier.
It is me
who will take care of my child.
My gosh, why do you look so scared?
It's okay.
It's all right.
Yes, good boy.
Do not tell anyone
about what you saw or heard here.
If you do, I'll kill you.
Even if you run away,
I will chase you down no matter what
and make sure
I kill you.
The... The butterfly killed Mom.
Okay?
Answer me.
I said, answer me!
There was... There was a butterfly
on that woman's jacket.
There was a butterfly
sitting on her jacket.
"Her jacket"?
That butterfly...
Do you remember what it looked like?
Yes.
Yes, I do remember.
Well...
Gosh.
Actually,
there was a mom butterfly.
And I saw a tiny baby butterfly
sitting on the mom butterfly's back.
It was sitting on its back?
Yes, there were two...
I saw two butterflies.
The mom and the baby. Two butterflies.
I think that's why we're meant to be.
If someone shows up when you need them,
you call that destiny.
And I
need you.
I hope it's going to be
a happy ending this time.
Your book is quite engaging.
Yes, I know.
You heard about your father, right?
How much time does he have left?
Let me rephrase that.
When will he die?
I wouldn't be surprised
even if he passed away tomorrow.
I'm sick of doctors telling me
the same thing over and over.
You know,
if you're okay with it,
why don't we take your father out
for a walk when you have some time?
-Ju-ri.
-Yes?
I...
don't want to.
Yes.
So I took off my shirt right away
and put it over his head
like Gang-tae does for me all the time.
Then he stopped screaming and calmed down.
My gosh.
Great job, Sang-tae.
I'm so proud of you.
I know.
Yes, the cafeteria. I'm at the cafeteria.
So I...
Where was I?
Anyway, I asked someone to call
OK Psychiatric Hospital
and came here with him in the ambulance.
There's a storybook that I like.
It's called The Boy Who Fed on Nightmares.
-I lent him that book.
-My, how sweet.
He can't keep the book though.
I paid a lot of money for it,
so I can't let him keep it.
Anyhow, he kept thanking me.
He said he's grateful to me.
He's grateful.
-Absolutely.
-Yes.
Sang-tae.
Let's wait for Gang-tae
and go home together.
Ko Mun-yeong, she's a lot older than you.
You need to say hello to her first.
Hello.
Yes, hi.
Shall we eat out? It's been a while.
No, I want to eat at home.
We shouldn't be eating out.
We have to save money to live better.
It looks as though
the three of you are actually a family.
I'm getting jealous here.
No. Strictly speaking, we're not a family.
Gang-tae and I have the same surname,
Moon, whereas she...
What was your surname? Right, Ko.
Ko and Moon.
Different surnames.
And she's not on our family register.
We're not a real family,
but we're like a family.
-The family register isn't everything.
-What?
A family is...
-A family is...
-Yes?
You become one
if you take a portrait together.
What? A family portrait?
That's right. Forget the family register.
A family portrait is the proof
that you're a family.
The two of you are so much alike.
Our eyes... Do our eyes look alike?
No, we don't look alike at all.
I can't pinpoint it,
but I think there's some resemblance.
You're wrong. I'm very pretty.
Don't lie, Ko Mun-yeong.
You cut... You cut your hair.
What time do you get off work?
What happened to your hand?
I hurt it while working.
Who's the jerk that did this to you?
Who did this?
I'm asking you who did it.
What's going on?
Are you mad at me?
Am I going bonkers again
without being considerate
of your feelings
like an empty can?
I'm just tired.
I didn't get much sleep last night.
Go home with Sang-tae.
I have to work the night shift as well.
Really?
Then you'll probably be off tomorrow.
That's great.
The two of us and Sang-tae
should take a family portrait tomorrow.
I already made an appointment
at a fancy photo studio.
We should stop by a tailor shop on the way
and buy a couple of suits.
Maybe another time.
-What?
-Let's do it some other day.
-Not tomorrow.
-But I already made an appointment.
-Cancel it.
-No, I don't want to.
Let's not put it off
and just do it tomorrow.
We have to take a family portrait together
to become a real family.
Leave!
Please.
Just leave.
I have to work.
I'm going to take a photo!
I have to look cool.
One... One, two, three.
One, two, three. Look cool.
One, two, three.
What do I do to look cool?
Jeez, why the heck is he mad at me again?
I mean, just why?
Darn it. Yesterday was so nice.
We drank together all night.
Did I do something silly when I was drunk?
Why is he angry? Just why?
Was that a soliloquy or a question for me?
I'm asking because
I can't quite figure it out.
Did you order ten boxes of pizza
at this late hour
just to make me come all the way here
because you wanted to know why he's angry?
It's obviously not because
I wanted to eat ten boxes of pizza
in the middle of the night.
Why?
Why is Gang-tae upset?
You must know since you're his bestie.
He never really opens up to anyone.
Do you know how I've managed
to stay close to him all these years?
By having no idea of
what goes on in his mind
or how he really feels.
You see, Gang-tae is an expert
at hiding his feelings.
Nothing good will come out of
prying and forcing him
to share his feelings and thoughts.
All you can do is just be there for him
and try to comfort him quietly.
That is
all I do.
Obviously, he's never
even had a chance to whine
or complain to his parents.
He got so used to just putting up
with things and keeping it all inside.
Then one day,
he realized he'd become an adult.
But he's still a kid inside,
so how would you understand
his feelings and thoughts?
Even parents can't fully understand
their own child.
ROMEO AND JULIET
We look like Romeo and Juliet.
You're right. The ill-fated mortal enemies
who should've never crossed paths.
No, they were meant to be. It was fate.
It was tragic fate.
ROMEO AND JULIET
Your hand didn't do anything wrong.
Your heart is the problem
because you can't control it.
Sir.
Yes?
I think the "butterfly"
that killed my mom was...
Mun-yeong's mother.
Are you sure?
The possibility that it may be true
scares me.
I hope I'm wrong.
No, I wish I had stayed in the dark.
Isn't it just too cruel?
I was beginning
to feel like I could finally
breathe a little.
I was finally
starting to get the urge to live
just like everyone else.
Because of that damn butterfly,
I've had to
crawl and suffer all these years.
But how could that butterfly be
her mother?
I always thought
I'd tear the butterfly to shreds
if I ever crossed paths with it,
but I can't even do that anymore.
I feel so guilty when I think
about my mom and my brother.
What do I do?
I promised my brother
that I'd fight the butterfly
in his place.
I...
I told him that we shouldn't run away.
This is so messed up.
I just want to run away.
I don't want Mun-yeong
to suffer like this,
so I hope
she never finds out about this.
I don't want her to be hurt.
I don't want her to ever care
about other people's feelings.
I hope she can just live without emotions
like an empty can.
I'm so happy that you and Sang-tae
live here with me now.
I used to
hate this place so much.
Why?
Because my dad lost his sanity here
and my mom
died in this very house.
Blood kept gushing out
from her head.
And my dad locked her up
in the basement.
But the thing is,
she vanished after that.
My mom vanished.
She vanished?
Yes.
I don't know if she actually died
or if she just disappeared.
I guess only my dad knows the truth.
If...
If your mom comes back,
how do you think you'll feel?
I'll be terrified.
And I'll feel suffocated.
But you know,
she is
still my mom.
-Is he coming?
-No.
He won't wake up.
He won't even answer me.
He's just sleeping
with the blanket over his head.
He's such a sleepyhead. A sleepyhead.
I guess he's tired.
Sang-tae, let's take it another day.
But I'm...
I'm wearing my nice clothes today.
And I got up at 6:50 a.m.,
which is so early. Very early.
I even styled my hair with wax.
And yesterday... Last night...
I practiced so many cool poses last night.
What do I do?
-Let's go, Sang-tae.
-What?
Let's just go and take some photos
for the book, then.
Yes, photos.
Let's take photos.
Yes.
GANG-TAE
PHOTO STUDIO ADDRESS
-Hello!
-Hello.
Hello.
Are you okay?
Are you in a bad mood today?
I'm always in a bad mood.
Don't worry about me.
Will my photo really be included
in the book?
Yes, of course. You're the illustrator.
Right, I am.
I practiced so many cool poses last night.
-You did?
-Yes.
Then show me.
One, two, three.
One, two... One, two, three!
Sang-tae.
Yes?
That's all fake.
You don't need to try so hard.
Just relax and be yourself.
That's the real Moon Sang-tae.
"The real...
Moon Sang-tae"?
Yes.
"The real Moon Sang-tae"?
The lady can sit on the chair.
Sir, please stand next to her.
Great. Sir, could you stand
a little closer to her?
-Sure.
-Nice. That's perfect.
Now, look at the camera
and give me a big smile.
A big smile, please.
Eyes on the camera. Here we go!
-One, two--
-Oh, look!
Wait. Just a second, please.
My brother... My little brother is here.
My gosh, my brother...
That's my real brother.
I'm not
too late, right?
Since it's for a family portrait,
please give me a big smile.
Here we go.
Please smile.
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three!
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
IT'S OKAY TO NOT BE OKAY
Ko Mun-yeong.
If I ask you
to live somewhere else with me,
will you come with me?
If
I were born as your mom's daughter,
and if you were born
as my dad's daughter...
My mom would beat you up to death
for being rude.
Don't trust anyone.
I don't care who it is.
I will not forgive
anyone who messes with my family.
Am I
part of that family?
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi