Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
You're so warm.
I'm hungry.
BATES MOTEL
PARKING LOT
Nice move.
You're cold, so go inside and warm up.
-Okay, let's do that.
-By yourself.
Hello.
My gosh.
You're both soaked.
For one night or just for a few hours?
-Well--
-Which room would you like?
The mirror room? The themed room?
-Or costumes?
-No.
Well...
Come here.
Come here. Come on.
-Do you want any add-ons?
-Sorry?
A love chair? A vibrating bed?
How about handcuffs or a whip?
I'll give you ten percent off
if you pay cash.
Let's go.
How about a room with a whirlpool tub?
No extra charge. Don't tell anyone.
-Come on. Let's go.
-No.
I like this place.
Come on. I'll take you home.
-I don't want to freeze to death.
-Our rooms are steamy hot.
-Do you live far from here?
-That's not the point.
What were you thinking? Why bring
your motorcycle in this torrential rain?
-Then just take a taxi home from here.
-Give me money for the taxi ride.
Hey, don't tell me--
That's right. I didn't bring anything.
Not even my wallet and phone.
Then if I hadn't picked you up--
I would've walked all night in the rain,
like a crazy woman.
Can you please think before you act?
Don't be so impulsive and reckless.
What if something happened to you
on that dark, remote road?
How could you just keep walking
all by yourself? You're fearless.
If something bad happened...
Why are you getting angry?
Who cares if I walk all night
or put on a strip show in the rain?
Why are you getting upset?
Were you worried about me?
Are you upset?
Does your heart ache?
Do you...
like me?
Well, I'm asking
because I really have no clue.
You know that.
So you'd better not act like you know
and understand everything about me
when you know nothing.
Don't be delusional.
You're all empty inside.
You're just loud.
Like an empty can.
I'm an empty can who won't understand
how you feel until the day I die.
What do you feel now?
Tell me.
Why are you all quiet?
Are you an empty can too?
I...
Just say it.
Tell her that you love her.
We'll... We'll get a room.
Just...
Just any clean and warm room would do.
It's 50,000 won.
What? You have no money on you?
What about your phone?
Even my mom has to pay on the spot.
Bye.
I guess you ran out of the house
in a hurry.
In such a hurry that you couldn't think
before you acted.
It's okay.
It's natural for men to act instinctively.
Go start your motorcycle.
Hey.
There's a cheap motel down the street.
They let you pay later. Go there.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
CHAPTER 5 RAPUNZEL AND THE CURSED CASTLE
Get off.
His taste is so...
Dry yourself with that first.
Give me your clothes.
I don't like dinosaurs.
This is fascinating.
You can take care of all your needs
in this space,
from eating and sleeping
to relieving yourself?
This reminds me of an animal stall.
Don't you feel like
you're a domesticated animal living here?
What? Was that rude?
Go get changed.
-Where's your brother?
-Downstairs.
-Don't call him over.
-I won't.
-I don't want you around him.
-Are you jealous?
Don't go near my brother, ever.
-Is this a warning?
-I don't care what you think.
Just leave him alone.
Will he want the same thing?
I should ask him directly.
What? What's the matter?
What's with that gaze?
-What does my face tell you?
-You're handsome.
-No, my facial expression.
-You look obnoxious.
What does it tell you about my mood,
emotions, and the state I'm in?
Not interested.
Take a good look at their faces
and try to read their emotions.
Learn, even if you're not interested.
If you don't like to feel the emotions,
just memorize them.
At least make an effort
unless you'll live by yourself forever.
I don't want to. Why should I?
Do it even if you don't want to.
I'm not autistic.
-I'm just a little--
-You're not the zombie kid either.
ZOMBIE KID
The kid who had no emotions.
All he had was the desire to eat.
But what do you think he really wanted?
Satiating his hunger?
Or feeling someone's warmth?
What do you think the answer is?
Food? Was satisfying his desire to eat
all that mattered?
Warmth.
This is what he truly wanted.
He didn't want to be just fed.
You wanted to impart that message.
-You're wrong.
-I'm wrong?
That's right. You're wrong.
Food was all that mattered.
He's a zombie, so he has no emotions.
He wanted to fill himself up
even if it was with his mom's limbs.
"Warmth"? Bullshit.
That's just the sickening pity
of sentimentalists like yourself.
Don't put words in my mouth.
I'm hungry. Give me something to eat.
Before I start chewing off your limbs.
Who's pitying whom?
WHEN USING THE SHAMPOO, PUMP THREE TIMES
SANG-TAE
WHEN BRUSHING TEETH,
DON'T GO OVER THREE MINUTES
Hypocrite.
Why... Why does he hate me?
Sang-tae.
Do as I say, please!
Are you still mad at me?
I'm sorry I yelled at you earlier.
I'll never do that again.
Forgive me.
Sang-tae, please.
That must hurt.
You're hurting yourself.
Someone slapped me in the face today.
I was slapped so hard
that my gums bled,
and I can't even hear well.
My face is all swollen,
so I look like Mr. Lumpy now.
-What do I do?
-"Mr. Lumpy"?
Where's Mr. Lumpy? Mr. Lumpy.
My lumps are all gone.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
Lying is bad.
It's deception.
The cops will come and arrest you.
Pinocchio is bad.
The shepherd boy is also bad.
Since you lied to me,
you deserve a scolding.
You need a good spanking.
Will you keep doing it knowing it's bad?
Answer me. Why are you all quiet?
It's because you know
what you did is wrong. Does it hurt?
Have you... You haven't eaten yet, right?
Come have a seat.
Are you happy you got spanked?
Why do you keep asking for it?
Are you doing this on purpose?
I got what I deserved.
Jeez.
All right. Come and eat.
Come on.
No.
What? What is it?
Well, would you mind...
Are you hiding your wife
somewhere in the house?
No, it's my landlady who's over 60.
I could tell.
It looks like she's a seasoned cook.
Just eat.
I want to live with this lady.
She's a great cook.
-What do you eat at home?
-I don't eat anything.
I don't have a mom
who'd give me her limbs.
Not even a live-in cook, unlike you.
Damn it.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Why are you standing here?
Didn't you hear that sound just now?
No.
The power is back on.
I heard someone humming a song
from over there.
Oh, that.
What exactly is "that"?
Didn't Ms. Yoo Seon-hae tell you?
Sometime after midnight,
you can hear a ghost humming a song
at the end of the hallway
on the second floor.
I clearly heard it.
What? A ghost?
She was probably talking nonsense, right?
Well, I'm not sure.
Ms. Yoo Seon-hae...
has been making a living
communicating with ghosts.
What?
She was a shaman.
Wait up!
I should make some coffee.
I saw nothing out of the ordinary
while making rounds.
Okay, thanks.
-Where's--
-He's washing his face to wake himself up.
Are you sure?
-Do you want some coffee?
-Sure, thank you.
How are Mr. Ko Dae-hwan's vitals?
His blood pressure is still
on the high side,
and he's experiencing
some sleep disorders.
Well, by the way...
Earlier in the garden...
Yes?
Why do you think he did that
to his daughter?
Some post-surgical complications
can result in sudden aggressive outbursts,
you know.
Here.
What if that wasn't the cause?
Then what? Are you saying
he attacked her to kill her?
No.
To live.
I mean, because he didn't want to die.
If he became aggressive like that
to protect himself...
Die!
Ms. Nam.
Yes?
You said you and Ms. Ko Mun-yeong
know each other.
Shall we
become friends?
But you tried to hide it,
which means you two
aren't really on good terms.
Go away, please!
Then now,
ask yourself this.
Are you not able to keep your personal
feelings aside when it comes to those two?
You shouldn't let countertransference
get in your way.
You're a professional, you know?
COUNTERTRANSFERENCE: A THERAPIST'S
EMOTIONAL ENTANGLEMENT WITH A CLIENT
Finish it quickly and lie down here.
You must've been
a servant in your past life.
And I must've been a mistress.
Look at you working so hard.
You look scrumptious from behind.
I mean, you look stunning,
not "scrumptious."
-My bad. That was a slip of the tongue.
-Get up.
I'll give you money for a taxi,
so go home.
No, I'll sleep here tonight.
-Who says you can sleep here?
-I can do as I please.
-Come on. Get up.
-No, I'll sleep here.
-I'll drag you out.
-You brought me here.
I never said you could sleep here.
Come on. Get up.
You clothed me and fed me,
so let me sleep now.
-I'm not raising a newborn. Let go.
-Let go of me, or I'll scream.
-Get out!
-Sang-tae!
Hey, buddy! Let's have dinner together!
Hey, why... Gosh, why did you come out?
-Sorry, Jae-su.
-Jeez.
Hey, why are you covered in sweat?
Oh, my room is very hot.
Gosh, it's so hot. You don't feel hot?
Hey, are you having hot flashes or what?
You're acting so weird today.
What do you mean?
I thought you'd probably be
eating all alone looking sad,
so I came to keep you company.
-Oh, I've already eaten.
-What? Already?
Yes. Your food will get cold.
Go downstairs and eat first.
-Go on.
-Hey, something's fishy here.
You even left Sang-tae downstairs.
Because you were with him.
-You prick, what are you up to all alone?
-Hey!
Gosh, Jae-su.
-You're using force?
-No.
-You're pretty strong.
-You know who I am, right?
-Yes, of course.
-You do, right?
-Yes, I sure do.
-You'd better watch out.
-Okay.
-I'll be downstairs. Call me if need be.
-All right, will do.
Open up.
Let me in.
Can you let me in?
Sure, if you let me sleep here tonight.
-Open the door first. Then--
-Then you'll drag me out.
No, I won't do that.
For real?
Yes, for real. Open the door first.
Okay.
Here, this is open.
We look like Romeo and Juliet,
staring at each other like this.
You're right. The ill-fated mortal enemies
who should've never crossed paths.
No, they were meant to be. It was fate.
Their tragic fate killed both of them.
Do you know why they both died?
Because only Juliet drank
the sleeping potion.
If they drank the sleeping potion
together, they wouldn't have died.
So let's fall asleep together,
side by side.
What the... Your logic makes no sense.
-Let me in.
-I'll sleep here tonight.
-Open the door.
-Sleep beside me.
Open up before I break the door.
How about your brother joins us?
Sang-tae!
What? It burst?
Why would the pipe burst out of the blue?
Shall I come up and take a look--
No, no need. Don't come up.
Jeez, you startled me.
-I guess it's because the pipe is old.
-It's dirty.
-I should call a plumber tomorrow.
-You often get a cold?
All the time.
There's water everywhere.
I should stay up all night to clean.
No, it's okay.
Just take care of Sang-tae for me.
Right. Thanks, Jae-su.
Yes. Today, you're my favorite.
Open the door.
You're a good actor.
Why did you become a caregiver,
not an actor?
Your lies carry a sense of sincerity.
It makes me want to believe them.
My brother...
Sang-tae
is always looking at my face.
My eyes,
the shape of my brows,
the corners of my mouth,
-and every single wrinkle on my face.
-He's angry.
He studies my face
to figure out my mood.
Even when I'm in unbearable pain
and extremely devastated,
my brother believes
that I'm happy
if I force myself to smile.
All I care about
is what my brother thinks.
It's fine even if it's fake.
Putting on a smile
isn't hard to do.
-"You have no common sense.
-You have no common sense.
-Are you that jealous?
-What's with you?
-This isn't good.
-I know how he is.
-He's usually nice,
-but he loses it when he's mad.
-I'm getting a bad feeling about today."
-I'm getting a bad feeling about today.
You jerk!
Then smile at me.
You said it's not hard to do. Smile.
Just sleep. It's getting late.
Were you like this even as a boy?
I saw your photo.
Did you put on a fake smile
even when you were little?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Then what about that woman?
The woman you liked.
You said my eyes reminded you of her.
Do you still think about her?
-Do you miss her?
-No.
I want to forget her.
She must've been a total bitch.
No, quite the contrary.
I was a jerk to her.
She saved my life,
but I ran.
Like a coward.
And I've been running away
since then.
Then why did you pick me up earlier?
You ran to me instead of running away.
Right, I'm regretting it now.
But I have to say,
I was quite smitten.
What is...
Hey, Jeong-tae!
What? What's up? What's this sound?
-Call the nurse. The nurse!
-What?
-Darn it.
-Hurry!
What's wrong? Professor Ko!
What's the matter?
Can you hear me?
Gosh, he's so loud.
Jae-su, you're snoring so loudly.
Jae-su, are you that tired?
You're tired
because you're healthy, right?
Are you okay, Jae-su?
Gosh, you're too loud.
Way too loud.
Oh, boy.
My dear daughter, you must be exhausted.
Your butt has shrunken to half its size.
-All right.
-I'll take this upstairs.
Goodness.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I'm obviously here so early
because I slept here.
What about you?
Do you deliver milk as a side job?
No, I live here.
This is my place.
So,
you're the one who suggested that
he should move into this house?
That's right. I recommended
that he should live here
and also told him about the hospital.
He made the choice though.
It sounds like you're saying he returned
to Seongjin City because of you.
Do you like him?
You do. Have you told him?
-It's none of your business.
-I have.
"I love you.
I love you!
I said, I love you!"
Like that. With all my passion.
-Don't lie.
-I really did.
He kept clinging to me
looking like he wanted something from me,
so I gave him what he wanted.
Are you giving alms or what?
You thief.
-What?
-Don't drool over him.
He was always mine.
Is everything yours
once you set your eyes on it?
If you can't make it yours, you would even
destroy it to get your hands on it.
Then you'd play with it a little
and toss it out when you get tired of it.
You call that "love"?
That's just obsession
and greed.
Two-faced bitch.
You bad-mouth people like crazy
but act all coy to their faces.
You always act nice, weak, and innocent.
That's why you never had any friends
in school. Do you get it now?
You crazy...
You evil witch.
Do you have a death wish?
-Gosh, go to hell!
-Hey, are you on something?
-What the... You need to be on something!
-You...
-Hey, let go!
-You!
Seriously, are you high?
-Hey!
-Why you little...
This is why you'll always fail.
-Damn you!
-Have you lost your mind?
Ko Mun-yeong!
Let her go.
Let go.
-What's going on?
-What's all this noise?
What's happening?
Wait, that bitch hit me first!
Enough.
What? Why am I getting crap for this?
That two-faced bitch hit me first.
I don't care who started it.
-Then why are you only taking her side?
-Take her side?
"Ko Mun-yeong!"
You only shouted my name earlier.
Don't be so childish. Just go home.
Come with me. You need to move out
of this shabby house at once.
-I can't leave you here.
-Mind your own business.
I decide where I live.
And one more thing.
You don't own me.
How much did you hear?
"I love you.
I said I love you." From that point on.
Here.
I'm paying you back with money
for the love you showed me
out of sympathy.
Damn it.
That two-faced bitch.
Sang-tae, wait! Sang-tae!
Sang-tae.
Sang-tae, I...
The pipes are fine. Nothing burst.
Everything works fine.
Nothing burst. Everything's working fine.
Nothing burst.
Nothing burst...
Sang-tae.
I'm sorry.
I lied.
Lying is bad. If you lie,
the cops will come and get you.
You promised me you'd never lie again.
Sang-tae, I'm sorry.
I promise I'll never lie again.
Forgive me just this once.
Ms. Ko Mun-yeong...
Why was she wearing those clothes?
-What?
-That denim shirt and that T-shirt.
"It goes with anything."
You got it on sale
at Bomul Mart.
It was 9,900 won, the BOGO deal.
They're yours.
I know they're your clothes.
I let her borrow them.
It rained last night, you know.
Her clothes got soaked,
so I let her borrow mine.
-What about my clothes?
-What?
I also have nice...
I have a lot of nice clothes too.
I'll let her borrow yours next time
she comes over. The one with dinosaurs.
The one with the ultrasaurus.
It was 27,000 won.
That's more expensive than 9,900 won.
Although higher prices
don't always mean better quality.
Okay, I'll make sure she wears that one.
I promise.
Okay?
Come on, Sang-tae.
Get up and have some food.
You need energy
to cry as much as you want.
Get up!
I don't want to eat anything.
She's that girl, right?
The friend you brought
back when I used to run that diner.
She was never my "friend."
Did she pull out a lot of your hair?
Did you lose?
Is that why you're crying?
Ko Mun-yeong...
He shouted only her name.
He glared at her
without even glancing at me.
He always talks so politely to me,
but he talked very casually to her.
You're crying your eyes out
because of that?
He's closer to me.
Why does he call me "Ju-ri" so politely
and why is she...
Why does he call her
"Ko Mun-yeong" like that?
And those clothes too.
We bought them together at a BOGO sale.
I can't believe he let her wear them.
And she slept in his room...
How could he let her sleep in his room?
Well, he said
there was a bit of a situation.
You know that Gang-tae
would never fool around with a girl
in his room behind his brother's back.
Don't you worry.
You'll definitely get your chance.
Mom, how did you know?
What? The fact
that you have a crush on Gang-tae?
Everyone in this neighborhood knows.
Here, eat.
Why keep it all inside?
Since this happened,
you should just tell him.
-But what if he rejects me?
-Just keep at it.
What if he runs away?
Chase him to the end of the world.
I, too, had to make such efforts
to bring you into this world.
Here.
But I must say, Mun-yeong has grown
into such a pretty lady.
Pretty, my ass!
She is not pretty.
NEW SEONGJIN PUBLIC BATH
Hey, will you please pick up your phone?
Goodness.
-Hello?
-Mr. Lee.
-We're in trouble.
-Listen.
I told you nothing's important to me
unless it's a life or death situation.
We're all about to die.
What?
And when you read someone's book,
you can easily see
how that writer thinks and feels.
Then I guess you also know
what I'm going to do next.
But I, too, can attack you
with the tip of my pen.
Goodbye.
He got surgery for brain hemorrhage
and woke up in two days.
No wonder Suicide Bomber
has been so quiet lately.
Sir, take a look at this.
He's demanding a huge amount
of compensation.
If we don't give him that,
Ms. Ko will either end up in prison
or end up destroying her career.
What should we do?
Check how much cash we have...
No, never mind.
Tell the accounting manager to join us.
The manager quit a while ago
and won't answer any of our calls.
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
You never asked.
Sir, the printing house
and the distribution warehouse
keep calling us
asking for the overdue payment.
Sir, how did things go at Seongjin City?
-She's working on her next book, right?
-We're going to be okay, right?
-Mr. Lee!
-Sir, wake up!
-My gosh. Mr. Lee!
-Sir.
Mr. Lee.
-Are you okay, sir?
-Be quiet for a second. Hold on.
Give me a minute.
Gosh, no way.
Seung-jae.
Yes?
Do you hike?
Yes.
I used to be the chairwoman
of a hiking club.
Did you sleep with her?
Are you guys dating?
Do you like that lunatic?
Are you drunk already?
Then why did you ride Alberto
in the rain for her?
Why did you bring her home
when you don't even like her?
Why feed her and let her sleep over?
Was it for charity?
Are you a religious man?
The beer is a bit bland.
Gang-tae, don't act out of the ordinary.
-You'll die in the prism of your life.
-It's prime, not prism.
Anyway, you should be careful.
Have you forgotten already?
She hurt you with a knife
the first time you met her.
Yes, she did.
My gosh, are you reminiscing right now?
Do you miss it or something?
-What are you talking about?
-Hey.
People who are insane
don't act based on logic.
They turn into monsters
the moment they lose it.
Look. Let this scar be a reminder.
Next time, it might not be your hand.
Goodness...
She might just go for your neck.
You're right.
I should avoid her, right?
Of course. Don't ever get involved.
I should stay out of her sight.
Exactly. Don't even go near her.
But the thing is, Jae-su,
I am growing forgetful these days.
-Forgetful about what?
-Everything.
My scars.
The butterflies.
Even Sang-tae.
I sometimes just forget about them all.
So
you should remind me like this
from time to time
and help me come to my senses.
Okay.
Okay, I get it. So stop smiling like that.
Why?
-Do I look like Joker?
-No.
You look like Chucky.
I'm paying you back with money
for the love you showed me
out of sympathy.
It'll be enough for a taxi ride.
Damn it.
Did he give me that money
to get rid of me?
Am I only worth 30,000 won?
He lives like a poor beggar.
That cheap jerk! How dare he?
Darn it.
Cheap jerk!
That cheap jerk.
Cheap jerk.
My gosh.
Why is he so fickle? It confuses me.
Does he have a split personality or what?
Sang-tae, are you sleeping?
Sang-tae, who do you like more?
Me or Ko Mun-yeong?
I like you more.
You're my everything.
Who is it?
Mun-yeong.
We're doomed.
Why is she here?
I'm here
because Mr. Lee tricked me
into coming here.
With our company building deposit,
I paid that darn Suicide Bomber
the compensation he asked for,
gave our staff their overdue salary
and severance pay,
and paid all our subcontractors
their overdue payment.
And now, I'm broke.
You didn't give me my severance pay.
You just bought me this suitcase and
asked me to follow you on a business trip.
-Are you a con artist?
-Hey!
I brought you here
to take responsibility for your future.
How are you going to do that
when you've gone bankrupt?
Hey, I haven't gone bankrupt.
I still have Ko Mun-yeong. She's my hope.
Right?
Get out.
This is so annoying.
-Mun-yeong.
-Why do I have to be
the person who saves you
from this mess you're in?
Hey, come on.
Don't you know who caused this--
You caused this to happen.
Yes, that's right.
It's all because I was an incompetent CEO.
-It's all my fault.
-Incompetent jerk.
Now, leave.
Mun-yeong, don't be like this.
Just let me stay by your side
and help you publish your books.
Last time, you even asked me
to live with you.
Don't you remember?
Didn't you run away?
Someone else is going to move in here.
Who?
No way.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Young man.
Hey, young man.
Thank you.
I've had my eyes on you
for the past couple of days.
And I noticed that you're very handsome.
You also have a nice build
and seem very reliable.
EMPLOYEE CARD
"Moon Gang-tae"?
You also have a great name.
How old are you?
I'm 30 years old.
What do your parents do?
They're dead.
Both of them?
Oh, dear.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
So that nurse has a crush on you?
Pardon?
That's good.
What do you mean?
I'd like to introduce you to a nice lady
who would be perfect for you.
No, it's okay.
It's not because she's my daughter.
She really is a great catch.
You should meet her
when she visits me one day.
Well, I'll think about it.
I need to get back to work.
Let me know if you have a change of heart.
They'll be a really good match.
This isn't it.
No.
How about green?
Gosh, no.
This one?
My goodness.
The first step is always the hardest.
But once you take your first step,
things will get easier from then on.
Now, it's time for you to show me
what you're capable of.
No, no! This isn't right!
No!
-I'm sorry.
-Why did you do that?
-That was bad.
-Come here.
-I won't do it again.
-Sang-tae.
-You can't do that.
The hospital director isn't sane either.
Don't you agree?
Why are you crying again?
-You promised you wouldn't cry.
-You ruined it.
-A-reum.
-Because I'm jealous.
I also want to play tag like that.
Hold my hand. Let's go take your medicine.
-You need to get scolded!
-No!
Do you want to get scolded?
It's funny how people who should be
wearing a patient gown aren't wearing one.
-Why did you do that? Why?
-My goodness.
Do you want to get scolded?
Ms. Ko.
How do you feel?
Never good. Why did you call me?
I heard what your father did to you.
I'm very sorry.
You weren't the one who strangled me.
But still, I was the one who told you
to take him out for walks.
Then it was a medical accident.
You can't just end it with an apology.
Then let's do this.
You can strangle me instead.
Here. Go ahead.
What a crazy old man.
The sound of a ghost humming?
Yes.
By any chance, do you know what time
it was when you heard that last night?
I don't know.
I don't even know what date it is today.
I just heard it on my way to the bathroom.
Then did you happen to see anyone
in front of room 203
or in the hallway?
She said it was a ghost humming,
so it was probably a ghost.
Ms. Nam.
Do you actually believe her gibberish?
It's not gibberish.
I swear I can hear it.
That's called auditory hallucination.
And it's proof that you're crazy.
Hey, I'm not crazy.
Yes, I'm sure you heard what you heard.
Then are you saying I'm crazy?
Standing here with you like this
reminds me of the past.
Do you remember what you said
when I was crying on the rooftop
after I got slapped by a patient
back at Yongrim Hospital?
"Why don't you slap me
and make yourself feel better?"
I didn't know you'd really slap me.
I must've been crazy.
I don't know why I did that.
But thanks to that,
we became really close, didn't we?
Or are we not?
Are we not close?
Ju-ri.
Do you want to slap me once again?
Why?
Because I feel like you'll get upset
in a little while.
Are you
rejecting me already?
Don't bother
wasting your emotions on me.
I don't deserve any of that.
Because
you're going to leave anyway?
It doesn't matter. Just...
Just let me keep liking you.
That's up to me.
Do me a favor.
I hope
you don't run away
because you find me uncomfortable.
If you do,
it'll make me feel really pathetic
and sad.
Just continue to live with us at our house
while you're in Seongjin City.
My mom really likes you guys.
And...
Sang-tae likes living with us as well.
Please do that for me.
O Ji-wang is bad.
O Ji-wang.
O Ji-wang... O Ji-wang is a bad person.
He may be a doctor, but he's a bad person.
O Ji-wang is really fast. He's bad.
He... He needs to learn his manners.
Koreans should be courteous.
Sang-tae.
-Do you want to have fun with me?
-Yes.
FACILITY MANAGEMENT CHECKLIST
The number you have dialed is
currently unavailable.
Please leave a voicemail...
How... How much did you pay for this car?
Does it cost more than one million won?
Is it two million won?
It costs 100 to 1,000 times more.
How... How much money do you have?
Are you rich?
I'm 100 to 1,000 times richer than you.
I guess you like money.
Yes, I... I like money.
I like money, cars,
and I like you, too.
I like you 100 to 12,000 times more.
But where are we going? It's dark outside.
Where did he go?
I'm on duty again.
Are you looking for your brother?
Have you seen him?
He left earlier with Ms. Ko.
Why was she here?
She didn't have class today.
I don't know.
Is it okay
if I touch you?
Oh, my gosh.
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
-Do you like this place?
-Would you like to move in with me?
-Yes.
-Then sign this.
-Okay.
ILLUSTRATION CONTRACT
Where is my brother?
He's with me.
I warned you
to stay away from my brother.
The employee will live...
The employee will live in...
-I hung out with him because I was bored.
-the employer's...
Do you want to come pick him up?
Where are you?
We're at the cursed castle.
Okay.
Do you even know where it is?
Yes, I know.
How?
-Because I've been there.
-What?
That day when you saved me,
and I ran away from you.
Are you telling me
that you knew?
I'll see you when I get there.
Sang-tae.
Should I tell you an old tale?
Yes.
A long time ago, deep inside the forest,
there lived a little girl
in a cursed castle.
The little girl's mother
always told her daughter
that she's too special
to live among everyone else
outside the castle.
The mother told her daughter
that she must live inside the castle.
However, the little girl
felt like she was imprisoned.
So she prayed to the moon every day.
"Please
send me a handsome prince
who can save me from here."
"Will he come today?
Will he come tomorrow?"
The little girl
waited every day
for her prince to show up.
Earlier, I was too...
Get lost.
SPECIAL THANKS TO JUNG SANG-HOON
FOR MAKING A GUEST APPEARANCE
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
Let's live together.
This is our home now.
This is not our home!
It's mine! No! That's mine!
Gang-tae.
You took good care of him until now.
Now, it's time for you
to let him do what he wants.
No, I'm against this team!
You cause trouble because you can't even
control yourself.
So how are you going to care for him?
Sang-tae. Have you ever
heard the story of Bluebeard?
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee