Sub by Dramacool.ae
♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 42
Father!
Master!
Yitang stole the commander’s tally
so that we were rescued.
If the Demons come to attack us again,
I can’t get the young generation
in such danger.
Lord Gantang.
You’re just in time.
I was looking for you.
I’ve arranged military affairs.
Jinrong’s birthday is coming.
I’ll leave tomorrow for home.
What a coincidence! Look.
Here’s a letter from your home.
My daughter has been back home,
with all the tokens
for the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Go back home.
I’ll get the horse ready for you.
Okay.
I’ll leave tonight with light luggage.
General Wen knows me very well.
I stole
the commander’s tally.
I sent troops illegally
and broke the military law!
I’m sorry to General Wang
for his care and instruction.
I’m sorry to the whole Anping Army!
I’m guilty!
Yitang!
Yitang! Yitang!
What did you do?
You miser.
You don’t need to buy me drinks anymore.
I’ve destroyed my martial arts.
Wen Yu.
I’ll leave Anping Army
to you.
Hyah!
Assassins! Protect Lord Gantang.
We’re trapped! Go!
Don’t run after them!
Lord Gantang, it’s foresighted of you.
The assassins did attack us tonight.
Right ahead us is the territory
of the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
If they didn’t attack me,
they wouldn’t have a chance.
What have you got?
The blade looks like a weapon
from the court.
There are always disguises
in the art of war.
We used a trick.
They might have used one, too.
What do you mean, Lord Gantang?
They were very meticulous,
leaving no clue to us.
I’m not sure who they are.
But...
I’m afraid
something terrible may happen.
The world has been in peace
for merely two years.
People can no longer suffer.
The Fortress of the Forty-Eight
is right there.
I’ll travel all night to get home early.
There won’t be any problem.
General Wen.
Please go back with Anping Token.
Remember.
No matter what rumors you hear,
make sure not to take any rash action.
I can’t leave.
Lord Gantang.
If I leave,
you’ll be alone.
I’m afraid...
What are you afraid of?
Compared to
several hundred thousand people
on the border,
I’m insignificant.
The order cannot be disobeyed.
General Wen.
Take the order.
I...
I take the order.
Bravo!
You moved so swiftly,
like a graceful flying bird.
Don’t flatter me.
Have some hot wine to warm up.
Here.
Your craftsmanship is getting better.
You’ve made so many lanterns.
Are you going to sell them?
No.
We’ll fly them.
Which do you like? Pick one.
That one.
This one?
I painted it very carefully.
Look at the mountain.
You see the details?
The river and the pavilion.
Look. We’re here.
We’ll fly only one lantern?
I’ll pick one, too.
Which one would you like?
This one.
I heard
the lantern would fly
to the heaven.
Would you like to make a wish?
Yes.
♪Travel around with a long blade♪
♪Live freely and don’t get old♪
♪The sun shines in the Fortress♪
♪Though the world outside is chaotic♪
Fei.
I wish you could
live a long and happy life
and you could be always free
in the martial world.
♪Ignore the troubles♪
♪Hold your hands and smile in wind♪
♪So lucky to get the wooden peach
from you♪
♪You don’t know♪
♪My love is pure like ice and light♪
♪Even the dragon ages over time♪
♪So does the hero braving the world♪
♪Petals fly in the dream♪
♪Like greeting the old friend♪
♪Keep the vow we made until death♪
What wish did you make?
I won’t tell you.
♪However far to go♪
♪However high to reach♪
♪This moment is worth my forever love♪
Zhou Yitang is so crafty!
Wen Yu was the strongest martial artist
working for Wang Lin.
I didn’t expect losers like you
to kill him.
He doesn’t have martial arts.
But he’s more thoughtful
than most people.
We cannot defeat him,
unless Shen Tianshu goes personally.
I just gave him a lesson,
telling them
we’re not pushovers.
It’s been years,
but Shen Tianshu had no breakthrough
on his martial arts.
Seems like he has
his own inner demon, too.
I will make him
help us.
Ask Pathetic Clam
to take action tonight.
Why is there such a weird disease?
The pulse is so weird.
I’ve never seen any before.
I’m a doctor for the Third Prince.
May I have your name?
You use the martial art
of Route Gang,
Chong Vessel.
Chong Vessel sets in your body
with wrong circulation of vital energy.
When you practice rashly,
you have a bellyache.
The weakness of your martial arts
lies in Qichong.
Am I right?
I really underestimated you.
My respects.
Come in, please.
The Third Prince vomits sometimes.
Looks like he has disharmony
of spleen and stomach
-and lower adverse-rising energy.
-Come in, please.
Nonsense! Nonsense!
There’s no heat in his stomach
so that he can’t digest any food.
That’s why he vomits
every time he eats something.
He just needs heat-clearing pills.
He’s got lovesickness.
Nonsense! Ridiculous!
This is nonsense!
He just needs some heat-clearing pills.
Yes.
There’s no heat in his stomach.
It can’t be lovesickness.
No way.
She’s talking rubbish!
His pulse feels...
What is she doing?
How careless she is!
How... how dare she!
What is she writing?
Seriously?
Isn’t...
Isn’t she giving a casual prescription?
Get what’s in the prescription
and put it in the censer.
The Third Prince
will wake up immediately.
But I’m afraid
it’s not easy to cure him completely.
How was it going, Madam?
Such stupid doctors want
to detoxify my poison?
What a fool’s talk!
Doctor! Doctor! Please stay.
Doctor.
When we put the medicine in,
the Third Prince woke up immediately.
You have miraculous medical skills!
You flatter me.
I just restrained the disease
in the body of the Third Prince.
If you want him to get recovered,
I’m afraid
you need to cure him of lovesickness.
Please instruct us, Doctor.
Commander-in-chief, let me go
and tell Lord.
It’s okay. Don’t bother.
I’ll just wait.
Commander-in-chief,
sorry to have kept you waiting.
Lord invited you in.
Lord.
Here comes Commander-in-chief.
Lord Shen, you’ve locked yourself here.
What a comfortable life you live!
I don’t think you allowed me in
only because I waited
for such a long time.
I heard
the assassins you sent
to kill Zhou Yitang
failed their mission.
Without you,
they could do nothing.
You won’t easily give up.
I guess you’ve got a backup plan.
You know me very well, Lord Shen.
I had someone sneak into
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
I must get
the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
It would be better
if we could kill Li Jinrong
when the Third Prince was there.
We can only get fish in troubled waters.
Kill two birds with one stone?
It’s greedy of you, Commander-in-chief.
Aren’t you curious
about who I have sent to the Fortress?
Don’t you worry about her safety?
She’s risking her life for you.
You have the greatest talent
to identify and use people.
If you asked me to kill Li Jinrong,
I might not succeed
even after a desperate fight.
But everything has its vanquisher.
Since Pathetic Clam poisoned Li Zheng,
she can also poison Li Jinrong.
Why must I worry about her?
You don’t worry about her.
But you’re still willing to meet me.
Could you be moved by my sincerity?
Last time, you visited me
and asked me to kill Zhou Yitang.
You didn’t give a good reason,
so that I didn’t feel
any killing intent.
Now you tell me Pathetic Clam went
to the Fortress of the Forty-Eight for you.
Commander-in-chief.
I know her best.
In the past few years,
she only cares about flowers
in the manor.
If it weren’t for
the Color of Ocean and Heaven,
I couldn’t even ask her to do anything.
What did you
give her?
You’d better not know.
I don’t think I can get anything today.
I’d like to go.
She went there for you, Lord Shen.
Your people failed many times.
I told Tianying
I would withdraw everything
for supporting the Demons these years.
She went there, to keep your prestige
among the Demons.
She’s such a good woman.
Do cherish her.
I’ve thought about this.
Seems like
you have no more news to tell me.
Will you really look on and do nothing?
Commander-in-chief.
I’m no longer
a kindhearted young man
who would help people
if he knew they were in trouble.
Pathetic Clam worked for you.
If you want me to help her,
you should at least
give me something attractive.
How much money or grain
do you want this time?
None.
A powerful man like you
lives such a poor life.
You’re either too thrifty,
or
too heartless.
What exactly do you want?
I want you to send troops to help me
get the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Sure. We promised to join hands
and get it.
Yes, we promised.
Now you want me to kill someone for you.
You need to give me something more.
After we find
the Color of Ocean and Heaven,
do not
touch anything
in it.
Sub by Dramacool.ae
Stop!
Your Highness.
We’ve walked a long way.
Shall we take a rest?
Okay.
Mr. Bai.
How long will it take?
Don’t be anxious, Your Highness.
We’re arriving soon.
Your Highness, you’ve grown up.
You’re going to propose to a girl.
Hope we’ll succeed
and you can get the girl you love.
But Miss Zhou doesn’t look
like Xie Yun’s good friend only.
How shall I propose to her?
Your Highness.
Marriage is usually made
by parents’ order
and match-maker’s word.
Just go propose to Miss Zhou.
If Mr. Xie wants the same thing,
he will do it in his own way.
You won’t be stealing her girl.
Before we left,
most people in the palace knew
you came to propose to her.
If you failed and went back,
I’m afraid you would be laughed at.
Your Highness, before you try,
how do you know you will fail?
Try, as if getting rid
of your inner demon.
Anyway,
you must get rid of your lovesickness.
She’s right.
It’s also for the sake of your health.
Okay. Let’s move on.
Aye.
Token
Without me,
Fei would have lived a carefree life.
Madam, we’ve got a visitor.
Didn’t I tell Sheng
to stop all visitors?
Maybe he can’t stop this one.
Who is it?
The Third Prince.
Stop!
Today, I’ve finally realized
how vast this place can be.
It took us great trouble
to walk halfway.
We could hardly move on.
Luckily, you sent men to help us.
We came up alive, at last.
Your Highness, I heard
you’re seeking talents.
For your marriage,
you’ve racked your brains.
Sure.
This is a heroic place.
If I weren’t sincere to propose,
how could I convince other heroes?
Very well.
We don’t support
either your court or the other.
We have our own rules.
Sorry to have offended you.
Good point.
Mr. Li.
Oh, no, Master Li.
With a heroic cousin like you,
no wonder
Miss Zhou is also a heroine
and an outstanding girl.
Miss Zhou?
Aren’t you going to...?
You want to marry Zhou Fei?
Why do you want to marry her?
To guard your house?
Doctor, are you all right?
She’s alright.
After walking the whole day,
she’s so weak that she needs some rest.
How about this?
I’ll take you to your rooms
for some rest.
Mr. Li.
I’d like to take His Highness
to meet Madam Li.
Your Highness, it’s our honor
to welcome you.
Thank you, Madam Li.
This is the first cup of tea
I’ve had today.
Sorry for the poor condition.
Please forgive us.
Your Highness, I wonder
what you come for.
Lately, I was in danger a few times,
and Miss Zhou saved me.
I heard it’s your birthday.
I bring some gifts
to express my gratitude.
This is the Mountain-River Jade
I’ve treasured.
Seen in the candlelight,
the pattern looks
like the mountain and river.
Take it.
Insightful and Open-minded
I heard martial artists are easy-going.
Madam, you really behave
like departed heroes.
I’ll accept the Jade.
But please take away
the rest of the gifts.
These are...
Madam.
These are betrothal presents
to propose to Miss Zhou Fei.
Your father sent you?
His Highness
likes Miss Zhou.
He came here
with the approval from His Majesty.
Cousin!
Cousin, bad news!
The Third Prince...
He came to propose to you
with a lot of gifts!
What?
The Third Prince?
Propose to me?
Where’s Xie Yun?
Did he know the Third Prince came?
I didn’t see him.
Shall I go find him?
Tell him the Third Prince wanted
to marry me.
See how he responded.
Mr. Xie.
Look what a condition you’re in!
Why are you still here?
I was looking for you everywhere!
What do you mean?
Forget it.
Your sworn brother, the Third Prince...
He has come
and is now in the Hall of Elders.
Zichen has come?
That’s great.
That’s not great!
He came to propose to Fei!
You met my daughter?
A couple of times.
Unfortunately,
we met by chance
and we weren’t very close.
You came to propose to her
after meeting by chance?
It’s so romantic of you, Your Highness.
She met me by chance.
But to me,
I couldn’t forget her
for even one glance.
Your Highness.
This doesn’t work in this place.
Zhou Fei has grown up.
I can’t make decisions for her.
Talk to her personally.
Miss Zhou, what do you think?
Xie Yun?
I heard you were here. This is great.
What are you coming for?
I...
I want to...
I want to marry Miss Zhou.
Father has agreed.
Xie Yun, what do you think?
Are these all for me?
Miss Zhou.
These are betrothal presents
His Highness prepared for you.
Do you like them?
She...
I don’t think
she likes any of this.
This blade looks good.
You have sharp eyes, Miss Zhou.
Mount Kunwu is said
to be sixty miles east
from the Yi River.
On the mountain is lots of copper
as red as fire.
Made of it,
the blade will cut jade like mud.
This is Kunwu,
the famous blade made of such copper.
What?
You’re also interested in this?
No.
I...
I just...
I just want to have a look.
Sorry, Xie Yun.
I should have told you.
After all,
you’re Miss Zhou’s close friend.
But if you don’t want us
to get married,
I will...
Zichen.
You want to marry me, don’t you?
Why did you ask him for permission?
You only need to ask me.
Come with me.
Wait!
Don’t follow up.
Tired?
Don’t push yourself.
I’m not tired. For you,
I would do anything impossible.
We just met a few times.
Why do you like me so much?
We grew up
under totally different conditions.
I must behave carefully
since I was little.
I can do nothing wrong.
But you’re always free and bighearted.
You’re the most special girl I’ve met.
So...
How passionate you sound, Your Highness!
But since I was little,
I’ve made a rule for myself.
Whoever wants to marry me
must have better martial arts.
Your Highness, would you like
to compete with me?
I...
I’ve seen your martial arts.
Miss Zhou,
you’re forcing me.
If you don’t want to compete, fine.
Leave as early as possible.
No.
Well,
Miss Zhou,
sorry for the offense.
Fei is great.
She tried to scare him away.
Bonehead, watch and learn.
Learn what?
It doesn’t work on him. Look.
Well, it doesn’t work on an idiot.
Nice move!
Are you alright?
You used great martial arts, Miss Zhou.
Do you get me wrong
or do you get yourself wrong?
Even if I’m fighting someone stronger,
I must have a try.
Or you couldn’t feel my loyalty.
Show your loyalty in our place?
You’ve overestimated yourself.
Everyone in your place is loyal.
I’ve never underestimated you.
Fine. How about this?
I’ve seen the betrothal gifts
you gave me.
I don’t like them.
I want the wild flower in the crevice
in the middle of Ximo River.
If you get it for me,
I’ll marry you.
If you fail,
leave in the way you come.
What do you think?
Fine. It’s a deal, then.
Doomed.
The Spinning Wire Formation
over Ximo River is still on.
The Spinning Wire Formation?
What is that?
What’s this?
The Spinning Wire Formation.
It’s as fast as the wind
and as sharp as a blade.
It’s made against robbers.
With this on,
who can get the wide flower
from the middle of the river?
I first met her
in the Ximo River.
I thought
she was the Weed Spirit in the river.
Your Highness,
would you still like a try?
I...
I’ll have a talk with him.
You’re no longer kids.
Could you stop eavesdropping?
In this world,
seems like only you can do it.
Xie Yun.
You...
You and Miss Zhou...
Did I... did I do something wrong?
Zichen, did your father really
allow you to come?
He ordered you to come?
I insisted on coming.
Father didn’t agree at first.
We even quarreled.
Zichen, you always say
you’re inferior to me.
But I can’t propose to my beloved girl
like you do.
If you really like her,
why don’t you tell her?
I’m dying. Even if I told her,
nothing would change.
I’m living a good life already.
Staying with her every day
makes me satisfied.
I want to be married to her.
Unfortunately, I...
But Xie Yun...
You’re a prince. How can you...
It doesn’t matter.
I should have been dead
in the war years ago.
I lived for extra years,
which was already a blessing.
I’ll certainly live in the way I like.
I prefer to teach students in this place
under her prestige,
and be a rent collector.
I feel my life satisfied, then.
Pretend I was married to her for peace.
What do you think?
Xie Yun, have you made up your mind?
Yes. The fiercer Fei is, the better.
In this way,
no one but me dares to marry her.
Fei?
Your Highness, did you understand?
You may leave us.
I...
Fei, you heard us?
I’m fierce?
Not really.
Not really?
No, no, you’re not fierce.
Zichen is young and naive.
Don’t take it seriously.
I don’t care what he said.
But...
I just heard someone said
he would like to be married to me.
Fei, you know that.
I was born with bad luck
and I won’t live long.
Bah!
What bad luck?
I haven’t despised you.
How can you despise yourself?
♪Travel freely♪
Miss Zhou.
♪With the flute♪
♪You got me caged in your heart♪
I never have good luck, good health
or even families.
Now I’ve got nothing, but a title.
I have no wealth and I’m dying.
My only betrothal present
is the wild flower.
If you don’t hate me for my short life,
please marry me.
With the landscape as our matchmaker,
we’ll share weal or woe.
We won’t leave each other unless we die.
♪Like greeting the old friend♪
What do you think?
♪Keep the vow♪
Okay.
♪We made until death♪
We won’t leave each other unless we die.
♪However far to go♪
♪However high to reach♪
♪This moment is worth my forever love♪
Man.
You used such a great move
on the training ground.
Nice move. Let’s have a competition.
-Mr. Yang, I’ve got work to do.
-Just one competition.
-Just once.
-Man.
Next time. Next time.
My favorite crispy winter jujube?
Thank you, Mr. Xie.
What I asked you to do...
How is it going?
Rest assured. I’m sure
Fei will be surprised
so that she’ll forget
the martial art thing.
Oh, there’s some vintage wine
in Hanshui Town near here.
It’s her favorite taste.
Could you
get one pot for me?
Hanshui Town?
Where the best dough figurines are sold?
Precisely.
You’re most familiar with this area.
Your problem is mine, Cousin-in-law.
Don’t worry. I’ll take care of it.
Thanks.
Bonehead, go down the mountain with me.
Go.
Man.
What you did on the training ground
was a nice move.
No. No. You used a better one.
No.
-If only Bonehead...
-Let’s teach each other.
-could be half as romantic as Mr. Xie.
-What do you think?
Let’s go. Go.
Let’s compete. Go.
I’ll go alone, then.
We’re busy up here.
You must tell our men
to strengthen the patrol
in and out of the Fortress.
Tomorrow,
we’ll celebrate Aunt’s birthday.
We mustn’t be careless on the patrol
outside the mountain, either.
We must be very cautious. Got it?
Aye!
Sheng.
Chuchu.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪