[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 9]
Boss.
Sir, what can I get you?
Have you seen this before?
Get out.
-There's a shop in front.
-Try your luck over there.
Boss, I...
I can tell that
you either want to buy
things you can't afford,
or you want to sell things nobody wants.
I've seen people like you.
Other shops didn't appreciate your stuff,
and you don't believe my small
shop can afford to buy your stuff.
You should go.
Boss,
I have a few pieces of spiritual arrays.
Please take a look at it.
The drawing is nice.
I can use it as leg pads for my table.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Wait.
How many spirit boards do you have?
May I know your name, sir?
Li Mu.
What about
your wife?
None of your business. I'm asking you,
how many spirit boards are there?
Get it all out for me.
This is all I have.
What did you see?
Nothing.
You're not very talented.
But I do feel some changes around.
You could be talented.
I've been seeing certain drawings
in my dream since I was a kid,
but I forgot most of them
every time I woke up.
These sketches are based
on the drawings in my dream.
But
these are just the tiny
pieces of the original drawing.
Kid,
sometimes, pushing
yourself too hard to look for it
could backfire.
Take your time, go home and keep dreaming.
One day
when you can remember
everything in your dreams,
come back to me.
Alright.
You've travelled so far
to open your store in this place.
It's because of this kid, am I right?
He helped you before?
No way.
Look at that plateau redness
on his cheeks.
Even his cultivation level is
only at the Natal Opening Realm.
Yet you're impressed by him.
Me?
It was just a favour to you.
Shao Yang.
You're here.
Did Pu Jiao do anything unusual today?
No.
If it really was him who sent
someone to kill Uncle Hua,
we have to find a way
to provoke him to do it again.
It would be best if he did it himself.
I've already done so.
[Before I find the
evidence to expose you,]
[there's one thing I have to do first.]
[What is it?]
[I'll marry Du Shao Yang.]
[Ling Borough will form an alliance]
[with Xingyun Pavilion.]
I've given him a reason to kill me.
And since he can't afford to fail,
he'll definitely come for me himself.
So with me as the bait,
it's perfect.
-No.
The ship has sailed.
What's done is done.
Your only choice now is to work with me.
Protect me.
-Yu Shi...
-I...
Are you just setting up trap
or are you being serious?
-Of course I...
-Setting up trap.
You used our marriage as a reason
to provoke Pu Jiao.
If Pu Jiao believes that
we're going to get married,
he would come for you himself.
Yes.
This is too bad for you then,
you are going to marry me again.
You want to get married?
And as soon as possible?
Why?
A marriage alliance between two families
was our original intention back then.
What about you, Miss Ling?
Haven't you been accusing Shao Yang
of murdering Blacksmith Hua
of Ling Borough?
I wasn't thinking clearly.
I thought about it afterwards.
Shao Yang wouldn't do that.
I'm willing to marry him
because I believe in him.
This is good for both
families to bury the hatchet
and make peace.
To mend the relationship between
our two families as soon as possible,
Yu Shi and I have
reached an agreement that
we should get married without delay.
After that, we'll go back to
Ling Borough and meet Chief Ling.
We'll clear up the misunderstanding
with the Lings.
Does Qin Lie know about this?
I'll tell him.
That means he doesn't know.
He's not going to come and
ruin the wedding again, is he?
We will take care of this matter.
Stepmother, please don't worry.
Fine.
Your marriage is settled then.
Master...
I said it's settled.
Pass my words.
The Young Master of
Xingyun Pavilion is getting married.
The town will celebrate the
joyous moment together.
Yes.
The marriage is settled?
I thought she is in love with Qin Lie?
That's true.
But Qin Lie doesn't know about it yet.
Well.
I shall kill her personally this time.
I'm going to turn their wedding
into a funeral.
[Miss me?]
I'm guessing that you missed me?
You've heard about it, haven't you?
Congratulations.
You're getting married again.
That's why I'm here to remind you.
Don't make any trouble.
Do you love her?
None of your business.
There isn't any sparkle in your eyes.
Looks like
you don't love her.
Women are not meant to be loved.
They are meant to procreate then?
I love power and status.
Do you know what it
feels like to love someone?
Your heart will become tender.
It'll make you feel powerful.
I'm already powerful.
A man's power of
fist is the most inferior.
The real power is
love.
Endless love
boundless love,
it will make you feel like a bird
soaring in the sky,
or like a fish swimming in the water.
Your heart will blossom like flower.
A flower that blooms in your heart.
What kind of nonsense books
have you been you reading?
Love
will make your heart tender.
It'll make you powerful.
It'll take away your fear.
Because you have her in your heart,
and she has you in hers.
You'll be by her side,
and she'll be by yours.
You know that
even if you lose,
you'll still have her.
So
you'll never lose everything.
You still have fear.
-I don't.
-Yes, you fear that
you would lose everything in the end
after you've been working
hard for your whole life.
By then,
you'll have no one by your side.
No one cares about you
and no one wants you.
All that's left is an emptiness.
-A pack of nonsense.
-Du Shao Yang!
If you don't love her and
you don't want to marry her,
but you're not in the
position to do anything,
do you believe that
I can ruin this marriage for you?
And I won't put you
in a difficult position.
I do.
I believe you.
But I don't need it.
I'm warning you...
Don't worry.
Once you're married, I'll leave.
I'll stop bugging you.
I don't touch married man.
For me, they are as good as dead.
I believe that
my dream man
will show up one day.
I'll wait here for you
to finish your wedding.
If you want to break the engagement,
come here and find me.
If you are married,
I'll leave.
You'll never see me again.
Where have you been?
I...
What's the matter?
None of your business.
I heard that you are getting
married to Ling Yu Shi.
Yes.
Who did you just meet?
What's that smell on your body?
This is impossible.
It can't be her.
You and Ling Yu Shi's wedding
is just a trap?
Yes.
You told them about Pu Jiao's plan
to deal with Qin Lie,
in order to gain their trust?
Yes.
[Although it's just to set up a trap,]
[I wonder if Qin Lie will have
a problem with the wedding?]
Miss Ling.
Come in.
Miss Ling, this is your
wedding dress for tomorrow.
Leave it.
Yes.
Du Shao Yang,
hand over Yu Shi to me.
Yu Shi was the one who
proposed this marriage.
She's marrying me willingly.
This is none of your business.
That's impossible.
You must have threatened her
by some means.
Xingyun Pavilion will not
tolerate your insolence anymore.
Get lost.
Ling Yu Shi that wench.
She's getting involved
with Qin Lie on one hand,
and seducing Gao Yu on the other.
Now she's going to marry Shao Yang.
Marrying this kind of woman is
a disgrace to our family.
Whoever dares to insult Yu Shi again,
I'm going to hurt her.
Take the mistress back to her room.
Qin Lie,
don't forget it.
-It was Yu Shi who...
-Shut up!
I was just wondering
what's with all the fuss here.
Turned out Qin Lie's here to make a scene.
Qin Lie, if you make any more trouble,
don't blame me
for having to attack you.
It's none of your business.
-Get lost.
-You're being ungrateful.
For the sake of Miss Ling,
let him off today.
I'll let him off
for the sake of Brother Li.
Guo Ying, Guo Hao,
take him outside and let him cool off.
I don't want to see him
again before the wedding.
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
It's our pleasure, Master Du.
It's messy here.
Why don't you all go back
to your rooms and rest?
Once everything is in order,
I'll send the invitation
to you personally.
I hope it won't delay the
time of the wedding ceremony.
It's fine.
I'm here now, nothing can be delayed.
You watched the woman
you love being snatched away,
yet the words you spoke
were still fair
and reasonable.
No wonder I'm attracted to you.
Shut up.
Hurry up.
Walk faster.
Where are you taking me?
Letting me cool off?
Who is it?
This is a wedding dress I chose for you.
Yu Shi,
can you put it on for me too?
This is not the time to joke.
The wedding is tomorrow.
Pu Jiao will definitely
do something tonight.
Why did you come out?
Don't let anyone see you.
You've worn a wedding dress twice.
Once for Qin Lie,
once for Shao Yang.
What about me?
Why did you
never choose me?
Gao Yu,
what are you trying to do?
Can I hug you?
Just for a while.
This is my only wish.
Stop there.
I'm just teasing you.
I saw that you were being nervous.
I'm just joking with you.
I'm not nervous.
Go back and hide.
Saintess.
Help!
Something bad has happened, Young Master!
Something bad has happened, Master!
It's Mistress.
She's dead.
What?
Huang'er!
-Mistress!
-Stepmother!
Sister.
Qin Lie.
What happened?
Qin Lie murdered my wife.
I didn't murder her.
I'm being framed.
If you didn't kill her, who did?
I'm going to kill you!
Qin Lie.
You've got the nerve to
resist despite being weak.
Stop it.
Your lover is a murderer.
Behave yourself.
He didn't do it!
Brother Li,
please help Qin Lie.
Please spare his life, we still
need to interrogate him for the truth.
That's enough.
Are you trying to take the
law into your own hands?
He killed my wife.
I also believe that he killed your wife.
But when did he start to
have intention to kill her,
when did he kill her,
including your wife's body,
we must investigate everything.
We can only convict him
once we get everything clear.
Take him away.
I'll question him personally.
-Yes, sir.
Gao Yu!
-Qin Lie.
-Protect Yu Shi!
Brother Li,
I'll leave it to you to
take care of the scene.
I'm going to interrogate Qin Lie now.
Of course.
Knock yourself out, Lord Pu Jiao.
This is all your fault.
She has nothing to do with this!
You're still defending her.
The one who died was my own sister.
The only family I have left.
Once Lord Pu Jiao
checks everything out,
if she really is involved,
I'll kill her myself.
Come with me.
Huang'er.
Who do you think
is behind this?
Whoever it is, this has
nothing to do with us.
Gao Yu,
let go.
Let go of me.
Let go.
Calm down.
Can't you see it?
We've been tricked.
It wasn't Pu Jiao.
Our plan has been seen through long ago.
Pu Jiao's stupidity, your sister's death,
Qin Lie's arrest,
the person behind all this
had turned our trap to her advantage.
And the person behind is?
Song Ting Yu.
I thought of a way to save Qin Lie.
I need to see him.
You'll get yourself killed.
At least I'll die with him.
I won't let you go.
Let go.
Let go of me!
Sister.
Yu Shi.
I can finally hug you.
Why?
Gao Yu was protecting Ling Yu Shi.
Although it was easy to kill her,
it could draw attention as well.
Killing Gao Huang'er was different.
I just needed to find
someone to take the blame.
Of course I would
pick the easy one to kill.
She is my stepmother.
Since she's the stepmother,
why are you upset?
Do you care about her
like she's your mother?
I told you
my entire plan.
But you
hid everything from me.
You killed my stepmother today.
Who knows
which person close to me
you'd kill next time?
You did well.
This Luminous Bead is yours now.
Now that you have this,
you can ascend to a new realm instantly.
How did I give myself away?
Du Shao Yang.
That's impossible.
I was ordered to come
here to set up traps.
I let Du and Ling families
turn against each other first,
then I'll capture
and have you all slaughtered.
You
are a smart guy.
You figured out my plan.
But Du Shao Yang is smarter.
He knew that joining my side is
better than forming alliance with you.
He sold you out long ago.
You don't believe me?
Then why didn't he save you
and walked away alone just now?
You don't really consider
him a friend, do you?
The word loyalty never belonged to him
Though there is one
word that suits you well.
Dumb.
You're going to die soon.
Speaking of Du Shao Yang,
well,
why didn't he help you just now
and walked away alone?
Because he is going
to the Luminous Pillar,
the place where you
usually met with each other.
Why is he going there then?
He's waiting for me to
give him his reward there.
The star and cloud were close once.
The light could break
the sincerest friendship.
Du Shao Yang,
you betrayed us.
When you discussed about forming
an alliance with me in secret,
you intended to force her
out and negotiate with her.
I thought you've got a point at that time,
but afterwards, I felt it's ridiculous.
You overestimated yourself.
Saintess Song showed herself indeed,
but she was not forced out by us.
She had already seen through us.
So you were bought off by her?
It's Xingyun Pavilion's duty
to share the problems of the Saintess.
And I
will profit from it too, of course.
For the sake of profit,
you even sacrificed your stepmother.
In this journey,
someone has to be sacrificed.
[3,000 years ago,]
[the opening of nether passageway had
led to the invasion of Dark Nether Race.]
[The human world
turned into a living hell.]
[Human race won a pyrrhic victory.]
[When the Chilan Continent
returned to peace,]
[it was already devastated.]
[Rebuilding of the continent
took thousands of years.]
[300 years ago,]
[the Profound Heaven Alliance
saw that people of this land]
[were scattered around and helpless
under the attack of spirit beasts.]
[They sent the strong ones
here to build the Icestone City.]
[And they made a peace treaty
with The Master of Frost]
[to return peace to the people.]
[Those strong ones
built the Luminous Pillar]
[on the roof of Xingyun Pavilion's hall.]
[It let the starlight
to guide people home.]
[But the strong ones'
kindness did not stop there.]
[To prevent the Dark Nether Race
from returning,]
[the strong ones injected a powerful
force into the Luminous Pillar.]
[If the Dark Nether Race returns
and northern land falls,]
[people can activate the
power of the Luminous Pillar]
[to destroy the entire Icestone City.]
[The activation of Luminous Pillar]
[is to let them die with the enemies
when their combat forces are drained.]
[To let them avoid torture]
[and save their dignity.]
[This is the strong ones'
love for the weaklings.]
[This is the final compassion
given by the strong ones.]
The activation of Luminous Pillar
requires the combination
of thunder and starlight.
Two spiritual forces as one.
According to the
Icestone City's ancestral rule,
the star and cloud were close once.
It actually has two meanings.
The first meaning is
the activation of Luminous Pillar requires
the combination of two spiritual forces.
The second meaning is
the master and the vice master
need to keep this secret together.
As for
the light could break
the sincerest friendship,
it expresses the strong ones' sadness
towards the destruction of Icestone City.
To conceal the truth that Soul
Reaping Beast did not die by my hand,
all those who know must die.
I deliberately appointed the
presumptuous Pu Jiao to set up the trap.
so that Qin Lie and Du Shao Yang
could see through it.
But Qin Lie was too kind,
he underestimated Du Shao Yang's ruthless.
Since they have turned against each other,
a battle between the two is inevitable.
Luminous Bead's power,
combined with Qin Lie's thunder energy,
the entire Icestone City and them
will be annihilated.
We're done.
Gong Mu Lie?
What happened?
It's you.
It was you who wanted
to destroy Icestone City.
I wanted you two to kill each other.
I didn't expect that
I almost made a huge mistake.
What huge mistake?
What exactly is going on?
I want you both dead.
Because you both are
too difficult to control.
I can't just kill you for no reason.
So I manipulated you
into killing each other.
Every time you were
in a difficult situation,
you somehow made a breakthrough
and grew stronger.
I was afraid that you can't beat him,
so I gave you the Luminous Bead
for you to strengthen your power.
I didn't expect that your battle
would generate such great force
that almost destroyed
the entire Icestone City.
It was you who stopped
this force of destruction.
Yes.
After your battle,
you two actually skipped a
level and rose to a new class.
One is on the pinnacle of
the Natal Opening Realm.
The other is on the early level
of the Manifestation Realm.
You are both very talented indeed.
It's easy to kill you,
but it would be such a waste to do so.
It's better to foster your talents
and get you to work for me in future.
The death of Blacksmith Hua is
Pu Jiao's presumptuous
move to start the rivalry.
By the time I found out,
the damage was already done.
I don't trust you.
What about my stepmother?
I asked Pu Jiao to kill some
warriors of Xingyun Pavilion.
I didn't expect he would misunderstand me.
In order to claim credit,
he killed Gao Huang'er.
I don't believe you.
So what if you don't believe me?
If I want to kill you,
I can do it very easily.
What are you trying to do?
Do you know about the Dark Nether Race
from the netherworld?
There are five dark tribes.
Among them, Horned Demon Tribe
have been residing
in the depths of the netherworld
underneath our Chilan Continent.
I only allowed Pu Jiao to
go on his own ways this time
because I have more
important things on hand.
Three days ago, the Horned Demon Tribe
launched an attack suddenly.
The battle with the netherworld
comes every 30 years.
It has become a routine over
the past thousands of years.
But it's only been 17 years this time,
the Dark Nether Race
has launched the attack.
Something is wrong.
At first light, I'll go to the
nether passageway in Purple Mist Sea
to take control of the situation.
This matter concerns the survival
of the entire Chilan Continent.
If you want,
you can come with me.
If you don't want to,
you can go your separate ways now.
But the war is in a dire situation now.
All forces across the world,
from the Red Copper Class
to the Bluestone Class,
as well as some party-less
independent cultivator
are going to Purple Mist Sea.
Even the Artefact Forging Sect,
who doesn't involve in worldly affairs
has sent Master Mo Hai
to lead the team personally.
Master Mo Hai?
What's the matter?
You want to recruit us?
Sure.
But only on one condition.
You're trying to negotiate with me?
Let's hear it.
Arrange a meeting with
Master Mo Hai for us.
You guys want to enter
Artefact Forging Sect?
Yes.
Fine.
But whether you can
win Master Mo Hai's favour,
you'll have to rely on your fate.