[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 10]
Pu Jiao is a petty man.
When he learned that Young Master and I
helped Saintess hunt down
the Soul Reaping Beast,
he got jealous
and tried to drive a wedge
between Young Master and me.
Both of us secretly set a trap,
with the intention of catching Pu Jiao.
Little did we know,
we still fell into his trap.
Po Jiao is sly.
He instigated
a fight between Qin Lie and me.
Somehow,
the energy of the Luminous Pillar
was triggered,
and the entire Icestone City
was almost destroyed.
Luckily, Saintess Song
got there in the nick of time,
otherwise Icestone City
would've been ruined.
And this is the chronology
of the whole incident.
I didn't know
that Pu Jiao could be so sly.
Luckily, Saintess Song
came to the rescue in time,
otherwise,
the aftermath would be horrible.
I've executed Pu Jiao.
After all, it was me who sent him here.
I also have to bear the responsibility
for Mistress' misfortune.
No, no.
You have avenged Mistress.
Thank you for your grace,
Saintess of Profound Heaven Alliance.
Please rise.
Do you have any other questions?
Since the truth has come to light,
we don't have any questions now.
The Horned Demon Race has invaded,
I'll set out to Purple Mist Sea
at first light tomorrow.
Qin Lie, Du Shao Yang,
come with me first.
Master Du, after the funeral
is taken care of,
deploy immediately.
Li Zhong Zheng and Lu Li,
go back and inform your master
to standby.
Yes.
That must be tough for you
to cover up such a big lie
for Song Ting Yu.
But the Horned Demon Race
has invaded.
For the greater good,
this is the only thing we can do.
General situation is one of the reasons.
Another reason
is to meet Master Mo Hai
from Artefact Forging Sect.
At the end of the day,
Du Shao Yang and I are just the same.
We're selfish.
When facing someone with such strength,
we have no other choice
but to obey her.
Besides, we also wanted
to negotiate with her using your
credit for killing the Soul Reaping Beast
in exchange for an opportunity
to get into Artefact Forging Sect.
Although the plan has changed,
we still achieved our motive.
We earned this opportunity
from Uncle Hua's death.
Now,
I'm not on par with Song Ting Yu yet,
but I will definitely claim justice
for Uncle Hua.
You'll depart to Purple Mist Sea tomorrow.
It's even closer
to the centre of Chilan Continent.
I wonder how the sky
looks over there.
I'll tell you after I come back.
Don't come back
and don't stop.
Follow your own footsteps
and go even higher
and further.
Yu Shi,
if I can go to a higher and further point,
and look at the sky full of stars,
I'll come back and take you there with me.
I promise.
I will definitely take you
around the world,
watch all the moon and stars.
I will take you
to see all the sceneries of the world.
I...
I'll wait for you.
Tomorrow, I'm going to Qisha Valley
with Brother Li.
I heard
that it is scenic too.
I also promise
that if there's a chance in the future,
I'll definitely take you
to visit Qisha Valley.
Sure.
By the way,
regarding Li Zhong Zheng,
watch out for him.
I have a feeling that he's up to no good.
Lu Li will look out for him,
I'm not worried.
You've always been slow to catch on.
How did you find out?
Li Zhong Zheng is obviously a bad guy,
it's not hard to tell.
I meant Lu Li.
What's wrong with Lu Li?
I'm going to visit Gao Yu.
I'll go with you.
Recently,
I always feel
that something is wrong with Gao Yu.
He was brought up by his sister,
now that misfortune fell upon her,
he's definitely devastated.
Go take a rest first,
I'll go by myself.
Gao Yu.
I want to be alone.
Is what you told Qin Lie true?
I know I won't be able
to hide it from you,
but please stop asking, father.
I'm not supposed to tell.
First of all, it is Saintess Song's order.
Second of all, if you know too much,
I'm afraid
you'll be dragged into the mess.
But rest assured, Father.
I will definitely
avenge Stepmother.
Regarding the revenge,
you can put it aside for now.
We should keep our priorities straight.
You going to Purple Mist Sea
with Saintess Song,
that's the priority.
I will definitely seize this opportunity.
What's the matter?
Tell me.
Back then,
did you really think
that I got drunk
because I was feeling dejected?
If you want me to believe it,
then I will.
I will play along with you two
and see what you're going to do.
Us two?
I've long noticed
you and Qin Lie
exchanging glances.
I really can't hide anything from you.
Since someone's trying to act smart,
then I'll act a fool.
I've never taken you for a fool.
I'm talking about Pu Jiao.
The trip to Purple Mist Sea
will be rough.
Apart from Saintess Song,
you should be even more alert to Qin Lie.
Don't take him as a friend.
Because Qin Lie
will never be your friend.
Yes, father.
Qin Lie!
[Xingyun Pavilion]
Do you believe in what happened before?
No.
Do you believe it?
I will never believe it.
Under the Luminous Pillar,
Song Ting Yu obviously
wanted to kill us there.
But I can't figure out
as to why she suddenly changed her mind.
And now she wants me to believe her,
that is impossible.
As for Uncle Hua and your
stepmother's death,
she is definitely involved.
Then do you believe in the Nether War?
It's a great deal,
she certainly won't lie about it.
Before we set out,
there's something that I have to ask you.
Before this, we were enemies,
and then allies.
At the end, I betrayed you.
Now we'll fight side by side. We...
I have a sense of priority.
For the well-being of Chilan Continent
and meeting Master Mo Hai,
I can put our personal issues
behind for now.
I can even work with you.
Okay.
Now you can keep all our issues
in your mind first.
Of course I will.
If I don't,
you will do it too.
You're right.
One day,
we will eventually put an end
to all our issues.
Uncle Li.
Let's talk tomorrow. It is closed now.
Aren't the doors
still open?
I like to leave the door open
even when the business is closed, alright?
Uncle Li,
I've come to bid farewell to you.
The Nether War has started.
I'm going to Purple Mist Sea Battlefield.
To be a cannon fodder?
Are you saying
that you purposely came to bid farewell
because you're going off to die?
Do we know each other so well?
I appreciate your reminder before this,
so I came here to thank you.
I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
Hold on.
Take this with you.
It might come in handy.
Go home and practice.
What is it for?
[Two pieces of mud crystals]
Forging artefact.
Forging artefact?
Two pieces of mud crystal,
four catties of golden sand,
one piece of black marble
and five catties of black iron.
What are these?
The list of materials for making
Terminator Profound Bombs.
Terminator Profound Bomb?
What is that?
Something explosive.
It packs quite a punch.
It's all there in the recipe.
Go back and study it.
If you manage to create it,
you can blow up whoever you want.
But do keep this in mind,
you must be careful.
Don't blow yourself up.
Thank you, Uncle Li.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Then I shall leave now.
Go on.
Terminator Profound Bomb.
Father,
Yu Shi sent us a letter.
Open and read it now.
Father,
a letter from Purple Mist Sea.
Mayhem in the battlefield.
[Xingyun Pavilion
was ordered to join the war.]
[Qin Lie is also involved in it.]
[The cause of Uncle Hua's death
has come to light.]
[It wasn't Du Shao Yang who did it,]
[but please forgive me for not being able
to tell you the truth.]
[Recently, my fire poison has flared up,]
[Li Zhong Zheng is planning
to take me back to Qisha Valley]
[to get rid of fire poison.]
[Apart from that,
Zhong Zheng also sent a message,]
[Xuan Xuan has to return
to Qisha Valley at once,]
[must not disobey the order.]
No, no.
She can't tell the truth?
Yu Shi knows what to do.
There must be a story behind this.
Have faith in Yu Shi and Qin Lie.
Qin Lie is going to aid the
Profound Heaven Alliance in battle.
Yu Shi has also become
the disciple of Qisha Valley.
These are good news. Good news.
These are good news indeed, Xuan Xuan.
Since your master
is asking you to go back,
then you should depart without delay.
Father, I am sorry.
I wanted to wait until Yu Shi comes back
before I leave.
I didn't expect that...
Loose ends must be tied up.
The truth must be known.
Only then will you be at peace.
Otherwise, what's the point of living?
I understand.
Being a disciple of Qisha Valley
was supposed to bring glory
to the Ling family.
But now I'm going against
my master's order
and leave Qisha Valley without permission.
I...
I'll say the same thing.
Whatever means the most to you,
then you should go after it.
Xuan Xuan,
don't worry.
I will take good care of Master.
But, promise me,
give yourself a time limit.
When the time has come,
whether you find him or not,
you have to come back.
Xuan Xuan,
sorry,
I can't go there with you.
Winter is coming.
We have to reconstruct the houses
which were destroyed
by the Soul Reaping Beast.
Thank you.
If Qin Lie can come back alive,
Yu Xin can do it too.
Yu Xin said he won't leave me
his entire life.
I didn't ask him to die.
How can he die?
He's definitely hiding
because he's afraid
that I'll scold him and beat him.
I have to find him.
The ice field is freezing.
As an outlander,
he must be suffering a lot.
I'm afraid
I won't have the heart to leave,
so I can't look straight into your eyes.
No matter where and when,
I will keep you in my heart,
and take care of my own safety.
I'm leaving.
Thirty li south is Purple Mist City.
[Purple Mist City]
To the southeast of Purple Mist City
is the boundless sea.
[Purple Mist Sea]
The sea surface is surrounded
by purple mist all year round
due to the transpiration
of purple seaweed,
hence the name, Purple Mist Sea.
In the western mountains
of Purple Mist City
lies the only nether passageway
in the Chilan Continent.
If you want to pass this passage,
we need to pass through Purple Mist City.
There are nine gates and thirteen camps,
[Frontline Fortress]
a total of 22 barriers
in Purple Mist City.
The most heroic warriors of the human race
are stationed inside.
The south, north and west sides
of the campsite
are full of towering
and unreachable ridges.
The cliffs and the ground are planted
with Demon Purifying Grass
which can purify demonic energy.
Purple Mist Sea
is an important bastion against
the Nether tribe.
Right now, the warlord
guarding the nine gates and 13
camps of Frontline Fortress
is Xie Zhi Zhang
[Xie Zhi Zhang]
of the Eight Extremes Temple.
Upon death, the Dark Nether Race
turned into shadows,
leaving an indelible mark on the land.
The shadows contain Nether energy
and must be cleansed
with Demon Purifying Grass.
Lord Xie,
Saintess Song is here.
We're cleaning up the battlefield.
This place is a mess.
I suggest you retire back
to Purple Mist City, Saintess.
How many soldiers did they send?
There were 300 of suicide corps.
How many casualties do we have?
Five hundred.
The enemy sent 300 soldiers
and we have 500 casualties.
For the past five years,
it was Saintess Xie who led us
in the Nether War.
But now Saintess Xie
is nowhere to be found.
Despite your lack of experience
in leading battles,
you questioned me as soon
as you arrived.
I'm afraid I can't answer you.
I've fought the Dark Nether Race
since I was nine.
How dare you say that I lack experience?
From what I hear,
you only stood guard
in Frontline Fortress
among a legion of soldiers.
That's not much of an experience.
Xie Zhi Zhang,
are you disdaining Saintess Song
for her young age?
Saintess Xie is young too,
but I've never disdained her.
That's because you're Saintess Xie's
second uncle!
That's because
every time Saintess Xie came here,
she'd ask about
the well-being of the soldiers,
not making accusations!
Saintess Song, please help yourself.
Don't just stand there!
Get to work!
Xie Zhi Zhang is ungrateful.
Shut up.
Ungrateful people
are just what I like.
You shut up, too.
Uncle Liang, stay here.
Both of you, come with me.
Saintess Song,
where are we going?
Don't you wish to meet Master Mo Hai?
The armoury hall is right ahead.
Master Mo Hai is the top armourer
of the continent.
I heard he has a bad temper.
I heard that he is harsh
and slanderous.
Some people also say that he is weird,
strict and arrogant.
Those are just rumours.
This blade is meant for attacking,
but it's made of magnetic stone.
-Wait.
-Defending while attacking is good.
Unfortunately, you've added water crystals
which counteracted the magnetic stone.
You used common level materials
and made a machete fit only
for outlanders.
Why bother fixing it?
Just get rid of it.
My blade!
[Lian Rou, Artefact Forging Sect]
Take it.
Thank you, thank you.
[Mo Hai, Artefact Forging Sect]
Little Ting Yu, you're here.
Dismiss.
Greetings, Master Mo Hai.
It's been so many years
since I last saw you.
Master, they are Qin Lie
and Du Shao Yang.
The young men who helped you
hunt down the Soul Reaping Beast.
I'm deeply grateful
for your help in this battle.
This time, the Nether tribe
made a surprise attack,
we were caught off guard.
Besides, it's your first time
leading a war.
How can I not come?
Must we go there?
She died.
We saw it with our own eyes.
I've fought her since I was young.
I can't be more familiar
with her scent.
She's certainly still alive
and staying around us.
How do you know
that we'll find her if we put to sea?
I'm sure we will.
She'll be waiting for me over there.
[There's no need to hide.
I saw it already.]
[I really don't understand
what's so interesting about it.]
[Of course you don't,
because you don't care.]
[Guess where I went.]
[Purple Mist Sea Battlefield.]
[Really?]
[So be it.]
[Father promised me]
[that I can also go to the battlefield]
[after I turn nine years old.]
[I went there one year earlier than you.]
[I'm only eight years old now.]
[Besides,
Eight Extremes Temple has decided]
[that I'll be the future commander
of the Nether War.]
[Apart from that,]
[I sailed.]
[It's the most beautiful]
[and mysterious Purple Mist Sea.]
[Are you envious?]
[Don't worry. If there's a chance,]
[I'll take you with me.]
[We'll sail to the middle of the
Purple Mist Sea]
[and admire the view there.]
[For real?]
[Yes.]
It's been so long.
Do you miss me?
Escaped by faking your own death.
What kind of mission
has Eight Extremes Temple assigned to you?
Now I know
why you didn't blow my cover
when you saw me behind Luminous Pillar.
So you have a misunderstanding.
I faked my death
because I don't want
to be a Saintess any more.
I want to fall in love with someone
and keep my nose clean.
What?
As the commander in chief,
you faked your death
for love and personal desire.
Do you still care about the life
of the people on the continent?
How dare you judge me?
Aren't you just the same?
You only think about that man all day
and even carry that thing with you.
Give it back to me!
So, the large figure standing
under the Luminous Pillar
of Xingyun Pavilion that night
really was Gong Mu Lie?
You saw him too.
That night, only Qin Lie and Du Shao Yang
were on the rooftop.
Are you suspecting that one of them
is Gong Mu Lie?
That's impossible.
They're not worthy enough.
Then are you suspecting
that Gong Mu Lie actually showed himself
or projected his consciousness
on one of them?
So you changed your mind,
spared them
and kept them by your side
just to find the answer?
Do you think it is possible?
It's likely to be Qin Lie,
but not Du Shao Yang.
Although Du Shao Yang is handsome
and ambitious,
he always made the wrong decisions.
If I were Gong Mu Lie,
I wouldn't choose
someone with such bad luck.
However, Qin Lie
always does the impossible.
He is more suspicious.
When you said
you want to fall in love with a man,
you meant Du Shao Yang, right?
That's why you told me to count him out.
If you dare lay a hand on him,
I won't let you off.
Won't let me off?
I'll report you to the
Eight Extremes Temple right now.
Let's see if you can run away from it.
One day,
Eight Extremes Temple will find out.
You betrayed Eight Extremes Temple,
let's see what you got yourself into.
I know I can't escape from it.
I also know that that day
will come sooner or later.
But before that day comes,
I want to fall in love.
Whether punishment or death awaits me,
I will not regret it.
Xie Jing Xuan,
I can keep it a secret for you,
as long as you tell me
if there's any good way
to deal with the Nether War.
Of course there is.
I've led battles in the Netherworld
for many years,
so I have plenty of ideas.
However, I won't tell you.
I will tell Du Shao Yang.
So, if you want to win this war,
be nice to him.
You're childish.
I'm telling you,
the Purple Mist Sea is my battlefield now.
Don't throw it into chaos.
You want to search for clues from Qin Lie,
but you don't know men well enough,
whereas Qin Lie hates you to the core.
Where do you even start?
Cast a love spell on him,
and he will be yours.
[Qisha Valley]
Is this Qisha Valley?
Qisha Valley is located
in the hinterland of Chilan Continent,
it has the most pleasant weather.
It's so much better than the North
where you're from.
The North is dry and cold,
it's not cosy and warm like this place.
Even the sun is brighter.
I really don't understand why some people
don't appreciate
the beauty of Qisha Valley
and like the frosty North?
Such poor taste.
If we go further,
we'll arrive at Water Valley.
Yiyuan Pond
in Water Valley
is a holy place for cultivating
water spirit art.
You will practice here from now on.
Let's go see Master first.
[Jiu Liu Yu, Master of Qisha Valley]
Master,
Yu Shi's fire poison...
Among the two daughters
of the Ling family,
one has fiery passion,
another one has water-like gentleness.
Good.
A disease needs time to be cured,
you will eventually recover.
Take this elixir and drink it.
Practice well in the future.
Thank you, Master.
Take her to settle in.
Yes, Master.
Miss Yu Shi, please come with me.
You stay here.
Tell Master what happened
in Xingyun Pavilion.
From now on, you will stay here.
The Heavenly Water Spirit Record
is a high-level water spirit art.
Using water as the source
of spiritual power,
it can cleanse you as well as
any living being.
When training, use this method
to perceive and refine
the water element in Yiyuan Pond.
Purify and absorb it
with your spiritual power.
Then the poison will be cured.
Thank you, Brother Li.
From now on, we'll be a family.
You don't have to be so polite with me.
Your hands...
Why are they so cold?
Li Zhong Zheng!
Master wants to ask you something.
Make yourself home.
Hey, don't you seduce my brother.
I won't seduce your brother.
I wanted to advise you
to keep an eye on him.
To go beyond is as wrong as to fall short.
If you bare your soul to a man,
he might be stressed out.
You're one to talk.
Come in.
Mister Du, your breakfast is here.
Didn't we agree
that all of us
will have breakfast together?
You?
How did you get in here?
This is Purple Mist Sea.
It's a battlefield.
Did you think this is Icestone City?
Mister Du,
Master Mo Hai is asking for you.
Alright, I got it.
You...
Ting Yu must've brought you here
to become my apprentices.
I just happen
to be in need of two helpers.
Your wish is our command.
I need someone
to be in charge of my daily meals,
and someone to run errands
and send my messages.
Choose one yourselves.
Don't like it?
I'll take charge of your daily meals.
Tang Si Qi, you...
There are many people during the day,
come back at night.
Leave now.
Go.
Why did you invite me over for dinner?
After inviting you,
I'll invite Du Shao Yang over as well.
I want to talk to both of you alone
and get to know you better.
After all, we are comrades
on the battlefield.
Comrades?
Du Shao Yang also said the same thing.
Why does this word
sound so odd when both of you said it?
Don't you ever think
that covering me up
in front of Du Hai Tian and Li Zhong Zheng
means you have the goods on me.
I can take your life anytime.
Just do it.
Why are we still eating?
Are you eating or not?
If you don't, I'll eat first.
Just ask me whatever you want.
I'll go to bed after dinner.
Come in.
What are you doing?
I made them myself.
Sit down and have a try.
How can I finish them?
You don't have to finish them.
Tell me which one you like,
so that I know your preference.
After this,
I'll cook dishes that you like.
Go on and try it.
Is it good?
That night,
we didn't perform the wedding ritual.
I didn't ask you.
Why are you telling me this?
Why didn't you ask me
how I got in here?
You're right.
How did you get in here?
Because they were short-staffed,
and I happen to know how to cook.
Purple Mist City
is the first barrier
to the Nether Battlefield.
There will be layers of inspection.
It's impossible for people
without any sectarian status to enter.
Who exactly are you?
What is your purpose of approaching me?
I'm a woman who's blindly in love.
A woman can do anything
for the man she loves.
I'm approaching you
because I like you.
Tang Si Qi.
I'm telling you,
I'm not interested in women.
Woman is not an interest,
woman is man's need,
an essential feeling.
Without feelings,
you'll feel incomplete
no matter how much you get.
Then, after I get what I want,
I'll come get you, alright?
Du Shao Yang,
on such a quiet night,
you and I are sitting face to face,
exchanging words in soft, gentle tones.
Delightful,
isn't it?
If you really care about me,
get out of here at once.
If you stay here,
you will distract me,
my future will be destroyed.
I did not come here
to destroy your future.
I'm here to help.
Would you like to know
how to wipe out the Nether tribe
and earn Song Ting Yu's favour?
Your cooking is not bad,
but it can't be compared
to Yu Shi's cooking.
So, haven't you figured out
what you want to ask?
You...
Thank you Saintess for your meal.
Excuse me.
You...
Qin Lie!
You really don't care about me, do you?
Then just ask me.
I've been asking you,
and you never said anything.
When I said I wanted to leave,
you lost your temper.
Why is your mood so unpredictable?
How dare I not care about you?
[Cast a love spell on him,]
[and he will be yours.]
Qin Lie.
[He is actually]
[you.]
[How did you]
[counter my attack?]
Saintess Song.
Saintess.
You...
[Why did I get countered?]
[It shouldn't be possible.]