[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 19]
Lian Rou, there is a
lot of demon aura here.
It's all demon aura out there too.
There is no way out.
It's the scent of Demon Purifying Grass.
This is a Demon Cleansing Pill
made from the Demon Purifying Grass.
But the efficacy of this pill
won't last for long.
How can there be
so much demon aura in
the Artefact Forging Sect?
The master has ordered a retreat.
Let's talk about this on our way out.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Oh, Gong Mu Shan,
why didn't you tell us
everything 700 years ago?
You only said half of it.
What do you mean the
Artefact Forging Sect can't be tainted?
You didn't make it clear.
And look at how things have turned out.
The time hadn't come back then.
I couldn't say it.
So the time has come now?
If it hadn't come,
I wouldn't have let my grandson
pull out the Spiritual Lines Pillar.
I think I understand
what you are trying to do.
I can feel that
in a short time,
the God Race will return.
And when that happens,
the Spirit Realm will turn into
a battlefield again.
Since the time has come,
I'm afraid that if we
don't do something early,
it would be too late by then.
But this is a risky move.
My friend, no matter how smart you are,
you're not infallible,
there is no guarantee that there
won't be any unforeseen problems.
There's always risk
in getting things done.
As long as the most important purpose
is served, it's fine.
Your precious grandson
has fallen into the Nether Realm.
Aren't you worried he might
get eaten by nether beasts?
Good fall.
Mang Wang, go.
[Mang Wang]
Go!
Song Si Yuan, I want to see Chief Song.
Si Yuan, go and invite him again.
Yes.
Forget it.
He called himself a Master?
More like a coward.
He has probably run away in fear
with his tail between his legs.
I'm here, I'm here.
I, Xie Yi, apologise for being late.
Forgive me for keeping everyone waiting.
Sorry.
Please forgive me.
-Master Xie,
-I'm sorry.
I, Song Yu, am not
trying to shirk my responsibility.
I've explained
this matter to Master Ying.
Everything that happened before,
I know nothing about it.
But
we are not shirking our responsibility.
Now...
I, Xie Yi, know that I've made a mistake.
I've made a mistake!
You're a Master.
Please get up, get up now.
I'm guilty, I shouldn't get up.
Because of my
recklessness and belligerence,
I have made a huge mistake.
I still regret it.
I'm here to accept my punishment.
Please punish me, Chief Song.
And of course, Eight Extremes Temple
is now under your command, Chief Song.
People say Xie Yi is a lunatic.
How are you crazy?
Now that you're kneeling like this,
what else can I do with you?
Lang Xie.
I'm filled with deep regret.
My heart aches.
I'm willing to accept any
punishment, Chief Song.
700 years ago,
the Sage forbade us from encroaching
on the Artefact Forging Sect.
Turns out it was because of the
nether passageway located
beneath the Spiritual Lines Hall.
I believe that these
12 Spiritual Lines Pillars
were also placed by the Sage
to seal the passage.
I, Song Yu, have no way of knowing
why he didn't tell the truth back then,
which led to the accident today.
Master Xie and I
are to be blamed for what happened today.
I didn't know the five great sects
would launch an attack.
You didn't know? Really?
Just passing the blame to others easily.
Lang Xie,
the opening of nether passageway
isn't just a threat to
the Artefact Forging Sect,
but it threatens the
whole Chilan Continent.
Why don't we set aside
our differences for now
and fight together against the enemy?
Well said.
Master Ying...
No, the current leader is still Qin Lie.
But unfortunately, Master Qin
has fallen into the Abyss.
It's unknown
whether he's still alive or not.
Master Ying,
to me,
you're the only leader, Master Ying.
I feel the same way, Master Ying.
You mustn't, you mustn't.
Master Ying, what about Master Xie?
He is forgiven.
Please get up, get up.
Master Ying, your heart
is as vast as the ocean.
I'm truly impressed.
It's nothing.
Master Ying,
now that the nether
passageway is wide open,
not to mention that the Dark Nether Race
could flood into the realm,
the biggest crisis right now
is the spread of the demon aura.
Master Ying, do you have
a plan to deal with this?
This is a Demon Cleansing Pill.
Refine it and absorb
it into your spirit court.
It would help you to resist
the demon aura for a while.
Next,
I'll need everybody's help to
plant this Demon Purifying Grass
in every corner of Firetop Mountain,
in order to prevent the
demon aura from getting out.
Also, the nether beasts that
came out with the demon aura,
need to be eliminated as soon as possible.
Brilliant plan, Master Ying.
Given the critical situation,
the Horned Demon army of
the Nether Realm may attack at any time.
We, the Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple,
will do everything in
our power to fight them
and protect everyone's safety.
However...
Chief Song,
you're trying to ask
if the Artefact Forging Sect
has any weapon that can
help the resistance, aren't you?
Of course we have.
Master Mo Hai is our most powerful weapon.
But you people
just murdered his wife.
Who killed her?
We'll deal with this matter later.
Master!
I said, we'll deal with this matter later.
Chief Song,
Saintess Song showed up
in the Artefact Forging Sect
again for some reason.
And she has fallen into
the Abyss with Qin Lie.
How do you plan to rescue her, Chief Song?
[Forest in the Abyss]
Qin Lie?
Show yourself.
[Kun Sen]
Human race.
The Horned Demons are comparable to
Netherpassage Realm human cultivators.
[What are you fighting for?]
[For the glory of the
Profound Heaven Alliance?]
[For the safety of Chilan Continent?]
[No.]
[What are you fighting for then?]
[For Gong Mu Lie.]
What a powerful weapon.
It has the same ability
to invade one's mind
like Soul Reaping Beast.
Thank you for your Demon Cleansing Pill.
What about you?
I'm a Netherpassage Realm cultivator.
Mind your own business.
Have you seen Yu Shi?
I got separated from her.
I haven't seen her.
You're wounded.
I'm fine.
Why did you hide it?
A saintess doesn't have
the right to be injured?
Now that we're trapped here,
and there's no way to find out
what's going on up there now,
let go of your pride as a saintess.
Yu Shi!
Qin Lie?
Qin Lie!
I'm here!
Yu Shi!
Qin Lie.
Why are you following me?
Where are you going to find Yu Shi?
The Abyss
is as large as the Chilan Continent.
How are you going to find her
in this vast Nether Realm?
Why do I always fail to protect her
at a critical moment like this?
Qin Lie, don't blame yourself.
I'm right here with you.
What's the use of losing your temper now?
The priority now is to find a way out
and protect ourselves.
If you find Ling Yu Shi,
and she falls into the hands
of the Horned Demons,
you'll still be able to protect her.
Qin Lie,
I'm going to give you two options now.
First, pull yourself together.
Kill our way out together
once we find the exit.
Second, I'll kill you now,
before you attract the attention
of the Horned Demons
and put me in danger.
Why is your blood
purple?
The demon aura.
Cultivators who have reached the
Netherpassage Realm and higher
are capable of resisting demon aura.
But if you are injured,
the demon aura will enter
your body through your blood.
You gave me the last Demon Cleansing Pill.
In that case,
our only option is to find a way out now.
You're not going to look for
Ling Yu Shi anymore?
Of course I'll keep looking for her.
But you are being attacked
by the demon aura now,
you won't be able to
hang in there for long.
I'll get you out of here first.
This Thought Breaking Crystal
contains the Horned Demons' memories
of the battle of Purple Mist Sea.
You can use it to find
the way to Purple Mist Sea.
Why me?
Why don't you do it?
When one is absorbing the
Thought Breaking Crystal,
he will need to reach
a state of selflessness.
Your senses will be shut down,
you won't be able to move or speak.
If I let you stand guard
while I absorb it,
when the Dark Nether Race attacks,
both of us won't be able to survive.
Although I'm poisoned by the demon aura,
my strength is still
much stronger than you.
Therefore, it's safer for
us to let me stand guard.
You once said
you're better than me.
You were right.
You can help him ascend
to a new realm so easily.
Qin Lie,
maybe she is the one
who can help you to go higher and further.
What's wrong?
I keep feeling that someone is beside me.
I think I hear Yu Shi talking to me.
Qin Lie,
I'm right here.
If it's meant to be, you'll
find each other eventually.
If it's not,
then that's it.
Qin Lie, wait for me.
Qin Lie.
You're awake.
Who are you?
[Zhao Xi]
I'm Zhao Xi. What's your name?
Ling Yu Shi.
You were dreaming just now.
Dreaming?
Am I dead?
It's the Nightmare Crystal.
Nightmare Crystal?
This place is different
from your human world.
Just like this place,
the Nightmare Valley,
where Nightmare Crystal
can be found everywhere.
When you are unconscious,
if your beloved one calls you softly,
Nightmare Crystal will
help you to come back.
You'll be able to return
to your loved one's side.
I was with him just now,
and yet I'm here now.
I couldn't see my own body,
I was just an apparition.
Actually
you've been here this whole time.
What you saw
is the reality
reflected by the Nightmare Crystal.
They left.
I wanted to go after them,
but no matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't.
They?
He wasn't alone?
She was nice to him.
She would rather die
than kill him.
Someone came between you two?
Maybe
it's me who have come
between them from the beginning.
If you like him, go after him.
Don't give up.
If you love him, then try to let go.
Otherwise, you'll be miserable.
I surprised you, didn't I?
We Heaven Race know a thing
or two about relationships too.
You belong to the Nether tribe.
Don't be afraid, I won't hurt you.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have saved you.
[Human race?]
Aren't you afraid your
people will find out?
I am.
That's why I took the
hidden path on my way back.
I took a big detour
to avoid crowded areas.
This is your house?
It's a bit shabby, isn't it?
Don't worry, I'm not going to hurt you.
Black Gold Vines
were abundant in the nearby valley.
But they were all used by
nether beasts to build nests.
I'll steal some back later
to make a bed for you.
That way you'll have a bed to rest.
I think I can understand now
why you people are
determined to go to the land above.
It's just that
why do you have to go to
war against the human race?
Wouldn't it be better
to skip the bloodshed and live in harmony?
It's you human race who...
What?
Nothing.
The Nether Crystal
is a treasure of the Nether Realm.
I heard from the older
generation of the tribe
that there used to be
a lot of nether crystals.
Even the flowers that bloomed on
the trees were nether crystal flowers.
They shone brightly
throughout the Nether Realm.
As the war went on and on later,
the strong ones consumed
too much of the crystals for cultivation,
which caused the crystals
to become less and less,
while the Nether Realm
became darker as well.
Without the daylight,
it's always night here.
Zhao Xi,
thank you.
Are you really a human race?
Why
are your hair and eyes purple?
Are you sick?
I don't know.
Probably because I've been tainted
by the demon aura.
I've seen humans tainted
by demon aura before.
They didn't look like this.
You look quite
tired and weak.
Get some rest.
I'll go get you a glass of water now.
I heard that people on the ground
can wash their faces
and bodies with water,
is it true?
Water is precious here.
We can only get one glass per day.
I'll go get my water for today.
You mustn't go anywhere.
[Why]
[is your blood purple?]
[The demon aura.]
[Cultivator of Netherpassage Realm
and above]
[is capable of resisting demon aura.]
[But if you are injured,]
[the demon aura will enter
your body through your blood.]
[I've seen humans tainted
by demon aura before.]
[They didn't look like this.]
[I can only use my power to
suppress the demon aura for now.]
The passageway has
been open for a long time,
but so far the Dark Nether Race
hasn't struck yet.
The longer they wait,
the worse it could be.
A storm is brewing.
This nether passageway
was opened suddenly,
it probably took the
Dark Nether Race by surprise too.
But the nether beasts that
ran out from the passageway
are getting stronger.
It's probably part of the
Dark Nether Race's plan.
My guess is that
they must be reorganising
their armed forces at the moment,
attempting to conquer
Chilan Continent in one fell swoop.
Also...
Say it.
About those nether beasts
that rushed out with the demon aura,
a few escaped during the chaos,
they're still missing for now.
I've ordered the sects to
send out their best disciples
to track them down and kill them.
It happened so fast.
I've made the decision
without your permission.
Please punish me, Chief Song.
You are my own brother.
I would never blame you.
I was afraid that the
Artefact Forging Sect
would grow more powerful and
become a disobedient force,
that's why I turned a blind eye
when the five great sects
attacked the Artefact Forging Sect.
I didn't expect
I would have to rely on them in the end.
Brother,
this is obviously that
lunatic Xie Yi's fault.
Even if Xie Yi did nothing,
if they didn't submit to me,
I would still attack them myself.
It'll still end the same way.
We can only blame the Sage from back then.
If he had said everything clearly,
we would not have attacked
the Artefact Forging Sect,
we would've done our
best to keep them safe.
And we would not end
up in this situation today.
No one knows
what the Sage's intention is.
Chief Song.
You keep an eye on that side.
Yes.
Chief Song.
Yi Yuan, what's the situation out there?
Chief,
all the residents of the Armoury City
who inhaled the demon aura
have been placed
in several warehouses in the west.
They are being treated by people of
the Artefact Forging Sect
and Cloud Sky Mountain.
And the whole Armoury City
has been vacated
for the disciples of
various sects to live in,
as a temporary military camp.
Water-Moon Sect,
Crimson Flame Association,
White Camel Mountain and other forces
have also sent their elites
to rush here without delay.
How are the masters of the five sects?
Other than missing a finger,
they are fine.
However,
they were the ones who attacked the
Artefact Forging Sect first,
and they were really rude.
Chief, I'm a citizen of Purple Mist Sea
and a member of the Artefact Forging Sect.
I help both sides and neither side.
They really crossed the line.
So?
So in order to avoid evoking hatred
from the Artefact Forging Sect
and destroying our alliance,
I've sent them back to recuperate.
I've sent someone to look after them.
This way, they won't
come running out again.
You did a great job.
I made the right decision picking you
to be my liaison with the
Artefact Forging Sect.
Thank you, Chief Song.
Has Master Mo Hai started crafting
the Terminator Profound Bombs?
Go and tell Master Mo Hai personally
if there is anything he needs,
I'll do my best to provide to him.
Yes.
Whether we can reseal
this nether passageway,
it's all on him.
Lord Lang Xie.
Shao Yang,
has there been any news
from the disciples of the sects
sent to hunt the escaped nether beasts?
No news at the moment.
My lord, what about Ying Xing Ran?
You'd better called him Master Ying.
Qin Lie is in grave danger.
The position of sect master still
belongs to Ying Xing Ran.
Even the three elders
are trying to boost various disciples'
morale to fight the enemy.
Even the chief of the
Profound Heaven Alliance
and the Master of the
Eight Extremes Temple
have to bow down before him now.
He's now high and mighty.
It's too early for him to get excited.
Qin Lie may be a menace,
but he is an anomaly.
He has escaped death many times.
This time,
I really hope he dies.
But my intuition tells me
that he'll be back.
The fact that you have such an intuition
means that deep down inside,
you still hope he can survive.
Your fate are tied together,
it's inseparable now.
Lord Lang Xie, Shao Yang.
Here comes the upstart of the
Profound Heaven Alliance.
Why are you being so hostile to me?
I'm just an errand boy.
Is Lian Rou in there?
No.
Lian Rou.