[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 20]
Elder,
on behalf of Chief Song and Saintess Xie,
Yi Yuan would like to ask
if you need anything.
Nothing.
Ask Yi Yuan
to send my message to Xie Yi.
How was it?
Elder said there's nothing that he needs,
he just wants you
to send his message to Xie Yi,
tell him to take good care of himself.
I don't think it's a good time to do this.
How is this not a good time?
Should I do it for you?
Xie Yi killed Commander Feng.
It's just a matter of time
before the Bloody Spears and Elder Mo Hai
make him pay the price.
Alright,
send my message to him as well,
tell Saint Xie
to take good care of himself.
Alright,
you should take care of yourself too.
I should leave now.
What are you thinking about?
Some got themselves into trouble,
some are preparing
to fight against Dark Nether Race,
whereas I can only stand guard here.
It's kind of boring.
Really?
You've been staying up
for two days and two nights.
Go back earlier and rest.
Yi Yuan.
I need a favour, but,
keep this between you and me.
Sure.
What is it? Fill me in.
Senior Tang Si Qi
sneaked out early this morning.
She said she wants to rescue
Artefact Forging Sect from the outside.
Senior Si Qi?
Now I know why I haven't seen her lately.
If you can,
try to look into it
in Profound Heaven Alliance
and Eight Extremes Temple.
See if there is any news about her.
However,
you must keep a low profile.
Shao Yang,
do you like her?
Don't ask so many questions.
Alright, I'll look right into it.
I am Ku Luo.
[Ku Luo, Ku Lu]
I am Ku Lu. Who is up there?
Both Mortal Realm and Netherworld
are separated by Earth.
But you've been stirring up a storm.
Aren't you afraid
that you might provoke us,
and we then invade the Netherworld
and exterminate your race?
On what grounds?
On what grounds the humans
get to live on the land
where the sun shines
and the plants grow,
whereas the Horned Demon Race
has to live
in the dark and humid underground
without the sun?
We don't have clean water,
delicious food,
bright and warm sun.
And all these
were supposed to belong to us!
You drove us away!
You killed our people!
Don't try to argue your way out of it.
You still have time to retreat.
However, if you still insist on fighting,
don't blame us
for exterminating the Nether Tribe.
Fight!
-Charge!
Fighters, listen up!
Yes!
The Dark Nether Race
must be killed without mercy!
Kill without mercy!
This seems to be the enemy's camp,
but why aren't the Dark Nether Race
guarding it?
The passageway has been opened.
It's a great opportunity for us
to seize upper hand.
The army should have been summoned
for the war.
Let's get out of here.
Hold on.
Your injury seems severe.
I'm fine.
Even if I was unhurt,
we'll die if we're stuck here.
Let's go.
Look, what do you think about this?
Isn't this even more obvious?
No.
In this kind of harsh environment,
being seriously ill or dying
is a norm to us.
Some people are so ill
that their bodies are festering.
They can only cover themselves up
like this
as not to frighten the children.
Although the nether passageway
has been sealed,
Sky Ladder goes straight to the ground,
that place must be guarded
by strong human beings.
If they see you,
they might actually lift the blockade
and let you go.
You have to follow me closely later.
If anyone asks, don't panic.
I'll take care of it.
Zhao Xi,
if I can make it back alive,
I might actually fight against
your people.
Won't you regret saving me?
As a matter of fact,
I should've killed you
or handed you over
and taken credit for it,
but I couldn't do it.
Ms Yu Shi,
in fact,
the Dark Nether Race that you talked about
is not as evil as you think.
Both parties just happen
to have different goals
and opposite standpoints.
Zhao Xi,
after I go back,
if I meet any Dark Nether Race
who has never harmed human beings,
I will definitely spare his life.
Is she sick?
My sister has abscesses on her face,
so she covers her face up.
Why aren't you resting at home
if you're sick?
Brother, she's terribly ill.
I still have a glass of water unclaimed.
Go get it and give it to her.
Thank you, brother.
I had always been curious
about the life you're living
in the Netherworld.
Us?
We eat human flesh.
It's terrifying.
I scared you, didn't I?
Actually,
although we're of different races,
we share the same nature.
There's not a race
which is absolutely good,
there's not a race
which is absolutely evil.
Ms Yu Shi, are you sure you're fine?
I'm fine.
It's just that
I've breathed in so much demon aura,
but I don't feel uncomfortable at all.
Could you also
be a part of the Dark Nether Race?
That's impossible.
I don't have
the shadow pattern of Shadow Tribe,
nor do I have
the long horns of Horned Demon Race.
Our priestess said,
before we came to the Netherworld,
we didn't look like this.
The men were handsome and dashing,
the women were elegant and beautiful.
We were the most elegant race
in the entire Star Realm.
Star Realm?
I only know that Chilan Continent
and several other continents
are called Spirit Realm as a whole.
What is the Star Realm?
The priestess only told us
that we were brought here
by a powerful venerable
to escape the war.
As for what the Star Realm is,
she didn't say anything.
I think she actually made that up
to comfort us.
There might actually
be a secret behind this.
It's just that the time hasn't come,
so the priestess can't tell you anything.
In fact, I feel like
a secret that I don't know
is lying within me.
But I have a feeling
that this secret will be revealed
in no time.
Your secret
might change everything that you have,
including the man whom you care about.
Are you scared?
I will take it and face it.
There's nothing to be scared of.
Yi Yuan.
How did it go?
I've looked into it.
I didn't find any news about her.
Where on earth is she?
These few days,
I turned the entire Armoury City
upside down
but couldn't find her.
Could she be dead already?
What are you guys talking about,
sneaking around out here?
Lord Lang Xie.
Yi Yuan and I were discussing
about the reason
of Dark Nether Race's sudden retreat.
Exactly.
Yesterday, the mysterious man
came out of nowhere.
The Dark Nether Race kneeled before him
as if he was Evil God.
After that, he went to the Netherworld
with the commander of Dark Nether Race,
and they've been biding their time
since then.
They've been on a stand-off with us
for a day and a night.
They seem to be waiting
for some instructions.
I'm afraid they're deliberately
dragging it on.
The greater the invasion of demon aura,
the greater the loss of our combat power.
We only have limited Demon Purifying Grass
after all.
Yi Yuan,
go and ask Mo Hai
how long
can the remaining Demon Purifying Grass
last us.
Besides that,
ask him about his progress
on the Terminator Profound Bomb.
Affirmative.
Go back and get some sleep now.
If you're still looking tired like this,
I'll throw you into the Netherworld too.
Affirmative.
[Where on earth]
[is this woman hiding?]
Shao Yang!
You have to take your own path.
If you do not want my help
or let me follow you,
I will not go against your will.
But if you miss me,
remember,
I'll be waiting for you
in the pavilion by the lake.
Lake?
Si Qi!
Si Qi.
I'm such an idiot.
[Evil God Mountains]
So this is the Evil God Mountains.
If we want to get
to the Sky Ladder of Purple Mist Sea,
Mountains of Evil God
is the only way there.
Along the road,
there will be more and more
Horned Demons.
[Du Du, Priestess]
This is weird.
These people seem to have come here
to worship something.
What are you thinking about?
Do you still have Gao Yu's
Evil God Ring with you?
My gut tells me they're related somehow.
I'm afraid Artefact Forging Sect
has already fallen.
I wonder how Gao Yu is doing now.
When I fell into the nether passageway,
the ring flew away out of the blue.
I have no idea where it went either.
Only on important days
do we come here,
kowtow and pray for the protection
of the Great God.
But this is weird.
Why is there a worshipping ceremony today?
The holy light shines upon
the heart of the brave.
So many lives have been sacrificed.
It's tearing our hearts out.
The glory of our Great God is still here!
Bless the bamboo tent,
for it shall never fall.
Bless the mountains,
for they shall never collapse.
Bless the Nether River,
for it shall flow eternally.
Bless our holy race,
for it will live forever!
Today,
the Great God Ring which belongs
to the last Great God of our race,
Luo Lin, The Great God,
has finally found its host.
The Great Ring has returned,
the child of Luo Lin, The Great God
has finally been born.
Today,
as soon as the child
of Luo Lin, The Great God
steps onto the altar of Great God,
absorbs and refines all the gifts
of Luo Lin, The Great God,
once again,
our race will have a Great God!
Great God, Great God!
Let's get out of here.
[Qin Lie?]
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Qin Lie?
Qin Lie!
What exactly are you?
Why did you take me here?
Mr Xue Li?
Have you been following me?
Yes, I was protecting you.
Since you fell into the Netherworld,
this little thing came out of nowhere
and entered your body.
You knew that this thing
entered my body long time ago,
but you didn't tell me.
Why should I tell you?
It's not doing you any harm.
Mr Xue Li, this is my body.
Don't worry.
This little thing
is covered in thunder and lightning.
It has the same nature as yours.
It is not harmful but useful to you.
Can't you see?
It brought you here, that's the proof.
This is the thunder pool.
There lies the real core of thunderbolt.
I can feel
that you've perceived
the essence of frost.
The core of thunderbolt
is the essence of thunderbolt.
If you can absorb and grasp it,
you will benefit a lot from it.
The essence of frost
caused my cultivation base
to improve by leaps and bounds.
Now that condensation of Yuan Lake
is approaching,
if I can refine the core of thunderbolt...
Song Ting Yu.
Ling Yu Shi?
How is Qin Lie doing?
I have no idea either.
Clear your mind from distractions!
Absorb it with all your might.
Enter into no-soul or no-self doctrine!
I will guard you!
Run!
Let's go! Run! Run!
Qin Lie, if you give up right now,
not only will your efforts
go down the drain,
you will also lose your mind!
Listen to me!
Just focus and refine
the essence of thunderbolt
that you've absorbed.
Leave the rest to me!
Isn't the Great God supposed
to protect the people?
Qin Lie? He...
Gao Yu?
Mr Xue Li,
is he dead?
I'm not capable of taking his life yet.
Qin Lie!
Yu Shi!
Get out of here first.
Step back!
Do you know Qin Shan?
Qin Shan is my grandfather.
Do you have any proof?
He is my grandfather.
What is there to prove?
Do you know my grandfather?
Did he leave anything for you?
No.
To be exact,
there's an orb inside my head.
Does that count?
The Soul Suppressing Orb?
That's right.
It's Qin Shan, our benefactor's belonging.
It belongs to him?
It was my grandfather
who implanted the Soul Suppressing Orb
inside my head?
My grandfather is a human.
How could he be the benefactor
of the Dark Nether Race?
He had shown us great kindness.
I'll let you off
to repay his kindness.
What did Grandpa Qin Shan do for you?
I guess
you really don't have any idea.
Since he didn't tell you,
I'm in no position to say anything
in case any issue arises.
The horn will be blown three times.
If you're still here by that time,
I will take your lives!
Madam!
Madam, tell me!
Let's go!
-Madam!
-Run!
-Madam, tell me!
Madam!
Yu Shi.
Who are you?
Qin Lie, stop it.
He is Zhao Xi.
He saved my life.
Zhao Xi, what are you doing here?
You left abruptly just now.
I was afraid that you might be in danger,
so I had been tailing you.
Just now, I was hiding somewhere else.
But a gust of strong wind took me up
and brought me here.
This place is far
from the Great God Mountains.
How did we get here in a flash?
It was chaotic at the time,
but the priestess
could tell right away
that she was on our side.
This means she already knew
that we aren't a part of Dark Nether Race.
She has impressive power,
and is definitely a great threat
to the human race.
The priestess
has never killed, she only saves lives.
Don't you...
Ms Yu Shi, thank you.
To you, I'm the Dark Nether Race,
but you...
You also saved me before.
To you,
I'm also from another race.
Zhao Xi,
we're leaving.
Remember me, I'm Zhao Xi.
This magic plant
is a Netherworld Demonic Fruit.
It has never seen the sun, just like me.
After you return to the ground,
can you place it under the sun
and call out my name?
In that way,
I might be able to feel the warmth
of the sun.
If there's a chance,
I'll take you guys to Herb Mountain.
It has ample sunlight.
It's best place
for the magic plants to grow.
I've never seen the sun since I was born,
but if I get to be with the sun
after I die,
I'll be more than happy.
Zhao Xi!
Song Ting Yu, what are you doing?
He was trying to kill me,
didn't you see that?
Zhao Xi,
why did you do that?
When I heard
that you called her Song Ting Yu,
I knew
that she's Saintess Song
from the Profound Heaven Alliance.
Our people died at her hands.
She even killed my father.
Zhao Xi.
Ms Yu Shi,
thank you for remembering
my name.
Zhao Xi.
Obviously,
you were already prepared to attack.
Did you know that he wanted to kill you?
I could see the murderous intent
in his eyes,
but Ling Yu Shi wasn't his target.
If he wanted to kill Ling Yu Shi,
he would've done it long time ago.
That means
his target was either you or me.
I had to do it.
Zhao Xi.
Yu Shi, I'm sorry.
Song Ting Yu,
how did your injury become so serious?
A hundred years ago,
when I entered the nether passageway
for the first time,
it was Uncle Liang who carried me.
When I got up the Sky Ladder
for the first time,
I climbed up by myself.
I was nine years old,
training my strength.
I had climbed for three full months
before I could finally see the sun.
I used to think
that the Sky Ladder was unachievable.
But after going through numerous wars,
I learned that it was not hard at all.
Climbing up Sky Ladder is hard,
but it's nothing compared to guarding it.
Now,
I'm afraid I won't get
to see the sun any more.
We've come this far,
and you're telling me
that you can't make it.
Then why did you drag us into this?
Song Ting Yu, you must get up there.
Don't make me look down on you.
Ling Yu Shi,
I wish to talk to Qin Lie alone.
Can I?
What do you want to say?
Why did you never ask me
the reason why I've been helping you
and protecting you?
Why?
Because I always have someone in my heart.
I know.
It's Gong Mu Lie.
The Tale of Gong Mu Lie
was destroyed by my father.
But,
I know,
Gong Mu Lie has always been my side,
protecting me,
because you are him.
Song Ting Yu,
wake up,
I'm Qin Lie.
I'm wide awake.
The moment the Luminous Pillar
of Xingyun Pavilion was activated,
Icestone City
was supposed to be destroyed.
But nothing happened.
I didn't kill you to cover it up either.
Do you remember that?
I do.
It was Gong Mu Lie who stopped everything.
I saw him.
I really saw him.
Back then,
only you and Du Shao Yang were there.
I am certain
that you are actually Gong Mu Lie.
Gong Mu Lie?
You're mistaken.
Starting from that day,
I've been trying to look for
traces of Gong Mu Lie in you.
But as time goes on,
I can't even tell
who that person in my heart is.
I used to carry Gong Mu Lie's book
around with me.
That'd make me feel safe.
I knew he'd protect me
and stay by my side forever.
After being with you,
I started to develop the same feelings.
After we got here,
I know
that although you're here with me,
all you think about is Ling Yu Shi.
Qin Lie,
I can't hold it any longer.
I'm destined to die here.
Before I die,
could I take you as Gong Mu Lie?