THE CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
INCIDENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND BACKGROUND OF THIS
DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
LAST EPISODE
I waited to ask you for a favor.
Get rid of...
Shim Su Ryeon.
Why were you so fixated
on killing Shim Su Ryeon?
Because you wanted Joo
Dan Tae and the penthouse?
Did Joo Dan Tae say that?
Did he tell you...
that I wanted to have him?
We have clear proof.
We found your fingerprints...
smothered all over the knife
used to kill Shim Su Ryeon.
This is your knife, right?
Su Ryeon.
Answer me, Ms. Oh.
Did you kill Shim Su
Ryeon with this knife?
Yes.
I killed her.
What? What did you say?
I...
hated Su Ryeon...
to death.
Here...
It's all my fault.
It's all because of me.
I should've dealt
with it more firmly.
But it's too late.
Why is that your fault?
There's no way to stop
a psychopath like her.
Well, I hope you stay strong.
You can go home now.
How can I drink this trash?
Mister. Where is my mom?
Let me meet her.
Is she okay?
Why did you arrest
an innocent person?
What is my mom doing here?
Your mom admitted everything.
What?
No.
That can't be true.
No. No...
REST IN PEACE, SU RYEON.
WE WILL REMEMBER YOU,
WE SEND OUR CONDOLENCES.
People are sending condolences
to the shocking murder case...
that occurred at the most
expensive apartment...
- Su Ryeon.
- in Korea.
- The victim is Ms. Shim...
- Goodbye.
- At the lobby of the...
- We will...
never forget you.
"MONTHLY BIZ"
Su Ryeon, I hope you
go to a better place.
Oh, dear.
Our house price will plummet.
- Oh, dear.
- It will hit rock bottom.
This is a total disaster.
Oh, dear. My goodness...
What are you thinking?
What if someone hears you?
Do you know how many cameras
are shooting this scene?
I know.
A person died.
It's a murder case.
That's why I'm so worried.
One resident murdered another.
Nothing like this
has happened before.
The price of our apartment
is falling each day.
I'm scared to think
just how far it'll drop.
How could you worry
about house prices?
I'm so scared I can't
even go pee at night.
How could Oh Yoon
Hee kill Su Ryeon?
Wasn't Su Ryeon the only
person who looked out for her?
She fell for a man
and lost her mind.
Poor Su Ryeon lost everything.
She got well and truly betrayed.
Did you see the news?
Oh Yoon Hee decorated her
place like the penthouse.
Not to mention that she lusted
after someone else's husband.
When I saw how she'd photoshopped
her face into their family portrait,
I got the shivers.
That must be why she started
working for Chairman Joo.
It's so freaky.
But still,
it's not exactly bad for us.
With this happening, the reopening
of Min Seol A's murder case...
will no longer happen.
- Really?
How can the police investigate
when Shim Su Ryeon's dead?
The victim's gone and now
the victim's mom is dead too.
We should thank Oh Yoon Hee.
It looks like all the people...
I couldn't stand got
dealt with at once.
Shim Su Ryeon, Oh Yoon Hee,
and Ro Na too.
Try not to show too
much of your joy.
Think of the time
we spent together.
If you think about it, we
aren't completely unlucky.
Don't you think, Attorney Lee?
If we were unlucky,
we wouldn't have been able
to live in Hera Palace.
The skies...
will eventually
side with the rich.
The tax we pay...
makes the world go round.
Oh, dear...
- Oh, dear... Poor Su Ryeon...
- Darling.
Oh, dear...
I'm proud of you for
getting through the funeral.
Stay here for a while until
I get the penthouse sorted.
Ms. Yang will bring
the things you need.
Get some rest.
What will happen now?
What do you mean?
Will we go back
to the penthouse?
I'll clean it up so it
looks like nothing happened.
You don't have to worry.
Nothing changes.
Mom died in there.
How can nothing change?
Are you really completely fine?
If you're too distressed,
take time from school...
and study abroad for a year.
Think about it.
It's always like this.
No one really worries about us.
Mom said she'd protect
us, but she died.
They're all liars.
It's so annoying. I hate it.
Let's not go back...
to that place.
CHEONG A MEDICAL CENTER,
SERVING PATIENTS FOR 30 YEARS
What do you mean?
Your medical malpractice
suit from a few months ago...
resurfaced recently.
We sorted that out.
The patient's aftereffects
have worsened,
and he voiced his
determination to sue us.
Plus, I heard you were
questioned by the police...
regarding the child who
died at Hera Palace.
Why didn't you mention that?
Dozens of posts a day
are covering our website,
all demanding an explanation.
What is it you want?
Don't you get it?
They want you to step
down as hospital director.
I think a hospital director...
should have that much sense
of duty for his establishment.
Is it you?
Did you make an issue of
this old malpractice suit?
Your license will be
suspended for a year or two.
I contacted Johns Hopkins
University in America.
How about you study
there for a while?
Aren't medical mistakes
and malpractice issues...
all caused by a
doctor's lack of skill?
I nominated a new
director already.
Take care of the protocol
so he can take over quickly.
Yes, Director.
You kicked me out
of the hospital...
and took everything from me.
Is this the ending you wanted?
I'm only returning
everything to how they were.
The hospital and the foundation.
And Eun Byeol.
The director title
doesn't suit you.
CHEONG A MEDICAL CENTER
You shouldn't have
been so greedy.
Now, there's nothing...
you can take or keep.
How do you feel?
I got a cake from your
favorite dessert place.
Will you have some?
Will you really not talk to me?
Fine.
I guess you'll speak first
when you get too frustrated.
Eat it when you're hungry. I
especially ordered chocolate.
Gosh.
Who killed Su Ryeon?
You look a mess.
I told the boys
to treat you well.
I'm sorry this isn't
exactly a hotel.
Who killed Su Ryeon?
Even a great billionaire
looks just as haggard...
when he's starved
for a few days.
So what if you have
buildings in New York?
You don't even have a
hamburger to eat right now.
Am I wrong? Answer me, Logan.
No, wait, sorry.
Kang Ho Dong, no,
Gu Ho Dong, was it?
You scumbag.
How dare you con me?
How could you dare try to take
the Myeongdong plot from me?
Thanks to you,
I got photographed going in and
out of the Prosecutors' Office,
my personal details got out,
and I almost had to
serve time in prison.
Why is that my fault?
That's on you for
living the way you did.
I don't intend to kill you.
I won't maim you either.
I'm letting you live
for one reason only.
I just talked to your
father James Lee.
What did you do, you psycho?
I bargained with him.
With Min Seol A's case.
I can't believe that
brat helped me out again.
Shut your mouth!
To save the life
of his sick son,
your father did some
very emotional stuff.
He adopted Min Seol
A from an orphanage,
made her donate her bone-marrow,
reversed her adoption
and left her penniless,
and even framed her for theft
and had her deported to Korea.
I also have...
details of his transactions
with Congressman Cho Sang Heon.
They all came into
my possession.
What'll happen to your father...
if this huge secret comes out?
Hey.
Are you ready to send
your father to prison?
Kill me instead.
No, no, no way.
I said I didn't
want to kill you.
You don't seem to know,
but you are worth so much.
In return for getting you back
in one piece, your father...
sent me quite a lot of money.
Oh, of course, he also returned
the whole Myeongdong plot.
Everyone keeps dying.
Min Seol A and Shim Su Ryeon.
Then adios, amigo.
You scumbag!
Who killed Su Ryeon?
You did, didn't you?
I swear with my
life, Joo Dan Tae,
I will kill you!
Joo Dan Tae, you jerk.
Stay right where you are! Hey!
It's been a while since
we spent time alone.
Whose fault do you
think that was?
I'm sorry.
But still, though it took a
detour, we're back together.
Isn't that what counts?
Now I know for sure...
that you are my most
perfect partner.
How about a toast?
I love you.
Oh Yoon Hee!
Explain why you're
here with him.
Tell me! What were
you doing with him?
- Let go!
- What are you doing?
What's your
relationship with him?
Did you sleep with him? Did you?
Did you sleep with him?
Tell me yourself. Tell me now!
Take your hands off my woman!
What?
How could you do
this to me? How?
Stop it!
I'm sick and tired of you.
Go and protect your
foundation instead.
Stop being so clingy!
Joo Dan Tae. You scum!
Stop!
Get some rest.
Keep a close eye on Oh Yoon Hee.
How dare you come here?
Is the great Cheon
Seo Jin doubting me?
Do I look like someone...
who'd fall for a
woman like that?
What does that mean?
I was planning on
using Yoon Hee.
Where can I find such
a great prey like her?
Tell me what you're planning.
I must give back to Su Ryeon
exactly what she did to me.
That will clean everything up.
My company, your foundation,
and Min Seol A's case...
will all go back to
where it belongs.
Are you saying you'll
get rid of Su Ryeon?
What about Yoon Hee?
I was going to ditch her
once I was done anyway.
If we play her just right,
she'll do exactly what we want.
Isn't she the perfect
way to get to Su Ryeon?
Is that why you needed Yoon Hee?
You still have it, Joo Dan Tae.
How can I help?
I need funds right now.
My accounts are frozen because
of Logan and I'm stuck.
Hello, Congressman.
Chairman Joo, you know
how things are right now.
It's dangerous to
meet like this.
I can't cover this one up.
I can't let you go
out on a limb...
and end up losing your
hard-earned seat in congress.
I'll take that to
mean you understand.
Until now,
this is how I've been
supporting you and your works.
It adds up to a hefty sum.
Would you mind if I sent that
to the Prosecutor General?
Chairman Joo, what
are you doing?
I'm Cheon Seo Jin, Director
of Cheong A Foundation.
How about you gain
some new connections...
and climb higher up?
I will help as best I can.
It's up to you.
I never go down alone.
If I live,
you will live as well.
The J King Holdings
case you're on,
and the Cheong A
Foundation corruption case.
Come up with a story to
close them right now.
SEOUL GANGNAM POLICE STATION
You have until today
to turn yourself in.
Hurry up and go to the
police station now.
If you refuse to cooperate,
Ro Na will end up...
just like Seol A.
SEOUL GANGNAM POLICE STATION
Secretary Cho. What
are you doing here?
Chairman Joo wants you at
the penthouse immediately.
He says it's important.
Ms. Yang, you're finally
making yourself worthwhile.
You gave me...
a great idea.
I'll take this and...
It's beautiful.
Now we just need Su Ryeon.
Go on. Call her.
If you say the
kids are in danger,
she'll rush right over.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Yang, what's the matter?
Ms. Shim, the chairman took
the kids to his study again!
She just got here.
She'll be up soon.
Seok Hoon! Seok Kyung!
How could you...
You're the one who
caused this whole mess.
What a pity.
Your revenge will end
with your own death.
Still, you'll be able to meet...
your dead daughter whom
you missed so dearly.
Are you happy?
Chairman Joo, I'm here.
Chairman Joo?
Goodbye.
Chairman Joo, are you in here?
Su Ryeon?
Su Ryeon.
Su Ryeon...
Su Ryeon, are you
okay? Su Ryeon.
What? I can't hear you.
Su Ryeon.
Su Ryeon?
Su Ryeon, get up. Don't die.
You can't die! No!
Su Ryeon, no! You can't die.
You can't die...
Did you do it?
You killed my wife?
How could you such
a horrible thing?
Take her away now!
Did you ever have
feelings for Oh Yoon Hee?
Not even once?
I swear I never felt anything.
If you're nice to poor people,
they tend to be so gullible.
Why would I fall for a
petty wench like her?
Thanks to that,
we were able to
protect what was ours.
But why did Oh Yoon Hee...
admit that she killed her?
The proof was so certain, so
she probably just gave up.
But I'm certain
there's something...
between Shim Su Ryeon
and Oh Yoon Hee.
It seemed like Oh Yoon Hee
did something very wrong.
Something that could
never be forgiven.
Something wrong?
What could that be?
I'm not sure.
Anyhow, it's a
good thing for us.
Oh Yoon Hee will be sent to
the prosecution tomorrow.
I heard a public defender
will take the case.
Then there will be no problem
in finding her guilty.
All of this will finally end.
You are such...
a terrifying man.
That's why I'm so
attracted to you.
Hearing you say that...
arouses me already.
But you didn't kill
her yourself, did you?
I heard the scene
was quite gruesome.
No way, me?
How could I do
such a cruel thing?
You know that I can't
even squash an ant.
I took care of it neatly,
so you don't have to worry.
I'm still curious
about something.
Who killed Min Seol A?
Who cares?
What's important is that we got
rid of the thorns on our sides.
We got rid of Min Seol
A as well as her mom.
Bye, bye.
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
Mister.
Are you still here?
There's no use staying here.
Please let me see my mom.
Something is not right.
There's no way my mom
would've done that.
I know her the best.
Do you know how much
she liked Ms. Shim?
This makes no sense.
Let me talk to her.
Can you please let me see her?
Your mom said no.
I asked several times, but
she said no. What can we do?
She said you can go stay
at your grandma's house.
I won't go.
I won't go anywhere...
until I see my mom.
I'm your public defender.
We found several items
in your house proving...
that you stalked Joo Dan Tae.
You sneaked into the
penthouse numerous times...
and stole Shim Su
Ryeon's things...
and even wore her clothes.
You pretending to be Shim
Su Ryeon is all on tape.
You will be transferred
to a detention center...
as soon as your warrant
is issued tomorrow.
I never asked for a lawyer.
Well, I know you have
no chance to win,
but you should show regret...
for your daughter's
sake at least.
That's how your sentence
will be reduced.
I heard your daughter
has been staying...
at the police station for days.
Are you really not
going to meet her?
No, I won't.
Just tell her to go home.
I admit to all my charges.
Just...
Wrap this up as
soon as possible.
She's coming out.
Did you really kill her?
Why did you kill her? Was
it because of your affair?
Why did you kill
her so brutally?
Why did you stab
her several times?
Is your motive because of
your hate toward rich people?
When did you start
envying the victim?
Did you envy her or hate her?
- Say something.
- Don't you even feel sorry?
Mom, it's all not true.
I know you didn't do it.
Please tell them it isn't
true! Tell them now!
Tell them now!
Mom. Mom...
Mom, look at me.
Mom, please look at me.
Mom, look at me just once.
Mom. Mom...
Mom... Mom!
Mom!
IT'S YOUR FAULT! MURDERER!
PSYCHOPATH
THE UNDERWORLD, GO
BACK TO BOSUK VILLAGE!
LEAVE, YOU PSYCHOPATH! A
MURDERER FULL OF INFERIORITY!
OH YOON HEE IS EVIL! A
DISGRACE TO HERA PALACE!
A MURDERER LIVES HERE.
OUR HOUSE PRICE IS
DROPPING. GET OUT OF HERE.
When are you going
to give me that?
It's nothing expensive.
I like it.
Hey.
Where have you been?
This place was a total mess.
I almost lost my mind
from all the noise.
I thought you ran
away or something.
What do you want?
Do you want to call me the
daughter of a murderer too?
Do it. Swear at me all you want.
I'm right here, so
say what you want.
Did you...
eat?
What?
Eat this.
You can't cry on
an empty stomach.
Just stay quiet and
pretend you're not home.
You don't know when
people will come back.
MURDERER
A MURDERER FULL OF
INFERIORITY! A DEVIL
Mom, what do I do?
What do I do now?
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
6 MONTHS LATER
Thanks to all your help,
I think I'll be acquitted.
How can I possibly repay you?
I told you...
that I'd help you
when you needed me.
This is nothing.
I will stay loyal to
you and your friends...
for the rest of my life.
And you know what
they said on the news?
That's all fake.
That dead woman made that all up
to receive settlement money...
for their divorce.
What?
What was the name of
her illness again?
Delusional disorder.
She blabbered about a daughter
that didn't even exist.
I can't believe that
kind of illness existed.
- Really?
- Yes.
Chairman Joo of J King Holdings,
who was charged for embezzlement
and investment fraud was freed...
without charges.
The police found out how the victim
of the Hera Palace Murder Case,
Shim, fabricated the
documents meticulously...
to take advantage of her
divorce with Chairman Joo.
The victim, Shim, suffered
from an illness...
known as a delusional
disorder...
Mom, can I stop now?
My arms are about to fall out.
Mother, please forgive us now.
We were all cleared
of our charges.
Do you know how much money
I spent to make that happen?
I hired 10 lawyers.
You even tainted your
father's reputation.
We'll never do that again.
Please forgive us now.
Mi Ja, don't you
think this is enough?
My son.
Don't ever get involved in
such a nasty mess again.
Your father is thinking of
making you into a politician.
A politician? Me?
It's about time a politician
is born in our family.
So you must be super careful
not to get caught up...
in any kind of scandal. Got it?
You too.
Yes, Mother.
A congressman?
That sounds awesome.
I know how hard it was being
investigated by the prosecution.
It's all thanks to you, who
helped uncover the truth.
Our alumni held demonstrations
to set you free.
Individuals in the music
industry have also released...
many interviews on media,
saying they stood by your side.
That's no surprise.
I believe you were repaid
for your kind deeds...
and secret donations that
contributed to our society.
I, Ma Doo Ki, truly believe so.
I'm happy to see that I've
led a meaningful life.
Cheong A's irregularities
won't be mentioned anymore.
Let's start fresh...
and I hope you devote yourselves
for Cheong A Foundation.
Of course, ma'am.
By the way, how is Eun Byeol?
She just returned from a trip.
She'll come back...
to school next week.
Since you've been discharged,
you'll have to go to school.
The doctor said you're fine, so
you'll have no problem studying.
I'll reserve special
lessons so you can catch up.
You'll get busy from now on.
Ha Eun Byeol.
How long will you say nothing?
I'm losing my patience.
What do you want?
Do you want to quit
school and singing?
Is it okay if you
don't go to college?
Yes, honey.
What? A party?
Everything has been
sorted out neatly.
It has been concluded that
Oh Yoon Hee and Logan Lee...
conspired to commit
embezzlement.
Since everything is over now,
I'm thinking of holding a party
with the people of Hera Club.
It's been rough for all of us.
That sounds good. Okay.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
What...
Go to your room and rest.
Mom.
Eun Byeol.
Did you just call me?
Finally, you've
come to your senses!
I knew you'd overcome it.
Is there anything
else you want to say?
Is there something you want
to eat? I'll cook it for you.
Why aren't you asking me?
Why I took those drugs?
Let's just...
forget about that.
You can start over again.
Nothing ever happened to you.
But that won't make
the past disappear.
If you live in the past, you
won't be able to do anything.
It's the most foolish
thing you can ever do.
Then are you okay
about your past?
I'm talking about
grandpa's death.
What?
You're no longer my daughter!
No! Cheong A is mine!
- You can't take it away from me!
- Let go!
Let go!
I said, let go! Let go!
Dad!
If I called an
ambulance that day,
he wouldn't have passed away.
I feel so bad now
that I think about it.
Back then, I only stayed
quiet to protect you.
Why are you suddenly
asking about your grandpa?
I took those pills because
I missed him so much.
What do you mean?
What do you mean? Tell
me so I can understand!
See? You're not over it either.
You also miss
grandpa, don't you?
I'm hungry.
I want to eat pasta
with tons of garlic.
You'll cook it for me, right?
Thank you for helping me.
You should move
to a better place.
I didn't expect you to pay me.
Take it.
You've become an important
person to me now.
100,000 DOLLARS
Gosh, you really need to stop
putting your books in upside down.
What will you do without me?
What's there to worry about? You
can organize them for me every day.
My goodness, did you twirl
your hair while studying again?
I can't stop myself
from twirling my hair...
when I study.
Should I just cut my hair?
Why would you cut your hair?
Do you know how much I
enjoy tying your hair?
How is your hair so silky?
Because I take after you.
I'm late. Tie my hair for me.
Drink your juice.
I'll do it quickly.
It's good.
Is it?
Drink it all. I added tons
of healthy ingredients.
This is all useless.
Just forget it!
Seok Kyung, what's wrong
with you? Calm down!
- Let me go. Let me go!
- Seok Kyung.
I said let me go!
Calm down. What's the matter?
I hate her. I hate her so much.
Seok Kyung.
Seok Kyung, calm down!
I won't ever forgive
her for leaving me.
It's okay. Calm down.
Calm down.
I hate her. I hate her.
It's okay.
Mom!
Mom.
It's okay.
Mom!
See?
You're not over it either.
You also miss
grandpa, don't you?
Does Eun Byeol...
know something?
No way.
It's not possible.
I heard Dr. Ha...
is going to resign and go
to the States. Is that true?
He wants to study more, so
there's no reason to stop him.
From what I heard, he got
kicked out by Seo Jin.
Honey, are you drunk?
- Did I say it out loud?
- Yes.
I heard Seok Hoon and Seok
Kyung will be studying abroad.
The kids wanted to go, so
they'll be gone for about a year.
Gosh, you're lying.
You just want the kids gone so
you guys can move in together.
You guys must be excited.
Now that both of you
got rid of your spouses,
there's nothing stopping you.
Oh, right. Today is the day.
Oh Yoon Hee's being
sentenced today.
Oh, you're right.
I totally forgot.
Are you sure you forgot?
I thought you purposely
held the party today...
to celebrate the war that
broke out in Hera Palace.
What do you mean "celebrate"?
People might get the wrong idea.
I'm just kidding. It was a joke.
What do you think the
court will decide?
I bet she'll get a long sentence
considering what she did.
She obviously has no hope.
She already admitted
to the murder,
so the trial is just
going to be a formality.
You never know.
You can never predict
how a trial will end.
I'm Kim Jung Min, a
reporter from SBC.
I'd like to talk to Ms. Oh.
She needs to go to court,
so she has no time.
And as you can see, she
doesn't seem interested.
Su Ryeon asked me for a favor.
I'll give you
exactly five minutes.
It wasn't easy for
me to come meet you.
How could you kill
her like that?
Just tell me why you're here.
What did Su Ryeon ask you to do?
PETITION
What's this?
It's a petition.
Please give it to Oh Yoon Hee.
"Oh Yoon Hee"? Who's that?
A good friend of mine.
She's going to surrender
to the police tomorrow.
And once she does, she'll
get punished by the law.
But I feel like she
might need this.
Then why don't you give
it to her yourself?
I'm worried I might
change my mind.
PETITION
Petition.
The Oh Yoon Hee I know...
is a very warm-hearted
and just person.
I hope Yoon Hee...
will safely go home and
return to her daughter.
I hope she gets the chance...
to build happy memories
with her daughter,
which is something I never
got to do with Seol A.
And thus, I earnestly ask for
you to be lenient with her.
From Min Seol A's
mother, Shim Su Ryeon.
Whatever it was that you did,
how could you kill someone who
was this worried about you?
I'm here because I promised
Su Ryeon to do this,
but it gives me the creeps
to be sitting here with you.
How could you kill her
just to take her place?
I heard she was nice to you.
Did you think you'd be able
to take over the penthouse...
and have Joo Dan Tae
once you killed her?
COURT
Mom.
DEFENDANT
Defendant, Oh Yoon Hee,
yearned to have the life
that the victim had...
and confessed that she hated her so
much that she wanted to kill her.
Also, there's a footage
of the defendant...
secretly entering the penthouse
and trying on the victim's dress.
Attorney, is there
anything you'd like to say?
The defendant already admitted
to everything as she testified.
However, please take
into consideration...
that she suffered for
a very long time...
due to financial instability
and had to raise a daughter...
all on her own.
This is so fun!
Here's the verdict.
Defendant, Oh Yoon Hee, was
jealous of the victim...
who trusted and helped her...
and brutally killed her by
stabbing her many times.
And due to the brutality of
the crime, her ill intention,
and the shock she gave
to the victim's family,
we cannot help but give
her a severe punishment.
The justice department
believes she deserves to be...
isolated from our society for
the horrible crime she committed.
Thus, we sentence her
to life imprisonment.
SEOUL GANGNAM POLICE STATION
Secretary Cho. What
are you doing here?
Chairman Joo wants you at
the penthouse immediately.
Chairman Joo.
Chairman Joo, are you in here?
Su Ryeon?
Su Ryeon...
Su Ryeon, stay with me.
Su Ryeon!
Wait. I'll call an ambulance.
Wait a little bit.
Su Ryeon.
What? I can't hear you.
Run away.
Run... Run away.
Su Ryeon.
I didn't kill...
Mom.
What did you just say, Ms. Oh?
I didn't kill...
Shim Su Ryeon, Your Honor.
I didn't kill her.
I swear on my daughter's name.
I'm not the culprit.
Please reinvestigate the case.
Everything was fabricated!
I'm not the culprit.
I didn't kill Shim Su Ryeon.
Please reinvestigate
the case, Your Honor!
I'm not the culprit!
Mom!
Ro Na.
I didn't kill her!
I'm innocent!
It wasn't me! I didn't kill her!
This trial doesn't count!
Let me have another trial!
No! I didn't kill her!
It wasn't me!
I didn't kill her!
- It wasn't me!
- Get going already!
No, please! I didn't do it!
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
3 SANG 19, 2607
We need help.
2607, Oh Yoon Hee, escaped
while getting transferred.
We need help now.
Logan, what are you doing here?
What's going on?
We have breaking news. A
defendant who received...
a life sentence
in court today...
escaped after the van got into an
accident and flipped upside down.
The defendant who ran away...
was the assailant of
the murder incident...
that occurred in Hera Palace.
- She stood trial for six months.
- Ro Na.
But today, she suddenly
denied all charges...
and threw a scene in court.
The police are searching
the nearby areas...
- Ro Na.
- and checking the CCTVs...
Where are you going?
Logan, I need to meet Ro Na.
Please tell her I'm alive.
The cops are already
at your house.
If you want to get
caught, you can go ahead.
No. My Ro Na... What
about my daughter?
How could you be audacious enough
to worry about your daughter...
even after killing two people?
You really...
give me the creeps.
What do you mean I
killed two people?
You must've thought you'd be
able to forget about it...
now that the one and
only witness is dead.
But unfortunately,
Su Ryeon told me
everything before she died.
She told me you killed
my little sister.
"Little sister"?
Your little sister?
Yes. My little sister.
My little sister, Min Seol A.
We've finally met.
I came all the way over
to Korea to find...
the person who killed my sister.
And that person...
was you?
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill her?
Why on earth did you
kill that poor girl?
Su Ryeon trusted
and waited for you.
She trusted that you'd
turn yourself in,
and believed you until the
end even when she knew...
you were the one
who killed Seol A.
But how could you
backstab her like that?
If Su Ryeon hadn't
stopped me back then,
I would've killed
you that instant.
Then Su Ryeon wouldn't have
died in vain like that.
No, I didn't kill Su Ryeon!
Don't lie!
You teamed up with
Joo Dan Tae...
and tried to get
rid of Su Ryeon.
But you know what?
Su Ryeon tried to protect
you until the end...
even when she knew everything.
But how could you...
do something like that to her?
You're not even human.
You deserve to die.
You're just a piece of trash
that doesn't deserve to live.
What? I can't hear you.
Run away.
You're right.
I'm responsible for
Su Ryeon's death too.
Since it's true I wanted
to get rid of her.
You're right.
Kill me. I deserve to die.
But kill me later, after I
get revenge for Su Ryeon.
I'll let you kill me
after I get revenge on...
Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo
Jin, who killed Su Ryeon...
with my own hands.
I give you my word.
So for now, please let me go.
Please help me. Please...
Do you expect me...
to believe you again?
No. You'll die here, today.
The police will never find you.
You'll be remembered forever
as a brutal murderer...
and a fugitive.
Just remain in
people's memories...
as a cold-blooded mom who even
abandoned her own daughter.
What do I have to do
to make you believe me?
I didn't kill her.
I swear I didn't kill Su Ryeon!
Joo Dan Tae framed
me for everything!
Shut your darn mouth!
I'll kill you just the same!
Just like how Su Ryeon died!
Just like how my
sister Seol A died.
A miserable and gruesome death.
Fine.
I won't ask you to
believe me anymore.
It's true I killed Min Seol A.
I was bound to be
punished for that.
Kill me. Kill me now!
But don't forget.
Even if I die,
the real culprit who
killed Su Ryeon...
will still stay alive.
Ro Na.
I'm sorry.
MY FRIEND
Su Ryeon.
Since we have much to celebrate,
how about we take a picture?
Sure.
Let's see.
That's too lame.
- Ta-da.
- A polaroid?
You're so old-fashioned.
I'm more of a classic type.
Since it's our first photo together,
I want it to be meaningful.
A one and only
photo in this world.
Gosh, that sounds so corny.
This is why you shouldn't
hang out with rich people.
They live in their
own fantasy world.
My beautiful friend,
Su Ryeon. I love you!
I hope we look good.
THE PENTHOUSE
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
THE PENTHOUSE.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH THE
PENTHOUSE SEASON 2.
THE PENTHOUSE 2