THE CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
INCIDENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND BACKGROUND OF THIS
DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
EPISODE 19
What's going on?
- This is gasoline!
- My gosh!
What is this? It's gasoline!
It's gasoline?
- What is it? What's wrong?
- It's a bomb!
It's a bomb!
What are you doing?
Can't you see us in here?
Stop this madness now!
Hey! Why did you set this
place on fire? Are you crazy?
Why? Are you afraid
you might die?
What the?
Was it okay when your
kids did the same thing?
Your kids also set a car
on fire and ran away.
What are you talking
about? We don't understand!
- Min Seol A.
- What?
What do you mean, Min Seol A?
That night... There
was a fire in the van.
What are you talking about?
Our kids lighted
candles on a cake...
and Min Seol A almost
burned to death.
That's a lie! That
never happened.
Don't make things up!
It's true. Jenny
told me that night.
Wait! I really
didn't know anything.
I really didn't know!
The kids probably got
afraid and ran away.
It was a prank.
That's all it was!
A prank?
Min Seol A almost
died that night.
Because of your
kids who ran off,
leaving her alone
in a burning car.
And after all they did,
your kids still didn't
show any hint of remorse.
How could you do that?
What? You're still alive?
Nice. We're so lucky.
Why? Did something happen?
I had a nap and just woke up.
MIN SEOL A, JOO SEOK HOON,
YOO JENNY, JOO SEOK KYUNG...
Do you know what you did?
Because of you, I almost died.
Because of the fire you started.
What fire? Do you smoke?
You should quit,
for your own sake.
I thought you liked to drink,
but you're a heavy smoker too?
LAUGHING
So what? Are you going
to do the same to us?
Who are you? Aren't you
Min Seol A's brother?
If you don't stop this immediately,
I will tear you to shreds!
Will you?
Give it a go.
I have no intention of
letting you all live.
- What?
- Please open the door!
- Jenny, Mom's dying!
- Save me!
Stop this now! Stop it!
Hey!
- Stop it!
- Save us!
Let us out!
- Save me, please!
- Let us out!
No!
Mom!
- Mom.
Please...
Write down what each of
you did to Min Seol A.
The clock's ticking!
Hey!
We got it!
Get out of the way.
What did you do to our kids?
If you harmed them,
I will kill you!
The kids, of course,
need time to repent too.
For what they did.
Shall we make a deal?
Confess everything
you did to Min Seol A.
Confess what happened on
the night Min Seol A died.
Don't leave out a single detail.
What do you want us to say?
Confess right now
if you want to live.
Don't say a word.
Don't fall for this!
You lunatic.
Are you saying we
should die here?
Get off me!
I'll go first!
I did nothing wrong at all.
I found out later that Min
Seol A was locked up...
in Hera Palace's
mechanical room.
Joo Dan Tae, Cheon Seo Jin,
you locked her up, didn't you?
Say it now!
You're blaming me now?
I did everything for our kids!
That's a joke. The
kids were an excuse.
You wanted to get the video
she had of your affair!
I told you to shut up!
Hey! Darn you!
Our lives and our kids'
lives are at stake!
And you still want
to point fingers?
You punk.
Let go of me.
- Come here!
- Stop it!
- You fools.
- What have you done?
- Get off me.
- Will you stop it?
Look at that! Do something!
You have five minutes.
I'll release the person who makes
the most truthful confession.
And their child too.
So, you don't care if you die?
Then I'll do as you wish.
No! No.
Me. I'll go first.
That night...
All I did was wipe the
blood off the fountain.
That goes for me too.
Jenny's mom told me
to wipe the blood,
and that's all I did!
Stop it! This is a trap.
They're putting on a
show to get evidence!
Hey. Keep your mouth shut.
You can die for this alone!
I can't die.
That guy, Joo Dan Tae said...
we should dispose of the body.
I honestly only followed
what Joo Dan Tae said.
- What a joke.
- Lee Kyu Jin, you stupid scumbag!
The bag.
You brought the golf club
bag to put her body in!
That golf club bag.
We moved that in your car!
- And your ex-wife, this witch.
- What?
She faked the girl's will!
- You two couples!
You made it look
like it was suicide!
Joo Dan Tae, you trashy punk.
You made it look like...
she fell from Bosuk Village!
- Are you crazy?
- It was all you!
- He said shut up!
- Get off me!
- Stop it!
- Let's try to get out of here!
It's all on you!
- I didn't do anything!
- I want to get out of here!
You two. If that girl
hadn't noticed your affair,
none of this would've happened.
Because of you two,
all our kids might die.
If something happens to
Jenny because of you,
I will crush you to a
pulp with my two hands.
Get off me.
Hey! Say that you
killed Min Seol A!
We might all have to die
because of what you did!
Why would I kill her?
Then was it you, Ms. Cheon?
I didn't do it!
Then who on earth killed her?
All our kids might die!
Listen.
Please! Please save
my daughter Jenny.
The one in a white dress,
the prettiest girl
there is my daughter.
If you'll spare my daughter,
I'll give you everything I own.
My home and building,
I'll give you everything.
Please spare my Jenny.
Min Hyuk. Min Hyuk, no!
- Min Hyuk! No!
- The truth is,
my mom is very sick.
She has two months to live.
Please let me live
for two more months.
Let me die with my mom.
Don't you lie.
- Please...
- How dare you say that?
- Darn you.
- Get off me!
- Let go!
- Let go of me, you jerk!
- Stop it!
What are you saying...
What was that?
- What happened?
- He blew up.
He blew up.
- Look.
- Where?
What's that?
Over there. Look...
There's someone there.
- Who?
- Who is it?
What?
Su Ryeon?
Shim Su Ryeon!
You think so much of your kids,
so how could you do
that to Min Seol A?
What does that have
to do with you?
Was it...
Was it you behind all this?
Shim Su Ryeon! That
woman's out of her mind.
Min Seol A was my daughter!
What?
The poor girl who was switched
and abandoned without my knowing.
She never got to hold my hand,
or call me "Mom" before
she died before her time!
The Min Seol A...
that you looked down on
and trampled all over...
was my daughter.
- How come...
- I knew it!
Hey, what did you
do to Eun Byeol?
Quit this stupid
joke immediately!
Su Ryeon.
Let's calm down first.
Let's all take a deep breath.
You won't really kill
all of us here, will you?
I will represent everyone
here and apologize to you.
- I'm sorry!
- Su Ryeon.
- Hurry!
- I'm sorry too.
- There you go.
- I'm sorry!
- I apologize!
- We apologize.
I don't care for
heartless apologies!
You lunatic!
Shut up!
You're only paying
for what you did.
See for yourselves.
See what monsters you
turned your kids into.
She's out of her mind.
She's gone. Where did she go?
- Where is she?
- Shim Su Ryeon!
Open the door! Open this door!
- Let us out!
- Open the door, Shim Su Ryeon!
Shim Su Ryeon!
Let me out of here!
Wait, wait!
I have to get out!
No!
What now?
No! No!
Save me!
What happened?
Darn it.
My gosh.
Let's go.
Wait for me. Wait up.
I had my hair done!
STATEMENT
- Let go.
- Are you okay?
What's this?
It's raw sewage!
- It's blood!
- Blood?
Darn it.
What should we do now?
Are you okay?
What is this now?
- Darn it!
- Dr. Ha!
Listen to me carefully.
As of this moment, Min
Seol A was never here.
Min Seol A did not fall
and die in this building.
Will this be big enough?
It's Min Seol A's bag.
I wrote a suicide
note. Set that up too.
We must finish cleaning
up in five minutes.
I'll go down.
With this,
all the proof is gone.
Even after her death,
we enjoyed the party...
as if nothing had happened.
It was the grandest
party in the world.
You'll never see such a
party even in your next life.
The lights around
the fountain...
were so beautiful.
Eun Byeol. Eun Byeol!
- Jenny!
- Mom!
- Dad!
- Eun Byeol.
Jenny! Jenny.
- Eun Byeol!
- My goodness.
GRACE JO'S PRIVATE
SOLO RECITAL
Silence!
What...
- Gu Ho Dong.
- Gu Ho Dong?
What are you doing?
Stop this right now!
I'll give you all the cash you
want! Stop this immediately!
Money?
How much will you give me?
Is it enough to
bring my sister back?
Are you really Min
Seol A's brother?
- Her brother?
- What?
I thought you were suspicious.
You were Min Seol A's brother?
Did you lock up and threaten my
child to avenge for a dead girl?
How can you call
yourself a teacher?
This is nothing compared to
what they did to poor Seol A.
Your kids are alive and well.
Don't forget.
You brought this
upon yourselves.
The letters of remorse
your kids wrote here.
I'll make sure to pass
them to the police.
You scumbag!
- Don't!
- Stop it!
Don't move.
- Gu Ho Dong!
Hey!
GRACE JO'S PRIVATE
SOLO RECITAL
I will catch and
kill you myself.
You jerk.
Okay, Chairman.
- What was it about?
- It's nothing.
Ms. Shim.
Hello. I was waiting for you.
Why didn't you
answer your phone?
I packed everything.
That's why I came to get you.
I haven't seen Ro Na
for a while as well.
Su Ryeon is at my
place right now.
Ro Na practices so hard.
What? Well, yes.
She met Grace Jo today.
She's so eager now.
The coffee's ready.
What do you mean?
What is all over?
The kids all confessed to
bullying and taunting Seol A.
The adults too.
They confessed the
disposal of her body...
and faking cause of death.
Then Joo Dan Tae...
- confessed it too?
- Of course.
He's the worst of them all.
He disposed of a corpse, destroyed
evidence, and set a fire.
He even slandered Seol A's name.
What about Cheon Seo Jin?
Did she confess to
killing Min Seol A?
No.
She denied it to the end?
Even when you said you saw her?
You said you saw the
ruby ring on her finger.
When Cheon Seo Jin...
pushed Min Seol
A over the ledge.
It wasn't Cheon Seo Jin.
What?
The person...
who really killed
my daughter Seol A.
It wasn't Cheon Seo Jin.
No?
Then... Who's the real killer?
It's you.
You killed her.
My Seol A.
Why did you kill her?
Are you okay? Did
you burn your hand?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Do you remember when I asked
to see you on the 47th floor?
The day I told you
Seol A's my daughter.
The person who pushed Seol A.
I saw them clearly.
Who...
Who was it?
She was wearing a ruby ring.
A red ruby ring.
Is something wrong?
I'm fine.
I'll call you back.
I thought it was odd...
how you disappeared
without a word.
But early the next
morning, Ro Na called me.
Hi, Ro Na. Why did
you call me so early?
A police station?
She was at a police station and
you weren't answering your phone.
PULL THE DOOR-HANDLE
I went in to wake you in
case you'd fallen asleep.
Yoon Hee.
This is Seol A's necklace.
However hard I thought,
I couldn't figure out why
you'd have Seol A's necklace.
Why are you so surprised?
So I went to ask you.
To see for myself. But...
Revenge?
You're just trying to
get what you want...
without getting
blood on your hands!
Why did you send me
to Bosuk Village...
when I didn't know anything and
get me involved with Min Seol A?
I need your testimony.
Go to the police station and
just tell them what you know.
The police station? Me?
My poor daughter
who died is in here.
Stop mentioning Min Seol A.
I have to go now.
You were a different person.
You seemed extremely anxious...
and it seemed like you
were hiding a huge secret.
So I followed you.
No matter how much
I thought about it,
I couldn't wrap
my head around it.
Why did you try to get rid of
Seol A's necklace at that timing?
It was as if...
you were trying to deny your
memories from that night.
What is this nonsense?
Are you crazy?
Did you lose your mind
because of your dead daughter?
I...
understand how bitter
and frustrated you are,
but don't blame an
innocent person.
Then why did you burn
Seol A's necklace?
Why did you have it
in the first place?
She gave it to me as a gift.
To thank me for helping her.
But you suddenly told me
she was your daughter,
and I didn't want you
to get the wrong idea.
That's why I tried to
get rid of it. That's it.
No.
You were drunk that night,
and you totally blacked out.
Then you remembered
after I told you.
So you tried to get rid of
the clothes and necklace...
that could've been used
as proof. Am I wrong?
Su Ryeon! Why are
you doing this to me?
I didn't do it.
I really didn't do it.
Quiet down.
Is it okay if Ro Na hears this?
Mom. What's wrong?
Are you fighting with Ms. Shim?
No, we're not.
Go get some juice.
- It's in the fridge.
- Just go get some!
Do you have proof?
Not just suspicion,
but real proof.
Actual proof that I
killed your daughter.
If you don't, get out of here
before I have you dragged out.
It is over...
between us now.
After Seol A died,
we carried out an autopsy.
The DNA of several people...
were found all over her body.
Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo
Jin's were on it as I expected.
But there was one
piece of DNA...
that we couldn't confirm.
It was left under...
Seol A's fingernails as
she struggled to fight.
The police investigation was
postponed because of that.
The DNA of the suspect...
does not match with the
residents of Hera Palace.
Do you mean we can't
catch the killer?
If there's DNA left under
the victim's fingernails,
it means there will be...
a noticeable wound on
the killer's body too.
I was curious.
Who Seol A was with
before she died.
I was doubtful, but
I still had to check.
Oh Yoon Hee.
It was you.
DNA TEST RESULT
DNA 1 AND DNA 2
MATCH IDENTICALLY,
WHICH PROVES THEY
ARE THE SAME PERSON.
DNA TEST RESULT
Do you remember?
When they held an
emergency parent meeting...
at Cheong A Arts High
School after Seol A died?
You drank? And after that?
I can't remember.
She just said she
can't remember.
What's that wound on your hand?
You don't remember that as well?
Finally, all pieces of the
puzzle have fallen into place.
That wound on your
hand is the proof.
What I saw wasn't Cheon
Seo Jin's ruby ring,
but it was Seol A's necklace
you ripped from her neck.
The one who killed
Seol A is you.
No!
- No.
- Was it because of Ro Na?
Because if Seol A was gone,
she would get into Cheong A since
she was on the waiting list.
Is that why you killed Seol A?
Stop this nonsense.
This is all just
your imagination.
You can always fabricate
something like this.
Why? Are you having
second thoughts...
on making Cheon
Seo Jin the killer?
Is that why you're
trying to blame it on me?
Oh Yoon Hee! How far
are you willing to go?
I could've gone to
the police right away,
but I wanted to give you a
chance to ask for forgiveness.
I didn't kill her. It wasn't me!
I know that you feel guilty,
but that won't bring
your daughter back.
You're the one who
couldn't protect her!
You're right. It's my fault.
For mistaking a
murderer as my friend.
What do you think Ro Na
will say when she finds out?
Will she understand and forgive
you when she finds out...
that her mom killed
someone for her?
Do not say anything...
to Ro Na about Min Seol A.
Don't sway that
vulnerable child...
with your ridiculous
speculations!
You really have...
nothing to fear when
it comes to Ro Na.
Honey. Let's go home.
Is this your answer?
Bring her to me politely.
I can go on my own.
I'll call you later.
You did the right thing.
You made the right choice.
For Ro Na to live,
you have no choice.
You did the right thing.
It's okay. It's nothing.
It's okay.
It's so cold.
Seok Kyung.
What are you doing?
- Let go!
- Seok Kyung!
It's okay. Calm down.
It's okay.
It's okay, Seok Kyung.
It's going to be okay.
Get lost!
Dad.
I'm so scared.
Min Seol A keeps chasing me.
It's okay. I'm right
here, so don't worry.
I'm right here, so
don't be afraid.
Did Mom kill Min Seol A?
Because of me?
Did she kill her...
to cover up my sins?
It's okay, sweetie.
It's okay.
You are...
Min Seol A's real mom?
You did something very
gutsy, Shim Su Ryeon.
Why on earth are you
acting up so much?
Are you foolish enough to
put your life on the line...
for a dead girl?
Say whatever you want.
If it weren't for you, she
wouldn't have died like that.
Why did you do it?
Was killing Seol
A's dad not enough?
Why did you switch...
those poor babies when
they were so young?
Then did you think...
I would actually raise
that jerk's daughter?
You're seriously too naive.
Why would I do that for
a darn loser like him?
Don't think it will end here.
I will make sure
you're punished...
for what you did.
You scumbag.
Who is it?
The one who made
you so confident.
Taking Hye In and sending
her to New York...
and preparing a show
like that today.
An amateur like you
couldn't have done it.
I'm certain there is
someone who's helping you.
Tell me. Who is it?
Fine.
I'll just send you to
your dead daughter now.
It's Logan Lee, sir.
Yes, it's me. I was
just about to call you.
Now?
Okay.
Don't take your eyes off her.
And make sure she
doesn't meet the kids.
What is this? What's going on?
Turn the lights back on. Now!
Turn the lights back on!
She's gone.
Find her now!
Stop!
Excuse me for being late.
It's okay.
I'll have the same, please.
So, Mr. Joo.
I heard you missed the
event with Grace Jo.
You know I put in a lot
of work into it, right?
You put me in a bad position.
So do you want to
tell me what happened?
There was an accident.
I guess you didn't
hear anything about it.
Something very interesting happened
in the limousine you sent us.
Oh, yes. I heard about
it from my secretary.
There must've been some kind of
confusion with the limousines.
Anyway, do you happen to know a
man by the name of "Ho Dong Gu"?
"Ho Dong Gu"? Gu Ho Dong?
Yes. This man called me...
and he asked me if I knew
the real Dan Tae Joo.
He claims that you and
others at the Hera Palace...
are involved in
some kind of a...
murder case.
Is this true?
He's not reliable at all.
You don't have to mind him.
Well... It's against my
policy to go around...
digging up other people's
private business matters,
but it did catch me off guard.
Considering the fact
that you tried to sell...
your living
daughter's property...
and now, a murder case.
I don't know if I can keep
trusting you as a business partner.
The investment
presentation is tomorrow.
The investors have high hopes
for this casino business.
You cannot be swayed now.
They're all just false rumors.
What if I don't believe you?
I'll prepare thoroughly and
prove you weren't wrong.
I will never disappoint you.
Investment presentation...
I'll be looking forward to it.
Okay.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
How did it go?
Wasn't Joo Dan Tae
suspicious of you?
He's a skeptical person,
so I'm sure he has doubts.
But since he is the president,
and the investment
presentation is tomorrow,
I think he's willing
to push forward.
I know how hard it was.
Why did you go to
Oh Yoon Hee's place?
I wasn't mistaken about
what I saw that night.
Have you forgotten that
Su Ryeon and I are close?
If that bothered you,
you wouldn't be here.
Am I wrong?
Hello?
Why are you so hard to reach?
Dan Tae's involved with
my daughter's death.
Come with me to the police
tomorrow and testify about Seol A.
You're the only person
I trust right now.
I must catch her killer.
Please help me, Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee is helping Dan Tae.
She betrayed me.
What did I tell you?
I told you not to trust her!
Yoon Hee is the murderer.
She killed Seol A.
What...
What did you just say?
The person who killed Seol A...
was Yoon Hee.
Calm down.
Now is not the right time.
Please give me more time.
I'll deal with it.
Why do you need more time?
What do you expect from her?
Yoon Hee has already
betrayed you.
She'll do everything she can...
to kill you along
with Joo Dan Tae.
I know that.
- But now isn't the time.
- Why not?
Why can't we just kill her?
Just like how she killed Seol A.
I want to do that too!
But that won't be the end.
What will we do after that?
Do you think Seol A would want
us to become murderers like them?
What about Seok
Hoon and Seok Kyung?
I'm their mother.
I can't end my life so
irresponsibly like this.
I feel a lot more angry
and furious than you do,
and it's driving me crazy.
But I'm trying my
best to stay calm...
because I know we can't solve
this by being emotional.
I'm going to take
revenge in my own way.
I'm going to leave her until the end
and put her through the most pain.
So just stick to the plan...
and do things one by one.
That's the best we can do now.
Chairman Joo, what
took you so long?
This is an emergency situation.
You made us wait for so long.
Why did you want to meet
so early in the morning?
Why do you think?
We almost died, and our
kids were in danger too.
Are you just going to
sit back and do nothing?
Did you find Su Ryeon?
- No.
- You failed to find her?
Good for you.
You're doing great.
What?
Now, we finally know that
Su Ryeon was the one...
who's been blackmailing us.
Does she not care how much
she traumatized the kids?
How could a mother do
something like that?
But we can't report
her to the cops.
We're no better than her.
The kids already know everything,
so what's there to be scared about?
Let's sue her...
for kidnapping,
confinement, and blackmail.
I won't forgive her for this.
Come to think of it, you were
right about everything, Ms. Cheon.
Su Ryeon really turned
out to be Seol A's mother.
That means she's
been lying to us...
and planning this all along.
Did we make any mistakes?
I bet she consistently
gathered evidence.
What if we all end
up going to jail?
You're the one married to
her. Didn't you notice...
anything suspicious?
You always acted so smart.
But seriously, are you dumb?
He must not have noticed because
he loved his wife so much.
I admit that I made a mistake.
But what matters is how we
deal with it from now on.
If you don't want to
get fooled by her again,
all of us better stay alert.
Do you not understand?
We already confessed everything.
What's the use of staying alert?
Think about what kind of
situation we were in yesterday...
before we confessed everything.
You're right. We were forced.
We made false confessions
because we felt pressured.
Bingo.
If we say we lied because
we felt threatened,
the cops won't be
able to arrest us.
We must come up with a
story and stick to it.
Let's say Su Ryeon got
all of you involved...
so she could divorce me.
She wanted to get a
huge amount of alimony.
One more.
Let's also add that Su Ryeon...
was delusional and thought
Seol A was her daughter.
That's a good idea.
There's no evidence to prove
that Seol A is her daughter.
But what about Gu Ho Dong?
What will we do about him?
I'll take care of him.
I'll do everything
I can to find him.
We worked very hard to build
the Hera Palace Kingdom.
I won't let them destroy us.
Never.
I apologize, sir.
Do everything you can
to bring Su Ryeon to me.
I don't care if
it's just her body.
Eun Byeol.
Did you sleep well?
You shouldn't go to school
today. I'll call the school.
I messed up my midterm exams,
so I can't skip school.
It's okay to skip school.
Look at me.
Are you really okay?
Eun Byeol is stronger
than you think.
Hurry up and go to school.
Get there faster than
others and practice singing.
You're right. I should
stick to my normal routine.
It's not like I
did anything wrong.
You and Dad are the ones who
didn't raise me properly.
Eun Byeol.
You're going to
proceed with that?
Is it really necessary to hold
the inauguration ceremony?
Don't you remember what we
went through last night?
I did nothing wrong.
So why must I cancel my
plans like I'm guilty?
I won't let Su Ryeon
have things her way.
We're divorced, so stop
interfering in my business.
Are you not worried
about Eun Byeol?
Can't you see that
she's all broken inside?
She has nightmares every night,
and keeps talking
nonsense. She isn't sane!
Right now,
the best consolation
she can receive is...
to see her mother
become the director.
That's what I can
do to console her.
What's going to change if
you just keep babying her?
We can't let her get haunted
by Seol A all her life.
You're incompetent
and irresponsible.
You're the worst father.
You really are a
frightening woman.
Do you know what's going
on inside Eun Byeol's head?
She's scared that you
might've killed Seol A.
I didn't kill her.
That's what matters.
Stop making a fuss and make
sure you attend the ceremony...
as the director of
Cheong A Medical Center.
I found this on Mr. Gu's
desk this morning.
RESIGNATION LETTER
Resignation letter.
Go screw yourselves.
"Screw"?
He must've lost his mind.
How dare he tells
you to go screw...
Ma'am.
It's for the better since
he was always a nuisance.
He pretty much left you a gift in
celebration of your inauguration.
And everything is going well...
with the inauguration ceremony
that will be held this afternoon.
Today, I'll be
singing for you...
as a surprise event.
I'll be singing your
favorite song...
Okay, you may leave.
Okay, I'll see you
later at the hall.
RESIGNATION LETTER.
GO SCREW YOURSELVES.
Gu Ho Dong.
There's something
suspicious about him.
I knew it. Logan was the
one helping Su Ryeon.
Can we meet right now?
It's important.
So tell me. Why did
you want to see me?
Is Su Ryeon doing well?
I've been wondering
where she was hiding.
I'm relieved to know
that she's with you.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I know she's staying with
you in your hotel room.
I already checked.
So you don't need to lie.
As you already know, I
work for J King Holdings.
And the chairman is
looking for his wife.
And as his employee, I should
tell him what he wants to know.
For instance,
Su Ryeon's whereabouts
and whom she's with.
Then you should've
contacted Mr. Joo.
Why in the world
did you come to me?
Because I'm curious.
Why are you...
helping Su Ryeon?
Don't tell me you've
developed personal feelings...
for your business
partner's wife.
Now Ms. Oh,
why is it necessary for me to
explain my personal feelings...
to someone like you?
I'm sure this project is
very important to you too.
And I'm worried you
might ruin everything...
because of your
personal feelings.
Is it because of Mr. Joo?
Because apparently, to me,
you're the one who seems like you
have personal feelings toward him.
What did you say?
Now, did you really think that I was
going to go and invest my money...
without doing any background
research on my business partner?
Listen.
I don't care if
you're his employee...
or his little Juliet.
Because it seems obvious Mr. Joo's
private life seems rather...
disturbing anyway.
So why don't we keep all
this nonsense confidential...
for the benefit of both of us?
Because you do realize that we
have a very, very important...
investment conference
coming up, right?
We can't trust you...
as long as we know
you're helping Su Ryeon.
I'll have to tell the chairman
about your relationship with her.
Listen.
When this is over, I'm
planning to take Su Ryeon...
to America with me anyway.
Did she agree to go with you?
I'm convincing
her at the moment.
Obviously, she can't live
with Mr. Joo anymore.
But isn't that what you
wanted in the first place?
For me to get rid of her.
Su Ryeon is going to go to
the States with Logan Lee?
Hello?
Did you find out who's
helping Su Ryeon?
No, not yet. I need more time.
Will you do me a
favor and speed it up?
Yoon Hee knows about
our relationship?
How?
I think she saw you
entering the hotel.
I made sure she
won't say anything,
but we never know when she
might tell Joo Dan Tae.
I hope she at least
stays quiet...
until today's
investment presentation.
If Dan Tae finds
out before that,
everything will
go down the drain.
We'll just have to
leave it to fate.
Judgment day has come.
It'll all go well.
I hope so.
We must succeed...
for Seol A.
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
I'd like to announce
that Ms. Cheon Seo Jin...
got voted as the next
director of the foundation.
THE 7TH DIRECTOR INAUGURATION
CEREMONY OF CHEONG A FOUNDATION
CERTIFICATE OF
APPOINTMENT, CHEON SEO JIN
Congratulations.
Now let's hear Ms. Cheon's
inauguration speech.
Hello, I'm Cheon Seo Jin.
First of all, I'd like
to thank you all...
for making time to
attend the ceremony.
I especially would like to
thank all the board members...
who trusted me enough
to appoint me...
as the director
of the foundation.
THE 7TH DIRECTOR INAUGURATION
CEREMONY OF CHEONG A FOUNDATION
I will stick to my
late father's goal...
and make sure Cheong A stays
strong and transparent.
I promise that to
all of you here.
THE 7TH DIRECTOR INAUGURATION
CEREMONY OF CHEONG A FOUNDATION
HA YOON CHUL
What is this?
I got a text.
She got in using
her connections?
THE 7TH DIRECTOR INAUGURATION
CEREMONY OF CHEONG A FOUNDATION
THE HEAD OF THE ART DEPARTMENT
FORGED HER DAUGHTER'S GRADES...
TO GET HER ACCEPTED TO
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL.
Ms. Cheon, I'm Oh Song
Yi from Jeonghee Daily.
Are you aware that
someone sent a tip-off...
regarding the school's
entrance exam irregularities?
Did you really forge your daughter's
score to get her accepted?
I heard she sang out of tune...
and ran out in the middle
of the test. Is that true?
Is it true that you received
bribes from a few mothers...
and forged their kids'
grades in return?
- Ma'am?
- What do you have to say?
- Is it true?
- Tell us what happened.
We'd like an explanation.
Do you admit to everything?
Please explain...
What's going on?
What is it?
"CHEONG A FOUNDATION'S
IRREGULARITIES COME TO LIGHT"
ACCORDING TO THE TEXT,
CHEON SEO JIN'S DAUGHTER...
HOWEVER, OTHERS SAY SHE GOT A
HIGH SCORE THANKS TO HER VOICE...
I guess it's true.
I can't believe it.
SOME PEOPLE THINK IT'S NECESSARY
TO CARRY OUT AN INVESTIGATION...
What do you think you're doing?
Stop what you're
doing right now!
Hello, I'm Prosecutor
Oh Joon Hyuk.
I'm a huge fan. I'm sorry
we had to meet like this.
We have a search and seizure warrant
along with an arrest warrant.
You need to come with us.
Let me go.
Who do you think I am?
How dare you touch me!
Let me go! Get off me!
Stop what you're doing now!
Ma'am, this is bad.
The prosecutors took everything
from the teachers' office.
Ms. Cheon, what's going on?
What kind of a crazy jerk
could've reported you?
Do you think...
It's not a big deal.
There must be a misunderstanding.
It'll quickly be taken care of.
I want you to stay here...
and make sure the students
and parents don't get wavered.
Get off me. Let me go!
Ma'am.
Do you think I'll let
this get in my way?
I'm...
Cheon Seo Jin,
the director of
Cheong A Foundation.
- Hello.
- Yes, this way.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Hello.
Since our Myeongdong land
has been set as collateral,
we're big shots in
this business deal.
So let's not rely on
Chairman Joo so much...
and get involved aggressively.
We should do that.
Nothing went well all this time
when we trusted Chairman Joo.
That's what I'm saying.
Wait. You didn't go to
the inauguration ceremony?
The women of Hera Palace...
were all dolled up to go
there since this morning.
I know you're divorced and
all, but you're still...
a director of a
Cheong A Foundation.
You should've cast a vote.
If you did, you could've saved up
something for yourself later on.
If this investment goes well,
should I pay my wife a
huge amount of alimony...
and get divorced?
Can you stop saying
such stupid things?
I can't focus because
of your yapping.
Focus on what? We
haven't even started yet.
Something feels strange.
Why isn't Logan Lee here?
You're right.
Our rich investor from
the US is running late.
What's taking Logan Lee so long?
Call him again.
He's not the type to be late.
UNLOCK
SIGNED BY LOGAN
LEE AND JOO DAN TAE
Mr. Hong, let's begin.
Did he answer?
I can't reach him.
His phone has been turned off.
How could he turn off his
phone on such an important day?
The investors seem worried,
so why don't we begin the event?
You should begin with
the business briefing.
INVESTMENT PRESENTATION OF THE
INTEGRATED RESORT AND CASINO
Hello, everyone.
I apologize for making you wait.
I'm the chairman of J King
Holdings, Joo Dan Tae.
INVESTMENT PRESENTATION OF THE
INTEGRATED RESORT AND CASINO
Our joint investor,
Mr. Logan Lee...
is still in discussion with
the headquarters in the US,
so I will begin the briefing.
The biggest casino
ever in Asia...
will be built in the
center of Myeongdong soon.
The integrated resort and
casino that will be built...
will include the
largest-ever swimming pool...
and shopping center in line with
the fourth industrial revolution.
I guarantee it will become the
best tourist attraction of Korea.
I'll explain more
through the screen.
- This is the rate of return chart.
- Yes, Eun Byeol.
- It was provided by Myungjin Bank.
- What? I can't hear you.
- The expected investment...
- Hold on.
by J King Holdings is...
What's wrong, Eun
Byeol? It's okay.
Don't cry and tell me.
Yes.
What?
Tell me slowly, Eun Byeol.
Okay, I'm on my way now.
DETECTIVE
We expect a yearly profit
of 3.5 billion dollars...
per year.
Amazing!
Are you Chairman Joo Dan Tae?
Yes, I am.
What is it? You can't come in
here without an invitation.
It's a private room.
You are under arrest for
embezzlement, investment fraud,
and violation of the
Capital Market Act.
Arrest him.
- What?
- What is going on?
What are you doing?
Why would I commit embezzlement?
I have never broken the law.
You can talk at the
station. Take him away.
Who sent you people?
Who ordered you to do this?
Are you kidding me right now?
What do you mean,
"embezzlement"?
Why would I steal
the company's money?
You sold Logan Lee's name...
and gave false information
to the investors...
to receive investments.
Why would I sell
Logan Lee's name?
He's my partner for
our casino business.
Call Logan Lee now.
You can ask him yourself!
Are you looking for me?
Logan. Logan!
I'm glad you're here.
There seems to be
a misunderstanding.
Please sort out this
ridiculous situation.
You still don't get it
now, do you, Mr. Joo?
I'm the one who reported you,
Mr. Joo Dan Tae.
What? What did you say?
I am the one who reported
you to the police.
THE PENTHOUSE
I told you you were
up for a surprise.
It's only fair that they
suffer the same way.
- You piece of trash!
What's wrong? Eun Byeol!
You should experience the
sorrow of losing a child too.
I won't let you have your way.
You want me to
kill Shim Su Ryeon?
I'll wait until you come back.
I'll reveal the whole truth.
Go on and try it. Let's
see who wins in the end.