THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
Why were you standing there?
That way!
Forget "no touching" today.
Your Highness.
Are you all right?
Who is that?
Let us go. Go out.
EPISODE 9
I let them sleep in separate rooms
so they can rest comfortably,
but I guess I made a mistake.
I heard something
break in the house.
I woke up to that sound as well.
The door was ripped too.
It is suspicious, so
we must take a look.
However, we may end
up interrupting them.
It would not be strange if all of
our household goods ended up broken.
That is the passion
of newlyweds.
We should protect their privacy.
Keep your distance from the
house as you stand guard.
Yes, sir.
I should go to the annex.
Will you keep watch over them?
- Yes.
- Take good care of them.
Control yourself, woman.
You had to cause this
trouble, didn't you?
Do you want to fight with me?
Who on earth are
you fighting with?
Stay out of it.
This is between
Kim So Yong and me.
As long as I'm in here,
I'll move this body as I please.
The soul inside supposed to
be the owner of the body!
You must be still drunk.
You are unable to distinguish
between a dream and reality.
- Thank goodness.
- What are you talking about?
Even when I'm drunk, I
always find my way home...
No. This isn't a dream.
There's no way you would
show up in my dreams.
I am sorry that I appeared...
in your dreams.
Forget about your nightmare.
EPISODE 9, LIGHT AND DARKNESS
That tickles, Hong Yeon.
It is not here. If this is
not the place, where is it?
What is wrong?
He was not flustered
because of the past.
- Hey. Hey.
- What?
I was told we should not
go near the main house.
- Why?
- I do not know.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
Honestly, I am worried
about our Queen.
Did you hear anything?
About the Queen.
I heard that she runs
around all over the place...
when she wakes up
in the morning.
My gosh. Stop talking nonsense.
I saw her all her life, and
I have never seen her run.
- My gosh.
- It is true.
- My gosh. That is strange.
- No, that is what I heard.
- No.
- I do not believe you.
It is not.
- Oh, my. The chicken!
- Grab it.
Stop right there!
He was wearing the robe of
the Department of Justice.
That means...
You will end up
dead. Stop drinking.
I am thirsty.
The more I think it is
wrong, the more I want it.
I feel like I will
die of thirst.
If you are thirsty, you must
drink water, not liquor.
Over here. Bring us some water.
Yes, sir.
The more liquor you drink,
the thirstier you get.
I slept so well as if
I got hit and fainted.
I know.
My body feels so light.
You. You.
The land this house is on
must be good. I slept so well.
Is it natural for you
to wake up next to me?
Why would this be unnatural?
Unlike in the palace, we do not
need to pick a date to share a room,
so it is more natural to sleep
in the same room at your home.
It makes sense.
He's in enemy territory, so he needs
to sleep next to me as a cover.
Your acting is so good today.
Okay. Let's pretend we
had a hot night together.
It was such a hot night
that it's a complete mess...
in here.
I guess you remember
it this time.
I would have been sad if
you had not remembered it...
like our first night together.
Is this a side effect of
her memory coming back?
I'm like a calm
baby when I sleep.
I don't have time to waste here.
I need to become an irreplaceable
person to Sunwon soon.
So that even if a catastrophe
occurs in the Han family,
they will never find me.
The man in the mask and
I had the same target.
How much does Kim
Byeong In know?
The ledger must not
go into their hands.
I will return to the Palace
today no matter what.
I will get the ledger
You will get sick like this.
When is the Queen
returning to the Palace?
I will send a letter so she
could return with King quickly.
I have never found life in
the Palace to be boring,
but with the Queen gone for a
couple of days, it feels so empty.
Is the Queen's food
that exceptional?
It is not about her cooking.
I have grown to like her.
Affection can be
quite a scary thing.
I was hungry this morning...
I mean,
I missed the Queen dearly
which made me wake up.
Gosh, you have my
sympathy, Your Highness.
This is why being tamed
can be a scary thing.
I am under the impression
that I am using others,
but at one point, it was
me who had been tamed.
That is why you must find other
people who can be of use to you.
I will instruct the royal chefs
to learn the Queen's recipes.
You have made my life at
the palace very comfortable.
I have no reasons
to leave the palace.
This is why I hold
my current position.
It is to keep the perfect
world you have, Your Highness.
Oh, right.
Tell Byeong In to come and
see me from time to time.
Do you...
need to speak to him?
He is your adopted son. I
had been too indifferent.
I can give him some
errands from time to time.
You are getting old now.
You must focus only
on important matters.
Everything that concerns
you is important to me.
What are you doing?
Starting now, the
Department of Justice...
will check the identities
of the royal guards.
As royal guards serve to
protect the King by his side,
we must be thorough to
check their identities.
Do not allow them to
take a step forward.
All of the royal guards
have been verified...
through proper channels.
People can easily buy and sell
genealogy charts nowadays.
Who knows?
Some guards might
have entered...
the palace to plot treason
with fake identities.
Cooperate with us, so we
can fulfill our duties.
If you cannot find any
evidence of your claim,
I will...
use my authority to
the fullest extent.
That is if you can continue
to hold your position.
Unless you are involved
in the scheme, step aside.
- Search everywhere.
- Yes, my lord.
Search every corner.
Do not leave any document.
Bring all of them to the
Department of Justice.
- Yes, my lord.
I hope you had a peaceful night.
I have brought in
a beautiful bird.
What do you think?
The bird has beautiful feathers.
I have brought this precious
bird in to celebrate an occasion.
Do you have good news?
The ill-fated relationship
between the Queen...
and the Royal Noble Consort Eui
is stronger than I had thought.
There is something
I have not told you.
In fact, I have not told anyone.
It is a secret that only
the Queen and I know.
The Queen believes I have stolen
the King from her because of...
what happened eight years ago.
The poison on our arrow
is growing stronger.
It is time for us to
use our second item.
Yes.
It is difficult to
find something similar,
so it is taking me some time.
But I will bring it to you even
if I have to make it myself.
Use this.
They will find out about
our royal guards in no time.
Let us find a way.
A man from the Department of
Justice ran into you last night.
He saw your face. Will
that be a problem?
I do not think he recognized me.
If we run into each other again,
he will realize I was
going after the ledger.
But he was wearing a unique
mask. It looked like a goblin.
Did he have a scar on his chin?
Yes. It seemed like an old scar.
He is the one who
tortured O Wol.
So this confirms
that Kim Jwa Geun...
had made his move
through Kim Byeong In.
Fortunately,
he does not know that the location
of the ledger has changed.
Tonight is the last
chance we have.
Your Majesty, I have a
letter from the palace.
This is the letter from
Training Commander Kim Jwa Geun.
The head of the Department of
Justice has come to deliver it.
Any member of the
Department of Justice...
could have easily
brought it to me.
But you brought it instead?
Do you have that much
time on your hands?
I have brought it personally
as it is very important.
Your Majesty and the Queen are asked
to return to the palace right now.
The Training Commander...
is demanding me to
return to the palace?
He is relaying the message
from the Grand Queen Dowager.
I will stay here one more
night for the Queen's health.
- Tell him that.
- But...
I am done here.
Do not disturb the
Queen's rest and go back.
Gosh.
His Majesty seems very concerned
about the Queen's health.
I will relay that to him.
I will have breakfast with
the Queen in her room.
Bring us your usual breakfast.
Please make it light.
Yes, Your Majesty.
We will serve you
our usual breakfast.
As Royal Noble Consort
Eui's house is nearby,
I will ask about
O Wol and return.
That is a great idea.
I felt bad for turning
her away yesterday.
I will not be at the
palace for one more night.
Please look after her.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The Queen used to stay here all
day. But now that the Queen is gone,
the royal kitchen
feels so empty.
Now, I can breathe again.
Hey, you punk. Add
more canola oil.
You punk.
You must chop it more finely.
You must cook it quickly
not to mess up the shape.
Things here are surely
pleasant and peaceful.
I do love being the boss.
- Royal Chef!
- Stop it.
- Royal Chef.
- Go back in.
- Yes, my lord.
Excuse me, Court Lady Choi.
Court Lady Choi.
By the look on your face,
I take it that the Queen
has not recovered yet.
No. She has made
a full recovery.
Then, why the long face?
Lately, Her Highness has
put me through a lot.
So when she is not around,
I thought I would
not have to nag...
and I would feel at ease.
And?
I think I am getting
even crazier.
I am worried to death about how
unruly she would be without me.
Oh, my. They say you care more
about a troublesome child...
rather than a good child.
Stop frowning.
Here.
Open it.
I picked it up off the
ground on the way here.
These days,
you seem like mine but not.
These days, you seem
like mine but not.
Why did he give me the trash
he picked up on the way here?
My goodness.
The more I get to know
him, the weirder he gets.
He could just throw it away.
Why would he give it to me?
Oh, my.
Have you heard from O Wol?
Oh, no.
Did something bad happen to her?
She did not arrive at the house.
I think she went somewhere else
as she feels sorry for you.
I have been asking around about
her. Do not worry too much.
I told her about it over
and over but she still...
I am looking for the
norigae you handed to her.
If she had to go to the other
place, she would have sold it.
I am scared...
if I lose all my people.
When is His Majesty
coming back to the palace?
He is going to stay...
one more night.
It is not what you are thinking.
I cannot tell you the detail,
but it will be over tonight.
It is probably not
that the King...
does not have time to
care about other things,
but his feelings
for me have changed.
Probably it is only me who is
hanging onto the childhood memories.
I remember when I came
back to Hanyang...
and met you with His
Majesty two years ago.
Even if that day was the
first time he saw you,
he definitely...
would have loved you.
Your words encourage me.
So this is the usual breakfast.
I'm the one who needs to convalesce.
Why would you stay one more night?
I am staying to take
care of you, My Queen.
You receive treatment from doctors
and get medication from pharmacists.
The King has to take care
of politics, not my health.
Do you know how much the
citizens are suffering?
What you said is
right, My Queen.
Yes, eat the terrapin
soup quickly...
and go act like a king.
Don't waste the sacrifice
of the terrapin.
Rather than the sacrifice
of the terrapin, I will...
go out in disguise to see what the
people are going through today.
I will come back at a late hour,
which means I have to
stay one more night again.
You don't want to be at
the palace too, right?
How awful if it's even worse
than your in-laws' house.
Yes. It is nice and
comfortable here.
What kind of person is
Grand Queen Dowager?
She is the older sister
of Lord Kim Jwa Geun.
She did not once stop out of the
palace after she entered the palace.
If I present specialties
from outside the palace...
to Sunwon who never went
outside the palace...
You know...
They always eat gukbap
in period dramas.
What does it taste like?
How would I know the taste
of such a lowly food?
It is not that great.
It's scary how much you can
miss something from the past.
They made broth with beef
brisket and white radish,
seasoned it with doenjang and warmed
the rice up by pouring the broth.
It has a lot of meat too. It's
humble but has its own charm.
Jeotgal isn't used for the radish
kimchi that accompanies the gukbap,
so it goes well without
overpowering the taste.
They said Heonjong had gukbap every
time he went outside the palace.
Darn it.
I have to pay taxes for my neighbor
who ran away without paying them.
They are basically thieves.
Watch your tongue.
Do want to be beaten to death?
It is either I die
from biting my tongue,
or I run away and join bandits.
Watch my tongue? I
have nothing to lose!
They are taking everything. I
wonder what the King is doing.
What do you expect?
Of course, he is one of those
who are taking everything.
He is a puppet king who was given
the throne to turn a blind eye...
to these things and approve
anything they ask him to do.
Darn it.
Hey, hey.
I was listening behind you.
I see you have been
going through a lot!
The people are dying because
of such a foolish king.
Take this drink and
forget your worries.
From what I see,
you look like a
person of position.
I am a fake aristocrat.
The genealogical
was so expensive.
I am basically a beggar without this
garment and the genealogical record.
I heard some young people are
all looks but no substance...
these days and you
are one of them.
How dare you!
The country itself is all
looks but no substance.
If people have substances,
it will only be taken away.
That is funny.
Oh, my. This fake nobleman...
- has an interesting point of view.
- It is funny.
They made a man from the
traitor family a king.
It is not only empty
but also rotten!
Does it make sense that a
person from the family...
that committed treason throughout
generations from his grandfather,
father, and brother
became the King?
And what was the King thinking
when he accepted the throne?
He is living at the
mercy of the Kims...
who killed all his family
like a gutless loser!
I know.
- Darn it.
- It is true.
You've crossed the line.
You're free to curse at him,
but it's not nice to
talk about his family!
There's a line you shouldn't
cross even for malicious comments!
Moreover,
do you think being a king is all
about living a comfortable life?
Being on the throne, he's living
in danger of getting poisoned...
and getting his head chopped
off all the time. It's brutal!
Are you from the palace?
Are you a spokesperson
of the King or what?
Who on earth are you?
Me? I am...
I am a member of
the King's fan club.
- What?
- What is that?
"Fan club"?
Anti-fans are fans too.
Anyway, talk about his
family one more time.
I will just flip the table!
- Got it?
- Okay, okay.
Do not come near me!
I am sorry.
The bill, please!
Come here.
Oh, my.
Look at your temper.
Let go of me. Let go.
I really didn't get upset.
You said you're in disguise.
Your identity can't be revealed.
So I got angry for you.
Why? What?
You're a flipping
amazing actress.
Do you even know
what that means?
Is it not something good?
What does "fan club"
mean by the way?
I can say they're
honorable people
who wish for
someone's happiness...
and success with pure hearts.
So it is like a spirit guide.
How about "anti-fans"?
Well...
Those who are even more interested
in that person than the fan club?
Even more powerful spirit guide.
I do not deserve such
feelings you have in me.
Whatever. If I get dethroned,
I'll sell gukbap
and make a living.
Do not say such a thing.
I will not let that happen.
I am also your anti-fan.
Sure. That surely reassures me.
We should go our
separate ways now.
You and I have different goals.
Let's see if there's a good
restaurant people line up for.
"An" must mean
"comfortable". "Ti"...
"Fan"?
I thought I had devoted
myself to my studies.
I have a long way to go.
- Try our sample.
- My goodness.
- There is a lot.
- Oh, my.
- You should buy some, my lady.
- Try it.
- I want it.
- Gosh. What are you doing?
That looks good.
You startled me.
What are you doing?
If you go into sketchy alleys,
dressed in expensive clothes,
you will easily become a target.
- What target?
- My goodness.
May I ask what you rich
people are doing here?
This is what I am talking about.
Step aside. I do not
want to hurt you.
Do you like her?
Gosh, there is no point.
And quit dreaming...
that I am the only one here.
This is what I always felt.
As you are an educated bandit,
your expressions are classy.
- Be classy.
- Yes.
Do not worry. I
will protect you.
I am your anti-fan.
What is he saying?
That scared me.
Regardless of the
era and where I am,
I should always stay
away from shady places.
Take care of them
for me, Cheoljong.
But if something happens to him,
will history change?
Hey! I was in the
Special Forces!
He already lost?
Cheoljong.
Are you dead?
I don't know how to get home.
My gosh. What brings
a rich lady...
I thought you came back because
you were worried about me.
Did you come back here because
you cannot find your back home?
What happened to those thugs?
They ran after a guy who was
wearing a more expensive robe.
Do not worry. I
will protect you.
I am your anti-fan.
What is he saying?
The era we live in
is not peaceful...
that you cannot
show us your back.
You must recognize a
crisis when you are in one.
My gosh. That was like a poem.
Hey. Is that from
the Qing Empire?
It looks nice. If we sell it, we
can feed ourselves for five days.
Take it off.
You should never show your back.
I did not kill him.
But I plan to kill the
next guy that comes at me.
By the way, why is
he on the ground?
He is drunk.
Anyway, you got so lucky.
What's up with your clothes?
Come to think of it, I will not
be able to go around unnoticed...
in a nobleman's robe.
What are you doing?
I need to buy some things.
I left in a hurry, so
I couldn't bring money.
- Okay.
- You are robbing a robber.
Hey. No.
Let me see. It is not fair
to take the whole thing.
Have a bowl of gukbap.
Here.
- Let's go.
- What do you need to buy?
Go on.
He knew how to fight.
Seeing how he was
guarding the room,
I am sure the item exists.
Will you be able to recognize
him if you were to see him again?
Of course. My lord,
I need the medicine.
I made myself very clear.
I said if you failed, I will
not give you the medicine.
How will you pay me back?
Will you give me your hand?
I will repay you.
I swear it on my life.
All right. Guess what this is.
This is the moon jar
from the Goryeo Dynasty.
Really? This is so valuable.
- How much is it?
- It is fake.
Buy it if you want to use
it as a protection again.
How dare you con me?
Pick one.
I'm all-in.
My gosh. My lady, you cannot
gamble that much money.
This is a capitalistic
society where money wins.
- I'm all-in.
- I am sorry.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- My lady.
My lady.
- Open it.
A trickster like him must have
his gang around the table.
I am sure all the spectators
are there to encourage gambling.
You were born a king.
And yet, you seem to know
the streets inside out.
Goodness. But you
denied it so strongly.
That is my weakness.
My family has swept away in
a scheme to commit treason.
Prince Ganghwa.
My family history is my
weakness that drags me down.
Do you have nightmares...
where you get chewed out
in the court or what?
A real nightmare is not the
dream I have when I go to sleep.
A real nightmare...
Why did you stop midway?
I forgot what I
was about to say.
Actually,
I have been meaning
to ask you a question.
How come you have not told
anyone about that night?
- About what?
- How I tried to harm you.
Oh, that? I do not
want to get involved.
I just want to skate
over all the hardships.
I wish there would be
peace in our empire soon,
so I could lounge around.
Saving the empire is
totally not my style.
Gosh.
I should get up to greet
you, Prince Yeongpyeong.
But I slept on a cold mountain,
so my whole body aches.
If I had stayed there
for one more night,
my handsome lips
would have gone numb.
- Are you done?
- What do you mean?
Your whining.
Including some bragging.
I do have more to go on,
but I will stop here as you
seem to have an urgent matter.
Gosh. All right.
What is this about?
I heard that you
make the best masks.
Go pick some over there.
My gosh. The teeth...
I do not want a typical mask.
I am thinking about selling
unique masks to civil servants.
"Unique"?
These days, you seem
to be mine, but not
At the same time
Boil the water.
- Boil the water.
- My gosh.
Yes, sir.
- Royal Chef.
- Yes?
The Grand Queen Dowager would
like a late-night snack,
but I am not sure if you
will be able to make it.
Why you...
I have worked in the royal
kitchen for 30 years,
and it has been 12 years
since I became the Royal Chef.
How can I be worse than the Queen?
If anything, I am better than her.
I trust you fully.
Darn it. Again.
Again.
Hurry up.
This is all we have?
I milked all the cows
we have in the barn.
There is not a single
drop of milk left.
Nonsense!
What?
You incompetent jerk!
Your Highness.
I suddenly feel so annoyed,
and everything upsets me.
Neither one of
these mixed-up body,
and the other body that's
lying like a corpse,
feels like me.
I don't even know if my name is
Jang So Yong or Kim Bong Hwan now.
Well, your memory came back.
so I am sure you feel confused.
Do you know what
I hate the most?
I'm getting more
accustomed to this body.
I feel comfortable
wearing a skirt now.
You must be on your period.
I will bring you a pad.
SANITARY PAD
I'm...
on my period?
Court Lady Chun!
Yes, Your Highness.
Why has the Queen not
returned to the Palace yet?
I will send another
letter right away.
It is not like we are at war.
Send it as soon as the
sun rises tomorrow.
Yes, Your Highness.
Is my brother's word
not as powerful anymore?
It is a sin to get older.
I am so hungry.
I still have one left.
There is nobody in here.
Special Director Hong.
It is you. Come in.
Were you waiting for my return?
How did you know
I just came back?
Goodness.
Hold on.
How could you look so
terrible in two days?
Special Director Hong.
Did you lose all your
money to a swindler?
Did you lose the
deed to your home?
That is a mistake I made when
I was 14 years old and naive.
It is a bigger problem.
Did you lose the
deed to your land?
That already happened when
I went to get back the...
Your family has had a
lot of misfortune too.
Should I choose family or love?
That is the question.
Poor thing.
Poor thing. Goodness.
It really is a big problem.
Your Highness. The
Grand Queen Dowager...
requests that you come to
Tongmyeongjeon Hall quickly.
Did you call for me?
You do not believe that
you are at fault...
for the death of the
late king. Am I right?
That is why you are doing all
that you can to blame my family.
Your Highness.
You may insult me all you want,
but please protect
our late king.
You are using my son
as a shield again.
I cannot believe you are impudent
enough to blame someone else...
to cover up your guilt.
A human being must
know themselves...
to avoid making the
same mistakes twice.
Thank you for your lesson.
I am so tired that I
cannot take off my socks.
I would gladly take
them off for you.
It is Surit-nal soon.
That is the expiration
date of my tolerance.
I have returned.
I see.
I heard that the Department of
Justice was quite busy today.
I heard you went against
the Royal Guard Division.
Many things were suspicious,
so I wanted to find evidence
before reporting it to you.
There are many suspicious people
in the Royal Guard Division.
There are exactly
seven, I believe.
Were you aware of them?
Did you think I left them
alone because I was unaware?
If you look into them like that,
what do you think they would do?
They will dig themselves a
deeper tunnel and go into hiding.
They'll become more
clever and act in secret.
What you can see
cannot pose a threat.
You have to make them believe
that you do not see them.
That way you can go after
and kill them right away...
when they cause a problem.
I was short-sighted.
Did you think...
I simply put him in
that position because...
he is not capable of doing
what a king should do?
It is because I implanted
fears into his mind myself.
It is easy to handle
those who have fears.
If the one sitting on
a higher seat fears me,
my power is greater than his.
When it comes to matters related
to the King, I will ask you first.
Go in and take a rest.
They will never find
you if you hide in here.
I will come and get
you no matter what.
But until then, you should
never, ever come out.
What about my brothers?
What about you, Mother?
I am fine as long
as you are alive.
You are my only son.
If you die,
I will die anyway.
Hurry up!
It is all an illusion.
It is not real.
I should hurry and
get the ledger.
Was I mistaken?
It is impossible.
I am innocent, Won Beom.
I am falsely accused. I
cannot close my eyes, my son.
Won Beom! Won Beom!
- I did not do it.
- Won Beom.
- You are the only one who is alive.
- I am resentful.
- No, it is a lie.
- If your whole family died...
It is just a fear
inside my mind.
- No, no.
- I curse you.
- No.
Kim So Yong.
What is it? She
looks just like her.
Do you think you will be like
the number one Kim So Yong?
There is something they have in
common. They do not have mothers.
"This book is written
by a scholar of Joseon."
DONGMONGSEONSEUP, KIM SO YONG
I will discuss the summary
of Five Relationships.
Father and son, ruler and
subject, husband and wife,
elder brother and younger
brother, and friend and friend.
These are Five Relationships.
You memorized everything
until the book is ripped.
Why would you recite it again?
Today is my mom's funeral day.
It is her book.
So that is what you do
when you miss your mom.
DONGMONGSEONSEUP
I cry every day.
Then I found a
way to see my mom.
What is it?
If I die, I can see my mom.
You are alive.
Did you also come here to die?
What are you talking about?
I came here to die.
Do you want to live? Because
you are scared of dying?
No.
Everyone died except
for me. That is scarier.
Then...
let us go together.
Let us do it on
the count of three.
Yes.
The sound is coming from here!
Brother?
Do you know how much
I worried about you?
The whole family was
searching for you.
Brother.
I will come down.
Just give me a ladder.
Fine.
I am sorry. I thought about
it, but I want to live.
You actually want
to live too, right?
I will come back.
If you want to live,
if you want to live again,
come up to give it back to me.
- Does it reach the ground?
- Yes!
Father.
Please.
Lady So Yong, Lady So Yong.
Father, please. Please, Father.
Father! Please!
Please, Father!
- Please.
- Put the rock on it.
Father, no! Please no!
Father! You cannot do it!
No! Father!
Please no! Father! No!
Please, Father!
You cannot do it!
Father, no! Please, Father!
Father!
Both Mother and that child...
I did not believe
their promises anyway.
It will only stop after I die.
It will not stop until this
well is filled with rainwater.
Never.
Save me, save me!
Save me! Save me!
Save me! Please!
I am sorry! Please save me!
It is my fault.
I am responsible for his death.
Because I did not
keep the secret.
Because I told the
maidservant about him.
You heard what the adults said.
His family committed treason.
He did nothing wrong though.
You are a good
person, are you not?
Please, Brother.
Hurry up and come.
My brother is indeed
a good person.
Save me. Save me.
Please. Save me.
We should hurry and go.
You really came.
You came as you had promised.
DONGMONGSEONSEUP
I want to live.
Like you.
KIM SO YONG
People are afraid of darkness.
So they try to chase it away
by lightening it up with light.
CONFIDENTIAL
But the stronger the light is,
the darker the shadow is.
Hwa Jin.
MR. QUEEN
What happened?
I know right. I
almost touched him.
It was dangerous.
You might have
come as you wanted.
But you cannot go as you want.
I am sure it is fabricated.
You are saying it
is a fake identity?
I will defeat the barbarian
using another barbarian.
This is how I become
irreplaceable.
From K-food to K-beauty.
Fears and anxiety
paralyze one's reason.
You are indeed my anti-fan.
I had a lot of concerns,
but I found a way.