#ROMANTIC
#FREE-SPIRITED
#GIRLCRUSH
#VOLUNTARILY SINGLE
#IN A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP
HOW IS YOUR LOVE?
LOVESTRUCK IN THE CITY
One day, we wanted to know
how men and women in the city date.
To satisfy our curiosity, we decided to
follow several men and women in the city.
What is this? Are you filming me?
You didn't tell me about going on camera.
Hi, there.
You should have told me about this.
I would have put on a jacket or something.
Can this help promote my agency?
Hold on.
Hello.
Do you have a script?
Do I just talk?
Hi.
So should I look at you? Or the camera?
I'll just talk to the camera.
Gosh, this is awkward.
Should I introduce myself first?
Hello. My name is Park Jae-won…
I don't have to be formal?
Hi. I'm Park Jae-won.
I'm an architect. And I'm 32 years old.
Oh, my. This is so awkward.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Eun-o. I'm 29.
O3 MARKETING AGENCY
I'm a marketer. A pretty marketer.
My name is Choi Kyeong-jun. I'm 29.
I'm working at the company
my father and my uncle established.
I'm an architect.
My name is Suh Rin-i. I'm 29.
My job?
I have so many.
I'm interested in so many things,
so I can't pick just one.
MULTIPLE JOBS? PART-TIMER?
UNEMPLOYED? OUT OF WORK?
Done. Do it again?
This is kind of uncomfortable.
I'm a gym teacher at a high school.
I'm 30. My name is Oh Seon-yeong.
I love Seoul. And my life is fun.
People call me Serial Dater
because I'm always dating.
Will you add captions, too?
Where can I watch this later?
On TV? At a theater?
I write novels. I'm a novelist.
My name is Kang Geon. I'm 29.
We won't intervene in their lives.
When we think it's necessary,
we will share their interviews
with the others
or edit them to make this entertaining.
So
you may share what I said
in my interviews,
but they won't know who said it?
No? They'll know?
So will we know who's participating
in this interview thing?
Is that a yes or a no?
Fifty people?
Then, I might know some of them.
Yes, I'm in.
I see. So I can use this next time?
We won't be able to see each other, right?
But what do I get if I do this?
Nothing?
How come I'm getting nothing in return?
Not even money? I won't do it.
Wait. Then there could be
someone's ex-boyfriends or ex-girlfriends.
There's no one from my school, right?
They promised to treat their cameras
as their friends
and tell only the truth.
But some incidents made us wonder
if they were telling us the truth.
What? About my dating life?
When I was in a relationship?
I'm cool and gentle.
I don't get clingy. I'm just cool.
I'm true to myself when I date
and when I break up as well.
I'm passionate.
I fall in love fast
and fall out of love fast.
I just get over them when I break up.
A girl hit me in the street.
What's the point
of winning over a girl? Gosh.
Slate? What? Clap?
This? Clap?
One, two, three.
What is this?
I don't play games.
I think I'm quite nice.
Before I met my current boyfriend,
I'd dated
five men. Or three?
Wait. Let me do it over.
We'll let you be the judge.
OH SEON-YEONG
SUH RIN-I
CHOI KYEONG-JUN
KANG GEON
LEE EUN-O
PARK JAE-WON
DO YOU KNOW WHICH MAN OR WOMAN
YOU ARE COMPATIBLE WITH?
Do you know who you are compatible with?
-Bye.
-Men I'm compatible with?
Women I can have fun with.
Men I can talk to?
Talking isn't everything.
We must connect physically, too.
Are you asking what I think you're asking?
Why is everyone playing innocent?
It was about that?
Why can't you say it? Just be blunt.
Fine. I got it.
Cut it.
Have a good day.
It's about intimacy, right?
I can tell by the smell. It's pheromone.
Some smells work well for me.
Well, I think it depends on the man.
Seriously? Tell him
not to give himself too much credit.
Usually, I take the lead.
Yes. Next fool.
I'll be honest. There was one time
when I had to follow the girl's lead.
Just once.
Once? I doubt that.
I don't think dating is a big deal.
No. I think it's important.
Dating changed me.
I've dated a lot of women.
I loved it every time.
You think the girls felt the same way?
Men? They are all the same.
There's someone I cannot forget.
I have one, too.
It was a year ago.
She was the only one I could see.
It felt there was only
the two of us in the world.
I felt complete.
I felt a spark every time our fingers met.
I thought it was love, then.
I'll remember him forever.
Then, you shouldn't break up with someone
you feel that way about. Don't you agree?
Right. I messed it up.
No. I messed it up.
No, it was my fault.
Right. It was her fault.
Right. I don't want to make any excuses.
Of all people, why me?
Why did it have to be me?
He came to me when I really needed
someone like him.
I wish I'd never met her.
Thanks to him,
I've become who I am now.
I was a fool.
That fool
was a gift to me.
YANGYANG INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
BIN'S COMPLETE SURFING
Name, Park Jae-won. He's about 182cm tall.
Any other physical traits?
He's handsome.
He could pass for a hot model.
Which exit will he wait for me?
Send me his phone number.
There are so many people here.
No. Never mind. I'll just park
my car in the parking lot.
HANDSOME
-Did you find him?
-Ra-ra, let's end the call.
It better be him.
Are you Park Jae-won from Seoul?
-Yes. Hello.
-Hello.
You're here to pick me up.
-Hi.
-Is that all the luggage?
-Yes.
-Let me.
-No.
-No. I'll do it.
-I'll do it.
-It's fine.
-All right.
-Thank you.
-Get in.
-Okay.
-Put on your seatbelt.
What about Ra-ra?
Well, she's busy
with her ramyeon restaurant.
Ra-ra's Ramyeon.
"We serve all kinds of ramyeon."
That's the motto.
Right, I know that.
She ran it in Jeju Island, too.
-Right?
-Yes.
You asked me what kind of women
I'm compatible with.
I am
attracted to strange women.
And I'm compatible with such women.
ROLLING STARS IS A 4-PERSON
BRITISH ROCK BAND FORMED IN 1968
"HELLO, MY BEACH" WAS RELEASED IN 1978
THIS SONG HAS BECOME
REPRESENTATIVE OF THE BAND
ITS BLUNT, STRAIGHTFORWARD LYRICS
AND INTENSE MELODY STAND OUT
IT'S AN UPBEAT, COUNTRY SONG
ABOUT A MAN'S WISH
TO GET HIS OLD LOVER BACK
DESPITE HIS RESENTMENT TOWARDS HER
Have you ever
met someone and felt like
question marks were floating around them?
"What is she like? She looks fun."
You're curious, so you want to know more.
Do you know this song?
-Yes.
-Let's sing it together.
I couldn't let you go
So even the time
Couldn't take you away from me
Our memory together
Was deeply stuck like a thorn
I couldn't realize that it was hurting me
Sing it, everyone!
The memory of you and our past love
Became a thorn piercing through my heart
I begged you to go
I wanted you gone forever
That's how I fall in love.
I'm attracted to intense women.
Same here. It's fun to follow their leads.
I do everything they tell me to.
I like bubbly and cheerful women,
but she was like…
She was feisty.
She was just like that.
The level of her feistiness
was just right for me.
I was curious about you.
-Pardon? Me?
-It's funny, you know.
You rented a camper trailer
without the license.
I moved the trailer you rented
to a nice spot near the beach.
It's a really good one, by the way.
I've had 2 wishes ever since I was 20.
The first wish was
to live a month in a camper.
And the second wish was
to surf for a month, nothing else.
-You must like surfing, too.
-Yes. A lot.
But you can't tow the trailer.
I rented it so I could just sleep in it.
No honorifics?
You dropped yours first.
When in Ra-ra's Ramyeon.
I see. That's how she still rolls.
It's fun to speak casually.
So do you work there?
As a part-timer during my stay here.
Then, how will you get around?
I'll walk. I like walking
and riding bikes and motorcycles.
This makes no sense.
You'll just leave the trailer there.
I'll sleep in there.
Places like that would look beautiful
on rainy days.
Wouldn't it be nice to drink coffee
and listen to the rain over there?
Well, probably.
Right? Then, I'll make a U-turn.
Now? Hold on.
Where are you going all of a sudden?
To drink coffee in a camper on rainy days.
-What?
-Get the Class One license first.
You want me to get a license?
-Ms. Kim Se-jeong.
-Yes?
You scored 68 points.
You failed. Come out.
-What?
-Come out.
DRIVER'S LICENSE TEST
-You may begin.
-All right.
-Get out.
-What?
You may begin.
What are we doing here?
Ta-da!
I should've known that she was crazy.
But I found her craziness fun.
So that makes me crazy, too.
There are certain things
you only realize until much later.
Like when you realize you've been conned
after you were conned.
I now understand
how some people can be just blinded.
-My cousin was--
-Shut it.
-My cousin was like that.
-Hey. Stop that.
-Hello.
-Come on.
Hi, Han-gyeol. Wait.
What are you doing?
Mr. Park told me to throw it out.
I did. I'm changing the layout.
Have you gone mad?
The CEO already approved it.
The client is on board, too. Why?
I don't like where the stairs
between the first and second floors are.
We've changed it three times already.
What do you want now?
I'm not sure.
Do you have a plan?
You don't.
Damn it.
Ms. Lee Han-gyeol! Bring that back!
Don't throw it out. No!
Whenever I see a camper trailer,
I think of her.
Register for the test today
and take the exam tomorrow.
It only took a day for me
to get mine here.
-Right. You don't have your ID photo.
-Of course, I don't.
What?
-Hurry. Go inside.
-Come on.
-All right.
-No one looks good in these photos.
Let's see.
Here it goes. Smile.
Say, "Braised kimchi."
"Braised kimchi"?
What? Now? Braised kimchi.
ROAD TEST
It looks exactly like you.
-It does?
-Yes.
Seriously?
My gosh, look at this photo.
-I look awful in this.
-Put it on now.
I really hate this photo.
APPLICATION
All right.
Come here.
-Come here!
-Oh, my.
Wait.
All right. Let's go. Here we go.
Jae-won, you know
how to use the control panel, right?
Let me say this just in case.
Don't turn off the main power.
If the fridge's turned off,
it'll be a mess.
And as for the awning, when it rains,
you need to slant it. Okay? To this side…
What is it? Are you listening?
She sparkles.
Right. Doesn't she?
-She has a beautiful smile.
-Hey.
She's making Ra-ra and me
laugh a lot these days.
-Good girl. You're such a good girl.
-I noticed. She's fun.
-Good girl.
-She was dumped here.
-Do you like that? Do you?
-What?
A guy came to surf with her,
but he dumped her here.
How did she end up with such a jerk?
Look at her. She's so bubbly.
-Do you like it?
-She eats a lot.
That's the only drawback.
I like big eaters.
Do you want to take her?
-What?
-You can take her to Seoul.
Me? Really? Can I?
-Will she just come with me?
-Just take her.
She'll follow you if you feed her well.
By the way, when you bring her to Seoul,
get her neutered first.
What? What are you talking about?
I don't know how they found out.
Male dogs keep coming.
It's a hassle to chase them away.
Ma'am, does it feel nice?
I see. You were talking about the dog.
Yes. Our dog.
What? You weren't talking about the dog?
-Were you talking about Yoon Seon-a?
-Is that her name?
BIN'S SURFING & RA-RA'S RAMYEON
-Oh, right. Your phone.
-Okay.
Here you go.
Good.
Get your own phone.
Why would I?
I only use it to pick up customers.
-All right. Here.
-Thanks.
-What's going on?
-We're having a barbecue party.
Come and have fun.
Sorry for being too casual.
But that's how we roll here. Come on in.
What is this place?
This place is awesome.
-Gyeong-gu!
-Hey.
Here.
Here I go.
Is that all you've got, Gyeong-gu?
You try it, then.
-Me? Okay.
-Yes.
-Go!
-My gosh.
-Nice.
-Yes!
-Bottoms up!
-Is it my turn?
-It's okay.
-Hurry up.
-Hold on a second.
-Ra-ra, we need more food!
-Okay.
-That's all I've got.
-Thank you.
-You have to go slow.
-You're good.
-All right. Take your time.
-I will.
-You can do it.
-I can do it. I'll go slow.
Going well?
I think so, thanks to you.
Seon-a. It's the last round.
-I need your support.
-Okay.
Wait.
-Here I go.
-Standby, three, four.
Okay. Great.
-Yes!
-Nice.
That's it. That's the last one.
-Nice. We won.
-Yes, we won.
-I'm sorry.
-Gosh.
What's going on?
Let the game begin.
Gamers, come on out!
Four men and three women.
Two men and two women.
Three men and four women.
-Come over here!
-Over there!
Four men!
What? It's just us?
Three, two, one.
-One man and one woman.
There are only men left.
Come on. There are no women left.
-That's random. My bad.
-What was that?
Is it broken?
When I look at a girl's eyes, I can tell
if she's compatible with me or not.
I can sort of see
her facial expressions in her eyes.
I just felt it at that moment.
I knew that she and I would be compatible.
Tonight's winner! Congratulations!
Good job, everyone!
I liked everything about her.
Her breathing sound
and her smell up close.
Her weird hairstyle and clothes
she threw together without much effort.
Everything about her seemed perfect.
I just liked her.
I find others' dating stories
kind of funny now.
"At that moment, the fireworks went off."
I'm sorry. I laughed too loudly.
I bet they heard bells, too.
I heard cannonballs.
Well, everyone thinks
their love life is special.
It's a beautiful story.
A man went on a trip
and met a beautiful woman there.
And fireworks went off that night.
Their eyes met.
And their hearts fluttered.
I'm serious.
All those things happened all at once.
It's possible
if that woman was insanely attractive.
That's when you must realize,
"I'm not myself right now."
Let's say you came back to your senses.
But what if you don't get together?
You'll be alone forever.
No, I'm not. I am not alone.
If I get to live that moment again?
I would still…
If I were to meet him again,
I would fall in love again.
Yes, I think I would.
Boom, boom.
Boom!
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs