THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
They say your arrow does not fly
straight when you are troubled.
EPISODE 11
I apologize for requesting
a meeting with you so late.
Why would you say such a thing?
You are seeking me out
when you are troubled,
so I am grateful for that.
If only this was a dream.
If only this would all end when
I wake up. That would be so nice.
I have something to give you.
CONFIDENTIAL
Please drag the Queen down into
the nightmare I am living in.
My King.
You appeared in my
dreams last night,
and such a big power
came into my hands.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
NO TOUCHING
AWESOME, MAGIC HOUR,
ATTENTION SEEKER
SHOWDOWN, JASMINE
TEA, ILL-MANNERED
You're so cute.
Your Highness.
My, did you lose your voice because
you've been calling me nonstop?
Your Highness.
How is the temperature
of the water?
I like it.
What on earth are
you doing here?
My Queen.
Today,
I shall forget "No touching".
Your Highness. Are you awake?
Goodness.
How did you end up looking
like an executioner overnight?
How dare he ruin
my sexy bath dream?
Call him in right now!
Yes, Your Highness.
Call him in...
Who shall we call?
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
You look like you are in
good spirits, Your Majesty.
I slept the entire
night without waking up.
Start preparing for
the banquet today.
Okay.
EPISODE 11, THE ONE
WHO CANNOT BE FORGIVEN
Doctor.
I had a nightmare.
But what's scarier
than the nightmare...
is the fact that
I felt disgusted,
but I also liked it
at the same time.
I don't know if this is how I feel
or if it's how this body feels.
I feel like I've been assembled
by pieces from here and there.
That's right.
It feels like I've
become a set of Legos.
Who on earth am I?
But the thing is...
why are you calling me "doctor"?
You're making me
break character.
Just listen. It's just
a type of convention.
So what is the
opinion of the expert?
After you've been in
a vegetative state,
some of the common side effects
are changes to your body.
It's common?
So this is common.
That is actually
quite comforting.
Just hearing that makes me feel
like my anxiety is going away.
One who can heal without
performing any acupuncture...
is truly a great physician.
It turns out that...
our royal physician's
specialty was in psychology.
Then when will my mixed up
and duplicitous state...
going to be relieved?
Those are all issues
related to your heart.
Once you accept it, it will
not trouble you anymore.
If it does not trouble you, that
is when you can start living.
I have to accept
myself as who I am?
It makes sense. The only consistent
thing about me was my inconsistency.
Oh, right.
The medicinal herbs you used
for the beauty cover were great.
Take that experience...
and make something
to apply on the face.
Elasticity, glow
and brightening.
Make sure the functions attract
attention as soon as you hear them.
She's going to need a new one
every 28 days, so make a bunch.
Why is it every 28 days?
That's how long it takes
for your skin to regenerate.
Every time she has dead skin,
she will need me.
Your Highness.
Great Lord Yeongeun
has come to see you.
Was it really the Royal
Consort's court maid?
That is what she believes.
I am hoping that the court
maid who sold the norigae...
was O Wol.
She must be really upset.
I must go visit her.
Your Majesty. The Royal Consort
Eui has come to see you.
Tell her to come in.
Royal Consort.
Excuse me.
I have drawn a
composite of O Wol.
Because I am the one who
remembers her appearance the most.
I am sure...
that the person who sold
the norigae was O Wol.
There is no way she would end
up like that in the Palace.
You will be able to
know for sure with this.
Please excuse me.
Okay.
I just heard.
You must have been so
upset alone last night.
I pulled myself together all
night, so do not worry too much.
I have something to tell you.
It is about how you
feel towards the Queen.
It is harder to
overcome yourself...
than to overcome another
person. That is why...
you should not try to
stop your feelings.
What I want from you
is not your apology.
Are you doing okay so far?
It has only been a day since
I have returned to the Palace,
so I am fine.
However, I will be busy due to the
investiture of the Royal Concubine.
The investiture of
the Royal Concubine.
While you were at home,
did anything strange happen?
Anything strange?
I picked up a king while I
was passing by the well but...
No. Is something wrong?
Well...
After having the
two of you at home,
the house feels empty
without you there.
I suppose that is the problem.
Why don't you see His
Majesty before you go?
I'm saying the parties involved
should handle it on their own.
No, it is okay.
I am sure he is busy
because of the banquet.
Your Highness, I have brought the
letter to the house of the fiancee.
You should take care of
business. I will get going now.
Your Highness.
Even if they fill the
spot of 100 concubines,
they cannot dare...
to fill the spot of the Queen.
Right. Of course.
Please take care of yourself.
Goodbye.
HAN SI OK
Take out everyone
from the Han family.
We don't want to end up
like "Romeo and Juliet".
What happened with what I asked
for? The Han family registers.
Pyeongsan Han clan.
Hanyang Han clan.
Anbyeon Han clan.
- Yangju Han clan.
- Hold on.
Are all of those Han
family registers?
Yes, Your Highness.
Gosh, this is
getting out of hand.
This won't do. I need to
win her favor properly.
DS. I should start doing that.
- DS?
- Door-to-door sales.
Is it already time for a meal?
It is time for you to
share it with your skin.
My gosh, you are
blinding my eyes.
This glow must be from
out of this world.
Thanks to you, my entire day is
filled with taking care of myself.
I have not been paying
attention to the investiture.
I am sure you are doing well.
I am doing my best.
Of course. If you see one
thing, you have seen it all.
You do everything so well,
so I trust you.
There is something that...
I prepared especially for
you, Grand Queen Dowager.
If you sprinkle this
magic powder on your hair,
it will make you look
10 years younger.
It's hair powder.
You do not need to bother
with putting mulberry juice...
on your head every morning.
Oh, my.
Gently. sprinkle the powder.
Sprinkle it.
It is a completely
different person.
Her eyes were a
bit more slanted.
Wait, was her left
eye more slanted?
I'm hungry too
Okay.
Her face was slim, and
she had chubby cheeks.
She had a wide forehead,
and her eyes shined.
Like this.
Her nose was straight
but round at the end.
Your Majesty. The
Royal Chef is here.
I think sweet flag liquor would
be good. What do you think?
Pardon?
Oh. I was lost in my thoughts,
so I was ahead of myself.
I was thinking about the
liquor to have at the banquet.
Your Majesty. I have
prepared something.
Punish me with
death, Your Majesty.
You can be at ease.
That way things
will go smoothly.
If you say so.
Are you comfortable like
that? Come here then.
Hey.
It is a traditional
banquet set-up.
The banquet I have in
mind is a bit different.
I want to reduce the number
of dishes and remove...
the big, unnecessary
set up in the middle.
- I apologize, Your Majesty,
- Okay.
but a royal banquet...
is supposed to be big and fancy.
So as unnecessary
as it may be...
Have you lost your mind?
Starvation is common
for the people.
How can I waste food
just to please our eyes?
Then, as for the
food we will prepare,
we will bring starving people
outside the palace and feed them.
Modest, but not shabby.
Fancy, but not extravagant.
That is the banquet
I have in mind.
I will give everything I
have for the next two weeks.
Let us work together.
Your Majesty.
How can a man cry
so easily like that?
I cannot believe he kept
such a detailed record...
of the sources of the bribes.
The Queen's father is more
meticulous than I thought.
Royal Noble Consort Eui's enemy is
not the Kim clan. It is the Queen.
That is why she fails
to see the big picture.
We must use the ledger
more effectively.
We will bring the fall
of the Kim clan...
and dethrone the Queen as well.
A ledger?
What was he thinking? How could
he keep such a dangerous item?
I should...
Keep it a secret for now.
If the clan finds out,
people will be agitated.
My goodness. That man...
Anyway,
who do you think
has the ledger now?
The King stayed at his
house for two whole days...
and ignored the request of
his attendance in the palace.
The...
The King?
He is planning to expose us
at the banquet on Surit-nal.
He may have a weapon with him,
but we must make him weak,
so he cannot hold his weapon.
From Kim Mun Geun's
point of view,
I am the only suspect left now.
But he cannot question the King
if he had stolen the ledger.
He must be in a tight spot.
Have we found out the identity
of the man behind the mask?
No one from the
Department of Justice...
has a scar on their chin.
Even if we fail to
obtain the ledger,
we must be able to devise a
plot to carry out our plan.
Have you looked
into other clans?
The law of five seconds.
It only takes five
seconds to fall in love.
Your Highness, everyone is here.
- This is everyone?
- Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Let me see.
Women I felt a spark with...
She was nice too.
Lady Yoon. I'd love to know
more about your life...
because you have
such a nice aura.
In my hometown, there is
this beautiful mountain.
It is called Mount Gamak.
- Mount Gamak?
- Yes, Your Highness.
That is amazing.
- "Amazing"?
- Your Highness.
- Yes?
There is a big
palace in my town.
The palace was built
by King Jeongjo.
Is Hwaseong Palace is the only thing
you can brag about your hometown?
That is all you ever talk about.
Now, you may have one more
thing to brag about...
if you become a
consort, Lady Hong.
Your Highness. Thank you.
In the empty lots from my hometown,
there are many peach trees.
When the flowers are in bloom,
they are gorgeous.
And my mother dreamed of
peaches when she had me.
I knew it.
If a peach were to
be born as a girl,
it would look just
like you, Lady Min.
Peach.
If you can win over
these three clans,
you can have a dragon and
two phoenixes on your sides.
So you will be riding
on a white tiger's back.
As Hwaseong Palace
guards the gate...
and I adore the
scenery of Mount Gamak,
the sweet aroma of
peaches fills my room.
The Papyeong Yoon clan.
The Namyang Hong clan.
The Yeoheung Min clan.
This is a good
balance of the clans.
Innocent, sexy, and cute.
How harmonious.
Gyeong Ok of the
Papyeong Yoon clan.
Ja Yeon of the
Yeoheung Min clan.
Sim Hyang of the
Namyang Hong clan.
I assign you the rank of Grade Two
in the Internal Court, consort.
The three of these consorts and
their families joined my family.
So tell the elders
of your families...
to attend the
banquet on Surit-nal.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
The King started to
build his own allies.
But they are bound
to leave him...
once they find out he
is weak as a kitten.
The King insisted
on having a banquet.
Is this what he wanted?
- I hope you are getting it ready.
- Do not worry.
Yes!
Everyone must've been dying to
see what was beyond the walls.
They are so good at neolttwigi.
The Queen Dowager is coming.
I hope all is well with you.
It has been a while,
Royal Noble Consort Eui.
- Hello, Your Highness.
I will head to the archery
range and practice my archery.
It has been quite some time...
you woke up from the
vegetative state now.
But you did not
come to see me once.
I have been busy...
with selecting the royal
concubines after I returned.
My apologies.
Given that you had a near-death
experience, you seem too well.
I am very healthy.
So you must have given
up to hunt on Surit-nal.
Instead of practicing
your archery at the range,
you are here,
jumping on the plank.
I am sure Royal Noble
Consort Eui will win anyway.
I decided to enjoy the process.
I may be good at the "haunting",
but I am not good
at hunting at all.
"Haunting"?
Do you know why...
the young women of the
Internal Court going hunting...
on Surit-nal?
No, I do not.
On Surit-nal, we chase
away evil spirits.
People used to chase
away the evil spirits...
with the blood from
their killings.
Now, we are hunting
animals instead.
Actually, there was a body
from the well at the palace.
People are saying she was Royal
Noble Consort Eui's court maid.
In the well?
Gosh. Why?
Your Highness.
- Please come.
Okay.
- My gosh.
- No way.
- She is so good.
- Your Highness.
A triple axel.
I can't sleep and feel restless.
Should I send a message
to my dear consorts?
What would be good?
A simple opening line that isn't too
burdensome but provokes emotions.
I got it.
Deliver these to them
at the royal villa.
Yes, Your Highness.
Oh, right.
Tell them to see if
the King stops by.
Yes, Your Highness.
One for each consort
at the royal villa.
- Check on His Majesty.
One for each consort
at the royal villa.
- Check on His Majesty.
Seriously?
After you.
- One for His Majesty.
- Check on royal consorts.
What?
- One for His Majesty.
- Something has changed.
- Check on royal consorts.
"Are you sleeping?"
Well...
Are you sleeping?
Why is she so
curious about this?
It is three "Are you sleeping?".
The reply was delivered.
I sent 3. Why there's
only one reply?
Is everyone putting
too much effort?
Let's see.
What a beautiful handwriting.
She's indeed from a noble family.
I went out on a sleepless night.
There is something that shines
on the dark sky at night.
I looked up wondering if it was
the moon. But it was my friend.
What a cringey but
emotional text.
If so, I will also...
- Hong Yeon.
- Yes, Your Highness.
This is a reply. Send it to
the person who sent the letter.
I sometimes think
of other things.
I will be happy drowning to
death in the thought of you.
Please row to me.
Oh, I did not let you go.
My Queen.
I finally made use of what I learned
for the college entrance exam.
Nice. This is how I'll
rediscover my identity.
Okay.
Follow the same recipe,
but instead of
extravagant croaker,
pomfret would be nice.
POMFRET IS A KIND
OF BUTTERFISH.
Should I get some inspiration
for the poems for my letters?
My Queen.
Darn it.
You! I said you're not allowed.
But...
At the investiture, I was
acting like we were a couple...
as it was an official ceremony.
It's an important time for
me to rediscover my identity.
Please cooperate.
How rude.
Darn it.
How can she be so different?
She is shier than she looks.
The menu list for the
ceremony is completed.
Please work on that.
Did you check the offering
list for the Dano ceremony?
Here it is.
Why do they keep
saying "erection"?
The menu "erection" refers
to the list of foods.
Offering "erection" is a record
of items for ritual ceremonies.
What is the matter,
Your Highness?
Really? Am I the
only trash here?
Your Majesty!
You overwork yourself every day.
You should go and have
a rest, Your Majesty.
No.
We do not have time.
Let us keep going on.
I almost felt sorry
for him again.
This is not good. I should send
even more emotional letters today.
"Erection" is indeed
a dangerous word.
Unlike what history says, he has
a nosebleed for the other thing.
The name I will die calling!
It will linger in my mind
as I cannot forget it.
How can she be so
different day and night?
Is she having a hard
time deciding...
whether to forgive me or not?
There is no way to forgive
me for the broken heart.
Would there be a path
we could walk together?
I hope we can walk together
from the beginning next time,
even if it is in dreams.
Practicing sword at night?
Having one crazy
person is enough.
We need to prepare for the
sparring at the Dano ceremony.
Do it with the people from
the Department of Justice.
How do you evaluate
your own swordsmanship?
I do not know.
I never tried my best
because I am not interested.
That is why I need you.
An opponent whose
ability is unknown.
SURIT-NAL
LONGEVITY AND GOOD FORTUNE
DAEJOJEON HALL
The weather is
amazing, Your Highness.
Is that so? That's nice.
I hate when it
rains on sports day.
My father will come. So it
should be more glamorous.
It is the first day I will present
myself in front of everyone.
Pay extra attention.
Yes. I look pretty.
Everyone will be
looking at me, right?
Are you planning to
use a metal arrowhead?
Today, I have...
a big game to catch.
All right. This must
be delivered quickly.
Let us hurry.
Hello, my lord.
We have the fresh ingredients for
the Surit-nal banquet today...
and the royal offerings.
We must hurry to the
palace. Please excuse us.
- Do you have a document for them?
- Of course.
Here you go.
It is time to dress,
Your Highness.
Give me a moment.
It is a very important day.
I should at least try to
read my fortune with this.
Let me see. The card for
the Pungyang Jo clan.
TOJANG: A LOW CARD IN TUJEON
The rabbit card.
Well, luck is relative.
Let me see. And the
card for the King.
What?
"Injang". The ninth card.
Will the tables turn?
Now, this is for the Queen.
Dragon?
EOJANG
The eighth card. Darn it.
I hate my reading today.
Is the Queen...
plotting something again?
The Queen Dowager is here.
You could have let me know in
advance that you were visiting.
You will not even hide
your dislike toward me.
When I was the Queen, such
actions were unheard of.
Regardless of the eras,
no daughters-in-law would want to
be ambushed by their mothers-in-law.
Look at you, talking back to me.
I heard that you are cooking
for the Grand Queen Dowager.
But you have never offered
me a single refreshment.
You must fear...
your grandmother-in-law
more than you fear me.
My gosh. No, that is not true.
The Grand Queen Dowager
takes good care of herself,
so she seems young.
But she cannot defy time.
You should think more carefully.
I will live longer than
the Grand Queen Dowager.
I will serve you my
food some time...
I must eat it now.
I am curious about your cooking
which I only heard about.
I cannot wait.
Right now?
Is this the beginning of
bullying from my mother-in-law?
My gosh. I'm so annoyed.
What is she hiding?
Royal Chef. I need
the grain syrup.
What will I do without the fresh
ingredients for the banquet?
All the guards around
the wagon died.
What could I do?
My goodness. Come on.
- The dried fish.
- What?
The dried fish. The dried fish!
The Royal Chef is
too busy these days.
I can't boss him around.
Where's the grain syrup?
I WENT OUT ON A
SLEEPLESS NIGHT.
"I went out on a
sleepless night..."
Royal Chef. Royal Chef!
- Your Majesty.
What is this about?
Your Majesty.
These are precious ingredients.
They are all rotten!
They must have been
stored improperly.
Punish me with
death, Your Majesty.
That cannot be.
No one would have ruined them
unless their safety was guaranteed.
Royal Chef!
Your Majesty.
We have a problem.
Someone added stones
in the rice jab.
- What?
- We cannot serve anything.
Do not worry. Do everything
you can on your end.
I will do whatever it takes
to get those ingredients.
Yes.
Goodness. What are you doing?
Royal Chef! Hey!
I should show her how I'm
bringing the food all by myself.
That will help her
feel better, right?
The mix of sweet grain
syrup and salt makes...
the perfect example of
sweet and salty dishes.
Over there, I see a
beautiful mountain
Secretary Han?
You jerk!
How dare you?
My popcorn!
You!
That scumbag!
Where are the refreshments?
Well...
Here.
You can look forward to
your life at the palace.
Given the circumstance,
you must get the ingredients...
once you are done with your
demonstration of martial arts.
Yes.
Thank you for inviting
us to this banquet.
You deserve to be here.
The consorts are
doing well here.
I hope all is well with you.
- Yes.
Anyway, have a good day today.
Is the Queen Dowager
not here yet?
I will find out.
TONGMYEONGJEON HALL
I thought you ran away.
Of course not.
If anyone has committed a crime,
they must be punished accordingly.
I am glad that you
are aware of it.
The Queen sent me some
snacks in the morning,
and I started getting ready
late because I was tasting them.
The Queen did?
I feel like I'm going to die being
stuck in the middle like this.
Is she having another
misunderstanding?
No way.
The Royal Guard Division will put
on a martial arts performance.
Attention!
Round one.
How dare he try to harm
the Queen with that sword?
Spar.
Oh, my. The King has
prepared very well.
Grand Queen Dowager. It
is time to go hunting.
Your Highness. You should
change into your hunting attire.
I will be back,
Grand Queen Dowager.
I will be back.
First line, prepare to shoot.
Fire!
I thought this was all for show.
It's all about what
items you have.
I think I look cool right now.
I like it. I look
cool right now.
Why does she look so determined?
There are always those who
take sports days so seriously.
What's with that glare?
A bird is worth 1 point, a
rabbit is worth 2 points,
a badger is worth 3 points,
a boar is worth 4 points,
a deer is worth 5 points,
a wolf is worth 7 points,
a bear is worth 9 points, and
a tiger is worth 10 points.
WOLF, TIGER, RABBIT, DEER
You will each be
given 10 arrows.
For a fair match, your
court lady and court maid...
will not join you.
How cruel.
This would make people
sign a national petition...
if it happens in
the present day.
Then we will get started.
You may now go.
I should just waste
some time and come back.
The hunting competition
today is so predictable.
It is a competition for
the pride of each family.
But the Queen does
not seem interested.
I did not know you have enough time
to care about a playful competition.
You might see your
son's face today.
It is time to give you my gift.
On the night when the Queen has
fallen into a vegetative state,
Royal Noble Consort and the
King were going to share a bed.
The Queen woke up...
only a day after she fainted.
Do you mean she pretended
to lose consciousness...
to keep them from sharing a bed?
The Queen put
everything at stake...
to win the King's heart.
Diving into the lake...
throwing herself in front of the
sword pointed at Consort Eui.
She even put the last
thing she has at stake now.
The Queen abandoned her family.
I was getting bored, and
you told me a funny story.
The King insisted on giving
a banquet out of nowhere.
And the Queen rushed the
investiture of royal consorts...
to select families in power.
As if she chose the ones
who can support the King.
The King will reveal
the true side...
he has hidden in front
of the officials today.
As a strong ruler.
Can you see it now?
The Queen moves for the King.
Are you not afraid of your
future saying such things?
You must have believed the
Queen would never betray you.
I was actually disappointed.
You were bewitched by the
Queen's cheap tricks...
and fooled like that.
I guess you are old now.
I will tear those lips off.
The Queen pretended to faint.
Then I committed no sin.
So I am not afraid anymore!
Why did you stop playing?
You made Grand
Queen Dowager upset.
Next,
the King will grant
you with Dano fans.
You have worked hard. I am
excited for the banquet.
I also saw you working hard.
Grand Queen Dowager has come.
You are here.
The royal banquet was so boring.
I could not stand it.
I was wondering if the
banquet here is any better.
I am sorry that I
could not please you.
I wanted to see the martial arts
demonstration but I was late.
Well, it is just as boring
to see the staged event.
I would rather have
them spar for real.
I will make the royal guards
compete with each other.
How about doing it yourself?
I heard you chopped
firewood in Ganghwa...
and delivered water for living.
With that stamina, it
would not be so hard.
Manual work and martial
arts are different.
Furthermore, I only have sat on
the throne for the past few years.
My body became stiff.
You may use a Dano fan
instead of a weapon.
How about competing against the
head of the Department of Justice?
You are around the same age.
The head of the
Department of Justice...
is a warrior who has
professionally trained for years.
I am worried the
King might get hurt.
If you want to watch a
match, I will have others...
I have to see how
the King fights.
What do you say?
Father was wrong.
Please see the King's
true face on Surit-nal.
DEER
Darn it.
BEAR
Go.
You are not the prey I
have been looking for.
Is it the wrong way?
I think I saw this tree earlier.
Where should I go?
We will hold a fan in our hands.
The person who takes the fan
from the opponent will win.
Be gentle.
What is going on?
I said be gentle.
How will you take responsibility
for hurting the King's body?
It is Grand Queen
Dowager's order.
I cannot do anything
but do my best.
So you have Grand Queen
Dowager behind you.
Then I shall teach you
a thing or two again.
Let me show you who
this palace belongs to.
You said he is different
from the late King.
He is indeed different.
Whatever.
I should just take a nap. They
will find me when it's over.
My gosh!
What are you doing here?
What do you think I am
doing? I am hiding to live.
It's not like you'll die for
real. Why are you so scared?
I know but the arrow
hurts quite a lot.
I still have bruises
from the last year.
You're such a crybaby.
Don't worry. I'm not
interested in hunting.
I will get shot by someone
else's arrow anyway.
My gosh.
How can you just come
back here like this?
TIGER
Like this?
Thank you, Your Highness.
This is a souvenir.
Go.
Already?
I did not know the Queen's
archery skills were that great...
to catch a tiger so quickly.
She is an archery master.
I did not see her and only
heard the sound of the wind.
Then I got shot just like that.
Really?
It was you.
You were that person.
I will not forgive you.
I will take your life.
MR. QUEEN
I have regretful news.
My hand slipped...
and I shot an
arrow to the Queen.
The banquet is about to begin, but
the ingredients did not arrive.
Is this all?
Is it you who put the drug?
The name is Lee Saeng Mang.
I will make a new menu list
according to the ingredients we got.
How dare you fry
my precious needle?
What we will make today
isn't ordinary food.
It's the face of the president.
How dare you refuse to obey
the orders of your superior?
- Catch them!
- It is not disloyalty but mutiny!
You have to pay the price for
letting your temper control you.