Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 16
It’s still early in the morning.
I wondered what was shining.
Turns out my sister is gleaming.
Sister.
You know I care for you.
The latest news through the grapevine.
In Feixian House,
there has been a great storyteller.
He’s got a glib tongue.
He tells stores so wonderfully!
So…
Go have fun with me?
You’ve been bullied by me since little.
It must be hard for you to grow up.
Go enjoy the storytelling with my money.
Thank you, Ban Heng.
Your Majesty.
Princess Royal’s funeral has been done.
Commander Shi takes care
of sealing her mansion.
This is the receipt
from the Imperial Household Department.
Duke Ban and Princess Ban asked
to see His Majesty!
Your Majesty, thank you
for making me Duke.
Long live Your Majesty!
You’re my cousin.
Families don’t need to say thank you.
Your Majesty, I know you care for me.
But I’m extremely afraid
when I’m promoted to Duke Jingting
without making any contributions.
Are you blaming me
for not protecting Aunt?
Your Majesty.
I don’t mean that.
My mother regarded you
as her own son.
Since so,
you should accept my award.
Aunt is gone.
I’ll let everyone in this world know
I’m taking care of the Ban family
and you can reply on me.
In this way,
Aunt won’t worry in the heaven.
Hua.
Since Aunt entrusted me
with your marriage
before she died,
I will get you engaged...
Your Majesty.
Today, I came
to reject the engagement.
What?
When Grandmother was alive,
I neglected filial duties to her.
I offer to guard by her tablet.
As for my wedding...
I don’t want to marry Count Cheng’an.
Hua.
Your Majesty, please grant my request.
Hua, you’ve been living a rich life.
It’s hard to guard by the tablet.
How can you bear with that?
For Grandmother,
I can bear with anything.
Since you have filial piety
for your grandmother,
let’s talk about your wedding
another time.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I’ll leave, too.
Wait!
Your Grace.
Sorry.
Grandmother! Grandmother!
Look. I made it myself.
Grandmother, wish you a long life!
Let me have a look.
So beautiful!
Grandmother! Grandmother!
She did such a poor embroidery.
Have a look at my gift.
This is an official porcelain
of the former dynasty.
It cost me totally fifty taels.
No, no!
He was so stupid that he was deceived.
This isn’t an official porcelain.
Fine. Fine.
This is fake!
-It’s genuine!
-It’s fake!
-Genuine!
-Fake!
All right! All right!
Don’t bother if it’s genuine or fake.
You have true heart for me already.
In my eyes, no gifts are better
than my grandson and granddaughter.
Don’t worry, Grandmother.
I’m doing fine.
You loved it when I smiled.
I will keep smiling.
In such a big capital,
no one can bully our family!
Ban’s Ancestral Hall
Ban Hua.
I hear you’ve eaten nothing for days.
You can’t do this.
Even if you’re guarding
at your grandmother’s tablet,
you can’t fall sick.
I don’t want anything to eat.
But you must eat!
If you keep eating nothing,
I’ll never go back to Aipo State.
What does it concern me?
Because I’m worried
that a beautiful girl like you
will be starving to death
after I leave.
What’s wrong?
This is my favorite jerky.
It smells bad.
How can I eat it?
Well, try more.
Then you’ll get used to it.
After you marry me in the grasslands,
there’s nothing else to eat.
Who will marry you?
If you don’t want to marry me,
why did you refuse
to marry Count Cheng’an?
None of your business.
Oh, I understand.
Local girls like you are different
from those in our grasslands.
You say no,
but you mean yes.
This is for you.
An umbrella?
I made it myself.
It’s a rare gift.
You look rough.
I didn’t know you could
make such a delicate thing.
You bet.
After I leave,
you can use the umbrella.
On rainy days or sunny days,
you will think of me.
Thank you.
If you really want to thank me,
go back to the grasslands with me
and be my forever love.
Wait, then.
I’ll think about it in my next life.
Fine.
I’ll have a chance in my next life.
Sister.
Father and Mother worried about you.
They sent me to check on you.
You used to be strong.
But now you’re so weak.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I just woke up
and I felt a bit dizzy.
You should have more rest, then.
I’ll go talk with Grandmother.
Have something to eat.
I’m not hungry.
You eat it.
You’d better have some.
Come on.
All are costly foods.
A feast of delicacies.
I want the porridge.
Fine. Here. Here’s the porridge.
There are wolfberries and longans in it.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
I didn’t prepare them.
You didn’t?
I prepared this. It’s already cold.
Rong
Why did you stop?
You haven’t had anything for days.
Luckily, you like the porridge.
Have some more.
Since he doesn’t want to be sincere
or tell me the truth,
why did he give me the food?
I don’t want it anymore.
Young Master.
Why didn’t you
have anything to eat again?
Thank you for your concern, Uncle Rong.
I’m getting old.
I don’t understand young men like you.
But if you keep a secret,
why don’t you tell Her Grace?
It’ll be better
than being awkward like this.
I certainly know that.
But I keep something from her
just to protect her.
Keeping a secret
doesn’t always mean protection.
People think alike on reasonable things.
Her Grace is a frank girl
and she’s very kind.
I’m afraid
she prefers the truth
to the box of cakes.
General-in-chief of the State’s Tablet
Princess Royal Dening’s Tablet
Princess Royal,
wish you peace and happiness
in the heaven.
Why do you think
you can worship my grandmother?
Hua, if you want to know the truth,
I will no longer keep it from you.
No matter what reason you have,
I must know everything
about my grandmother’s death.
In fact,
before I was ordered
to break into Princess Royal’s mansion,
I had met Her Highness.
Your Highness,
can you tell me the truth now?
I asked to meet you
so that I’ll tell you everything I know.
Xia, you’re reading this letter.
It’s the last thing I want to see.
You’re finally taking revenge.
I want you to be safe all your life.
But I also don’t want you to forget me.
If you stop reading,
there’s a turning back.
If you finish reading the letter,
you can never regret.
Think carefully about it.
The Ban family and our family
are under such condition
because of the Tiger Tally
of the Ban family.
To generals,
the Tiger Tally represents
Old General Ban.
His Majesty felt threatened,
but he didn’t dare
to ask Old General Ban
to hand in the Tiger Tally.
To get promoted,
Yan Hui had an evil plan.
Since we got on well
with the Ban family,
he forced your father
to get the Tiger Tally.
Unexpectedly,
this was a trap
to kill two birds with one stone.
With the Tiger Tally,
the Ban family would be ruined.
Without it, our family would be ruined.
Overnight,
our family became traitors.
Your father was executed.
Even your elder brother
was assassinated.
Son, I’m sorry.
To keep you alive,
I had to take a risk,
exchanging my life for yours.
I can’t watch you grow up,
be an official,
get married or have children.
But I want you to live your life
in forever peace.
Your Highness, did you have another plan
or did you do anything evil
so that you didn’t dare
to tell me the truth?
Somebody!
Yes!
Search the mansion carefully!
If you find any suspicious man,
take him back for interrogation!
Yes!
After deceiving Cui,
Princess Royal and I
estimated the situation
and knew something terrible
would happen.
We then used their trick and set a trap.
Unexpectedly,
she sacrificed herself
to protect your family.
Over the past decade,
you’ve been living a hard life,
Your Highness.
I got out of my way
to send you to the Crown Prince,
because your mother asked me
to keep you alive.
But you must understand.
Yan Hui was the chief plotter.
But I always think
he couldn’t have hurt us
without the permission of His Majesty.
I know.
Since you know,
why do you insist on investigating?
I kept it secret from you
because I was afraid you would
take revenge on the Yan family
and ask His Majesty for justice.
If your mother knew it in heaven,
she would blame me!
But Your Highness,
forgetting the family feud
will be ungrateful.
In such a complicated world,
how can I survive
if I’m ungrateful?
I’m getting old.
I can’t be as sensible as you.
I have trusted Minister Shi for years.
But I still don’t understand him.
He helped me get out of danger.
Now, why is he tricking us
on Hua’s marriage?
This is really thought-provoking.
I’m afraid the Shi family wants more
than we can imagine.
You’re a smart man.
My family is
amidst enemies.
You must have taken trouble
to mediate in it
and set such a trap.
You flatter me, Your Highness.
I knew
Prince Luo would drive a wedge
between us.
Unexpectedly,
he found my mother’s bracelet.
No offense, but may I ask?
You’ve hidden your capacities for years.
Have you ever regretted?
People born in the imperial family
have no right to regret.
Tell me.
Have you ever been scared
of evil enemies?
I’m never scared.
If I entrust Hua to you,
will you still not be scared?
If Her Grace likes me in the way I do,
I will never betray her!
Good!
Sounds like your father.
Since my husband died,
I’ve been behaving willfully
and haven’t begged anyone.
But now...
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You mean
Grandmother knew she would die.
So, the assassin...
Yes.
She arranged the assassin herself.
Aunt!
Princess Royal Dening’s Tablet
Only in this way
can she protect the Ban family
in front of His Majesty.
But I don’t want protection!
I just want my grandmother back!
Hua.
Princess Royal got His Majesty
to protect you
with her own life
and asked us to get married
so that His Majesty would stop
suspecting us
and our families would
get back together.
Let’s not waste
her painstaking plan.
I hate it most when people deceive me.
In front of my grandmother’s tablet,
let me make it clear.
I’ll only marry a man
who has a true heart for me.
I have a true heart
for you.
If you do,
why didn’t you discuss with me?
You hid the plan from me
so that I saw my grandmother die
and would no longer stay with her?
Why did you do this?
Because I must protect you
and your whole family!
I can’t get you hurt.
Haven’t you got me hurt enough?
I want nothing, but a true heart.
But you always had plots.
When the plots were against me, fine.
But in the end,
you even got my grandmother killed.
I never had a plot
against Princess Royal.
She was incurably sick
and she was dying.
That’s why I agreed
to set the trap with her,
so that we could protect you
and your family
all your lives.
Say no more.
I won’t believe you.
Leave.
I ask you to leave!
Your Grace.
Take care.
♪I wait and wait all my life♪
♪In my dream I want the eternal♪
♪I want nobody but you♪
♪I would fulfill my dream♪
♪I wait and wait all my life♪
♪I want to spend my life with someone♪
♪We will meet however hard it is♪
♪Regardless of the floating life♪
♪We stay in a small town♪
In my eyes,
you’re Rong Xia,
the unique man I care for.
♪In my dream I want the eternal♪
♪We will meet however hard it is♪
♪Regardless of the floating life♪
♪We stay in a small town♪
♪I have you to love in my life♪
♪Hope I could stay with you♪
General-in-chief of the State’s Tablet
Princess Royal Dening’s Tablet
Your Grace, are you alright?
Your Grace, what happened to you?
Your Grace!
Somebody!
Ban’s Mansion
According to the doctor,
my sister is having a cold.
She just needs some rest and food.
What’s wrong with you?
We feel sorry for your sister.
She kicked Count Cheng’an out.
I also feel sorry for him.
Your sister kicked him out,
but she felt hurt, too.
She cared for Count Cheng’an
and didn’t want him
to be involved with our ruin.
Then she turned him down.
Is that so complicated?
Why... Why didn’t she just say it?
What an idiot!
If she said that directly,
it would be more complicated.
It would be harder to solve the problem.
What problem
are we going to solve?
My sister’s marriage
or what hasn’t happened yet
in her dream?
He’s right.
Maybe we should think
about it carefully.
What can be the best choice
for our daughter?
Teach Young Master Ban martial arts?
You are as good at martial arts as I am.
Why don’t you teach him personally?
No offense,
but why did you fall out
with Count Cheng’an?
There’s no future
for him and me.
If so,
please entrust me with your future.
I will protect you, love you
and never regret.
If you can’t forget Count Cheng’an now,
I can wait
until you forget him.
Mr. Shi.
It’s not as simple as you imagine.
What reason do you have?
Please tell me.
The Xie family broke off the engagement.
Xie Qilin was blind.
Grandmother died.
Before such things happened,
I had dreamed of them.
In my dream,
my family was also confiscated,
and we couldn’t protect ourselves
in such trouble.
I don’t want to get others involved.
So, you still love Count Cheng’an?
A mere dream scared you.
It’s not you I used to know.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
I’m sorry.
Princess Royal said
you looked most like her.
In her life,
she was proud and she also suffered.
She had to keep her feelings secret.
But she only wanted you
to live a carefree and happy life
like she did
in the first half of her life.
Sister, are you alright?
Heng.
You’re the only son of our family.
You must practice martial arts hard.
I’ve told Softy.
From today on,
you’ll practice for six hours a day.
If you don’t work hard
and only enjoy the life,
when things in the dream happen,
how can you protect our family
or our parents?
Sister, we have you.
What if I’m gone?
I’m strong.
But if someday,
I can’t hold on,
we have to rely on you.
Understand?
Yes.
It’s been days only.
Your Grace, why do you look so thin?
Mr. Xie, enjoy the tea, please.
Seems like the rumors are true.
You really keep a simple diet
and live a simple life.
Mr. Xie,
I don’t think you come here
just to confirm the rumors.
With your soldiers, you searched
the Mansion of Peace and Longevity.
Instead of being punished,
you could marry Princess Ban.
I really admire that.
Mr. Xie, can’t you see
that His Majesty asked me
to marry Princess Ban
for the court condition?
So, it’s what His Majesty wanted?
Prince Luo and I thought
you tricked us.
Princess Ban’s marriage
has caused many conflicts.
His Majesty just didn’t want
more arguments.
You and His Highness
overestimated me.
Well, let me get to the point.
His Highness cares for the Tiger Tally.
Have you got any clue?
No, after searching
the Mansion of Peace and Longevity.
So, I guess
it’s being kept
in Duke Jingting’s Mansion.
Duke Jingting’s Mansion?
Minister Shi was ordered
to look for the Tiger Tally.
He asked Shen Yu
to sneak into the Ban’s Mansion.
It proves that the Tiger Tally is there.
His Highness just needs
to follow the clue
and find it out.
That’s great, then.
After you marry Princess Ban,
you’ll get the Tiger Tally easily.
With your help,
Prince Luo will get great power.
I’m dying.
I had meant to bury it with me.
But such condition
worries me.
Now,
I want you
to keep this for me.
It may protect the Ban family.
What’s this?
It’s what everyone wants!
I give it to you,
so that I’m asking you
to take care of the Ban family.
Can you do that, Your Grace?
I swear
to the heaven
that I won’t let you down!
If I get the Tiger Tally,
I wonder what I can get from Prince Luo.
This is an important thing.
When you get it,
Prince Luo will give you
whatever you want.
Stop!
Young Master, where are you going?
Her Grace ordered you
to practice martial arts for six hours.
Why are you escaping
within even a quarter?
Softy.
Don’t keep an eye on me
as if I were a thief.
I’m just leaving for some business.
I’ll come back and continue.
What business?
Uh... Uh...
Zhou Changxiao said he got
some information about Prince Luo.
I must go and get confirmation.
Information never waits.
Young Master!
Mr. Yao, what do you want to tell me?
There’s never a secret to you.
I’ll get to the point, then.
Minister Shi has a granddaughter.
Do you know?
Do you mean Miss Shi Feixian?
Precisely.
Miss Shi is beautiful
and very talented.
She’s good enough for you.
What do you think, Your Grace?
You may not know.
I was engaged not long ago.
In the mourning for Princess Royal,
I shouldn’t make it widely known.
Please keep it secret.
Which lucky girl?
It hasn’t been announced yet.
Please understand.
I see. I see.
Please enjoy the tea.
Young Master.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪