Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 15
I’ve been waiting for you,
Your Highness.
What’s the smell?
Smells like a hog lot.
Your Highness, if you hadn’t asked me
to come back hurriedly,
you needn’t have come
to such a dirty place.
You mean
it’s my fault?
I don’t dare.
If Father hadn’t summoned
the Crown Prince secretly,
I wouldn’t have
called you back in a hurry.
When you wanted me
to gain recognition from His Majesty,
political achievements would be
most convincing.
But why did you use
Princess Royal’s money
for disaster relief,
instead of your own money?
Do you think everyone is as rich
as the Ban family?
Time was pressing.
How could I get
such a large sum of money?
I’ll do anything for you, Your Highness.
But when I’m stuck here,
I can’t give you any advice.
All right. All right.
Don’t be anxious.
I’ll try
to get you out soon.
I don’t want to come
to such a place again.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Today, Rong Xia defended you.
But I still don’t fully believe
that he’s working for me.
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
I’ve got a plan.
If Rong Xia doesn’t cooperate
with us sincerely,
he’ll also be screwed
in my interlocked stratagems.
I’m leaving.
Cui?
Cui.
Madam Chang.
Why are you in the study?
I... I find too much dust in the study
when it hasn’t been cleaned
for a long time.
I came to clean it.
Okay.
Go to tell Her Highness!
Yes!
Who are you that come
in the middle of night?
Token
Get out of the way.
Yes!
Your Grace, why are you coming
in the middle of night
with the soldiers?
Token
At the behest of His Majesty,
this mansion has been harassed
by refugees
and things were stolen.
I’m ordered to come with soldiers
to protect this mansion.
Well,
Your Grace, please defend the mansion
by guarding around.
Madam Chang, His Majesty ordered me
to get in and check carefully,
so that I can make sure
no one is hidden here
and keep Princess Royal safe.
In this mansion, they are servants
who have been working
for Her Highness for years.
No one is suspicious.
You come with so many people.
If you disturb Her Highness,
I’m afraid you can’t explain
to His Majesty.
Her Highness is a royal lady.
Nothing can go wrong.
Madam Chang, please step back
so that I can get in for a search
and relieve His Majesty.
Ridiculous!
How would His Majesty
give such an order?
Unless His Majesty came personally,
none of you
would get in.
It’s indeed an order from His Majesty.
Madam Chang, if you insist
on stopping us,
sorry for being impolite.
You!
Your Grace, what do you mean?
If you dare to come forward,
you’ll be sorry!
This is an order from His Majesty.
Please make way, Your Grace.
I won’t.
Hua, step back!
Madam Chang.
Take Her Grace to the side hall
for some rest.
Don’t let her out without my permission.
Yes, Your Highness!
Your Grace, please go.
Go.
Since it’s an order from His Majesty,
Your Grace, come in, please.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Search!
It doesn’t feel right.
His Majesty knows
Count Cheng’an is friendly with us.
Why did he send Count Cheng’an
to search this place?
What does His Majesty really want?
Why did Count Cheng’an break in,
regardless of our relationship?
I thought you were
only talented in literary.
Unexpectedly, you’re also good
at deploying the soldiers.
It’s wasting your talent
to search my mansion.
Your Highness.
I’m just executing the order.
No offense.
Search!
Yes!
Mother!
Your Highness.
Why is this bracelet
in your study?
This doesn’t belong to me.
I’ve never seen it before!
You’ve never seen it before?
This is my mother’s bequest.
Your Grace.
You racked your brains to break in
just for this?
It was smart of you.
Without the warrant from His Majesty,
I’m afraid I would never know
you hid my mother’s bequest
in your study!
How dare you!
My parents died out of a reason.
You insisted that you knew nothing.
If you really didn’t know,
why would you have my mother’s bequest?
Don’t you fear
that my parents would question you
in your dream?
Your Highness, over the years,
how could you sleep soundly?
Madam Chang! Madam Chang!
Something wrong with Her Highness!
Your Grace.
Madam Chang, take me to see Grandmother.
Your Grace, I found nothing.
Neither did I.
Grandmother!
Grandmother, what happened to you?
Your Highness.
I’m fine. I’m fine.
Your Grace.
What did you do to my grandmother?
I just asked her
a few questions.
As for the reason why she’s angry...
You’d better ask her personally.
Asked her a few questions?
You’re just like confiscating my family!
Rong Xia.
Explain to me.
What you told me that night...
Does it still count?
Your Grace, I’ve got a duty to do today.
Let’s not talk
about personal relationship.
Fine. Let’s not talk about it.
Let’s talk about business, then.
His Majesty sent you
to protect my grandmother.
But you annoyed her.
What punishment
do you think you deserve?
You and I know very well
if Her Highness is well.
Please don’t throw mud at me.
Rong Xia.
Don’t you fear
that I’ll tell His Majesty?
Don’t bother, Your Grace.
I’ll tell His Majesty
what has happened today.
You!
Hua!
Enough!
His Grace is just following the order.
Don’t be rude.
Somebody!
Here!
Strengthen the vigilance
around this mansion
in case anyone suspicious approaches!
Yes!
Princess Royal was so angry
that she spat blood.
Rong Xia left with the bracelet
and went to report to His Majesty.
Your Highness, wait to see the fun.
Wonderful!
This is wonderful!
Next, the Ban family will perish
and the Crown Prince will be dethroned!
Congratulations, Your Highness.
When the Crown Prince is dethroned,
you’ll be the new Crown Prince.
Congratulations.
Your Highness, Count Cheng’an asked
to see you.
Let him in.
What brings you here?
Shouldn’t you be in the palace
and reporting to His Majesty?
I didn’t go to the palace.
Rong Xia, what do you mean?
Are you betraying me?
Don’t be angry, Your Highness.
Princess Royal shouldn’t be dead now.
We agreed to break down the Ban family.
They won’t be eliminated
before Princess Royal is dead.
Don’t you want to know
where the Tiger Tally is?
Tiger Tally?
If His Majesty doesn’t
dethrone the Crown Prince,
you’ll find it most difficult
to be the new Crown Prince.
But if you have the Tiger Tally first,
things will change.
Are you sure you can get it?
I will get to know where it is
from Princess Royal.
Fine.
Hua, stop guessing.
Hua.
Grandmother, I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have trusted a man like him.
It’s not your fault.
Count Cheng’an came
with an imperial order.
We had to bear with it.
But His Majesty always respected you.
Maybe he has nothing to fear
when he knows I’m dying.
Hua.
If I die,
do take good care of our family.
Grandmother, say no more.
I don’t like to hear that.
Why do I feel hungry?
You’re hungry?
Grandmother, would you
like something to eat?
I’ll ask Madam Chang
to get the food ready.
I’m not hungry.
Why did I suddenly
want some pomegranates?
I’ll go find some for you.
Silly girl.
How can you find any in the cold winter?
Grandmother, just wait for me.
I’ll go get some.
Hua. Hua!
You!
Softy. Softy. Softy.
I’m scared.
What are you scared of?
Is there...?
Is there really a thief in the kitchen?
When I’m here,
I’ll beat whoever dares to break in!
Go!
Three, two, one.
Catch the thief!
Your Grace?
Your Grace, why are you back
in the middle of night?
Your Grace,
are you searching the kitchen
because you’re hungry?
Why isn’t there any midnight snack
at the Mansion of Peace and Longevity?
Yeah.
I’m not hungry.
I’m looking for the pomegranate wine.
Someone gave it to me before.
Where is it?
You want to drink it?
No. Find it out for me.
Your Grace, what do you
want the pomegranate wine for?
Grandmother wants some pomegranates.
But look.
How can I get any in the cold winter?
I must do it some other way.
I see.
You want to make dough pomegranates
and pour the wine on them.
Clever girls!
Awesome! Awesome!
We made it!
What a hard job!
You’d better lie down for some rest.
Get me the pellet.
Your Highness.
If you take more pellets, I’m afraid...
Bring me the pellet!
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Grandmother.
-Your Grace.
-Madam Chang.
Grandmother.
Hua.
Guess what I brought.
I found some pomegranates for you.
How did you find any on such a cold day?
Look at you.
You really got me some pomegranates?
Grandmother, what’s wrong?
I didn’t expect
to taste some pomegranates again.
Who looks most like me?
-Who?
-Your Highness.
Who of the younger generation
looks most like me?
Madam?
Hua looks most like me.
Her Grace is fiery.
She looks more like Old General Ban.
When I was young,
everyone held a modest attitude to me.
I dared to love and hate, just like her.
When I see her,
I feel like seeing the young me.
Your Highness.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
I was born in the palace.
I should also die there.
Madam Chang, dress me up.
Your Majesty, Princess Royal asked
to meet you.
Get her in.
Your Majesty, it’s been long
since I last visited you.
It’s a fine day.
I come without invitation.
You’ll welcome me, won’t you?
Aunt, you can come whenever you want.
Come and be seated.
Get us some tea.
Yes.
Aunt, I was just going to tell you.
Yesterday, I sent more guards
to protect you.
Unexpectedly, Count Cheng’an was so rude
that he made you spit blood.
I’ll punish him.
I certainly know
you cared for me.
Count Cheng’an did nothing wrong.
It’s generous of you, Aunt.
I didn’t know you would come
and I didn’t have
your favorite tea prepared.
When I’m getting old,
I can’t help recalling the past.
It’s now winter.
I recalled the outing
I went to with your father.
You were just three to five years old.
You snapped a branch covered with snow,
thinking it was a caterpillar.
You yelled and ran to me,
giving it to me as a gift.
Yes.
You got all the snow on my head.
Your father scolded you.
Yes. Yes.
I remember.
I had black hair covered with snow.
But now, I have grey hair.
It’s been so many years.
Aunt,
you can even remember that.
That’s because
no matter how much time has passed,
how many difficulties
you’ve gone through,
or who you are,
you’re always the naughty boy
who tricks his own aunt.
My father died at a young age.
Without your help,
I would have been dead in plots.
I can hardly repay you in my life.
I remember another time.
You were like this tall.
You were playing with some crickets
when they suddenly ran away.
You cried loudly.
Yes.
Ban’s Ancestral Hall
General-in-chief of the State’s Tablet
Princess Royal Dening’s Tablet
Somebody!
Grandmother!
No!
I can’t be late!
Virtue Gate
Who are you? You mustn’t break in!
Your Grace, get off the horse!
Your Grace!
Chase after her!
When I was little,
I was indeed timid.
Aunt.
You always have great tea.
You even have spring tea in winter.
Aunt, if you like it,
I’ll have some sent to your mansion.
Get us more tea.
Are you going to fill me with tea
so that I won’t stay for dinner?
Whoever breaks in will be killed!
Mr. Shi, it’s Princess Ban.
Your Grace, please stop!
Your Grace.
Get out of the way!
Are you alright?
I’ll kill whoever stops me!
It’s you?
Let me say it again.
Get out of the way!
Stop!
Your Grace.
Are you trying to stop me, too?
Hua, I’ll explain to you later.
Time is running out.
Go with me.
Your Grace, please leave with me.
Hua, trust me for one more time.
Go with me, or it’ll be too late!
Can I trust you again?
I’m not hardhearted.
I will take you to Princess Royal.
Commander Shi,
do we still run after her?
No.
-Aunt!
-Somebody! Catch the assassin!
Aunt!
Sky-holding Gate
Ordered by His Majesty,
I’m guarding here.
I don’t mean
to disrespect you, Your Grace.
But I must follow the order.
Please wait here.
I’ll report to His Majesty.
When His Majesty allows, you can get in.
Sky-holding Gate
His Majesty didn’t summon me.
But I must get in today!
Please make way.
I’ll undertake full responsibility!
Aunt!
Your Majesty.
Come! What are you waiting for?
Check on her. You must save her!
So... Sorry.
Princess Royal’s heart is hurt.
I can do nothing to cure her.
Loser! Get out!
Get me all the Imperial Physicians!
Hurry!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Aunt, hold on.
The physicians are coming.
Aunt! Aunt!
Rui.
I’m here.
I’m already old.
I know I’ll die.
Aunt!
I’ve done enough to my nation.
But...
Hua. Hua. Hua!
Hurry!
Go get Princess Fule
and Marquis Jingting!
And the Ban family! Hurry!
Aunt!
Hua.
Grandmother.
I’m late.
I’m too late.
I’m so useless.
Don’t cry, good girl.
Why are you in a red dress?
You’re married?
Who is your husband?
Grandmother.
Be nice to Hua.
Otherwise,
I won’t let you off.
Don’t worry, Grandmother.
I’ll take good care of her.
Mother!
-Mother!
-Grandmother!
-Mother, what happened?
-Mother!
-Grandmother!
Son, here you are.
Yes. Yes. Mother!
-Mother!
-Mother, what happened to you?
Hua’s husband
looks handsome.
Take good care of them.
Aunt,
I will.
I...
I’m going to see my husband.
-Mother!
-Grandmother!
Your Majesty.
Bury me
with...
with my...
my husband.
Mother!
-Grandmother!
-Mother!
Mother!
-Aunt!
-Grandmother!
My mother is gone! Mother!
Mother!
I saw that in my dream!
Grandmother!
Hua, it’s not your fault.
Grandmother, wake up! Grandmother!
-Mother!
-Grandmother!
Grandmother, wake up!
Your Majesty.
I’ve adored Princess Fule
for a long time.
Please marry her to me.
Why are you saying this at this moment?
Your Majesty.
Princess Royal is dead.
I don’t want to break my promise.
It’s my honor to marry Princess Fule.
Please marry her to me, Your Majesty.
Mother!
Princess Royal Dening
is dead!
Princess Royal has great reputation
and is going to heaven!
Princess Royal is dead!
Emperor Yunqing fulfilled her wish
and buried her with Old General Ban.
Mansion of Peace and Longevity
She was buried in Ban’s Ancestral Hall
and was titled Princess Royal Dening.
Everyone in the nation should mourn
for three months
when there should be no entertainment
or wedding.
The whole nation will be in mourning
with an amnesty.
Sir, we’re not enemies.
I’ll... I’ll give you all this.
Please spare me!
Not enemies?
Madam Chang! Madam Chang, help me!
Cui.
Princess Royal was nice to you.
Why did you betray her?
I was confused! I was mad about money!
Madam Chang, forgive me!
Forgive you?
It’s what Princess Royal should do.
Ask her for forgiveness yourself.
Madam Chang!
Your Highness, thank you for saving me.
Don’t thank me.
If Princess Royal didn’t die
in the palace
and Father granted an amnesty,
I wouldn’t have got you out.
Watch your language, Your Highness.
Xie Chongjin, tell me.
We had planned to make Rong Xia
fight against Princess Royal
so that I could get benefits.
But now why are they
getting closer?
If the Crown Prince has more power,
my plan to be the Crown Prince
will be empty talk.
Is this your plan?
Princess Royal died unexpectedly.
It was also surprising
when His Majesty married Ban Hua
to Count Cheng’an.
But since Princess Royal is dead,
you don’t need to fear the Ban family.
You’re right.
I can take the chance
to get rid of the Ban family
and Count Cheng’an together.
Your Highness, there’s a bright future.
Why do you choose a worse one?
What do you mean?
Isn’t it the perfect chance
to get rid of the Ban family
or Count Cheng’an?
Your Highness,
have you thought about it?
When you don’t have real power,
even if the Crown Prince has
no supporters,
you can’t be the new Crown Prince.
But when you have the military power,
even if all ministers
support the Crown Prince,
you don’t need to be scared.
You mean…?
Just get to the point.
Count Cheng’an or Ban Hua isn’t the key.
The key is
the Tiger Tally.
-Greetings, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Before Princess Royal Dening died,
she asked you to take care of yourself.
Now, you’re so self-accused
that you don’t investigate
the assassination case.
I’m afraid Princess Royal will
be uneasy in heaven.
Sorry for my wild words, Your Majesty.
Please punish me.
I know
you care for me,
just like my aunt.
What have imperial guards got
for the case?
Your Majesty.
The assassin was disguised
as the tea servant.
He ran away from the study
after the assassination
and was caught by imperial guards
in the northeast.
Then he poisoned himself.
As for who he is
and when he sneaked into the palace,
I’m not sure.
There are so many imperial guards
in such a small palace.
But they can’t figure out
one single assassin.
What do I need you for?
Get out!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Don’t be angry, Your Majesty.
Commander Shi has great martial arts.
But he isn’t good at investigation.
May I investigate this case
and figure out what happened?
Now,
you’re the only one
who can help me.
You must figure out
who is behind the assassin!
General-in-chief of the State’s Tablet
Princess Royal Dening’s Tablet
What’s wrong, father?
Are you alright, Master?
I’m fine. I’m fine.
On the day
my grandmother was assassinated,
how did you know I went to the palace?
Why did you insist
on searching her mansion?
What did you do to my grandmother
in the study?
Answer me!
Hua.
I...
If you have anything to do
with my grandmother’s death,
I won’t let you go!
Hua.
Your Grace.
My sister said
she didn’t want to talk to you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪