A LOVE SO BEAUTIFUL
Sol-i. You're a total loser.
Sol-i, I made naengchae jokbal,
your favorite.
She's been in her room all weekend.
She won't come out.
What's wrong with her?
Was she dumped by the boy she likes?
Sol-i got dumped?
Who would dare--
I don't know if she actually was.
She'll hear. Don't make a fuss and go.
Shin Sol-i.
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry.
You wrote a love letter
on the answer sheet,
and you ruined the theater festival.
Do your parents know
how you've been behaving at school?
Hello.
Your student, Shin Sol-i,
is such a troublemaker.
Ms. Moon, shouldn't you supervise
your students better?
I'm sorry, Mr. Cho.
I'll warn her.
Sol-i, go on in.
Behave yourself.
Sol-i, Sol-i, Shin Sol-i!
How did it feel
to ask someone out in public?
Oh, Shin Juliet,
who's the Romeo you're madly in love with?
Can't you please tell me who it is?
Se-hyeong. That's enough.
Come on. Why don't you
just ask him out in public?
Ask him out.
Who are you? Let go of me.
Se-hyeong, if you're that bored,
want to hang out with me?
Let me go, Dae-sung. Let go.
-What?
-I can't breathe. Let me go.
Sorry, Sol-i.
I'm sorry, Sol-i.
If anyone makes fun of you again, tell me.
Okay, thanks.
I have to go to practice. See you.
Is Dae-sung your bodyguard?
I'd transfer to another school
if I were you.
I'd be too embarrassed.
It's embarrassing that you're in my class.
How could you say that to a friend?
Ha-young, what did you just say?
I'm an embarrassment?
That's right. It's so embarrassing.
Go back to your seat
while I'm asking nicely.
Whatever.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Excuse me for a minute.
Sol-i. Class will start soon.
Where are you going?
Sol-i. Sit here.
Come on. Let's study together.
Okay.
You calculated this wrong.
Don't mind me.
I can just refer to the answer sheet.
Sol-i. Eat this and cheer up.
Thank you.
By the way, Sol-i, are you sure
you don't have a crush on anyone?
No, I'm not interested in anyone.
I see. I'm sorry.
I'll study in the classroom.
I think she's telling the truth.
Isn't she?
Heon!
I missed you.
You're home.
What happened?
Geon wanted to surprise you.
Goodness, my son.
You've gotten more handsome and taller.
Here. It's for you.
Mom and I bought MUFC merch for you.
Eat up, Heon.
You, too.
LITERATURE
Geon, brush your teeth and go to bed.
I want to stay up a little more.
No, it's late. Hurry up.
Just a little more, please.
Come on.
Let me just finish this.
WRITE MESSAGE
SHIN SOL-I
Are you asleep?
What are you doing?
Shin Sol-i.
2006 CSAT
JUNE MOCK EXAM REPORT CARD
Sol-i.
We need to have a talk.
Ms. Moon called this afternoon.
-Why?
-Well, she said
you haven't been able to focus
on your studies these days.
She asked if everything was all right.
We were wondering the same thing.
Mom.
Dad.
-What?
-Yes?
Should I
transfer schools?
What do you mean?
Is someone bullying you?
Why transfer all of a sudden?
Well, it's just…
Everyone at Yuil High School
is so academic.
Lately, I've been thinking
I'm not qualified to study here.
Hey, hop on.
You aren't sick, are you?
No, I'm not.
Then why are you feeling so low?
Do you want to grab a bite after school?
Or a karaoke?
No.
By the way, Dae-sung,
how would you feel
if I transferred schools?
What? You're transferring? To where?
-Do they accept swimming students?
-No.
I was just kidding.
Let's go.
That really surprised me.
Hold tight.
Okay.
BYE, TAKE CARE
WOO DAE-SUNG
Yes, Dae-sung.
Why?
Okay.
Ta-da!
What's all this?
Get on this float.
Just trust me and hop on.
You'll feel better.
Isn't it fun?
I'll go faster.
That's freezing!
Take this.
Behind you.
Isn't it fun?
It's so fun, isn't it?
Stop. Hey.
I can't see.
What are you doing? Get out!
How is Sol-i?
She was so cute when she was little.
She's still cute, isn't she?
I'm really worried about Sol-i these days.
Unlike Heon,
she has no interest in studying at all.
And she'll be a senior soon.
I don't know if she'll be able to
go to any university in Seoul.
She must be worried, too.
She asked if she could transfer schools.
-Transfer?
-Yes.
She never said so,
but she must have been frustrated.
My husband and I
looked into several schools.
We found a nice boarding school.
We're thinking of sending her there.
What do you think?
WRITE MESSAGE
SHIN SOL-I
Are you really going to transfer?
You're getting lazy
after winning a few gold medals.
Who is she?
Answer me!
Do 500 more push-ups.
Hey, Sol-i.
Ms. Moon wants to see you
in the staff room.
I wonder why.
-What do you think it's for?
-I'm not sure.
I think Sol-i's parents are here.
-Let's go to the snack bar.
-Okay.
Sol-i
might transfer schools.
-What?
We haven't decided yet.
We'd like to hear your opinion first.
In my experience,
the first-year scores don't
necessarily affect CSAT results.
Some students improve later. Besides,
Sol-i made many good friends here.
If she transfers schools abruptly,
I'm worried she might
have a hard time adjusting.
Sol-i.
Sol-i, what do you think?
Do you really want to transfer?
Well…
I…
Say no.
Well…
I…
I'm here to pick up
the literature performance assessment.
Oh, right.
I think it's too heavy
for one person to carry, though.
Shin Sol-i.
Help him out.
-Pardon?
-Help him.
Shin Sol-i.
Don't go.
A FEW DAYS LATER
Heon, you waited for me!
-Who said that?
-Come on.
Why don't you tell me honestly?
Why did you tell me not to go that day?
You really didn't want me
to transfer schools, did you?
Shin Sol-i,
don't you have any self-respect?
No, I gave it all to you.
Heon, I'm going to give up on liking you.
-A neighborhood dog licked it.
-There's a dog in our neighborhood?
-Is it cute?
-Yes, it is.
I'll be making my debut.
Making you my lady
Why don't we spend the night here?
Let's find a place to sleep first.
-This is awesome!
-Awesome!
A shooting star! Guys, make a wish!
Heon, did you not make a wish?
What did you wish for?
For you to like me.
Truth or dare at this hour?
You must keep these secrets.
Don't tell anyone.
Heon, what should I do?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-hyun Yang
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs