3 YEARS AGO
JAPANESE FORCES
JOSEON FORCES
SANGJU
This will bring the dead back to life?
This plant?
Yes, it will, my lord.
The plant's essence...
when injected in the glabella
of the deceased,
will revive the body as a monster
that hungers for the flesh of the living.
However, if the corpse is decayed...
or if the center of the brain
has already been damaged,
resurrection is impossible.
[foreboding music]
[soldier 1] The Japanese
have us surrounded.
Sangju is all that stands
in Gyeongsang Province.
I heard the Japanese have reached
the Unpo Wetland.
Well, if that's true,
then Sangju is done for.
Oh, wait.
- Does that mean that...
- [shushes]
[gasps]
[crow squawking]
[foreboding music]
[foreboding music continues]
[squawks]
[crows squawking]
BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS BY YLAB
[theme music]
[snarls]
[distant snarling]
[suspenseful music]
[snarling]
[tense music]
[the infected snarling]
How are they out in daylight?
[tense music]
[snarling]
Prepare weapons, take your positions.
[blows horn]
It won't catch fire!
[snarling]
- [twangs]
- [snarls]
- [bow creaks]
- [twangs]
[snarling]
[screams]
[splashes]
- [snarls]
- [gasps]
Burn them now!
[arrows twang]
Get to the raft!
- [gunshot]
- [snarling]
- Get the rest of the brothers! Hurry!
- Go! Go!
Come on! Push!
[grunting]
[growling]
[grunts, groans]
[snarls]
[thumping]
[shrieks]
That's it! Push!
[sword rasps]
- [grunting]
- [flesh squelches]
[grunting]
Run! Come on, run!
[snarling]
[tense music]
[the infected snarling]
- [snarling]
- [flesh squelching]
Hyah! Hyah!
THE CITADEL OF SANGJU
The infected are coming! They're awake!
[guard 1] Master!
The monsters are at Byeongseong Stream!
BYEONGSEONG STREAM
[men screaming]
[tense music]
- [grunts]
- [thwacks]
We can't hold out much longer, sir!
Use the cannons! Fire!
[crashes, thuds]
[snarling]
[cannons firing]
- [grunts]
- [shrieks]
[pants]
- [snarling]
- [cannon fires]
[soldier 1] Bring more arrows! Hurry!
[soldier 2] Here! Take it!
[snarling]
- [thwacks]
- [growls]
[cannons firing]
[men screaming]
- [explosion]
- [snarling]
[grunts]
Push them back!
If you let them break through,
we're all dead!
[soldier 1] Yes, sir!
[snarling]
[men grunting]
- [snarls]
- [groans]
[gasps, grunts]
[flesh squelches]
- [gasping]
- [grunts]
- [body thuds]
Sir!
We cannot fight them any longer!
Your Highness, we have to flee.
[gasps]
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
THE CITADEL OF SANGJU
That's the citadel. They are falling back.
I need the rope ladders now!
[suspenseful music]
[rumbling]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
- Oh, no.
- [men gasping]
[all gasping]
[man 1] He's been bitten!
No...
[gasps]
It's a small bite.
[man 2] It will be okay.
[gasps, pants]
Please.
No, please!
[man 2] Help!
Oh!
[gasping]
[man 2] Please! Help!
Help! Help! Help!
[gasping]
No...
[man 3] What do we do now?
Sangju's our only option.
If we can make it, there's a path.
What if those monsters are there, too?
Do you want to stay here and freeze?
BYEONGSEONG STREAM
THE CITADEL OF SANGJU
[indistinct shouting]
- Help us!
- Hurry up!
Grab that!
- The infected are here!
- [gasps]
[snarling]
[men screaming]
[door thudding]
[suspenseful music]
[panting]
[Deok-soong] The infected got through
Byeongseong Stream.
Your Highness, I know of a passageway.
Built during the war,
on the north bank of the stream.
Let's hurry.
Protect His Highness!
We must go now!
[tense music]
HONGCHI GATE
[ominous music]
[locks clanking]
It's locked! The gate's locked!
[men grunting]
Damn it!
Form a blockade now!
- [indistinct shouting]
- [grunts]
[men grunting]
- [cracks]
- [grunts]
[the infected growling]
They're coming!
They're here!
[soldier 3] Get to your formation!
[guard 1] Hurry! Hurry!
[grunting]
[Mu-yeong] Form a barrier!
[snarling]
[screaming]
[thuds]
[men screaming]
- [grunting]
- [flesh squelches]
[men grunting, screaming]
[thudding]
[snarls, shrieks]
[snarls]
- [grunts]
- [flesh squelches]
[snarling]
- [grunts]
- [thuds]
Make way!
[grunts]
- [grunting]
- [thudding]
You must hurry!
Out of the way!
[locks clinking]
- [grunts]
- [thudding]
[clanks]
Sir! Your Highness!
The gate is open!
- Prepare, Your Highness!
- Prepare to run!
[grunts]
Your Highness!
- Go!
- Go, go, go!
Come on, go!
[grunts]
- Get inside! Now!
- No!
What's the matter?
You can't.
[foreboding music]
[sword rasps]
[gasps]
[snarling]
[thudding]
[growls]
Guard and protect my Lord Ahn! Now go!
[flesh squelches]
[growls]
[grunting]
[clanking]
[growling]
[Mu-yeong] We must keep moving.
[the infected growling]
[groans]
[gasping]
Sorry.
- [flesh squelches]
- [groans]
[gloomy music]
[government clerk] Your Highness.
[indistinct chatter]
What's wrong with you?
I thought Your Highness said
they retreated at daybreak.
I am at a loss.
They returned to corpses in the sun.
There must be a reason.
[sword rasps]
[foreboding music]
[the infected's growling echoes]
All right, they're here.
Makes no difference.
[foreboding music]
[snarling]
[grunts]
[the infected snarling]
[grunting]
[Beom-pal] Seo-bi! Seo-bi, help me!
Please! Seo-bi!
Seo-bi!
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[whimpering]
[the infected snarling]
[gasps, pants]
[gasps]
[snarling]
Oh. Wait, wait. The sun is out.
Why are they still moving around?
It's the cold.
The resurrection plant prefers it.
[pants]
[Seo-bi] If they are all alike,
then sunlight
is not what they are afraid of.
They only fear high temperatures.
But now that it's winter,
it stays cold even with the sun.
They will never cease now.
[sighs]
[snarling]
Their numbers have stayed the same
since their attack yesterday.
[stutters]
So... so?
That means they are
the only monsters nearby.
If there were more,
they would have attacked us.
[Beom-pal] Even if those are
the only other monsters around here,
the citadel would surely have hundreds!
How do you suppose we survive
the twenty pack?
If we cross the stream,
they should not follow.
Since they cannot cross the water,
we should head up this mountain.
It's far safer
than returning to the citadel.
Seo... Seo-bi. Up the mountain?
Where will we go?
Did you not tell me once before
that the Haewon Cho Clan
is able to guarantee your safety?
[Seo-bi] We will go to Mungyeong Saejae.
[Beom-pal gasps]
Wait, Seo-bi...
[gasps, whimpers]
SUNGRYE GATE
[foreboding music]
[indistinct chatter]
[man 4] I heard a rumor
that the plague is upon us.
There's been sightings...
[indistinct chatter]
ROYAL COMMANDERY DIVISION
Due to urgent matters, the Chief State
Councilor has left for Mungyeong Saejae.
Now what is it that requires my absence
from the State Council?
What do I have to see?
This matter is of great importance.
I requested your presence
to see it for yourself.
[Minister of defense clears throat]
[door opens]
All right. What is this?
[commander] Last night, we found
these women outside the north gate.
According to the autopsy, one of the women
had only just given birth.
The baby found with her...
have been strangled to death
prior to our discovery.
Is the culprit detained?
[commander] They said the woman uttered
something peculiar before she died.
She claimed the people in her village
did this to her and her child,
and that they would kill
every last one remaining.
Those were her final words.
Where is this village?
[door closes]
Outside the north gate
of Samgye-dong, Naeseonjae.
"Naeseonjae"? You're sure of it?
Yes, it's the private residence...
and current home of the Queen's family.
[crows squawking]
[blood trickling]
[foreboding music]
[clinking]
[bells clinking]
[female head court officer]
The Royal Commandery Division
knows about Naeseonjae.
We must seek immediate assistance
from the Chief State Councillor.
We cannot tell my father.
We must keep this a secret.
My father must never know.
[clinking]
[foreboding music]
When I give birth to a prince...
the Royal Commandery or anyone else,
will not be able to challenge me.
[snarls]
[ominous music]
[female shaman]
Before the crescent moon sets,
prepare a ritual table.
That day...
the goddess of childbirth
will bless you with a prince.
[foreboding music]
THE WALLS OF MUNGYEONG SAEJAE
[crows squawking]
He had a jade ornament
of the Haewon Cho Clan,
so that is why we let him pass the gates.
[gasps]
Uncle!
CHEONGSUDANG
[gasping]
It is I, your only nephew, Beom-pal.
A strange disease spread on my first day
as magistrate in Dongnae.
I barely escaped here with my own life.
[Beom-pal] Please, grant me shelter.
I see.
I appointed you magistrate of Dongnae.
And yet, it appears
all you've managed thus far...
is protecting your pathetic life!
[gasping]
Uncle, I'm not sure I understand.
Dongnae was placed in your care.
What were you doing exactly?
And the Crown Prince...
under your nose murdered the commander
of the Royal Army in Dongnae.
[gasps]
Wait, wait. Do you mean...
that Beom-il is dead?
I wasn't aware.
I promise, I wasn't aware!
Please believe me! I did not know!
You should be grateful...
that Haewon Cho blood flows within you.
[whimpers]
That man is Dongnae's magistrate...
and Haewon Cho Clan's only heir.
See that he is treated accordingly.
[Hak-ju sighs]
And what of the woman behind you?
[gasping]
The thing is,
she is a nurse who worked
for the physician, Dr. Lee Seung-hui.
[Beom-pal] I would not be alive
if it were not for her.
Dr. Lee Seung-hui, the physician?
Is that true?
Yes, my lord.
See to it that she has
accommodations as well.
[gloomy music]
THE CITADEL OF SANGJU
[snarling]
[foreboding music]
[dog whimpers]
[all gasp, whimper]
[crows squawking]
Even we care for rationing...
the food will only last five more days.
With these many refugees,
there's not enough.
In that case, each morning,
hand out food to every last one.
You're correct to ration,
but the people should not starve.
This is not the disease we know of.
Things were not like this three years ago.
They only ate flesh of humans.
Bites did not lead to infection,
and the infected did not rise
during sunlight.
He's hiding something.
Lord Cho Hak-ju knows more
about the disease.
He has deceived you...
and all of us, my lord.
What are you trying to say?
I feel...
we are paying for the decision
we made back then.
This is our punishment.
You have regrets?
My lord.
I have no regrets at all.
Three years ago, Sangju...
and Gyeongsang was spared.
If given the choice,
I would not change a single act.
My apologies.
I have forgotten my place for the moment.
I will join the others
and ensure the citadel's security.
[wind whooshing]
Your Highness.
I overheard Lord Ahn Hyeon...
saying odd things to one of his men.
[Mu-yeong] They spoke as if...
they already know many things
about this disease.
And it seems Lord Cho Hak-ju
is implicated as well.
Your Highness.
I believe it's best to leave this place.
I will escort you, Your Highness.
You will be much safer...
back to the passage
and up the north branch.
Why are you sharing
this information with me?
Sir?
Did Cho Hak-ju command you to?
Sir.
Lord Ahn Hyeon told me...
that the palace guards knew
I was en route to here.
Was that your doing?
So, then...
are you trying to sort out between...
Lord Ahn and I right now?
Your Highness.
You assume you can't trust me now?
I left everything, my pregnant wife,
I left my family to follow you.
I've come all the way
to Gyeongsang for you.
And even now, you still do not trust me?
[guard 2] Fire!
Fire over there!
Fire!
[gasps]
- [flame roars]
- [men screaming]
[whimpering]
[women wailing]
[thuds, crashes]
[gasps, pants]
[pants]
The food.
Were you able to save
any of the food inside?
No, sir. I'm sorry.
This was your watch! What were you doing?
How could you let this happen
on your guard?
We don't know, sir.
All of a sudden,
there was an explosion, and...
- [grunts]
- [groans]
Do you know how valuable
that warehouse was?
The lives of everyone here
depended on the food that was inside!
[guard 3] I'm sorry.
It is all my fault.
- [crowd gasping]
- You should die!
[government clerk] It was me!
I left it alone.
[indistinct chatter]
I did this.
[government clerk] The fault...
it's mine.
I couldn't let my child starve to death,
so I just tried to take some rice.
I didn't know this would happen.
I dropped my lamp.
I dropped it by accident.
[sobbing]
I'm sorry!
Just...
Just kill me.
[whimpers]
[somber music]
What does it matter?
We're going to die.
[government clerk]
Whether we starve to death...
or get eaten by those monsters,
we're all going to die.
[gloomy music]
MUNGYEONG SAEJAE
[both sigh]
Do you really think you can use that
to stop this disease?
There's always a way to stop it,
no matter how severe the disease is.
And this one is no different.
If I study this plant's property,
I am sure I can find a way
to put a stop to this disease.
As long as we stay in Mungyeong Saejae,
we should be safe.
[sighs heavily]
There are still people alive
in the citadel of Sangju.
We have to save those people.
Right. His Highness...
[Hak-ju] What is that in your hand?
[gasps]
Hand it over, now!
Do you know what this plant is?
[gasps]
It brings the dead to life.
It's called the resurrection plant.
This plant's behind...
It's behind this outbreak.
And how do you know this?
[gasps]
I first learned of this,
through this nurse.
Go on, then. Tell him how you know.
[gasping]
"The resurrection plant was used
to bring the dead King back to life.
This plant is the cause of this disease."
Is that what Lee Seung-hui told you?
Oh, what do you mean by that?
What do you mean... "The dead King"?
[gasps]
Please have mercy.
[Seo-bi] The only reason I found
that plant, is because read about it
in his patient journal.
You read his patient journal?
Then you must also know...
how to raise the dead back to life?
"If you mash the resurrection plant,
put it on a needle,
and insert it deep into the glabella,
in two hours time,
the dead will return to life.
That's what he wrote in his journal.
[tense music]
I will take that girl to Hanyang as well.
Make preparations.
[palace guard 1] Yes, my lord.
Hanyang? When? What for?
There is still unfinished...
work to do.
When it is done...
I will return to Hanyang
and meet the future prince.
SANGJU, LORD AHN HYEON'S RESIDENCE
[Ann-hyeon] Wait.
What did you say?
I will go to Mungyeong Saejae.
Your Highness.
Those monsters are everywhere.
Mungyeong Saejae
will be impossible to reach.
To save our people, I must go.
I will require your best men.
[foreboding music]
[sword rasps]
I will lead the way, Your Highness.
Let's go.
[clanking]
[squelches]
[snarls]
[growling]
[snarling]
[ominous music]
[locks clinking]
[somber music]
Extinguish your torches.
[flame sizzles]
[foreboding music]
[Chang] The north branch is very close
to the passageway.
The monsters fear water,
so if we cross the river,
we should be able to escape them.
[Sangju offficer] Even if you cross
the north branch,
Mungyeong Saejae
will not be easy to enter.
The Five Armies will be
guarding the gates.
[Chang] The number of soldiers
has dropped to a mere tenth
due to the war three years ago.
There are about 5,000 elite soldiers
in Hanyang alone.
But even for Cho Hak-ju...
it will be difficult
to send all those men.
At most, the number...
cannot be more than 2,500.
That's still half the available force.
There is not many to guard
all the gates of Gyeongsang.
They'll be undermanned.
[Chang] I agree.
If they are guarding every gate,
Mungyeong Saejae would have no more...
than 500 men.
It will not be possible
to guard all of Mungyeong Saejae's walls
with that number.
[Ann-hyeon] The northwest section
of the first gate is built very high.
Functionally, it requires little defense.
The amount of men on guard would be few.
WEST SIDE, SOUTH SIDE
Well, then, once you're
in Mungyeong Saejae,
what is Your Highness' plan?
[foreboding music]
Cho Hak-ju...
will die by my sword.
[Chang] For his shameless disregard
of the people,
for his traitorous attempt
to steal the throne,
I will punish him and reclaim my place.
I will end this disease
and save our people from starvation.
And I will survive...
and create a new world.
[foreboding music]
[closing theme music]
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi