BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS BY YLAB
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[growls]
SCHOLARLY INSTITUTION
NEAR THE CITADEL OF HANYANG
When dawn hits...
all of your families will be executed.
The bureau will make sure of it.
Because of your service to me.
Will you remain loyal with that knowledge?
[Chang] Everything is at risk.
Can you continue to fight?
[foreboding music]
PATIENT JOURNAL
[indistinct chatter]
Mom!
[whimpering]
Please! Let him go! Stop it!
[officer 1] Get back!
No!
[indistinct crying]
[woman 1] Please...
I don't wanna go,
- I don't wanna go, please.
- [children crying]
[crying]
Father!
[muffled crying]
[tense music]
[rasping]
Put me down.
[third state councillor] This country
has already suffered much.
Cho Hak-ju's death was only the latest.
We should postpone the executions.
Her Majesty made it very clear
these executions
must be carried out on time.
The Minister of War has a point.
Some of the soldiers' families
are of noble origin.
These executions should wait
until we know the truth behind this.
This order has come straight
from Her Majesty.
This is a royal command.
[officer 2] Sir, please step outside
for a moment.
What on earth is going on here?
I am here to make a confession.
The traitor, Prince Chang,
and soldiers from
the Military Training Corps
are waiting for back-up outside Hanyang
and Yeonggi Academy.
Now that I've given you
this information...
I ask you to spare my family.
[ominous music]
[Queen] It seems as though
my father was correct.
Chang is a traitor.
With every move, he digs his own grave.
[tense music]
[guard 1] Fire!
I heard their screams.
[breathes heavily]
[crashes, clatters]
Oh, it's empty, sir!
[guard 2] There's no one here either.
It must have been a trap
to lure the soldiers away from Hanyang.
Those bastards.
SEO YEONG-GO
LEE CHANG
[guard 3] The Crown Prince is here!
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[guard 4] Gather up the rest of our men!
Seal off the gates!
[guard 5] Hyah!
NORTH GATE, CITADEL OF HANYANG
- [guard 2 shouts]
- [horse neighs]
[horse snorts, neighs]
[guard 3] The Crown Prince is here!
He's at the gate.
How many soldiers do we have left
in the Police Bureau?
Only a few dozen men
left at best, my lord.
Many left with the palace guards.
Assemble the remaining soldiers.
We're going to need backup.
Ask the Minister of War for assistance.
[prisoners whimpering]
[woman 2] Please...
Please spare us.
ROYAL COMMANDERY
[prisoners crying]
"Good people of Joseon.
These individuals claim to be loyal,
yet, they cannot condemn
the traitor, Chang.
[Beom-pal] To make matters worse,
they joined hands with our public enemy
in pursuit of their own selfish greed.
Thus, all families of those sympathetic
shall be beheaded when..."
[prisoners crying]
I don't wanna die!
"This is an order.
Beheaded..."
[wailing]
[crying]
"...shall be..."
[sighs]
I can't do this.
Head of the commandery or not...
nobody should do this.
[gasps]
Your Highness.
[Beom-pal] Your Highness.
You made the right choice.
Sir, it's you.
Yes.
And I will return to my rightful place.
Will you join with me?
Your Highness, the Royal Commandery
is at your side.
Untie these people now.
They are guilty of nothing!
[clamoring]
Give me a sword.
I want to aid you if I can.
Hello, my lord.
The traitors are at the execution site.
My lord, what is the meaning of this?
Restrain all the guards!
[officers] Sir!
[foreboding music]
JINSEON GATE
I'm quite confused.
Why is Chang making his way to the palace?
What happened to all the soldiers
we stationed out there?
It appears the majority of them defected
including our Royal Commandery
[court lady] The gates have been sealed.
Not even the palace guards
are allowed access to the citadel.
[breathes heavily]
Your Majesty.
We should escape while we still have time.
[ominous music]
I will go to the Main Hall.
I need to prepare.
To welcome my son.
[court lady] Your Majesty...
[suspenseful music]
PATIENT JOURNAL
This cannot be.
That patient journal once belonged
to Doctor Lee Seung-hui,
the former royal physician.
[Gang-yun] Everything recorded within it
is true.
[sighs]
What should I do?
Are you here with an errand
from the prince?
The Haewon Cho Clan are very dangerous.
His Highness...
will like you to show
that you are different from them.
[sighs sharply]
We have successfully quelled the soldiers.
The Police have been contained.
And now, I will escort you to the palace.
The Crown Prince is on its way
to the palace.
[chief scholar] Wait. What does that mean?
The Prince is back?
Did you say he is coming?
Let him out.
[keys jangling]
[lock clatters]
It's over.
The Haewon Cho Clan's rule
has come to its end.
[retreating footsteps]
[second state councillor] Highness!
Oh, please spare our lives, sir.
You should understand,
Cho Hak-ju gave us the orders,
told us they were from her majesty
and we had no choice but to follow them.
[ministers] Please have mercy on us,
Your Highness.
Highness, we are all so happy
to serve under you from now on.
And to assist you, we have ordered
to disarm all of the palace guards.
Please, would you like to come inside?
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
You are finally here.
You've been away for too long.
Come here and pay respect to your mother.
You are not my mother.
[chuckles]
You deny your filial duties?
I'm disappointed.
Give up the throne.
It does not and will never belong to you.
And by doing this, you believe the people
will serve you instead?
They won't.
You're a demon.
A criminal that decapitated his own father
with his bare hands.
This throne belongs...
to my son, the heir to the king.
This child...
How do we know
he truly is the son of the king?
Why were pregnant women
found gathered and buried
outside your manner at Naeseonjae?
What events led to Your Majesty
killing those women and children?
I'm afraid that Minister Ho has a point.
I, too, have been hovering
my own doubts about this.
We must place all of the physicians
and the court ladies
under arrest posthaste,
so that the truth of this matter
may be found.
You doubt my child?
You dare question
he's the son of the king?
I am here
not because I care for the throne
nor to oust you for being a member
of the clan that you are simply born into.
The throne has responsibilities
you will never understand!
"The people of this land
regard food as a God,
and the King must serve
his people as such."
You have neglected your responsibility.
[ominous music]
Make your decision.
[chuckles]
Will you step down of your own accord?
Or do we need to drag you off of there
like a dog?
[soft chuckle]
So your father wasn't enough?
You will murder
your mother and your own brother?
I welcome you to.
I won't leave the throne.
Try pulling if you must but I won't move!
[breathes sharply]
Your Highness, there's no need to dirty
his hands with her blood.
Do not concern yourself.
I will bring the seal
and make her issue a royal edict
to announce your enthronement.
[second state councillor]
I will accompany him.
Hmm.
It's the Second and Third
State Councillors.
They're making their way here
for the royal seal.
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[creatures snarling]
[panting]
[ominous music]
[hissing, snarling]
[lock clinking]
- [court lady screams]
- [gasps]
[court lady groans]
[sighs]
[distant screaming]
[groaning]
Is anyone here?
You're too fast, good sir.
[groans]
[suspenseful music]
[Seo-bi groaning]
[yells]
[exasperated sigh]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music]
[keys jangling]
[suspenseful music]
[indistinct shouting]
[clamoring]
[creatures growling]
[gasps]
[court ladies screaming]
[growls]
[gasps]
[snarling]
[roars]
[third state councillor] Has there been
any news on the royal seal?
- [yells]
- [creature snarls]
Councillor, get back!
Councillor!
- Stay away!
- [creature snarling]
[third state councillor] Get back! Oh!
Oh, my... Get back!
I don't wanna... I don't want to... Oh!
Sorry, I have to do this!
[creature snarling]
[third state councillor screaming]
Stay away!
Stay away! Stay away!
- [growling]
- [third state councillor] Open the door!
Help! Open the door!
[gasping]
[third state councillor gasping]
[yelps]
[screams]
[gasps]
[indistinct shouting in distance]
[swords rasping]
You...
What in god's name have you done?
If the throne cannot be mine,
well then...
no one can have it.
[man screaming in distance]
[screaming in distance]
[panting]
[groaning]
The plague is here!
[panting]
[baby coos]
[Seo-bi] The plague is here!
The plague is here.
It's spreading at the Queen's Palace.
[woman screams in distance]
[breathing heavily]
Shut and barricade
all the palace gates now!
HEUNGHWA GATE
SUNGJEONG GATE
My lord, what is happening?
How did the sickness make it here?
How they're here is not important.
We have no time.
Regardless if they're officers
or noblemen,
you must destroy the head!
Put an arrow between their eyes!
Every single person
who has contracted this needs to die!
Understood?
[guards] Sir!
[panting]
Highness.
[court ladies screaming]
[snarling]
[groans, grunts]
Don't let them bite you!
[creatures snarling]
[indistinct screaming]
[woman wailing]
[gasps]
[screaming]
- [groans]
- [snarls]
[screaming]
We need to get you out of here!
Let's go! Hurry!
[grunting]
[clattering on door]
Someone's in here.
[groans]
[grumbles]
I said someone's in here.
[creaking]
[snarling]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
[yells]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[snarling]
[hisses, growls]
[groaning]
[gasping]
- [creatures snarling]
- [gasps]
- [guard yelps]
[action music]
YEONGYEONG GATE
Here... You take the portraits.
[gasps]
[creatures snarling]
[whimpering]
[gloomy music]
[yells]
[whimpering]
[shrieks]
[grunts]
[growling]
[gunshot]
[groans]
[panting]
Is that it?
Are they gone?
[sighs sharply]
[sighs]
People aren't screaming.
The screams have stopped.
What's going on?
Do you think they got it under control?
[creatures snarling]
Please! Please! You must go!
Get out of here! Go!
[groaning]
There are too many.
They're breaking the gates!
Sir, let's go!
[Beom-pal panting]
[suspenseful music]
- [swords clanks]
- [gasps]
[suspenseful music]
[crows cawing]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[thumping]
[panting]
[closing theme music]