[suspenseful music]
[snarling]
[flame roaring]
BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS BY YLAB
[theme music]
[snarls]
[Ahn-hyeon] This plant...
3 YEARS AGO
...you're saying will resurrect the dead?
[Cho Hak-ju] Correct.
Immune to the sword,
they transform into monsters
that hunger for human flesh.
Absurd. You can't bring the dead
back to life.
[Cho Hak-ju] It is the truth.
And if it is?
For what reason
would you show this plant to me?
Are you suggesting
we resurrect our fallen soldiers
so they can continue fighting
the Japanese?
[Cho Hak-ju] I am not.
If the corpses started to rot,
resurrection isn't possible.
What's more, we cannot simply kill
our soldiers who sacrifice.
Squandering our military is not an option.
[sighs]
You still have not answered my question.
What are you trying to say?
The sick people of Sumang...
we'll use them.
Turn them into monsters
and unleash them upon the Japanese army.
That is how we survive.
These are not animals on a farm,
these are people...
And what purpose do they serve?
They would be dead in due time.
Our blood is the currency used
for this war.
It is our sworn duty to guard the land
and our people.
So then,
you would break that oath
and kill those you once protected.
I will not take part in such crime.
Resurrecting the dead?
This is nonsense.
Such thing is not possible.
[Cho Hak-ju] Tell me something.
Is it the lowly commoner you fight for?
I do not fight for them.
I swore to defend
the royal family,
the keystone of this country.
And I will do...
what I must to not fail.
[chain clanks]
[creaks]
- [flesh squelches]
- [snarls]
[snarling]
[growls]
Soon, countless Japanese soldiers
will descend upon us.
Our 500 men will be no match.
So, tell me.
How long do you insist
on putting righteousness first?
Lord Ahn.
Sangju...
Think of the many innocent
who are at risk.
These dying souls
are a necessary sacrifice.
[snarling]
We can put an end to it...
if the two of us
turn a blind eye just this once.
[infected snarling]
SUMANG VILLAGE
[gasps, pants]
[man panting]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[screams]
[ragged breathing]
[foreboding music]
[bird squawking]
[water trickling]
[Cho Hak-ju]
Soon, the Japanese army will invade.
Close the gate facing Sangju.
The gate on the opposite side
can remain open.
[suspenseful music]
[explosion]
[gunshot]
- [grunts]
- [thuds]
[grunts, groans]
[tense music]
[horse snorts]
[Ahn-hyeon]
I will not forget your sacrifices.
I promise you, they will not be in vain.
[snarling]
- [growls]
- [groans]
[flesh squelches]
[gasps]
- [snarls]
- [sword rasps]
[grunts]
[thuds]
[tense music]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
If you want to kill these undead monsters,
focus your attacks on the head.
[sighs]
How is this possible?
Lord Ahn...
Lord Ahn Hyeon passed from his wounds.
He was dead. I'm sure of it.
He was.
As you all witnessed with your own eyes,
Lord Ahn had indeed died.
However, that nurse
brought him back to life.
As Cho Hak-ju has.
[Lee Chang] He brought my father back
from the dead.
[clanks]
I ask you...
tell us everything you know.
Dr. Lee Seung-hui, the one who taught me,
put his notes on the disease
in the king's patient journal.
This is the resurrection plant.
This is what I used
to resurrect the Lord Ahn.
Also, this plant was used
to bring His Majesty back to life.
[Lee Chang]
Patient journal, the one she speaks of.
My father,
he tried to tell the truth.
The Haewon Cho Clan...
and their leader, Cho Hak-ju,
are accusing me of treason.
They claim I'm after the throne.
These are lies!
I have only one true desire.
To see the Haewon Cho Clan punished
for destroying our nation.
The Haewon Cho Clan
is guilty of mortal sin.
You know that to protect their power,
they defiled His Majesty's corpse
without even remorse.
They oppressed the people
still devastated by war.
They are behind of this famine.
They deliberately starved the people.
And now this plague.
The Haewon Cho Clan's greed
is at the root of everything.
Open your eyes and ears now!
People of this land are sufffering.
Now is the time to rise up.
Face reality...
and do right by this country.
Will you join this cause?
[all gasp]
THE CITADEL OF SANGJU
[suspenseful music]
[twangs]
- [explosions]
- [infected screeching]
[Lee Chang] The people inside the citadel
cannot hold out that much longer.
We have to bring food as soon as we can.
I agree,
but even with our most skilled soldiers,
we cannot fight our way through that many.
[Lee Gang-yun] They greatly outnumber us.
We escape through this canal.
Using what we could,
send wagons of food back.
I think that's our only chance.
That area is one we know very well.
Let us take the food.
Our families are still in the citadel.
Allow us to do it, please.
They'll attack from all sides.
Still think you can do it?
If we take this route
to the canal,
and provide cover along the way...
JUSEOMYEON, JUNAMMYEON
it could increase our odds.
We could cover you
after you cross the river,
but in the mountains,
you won't be visible to us anymore.
How can we provide cover fire
if we can't see where you are?
[tense music]
Fire now.
[soldier] Fire!
[cannons firing]
- [infected snarling]
- [explosions]
[snarling]
[cannons firing]
FIRE
[explosion]
[snarling]
Look! Over there!
They are launching cannon fire
near the canal.
[men grunting]
Come on, everyone. Be quick.
Come on. Hurry!
[servant 1] Oh, they stopped fighting.
[servant 2] Move quickly!
[servant 3] Let's go!
[servant 2 grunts]
[sighs]
I don't understand. What is going on here?
It's His Highness, the Prince.
He's taking Lord Cho Hak-ju down,
and he's in control of Mungyeong Saejae.
Oh, that's great news.
His Highness regrets
that he could not be here.
He must resolve a matter in Hanyang.
However, I come bearing a message.
It is not possible to get everyone...
out of the citadel safely
as we are still outnumbered.
So, we will continue to bring you food
using this method from time to time.
So please stay here
and hold out as long as you can.
[indistinct chatter]
[children giggling]
[servant]
Come on, give me a hand with this.
THE BASE CAMP IN MUNGYEONG SAEJAE
How is he doing?
His body temperature keeps dropping.
Hmm.
But you are sure that my uncle
will not turn into one of those monsters?
I'm reasonably certain
that he will not turn.
Besides, not everyone
turns into a monster.
Like Dan-i.
He was bitten by the king,
and he never turned into one.
However, he did become bedridden
and died eventually.
The disease has changed.
Dongnae, Jiyulheon happened differently.
It was the ones who ate Dan-i's flesh
that became monsters.
They spread the disease afterwards.
Then, uh...
Then, what will the disease do
to my uncle?
Well, he may not fall prey to it.
He'll probably die from the symptoms.
Just as Dan-i had.
We have to treat him somehow.
Seo-bi, please save his life.
I know what he's done to His Majesty
is unforgivable,
but we cannot let him die
in such a horrible way.
Dan-i...
there was nothing I could do to help him.
This time, it has to be different.
If I cure him
and find out what causes the symptoms,
maybe I will find a way
to bring this plague under control
once and for all.
All right.
Just whatever you do,
please save my uncle's life.
His body temperature has dropped again.
We must warm his body.
Look around for any herbs that could help.
Sure. Okay. I can do that.
[panting]
Seo-bi. Seo-bi, wait.
Would this work?
This is a rare medicinal wood
that the Queen asked for.
Sappanwood?
It's used to treat
gynecological conditions and ailments.
Lord Cho would not benefit from this,
unfortunately.
[Beom-pal sighs]
[Seo-bi] Wait.
Did you...
say Her Majesty asked for this herb?
This couldn't be
for Her Majesty herself, could it?
Of course it's for Her Majesty.
Why else would I have worked so hard
to get it?
You mean the Queen herself used this?
No. That cannot be.
Did the Queen use it recently?
Is that really important right now?
My uncle has one foot in his grave.
Please, you must tell me.
[sighs]
I had to get this wood last month
and the month before.
What's wrong?
[rustles]
- [door opens]
- [both gasp]
- [horses galloping]
- [soldier] Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
[officer] Your Highness.
We have a problem.
[Lee Gang-yun] What happened?
Where are the soldiers who were on guard?
[officer] They were killed.
We found their bodies behind the building.
Who did this?
Tell me right now!
[officer] I was informed
that Your Highness' personal guard
passed the three gates with a carriage.
He said he was carrying out an order
by His Highness.
[tense music]
[panting]
Hyah!
[Mu-yeong's wife] What is this place?
His Majesty collapsed just a few days ago
due to smallpox.
The palace is in total chaos right now.
Unfortunately, I must work.
I cannot stay at your side.
And I worry about leaving you alone
since you're so close to giving birth.
This residence belongs
to an acquaintance of mine.
In just a few days, I will return for you.
If I am to wait here,
then who will take care of you
when you come home?
Even if it's only for a few hours,
who will cook your meals?
Please.
I want to stay with you where I belong.
I will never understand what I did
to deserve such a loving wife.
Especially when you suffer
with a husband as foolish as I am.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
You know I truly am.
I'll wait for you, then.
And there is no need to worry about me.
It will only be a few days.
So, please look after yourself
and wait for my return.
[sighs deeply]
Take her to the room.
This way, please.
[gloomy music]
[Beom-il] You made a wise decision.
I'm truly glad
you brought her here yourself.
Now you know your wife is in good hands.
And we are getting what we want.
If anything...
untoward happens to my wife
while she's here,
I will not...
ever not stand idly by.
[thwacks]
Know your place.
You have no right to threaten.
Shall I grab your wife by her hair
and drag her here?
And end her life before your eyes?
I understand the Crown Prince
is very fond of you,
but the Haewon Cho Clan
will not be threatened by a mere guard.
I need to know
where the Crown Prince goes,
and with who he meets.
Understand?
That's the only...
way your family's safety will be ensured.
[sighs]
[gloomy music]
Hyah!
[Mu-yeong] Hyah!
It has already been four hours
since they left.
If you know they are burdened,
they must be very far by now.
If Cho Hak-ju reaches Hanyang first,
he will return with the might
of the Five Armies.
The people are still scarred
by the last war.
We cannot let our country implode again.
But how will you catch him?
There are many routes
he could have taken to get to Hanyang.
I am a tiger hunter.
No one is better at chasing targets.
Allow me to join you.
[Lee Chang] Hyah!
- Hyah!
- [Yeong-sin] Hyah!
[Lee Chang] Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah!
[tense music]
Is anyone outside?
HANYANG CONFERENCE HALL
Why have we still not received word?
Lord, we have not heard any news
from the Queen's Palace yet.
But Her Majesty's labor pains
began hours ago!
What if something has gone wrong?
Have you considered that?
Stop making such a fuss and sit down.
Just have patience.
I cannot tolerate this nuisance.
Councillors,
are you not at all curious, though?
His Majesty was falling in and out
of consciousness due to the plague.
So why would the Chief State Councillor
take His Majesty to Mungyeong Saejae?
That is not important right now.
The only thing that matters,
is whether or not we can restore
the backbone of this kingdom.
[sighs]
[midwife gasping, whimpering]
[groans]
[screams]
[royal officer] Who ordered the killings
of the women and children?
[midwife] How dare you!
You dare to suspect Her Majesty?
The moment Her Majesty learns
about this betrayal,
you...
will face her Queen's wrath!
[panting]
Are you keeping a close watch
on the Queen's Palace?
Yes, sir.
We are monitoring everyone
from the court ladies,
to the court maids,
even the water maids are being tracked.
[panting]
Sir.
I was just informed
of something very strange,
from the people
who lent palanquins to Naeseonjae.
It seems that, there were more, actually.
[royal officer]
Six palanquins, not three last night.
[suspenseful music]
[royal guard] What can we do for you?
I am here to search
the servants' quarters. It is urgent.
We cannot let anyone
enter these grounds at the moment.
Surely the servants' quarters
cannot be off limits.
We are looking for evidence
of a serious crime.
Step aside.
[Queen's court lady]
What is the meaning of this?
Her Majesty
is in the middle of childbirth.
You dare make a scene?
This will not go unpunished.
The guards in the East Gate informed us
at around 10 p.m. last night,
they saw three palanquins
entering the Queen's private residence.
Wet nurses came to breastfeed the baby.
That's not a crime, is it?
Of course not.
The guards also mentioned
these palanquins entered the residence
without being questioned who was inside.
You instructed the guards not to ask,
but I must know.
And I already told you,
it was the wet nurses.
Step aside.
[second state] What on earth happened?
We arrested him at the Queen's Palace.
He had entered
the Office of Royal Delivery.
You dare barge into the Queen's Palace,
knowing full well
that Her Majesty is in labor?
[third state] Not even a king can enter
the Office of Royal Delivery.
I understand that you are the head
of the Royal Commandery Division,
but this is a serious offense
that will not go unpunished.
They arrested the head
of the Royal Commandery.
The soldiers investigating Naeseonjae
have left.
That matter is done.
[scoffs]
They dare to get in my way?
Those Royal Commandery rats
are as good as dead.
[Queen's court lady] It's as I said.
No one can outsmart Your Majesty.
Now that they have lost their power,
the Royal Commandery is finished as well.
No one stands in your way.
So then,
what of the baby?
The remaining pregnant women
have been sent back to Naeseonjae.
I...
believe they can expect
very good news soon.
[creaking]
- [Mu-yeong] Hyah!
- [Seo-bi groans]
Hey, sir!
We have to stop right now, please.
Sir!
Please, his condition is worsening.
[Seo-bi] Sir!
- [grunts]
- [horse neighs]
[sighs]
His body is ice-cold.
I could barely feel his pulse.
How much longer will he last?
Well, at this rate, he will die very soon.
[panting]
Please, good sir,
we must find a place to lie him down.
[panting]
[stuttering]
Wait...
Wait, Seo-bi.
[gasping]
[groans]
Uh...
[mumbling]
- [clinking]
- [blows air]
[sizzles]
[door opens]
[suspenseful music]
[horses galloping]
- [horse neighs]
- I'm certain they went that way.
It's the only route to Hanyang.
So we should be able to catch them now.
[panting]
Why did you do nothing?
Your Highness, he betrayed you.
And you knew it just as well.
I wasn't ready to lose anyone else.
That's why...
I wanted to trust him.
[dramatic music]
[Seo-bi] Excuse me, sir.
Do you know when His Highness will arrive?
You said he would follow
behind us shortly.
How is Lord Cho?
His condition is stable for now, however,
he does not seem to be doing well.
If it's safe here, we should continue
to wait for His Highness.
No, we have to leave now.
Gather His Lord.
Tell me the truth.
Prince Chang did not request
we leave, did he?
And you have no intention of waiting
for His Highness to catch us?
I know not why you are acting this way,
but I implore you to reconsider.
I could tell His Highness
is very fond of you,
He relies on you as well.
So, I thought you made it your duty
to keep His Highness safe.
I told you we're leaving.
No. I will not go.
There is something important
I must tell the Prince.
Look, this is sappanwood,
a tree that only grows in Japan.
It's medicinal.
It's very rare and expensive to procure.
- What of it?
- Traditionally...
it is used to remove blood clots
after a miscarriage or birth,
or to alleviate symptoms related
to improper or lack of postpartum care.
This medicine is very strong.
Women who are pregnant
should not be using it at all.
I have no time for this.
What are you trying to say?
The Queen...
I know Her Majesty is using sappanwood.
What do you mean "Her Majesty"?
You just said that it cannot be taken
while carrying a child.
Exactly. The Queen cannot be taking this
if she is still pregnant,
but the magistrate told me that she is.
Then he must be mistaken.
Sir, I am as confused as you are, however,
if what he said is true,
then we have to tell His Highness
as soon as we can.
And if Her Majesty is truly taking this,
we must find out why that is.
- [woman 1] Wait.
- [woman 2] Eh?
- [woman 1] Are you sure you're done?
- [woman 2] Uh-huh.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
Did you say...
it's taken after birth or a miscarriage?
Normally, yes.
[Cho Hak-ju coughs]
[coughing]
My Lord, are you all right?
Where are we?
I want answers.
What is this?
What is it used for?
I'm not sure.
Naeseonjae boarded several women
late in pregnancy.
Why were they gathered there?
What are you scheming
with those women at Naeseonjae?
You will tell me right now.
[horses neigh]
- [thumps]
- [gasps]
[groans]
[foreboding music]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[screams]
Escort Lord Cho! Quickly!
[soldier] Yes, sir!
[screams]
- [flesh squelches]
- [groans]
[grunting]
[groans]
[pants]
[arrows thwacking]
Sir!
[panting]
[gasps]
[gloomy music]
[stuttering]
Seo-bi,
the thing is...
I didn't have a choice.
My uncle told me to do this.
[panting]
[Seo-bi sighing]
Seo-bi, we have to go.
[Beom-pal]
If you refuse, he will kill you as well.
Go now.
Go...
Find out at all cost.
Go now.
Hurry.
[Mu-yeong's wife whimpering]
[muffled scream]
[muffled pant]
[muffled grunt]
[labored breathing]
[Mu-yeong panting]
[dramatic music]
Mu-yeong!
Mu-yeong...
[Lee Chang grunts]
Sir...
[sniffles]
I'm sorry, sir.
Your Highness, I'm sorry...
[Lee Chang sniffles]
...for all my foolishness.
I need help, hurry!
Please, someone help him right now!
Naeseonjae...
There are many pregnant women there.
[Mu-yeong] The Queen...
and her court are plotting something.
The nurse...
The nurse knows everything.
Naeseonjae...
My wife is there as well.
[muffled cry]
Family...
My family is there.
Your Highness...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for failing to protect you...
till the very end.
[Lee Chang sobbing]
[Lee Chang] Mu-yeong.
[sobbing]
Mu-yeong.
[somber music]
[baby wailing]
[cooing]
[suspenseful music]
[baby coos]
[ominous music]
[closing theme music]
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi