[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 23]
Ling Yu Shi is the Nether Queen?
And Qin Lie was a spy
of the Dark Nether Race.
He joined our sect
just to open up the nether passageway.
Yet, I once took him as the successor
to the master
of the Artefact Forging Sect.
As far as I know,
Qin Lie joined the Sect
to find his missing grandpa.
That was just an excuse.
His goal was the Spiritual Lines Pillars.
I don't think so.
From my interaction with him,
I find that
he values his relationship with others.
I'd rather believe
that he goes against the world
for his loved one.
You sure are good at disagreeing with me.
This is not the time to argue.
Mo Hai's Terminator Profound Bomb
will be ready soon.
That being said,
there will be a war any time.
But, my daughter...
Master Song.
The Saintess is back, Master.
They let her go?
Yes, and Qin Lie is with her.
He came to negotiate peace.
What about the Nether Queen?
Is she here?
No.
Nice to meet you, Master Song.
What a pleasure.
May I know where's Master Xie?
He can't be absent
from a peace negotiation.
The Profound Heaven Alliance
can call the shots.
"Call the shots"?
Master Song,
so you alone can decide for
the entire Chilan Continent?
Qin Lie,
how do you want to do it?
I'm just the middleman.
On behalf of the Dark Nether Race...
No.
The Heaven Race...
No, I mean
the Nether Tribe.
I'll let you know what I'm thinking.
War is not the answer.
In that case, it's better to make peace.
I was once told
that on other continents
besides Chilan Continent,
there are other races
who can coexist with the human race.
There's no unity among different races.
Living together in peace?
That's a joke.
Peace negotiation is an important matter.
I need to discuss with other sects.
So, you agree with having a negotiation?
Great.
The Nether Tribe
is sincere about this too.
That's why they returned
your daughter to you unscathed.
The first step to making peace
should be releasing Ku Lu, isn't it?
You don't have to answer me now.
When you have decided,
have Du Shao Yang and Master Lang Xie
pass your words.
Why the both of them?
The young Du Shao Yang can run errands.
As for Master Lang Xie,
I trust him.
Okay, I'll decide.
Good.
I'll take my leave.
Master Ying, this is important.
The Sect should express its thought.
Okay.
Good bye.
This might be a trick.
What do you mean?
Choosing Du Shao Yang is fine,
but why you too, Master Lang Xie?
The Bloody Spear Guard is strong.
If he sets up a trap
and kills you there,
it's the end for the Guard.
Qin Lie won't do that.
Nothing is certain.
At times like this,
we can't afford to lose the Guard.
Du Shao Yang, follow me.
I heard
that Lang Xie thinks highly of you,
and that you're his successor.
Yes.
I can tell that you're an ambitious man.
Is becoming a Bloody Spear Guard
all you want?
I'm willing to work for you, Master Song.
Go and tell them this.
I can let Ku Lu go,
but
the Nether Realm
must trade him with something.
The Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus?
So,
this is that sneaky Song Yu's plan.
I told you.
This kid will be useful one day.
Look,
he just brought me a great news.
What is a Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus?
A Spirit Herb at the bottom
of the Netherworld.
Song Yu is still at Fragmentation Realm,
not being able to ascend to Nirvana Realm.
Why is that?
Because he's afraid of ascending.
The ascension from Fragmentation
to Nirvana Realm is very dangerous.
One who fails will die.
But he can ascend
after consuming the Lotus?
It'll be of help.
Forget it.
You won't be able to reach there.
This is a waste of time.
However,
I'm pleased today,
for you have brought this good news.
My daughter happens to be free lately.
You haven't seen each other
for a while now.
You young people
should always keep in touch.
Go now.
Go on.
Yes, Master Xie.
Recently,
I've been thinking about this.
How did you fall for me
when we first met in Icestone City?
You're too obedient now.
Unlike the old you at all.
But,
I prefer the old you.
I've never been so eager
to have you return to normal.
Look, such a sweet couple.
Good thing.
That's what young people do.
Being lovey-dovey.
I will do my best
to complete the task you entrusted to me.
I hope you'll keep your promise
and release her
after that.
Now that you've started it,
let's get things straight.
I want the Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus.
You
are still unable to ascend
from the Fragmentation Realm?
That's not your business.
Don't be nosy, kid.
So,
you want another Lotus as an exchange?
No.
Only one Lotus is needed.
I want Song Yu's Lotus.
That's not possible.
Find a way, then.
You have to give it a try, don't you?
Or you won't know if you can do it.
Then,
what if I fail?
Never mind.
You just
can't see my daughter anymore.
Given her condition,
it doesn't matter if you see her or not.
Isn't it?
Think properly.
If you're caught,
you hold all the responsibilities.
And don't mention my name.
I won't admit it.
No one would believe you, young man.
Think carefully and give me a reply.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Now, that's a right choice.
Here's a friendly reminder.
Qin Lie is the Dark Nether Race's guest.
This is outrageous!
Ridiculous!
Master.
Shut up!
-Master.
-Shut up!
[Gong Mu Lie, Son of God of War]
Ridiculous!
This is absurd!
[Ye Xian'er]
-Let me go!
-Hush.
-Let go of me!
-It's okay. Now calm down.
-Let me go!
-Hush. It's okay.
Hush. Calm down.
Let me go!
How did you see my dream?
Who was that girl?
I don't know.
I think that's you.
As you're the only one
who can calm me down.
How did you see my dream?
It is the Scripture
of the Nine Hells' power.
The Priestess said
that the Scripture is in three volumes.
We only have the first volume.
By practising with it,
I'll be able to use the power
of Mother of Land
and enter someone's consciousness.
Dream is a consciousness.
Mother of Land?
Do you remember
that the strange woman in the dream
said this before?
"The Mother of Land
and the son of God of War"
"cannot fall in love."
I have no idea
who the son of God of War is.
But,
if I am the Mother of Land,
there might be a chance
you're Gong Mu Lie.
Okay.
Ling Yu Shi became the Mother of Land.
I thought
I no longer deserve to stand beside you.
If I'm Gong Mu Lie,
then,
we can be on an equal footing.
That depends on
what kind of person Gong Mu Lie is.
If he's a bad guy...
Gong Mu Lie is not a bad guy.
Why are you here?
My father changed his mind.
He asked me instead of Master Lang Xie
to come here with Du Shao Yang.
Du Shao Yang won't come inside
to avoid misunderstanding.
So, I came in on my own.
What kind of person Gong Mu Lie was?
Gong Mu family was there
since the beginning of Spirit Realm.
Gong Mu Lie was the son of Gong Mu Hao,
the God of War.
Son of God of War?
When Gong Mu Lie was born,
Gong Mu Hao already died
in the war
between Human Race and God Race.
Ye Xian'er was ordered
to grow up with him
and guide him along the way.
She was a teacher
as well as a close friend to him.
After he grew up,
Gong Mu Lie was so powerful
that no one in the Spirit Realm
could beat him.
He stopped many wars.
When everything was settled
and the Spirit Realm thrived again,
Gong Mu Lie left quietly
in order to ascend to a higher realm.
His whereabouts was unknown.
Did Gong Mu Lie have a grandfather?
He did.
His grandfather was Gong Mu Shan.
Gong Mu Shan?
Is he in the history book?
No.
He's not mentioned in the book.
What about Ye Xian'er?
Gong Mu Lie and her...
They stayed with each other forever
for sure.
Who are you?
Tian Chun?
What have you done to me?
I'm sorry.
I used my power
to see if you're hiding something.
If you don't trust me,
then why bother asking?
You said to invite the Queen over.
What took you so long?
Your Majesty, the Profound
Heaven Alliance's man is waiting.
Let's go.
Skip the formalities.
Just cut to the chase.
Master Song agrees with negotiating,
on one condition.
The Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus.
Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus?
It's a Heaven Class spirit herb
that could only be bred
in the Profound Yin Nether Sea,
and is one of the Three Treasure
of Nether Realm that includes
Nether Hell Demonic Fruit
and Black Jade Soul Essence
The main usage
of Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus
is helping a
Fragmentation Realm cultivator ascend.
The great Master of the Profound
Heaven Alliance on Chilan
hasn't broken through Fragmentation Realm?
No wonder he wants the Lotus.
Song Yu sure knows how to make a deal.
We agree in
exchanging the Lotus for Ku Lu.
Where?
Tomorrow at noon,
the mountain peak outside Armoury City.
Here you go, Master Xie.
Song is here.
You're always on my mind.
How is it going?
We have agreed
to release him first, and negotiate later.
And?
The Terminator Profound Bombs?
In the Secret Realm,
she tried to kill you.
And when you entered her consciousness,
she tried to kill you too.
What's her grudge against you?
She kept calling you Gong Mu Lie,
and me, Wu Chun.
And the Song Ting Yu in her consciousness
is not at all the same as her in reality.
You're the Mother of Land.
And I might be Gong Mu Lie.
This means
that Song Ting Yu
may be someone even herself doesn't know.
I want to
enter her consciousness again
-to make sure of that.
-No.
The Song Ting Yu in her consciousness
hates you.
That's too dangerous.
It doesn't matter.
I think
that Grandpa Qin Shan's
taking you to Ling Borough
-is not a coincidence.
-He deliberately did that.
He knew that
you're a royalty of the Nether Tribe.
If that's the case,
then Grandpa Qin Shan
is behind all this.
Yu Shi,
if I consent to
you entering my consciousness,
then you're not breaking the rules, right?
What do you want to know?
The Soul Suppressing Orb.
Close your eyes.
Think about the Orb.
The Soul Suppressing Orb?
Who are you?
[Gong Mu Lie, Son of God of War]
Yu Shi!
Yu Shi.
There were four people.
They seemed to be guarding the Orb.
What's inside it?
My mind is occupied by people?
Four of them?
Three men
and a child.
You know one of them.
It was Du Shao Yang.
What...
What about the others?
I don't know them.
Nor have I seen them before.
What's going on?
But they don't look harmful.
Not Du Shao Yang.
Hang on.
He doesn't really
mean me any harm.
When we first met at Ling Borough,
he was being friendly to me.
But I gave him the cold shoulder.
Since then,
no matter what happened
or where I was,
I always ended up
teaming with him.
Meaning,
the others
will show up around you sooner or later.
I'll get in there again.
No.
You were hurt just now.
Humans are unpredictable.
We don't know
what others are thinking
or hiding.
We may not even know
everything about ourselves.
Promise me.
Stop using this power.
It's too dangerous.
But we need the truth.
It will come to light.
There must be some other clues.
We'll look for it using the clues.
Give me your word. Don't use it anymore.
Okay?
As you wish.
Master Song, a man of his word.
You're early.
I'm sincere about this,
of course I'll keep my promise.
What have you done to my brother?
Before you suggested the negotiation,
we did torture him.
Don't worry. He'll recover soon.
Here's the Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus.
Let him go now.
Release him.
Ku Lu.
Are you all right?
Master Song,
I'm here on the Nether Realm's behalf
to negotiate peace with you
so that our people
get a chance to get along.
Our ancestors
fought against the God Race
and chased them
out of Spirit Realm together.
There's no point in blaming any party
for what the Dark Nether Race has become.
From now on,
I hope both races
can coexist peacefully.
What's wrong, Ku Lu?
-What's he trying to say?
-What is it?
How shocking.
What power!
Keep it. Let's go.
They tricked you.
It's the Terminator Profound Bomb!
Master Song, you deceived us!
Why did you do that, Father?
Qin Lie, run!
Qin Lie!
Qin Lie,
here we are again.
It's time I settle the score with you
for cutting off my finger.
Since I can cut off your finger,
taking your life will not be a problem.
Such stubbornness
when you're about to die.
Listen to my order!
Eliminate the Dark Nether Race!
Attack!
Run!
Run before my father attacks.
I can't hold on for too long.
No, I'm going to fight!
Don't be ridiculous!
You're outnumbered. You won't survive.
Nine Suns Explosion!
Qin Lie.
Ku Lu and I can hold them off for a while.
Protect the Queen.
Run!
What are they doing?
They're performing
the Nether Secret Spell,
giving up their lives
to reach the Great God's altar
in order to use
the warriors' power left on the altar.
You carry the weight
of the Heaven Race's future.
Go!
Go now!
Ku Luo.
After them!
The nether passageway has damaged,
and the demon aura has been blocked.
We can't return to the underground.
Everyone dies eventually.
I'd like to see where you can go.
We won't die.
Had it not been Master Song's plan
and Master Xie's
generous offer of help,
God knows when will we manage
to regain power
at the Artefact Forging Sect.
It's all thanks to Master Song's plan
to have a false negotiation
that we can annihilate
the Dark Nether Race on the ground.
I'm surprised
to find the six Terminator Profound Bombs
so powerful.
In that case,
the Dark Nether Race
can no longer create troubles.
Exactly.
What a shame.
We succeeded
by being treacherous.
All is fair in war.
What? You want to negotiate peace
with the Dark Nether Race?
With them,
there's no need to play by the rules.
Where's Mo Hai?
Master Mo Hai said that
he'll come back late
for he has something to attend to.
Lang Xie. Lian Rou.
Gather the Bloody Spear Guard
and all disciples.
I want to reorganize the Sect!
Yes, Master!
What?
I'm leaving the Profound Heaven Alliance.
At Qisha Valley,
you were taken as hostage easily
and let Qin Lie and Ling Yu Shi go.
I was already being suspicious back then.
You helped them again today.
And now you wish to leave the Alliance?
Yes.
Give me a reason why.
Because you used dirty tricks.
The Dark Nether Race
wanted to negotiate peace sincerely.
Yet, you broke your promise
and caused the negotiation to fail.
Negotiate peace?
The Human Race and the Dark Nether Race
have been in war for a millennium.
You've seen for yourself
how many of our fighters
died in the battlefield.
The human prisoners
in the Abyss...
Do you dare to look into their eyes
and tell them we're negotiating peace?
Ridiculous.
Moreover,
we're strong.
Why bother negotiating peace
with the weak?
You and your fancy words.
This is what you really wanted, isn't it?
We once fought together against the enemy
and God Race.
We were once allies!
Are you defending them
because of Qin Lie?
You like him?
No.
You fell for Qin Lie?
Are you sure
you want to lie to me?
Yes.
I like him.
I like Qin Lie.
And I like him for no reasons.
[Peak of the glacier]
Where is this?
The Land of Frost.
We're safe here.
That cunning Song Yu
was treacherous
He went back on his word.
I should've just poisoned the Lotus
and let him die.
Only his death
could satisfy me!
Calm down, Qin Lie.
Don't come near!
I don't know what happened,
but I can tell
that you and Qin Lie hold a deep grudge
against the new Great God.
Your Majesty,
the Great God is not as noble as you,
but to the Heaven Race...
Priestess Du Du,
I know what you're trying to say.
I can
let it go for the time being.
But when everything is over,
I will fight him to the death.
Please don't intervene then.
Okay.
The Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus?
Give it to me.
Keep your promise first.
Otherwise,
even though I'm no match for you,
I'm still capable of
destroying the Lotus.
Aren't you too impatient, young man.
Si Qi.
Why isn't she responding?
Be patient.
It takes some time to regain her senses.
Shao Yang.
Si Qi.
Rest well for now.
It's time to hand it to me.
Is this Song Yu's Lotus?
No, of course.
Given my capability,
how would I take it from Master Song?
But before the negotiation,
I met with Qin Lie
and asked for one from him.
It wasn't a difficult task
since we're close.
I wouldn't believe it
if you told me that you took it
from that crafty Song Yu.
These few days,
I've been observing
Master Song as you instructed.
I found that he has long
wanted to get rid of you.
Of course he would want that.
As
I want that too.
Master Song
must be consuming the Lotus now.
If he ascends first...
Let's see who is faster.
This can't be.
Yes, it can't be.
Master Xie,
how are you doing?
You two
set me up.
I will never forget
to avenge my wife's death.
[Something like Heartless Servant
actually exists?]
[That crazy Xie Yi turned Tang Si Qi]
[into a Heartless Servant]
[and forced Shao Yang to work for him]
[so that he can bring Song Yu down.]
[Shao Yang knew that I hate Xie Yi]
[for killing my wife.]
[So, he asked for my help.]
[Qin Lie,]
[will you help me?]
[That goes without asking.]
Qin Lie came to negotiate peace
on behalf of the Dark Nether Race.
In order to
keep in touch with me secretly,
he told Song Yu to choose
either me or Lang Xie.
Song Yu was well aware
that Lang Xie wouldn't do it.
As a matter of course,
I became the Alliance's representative.
Song Yu talked to me in secret.
So did you.
It's just
one Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus.
Song Yu wanted it.
So did you.
And I knew
it is time.
[Tell Qin Lie]
[that we need
two Profound Yin Nine-Leaf Lotus.]
[Tamper with the one given to Xie Yi.]
[He'll love this poison.]
[Since he loves turning people
into Heartless Servants,]
[let him get a taste]
[of becoming one.]
[Okay.]
[But we'll let Song Yu
have the other Lotus?]
[Song Yu pretends to be just and fair,]
[but is vicious and cunning.]
[You're right.]
[If he ascends successfully,]
[he'll be fearless.]
[Shao Yang,]
[this poison]
[can disable all kinds of spirit herb.]
[Apply it on Song Yu's Lotus.]
[Give him an unusable Lotus.]
I'm done talking.
The poison should have kicked in.
Who do you think I am?
Do you think you can set me up?
I won't be defeated
by this amount of poison.
Master Xie,
save your effort.
The poison I made
can't be removed easily.
Master Mo,
the poison...
Xie Yi.
Get on your knees!