[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 24]
Master Mo,
the poison...
Xie Yi.
Get on your knees!
Slap yourself.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Rong'er.
I
have avenged your death.
Get Du Shao Yang here right now!
Si Qi,
do you think I'm cruel
for doing this to your father?
Cruel?
Ask the victims he once hurt.
Ask them if you're cruel.
What's your plan now?
You're his only daughter.
Now that he's become like this,
you can take over
the Eight Extremes Temple Sanctuary.
Why must I do so?
I'd have to deal with Uncle Song if I do.
He's quite nice to me,
but look what happened to Song Ting Yu
who works for him.
You're not working for him,
but working with him instead.
Having equal footing
is not possible if I'm not as good as him.
To him
as well as everyone around me,
I'm just a junior.
Speaking of Song Yu and Song Ting Yu...
This isn't over yet.
Song Yu will realize that
he's eaten a drugged Lotus in no time.
Also, Shao Yang,
you must take control of the situation.
Okay.
Song Ting Yu
has been locked up by Song Yu.
What?
Little Ting Yu.
Where have you been?
I've been looking high and low for you.
You're thinking of me
even when you're in trouble?
You really are my sister.
I'm getting you out of here. Let's go.
How did you
get past the guards?
I couldn't do that.
Your father let me in.
Come on.
Shao Yang!
You have the audacity
to deceive my father?
Master Song is eager to meet Qin Lie.
So, I told him
that you're the only one who can do that.
Why not let Saintess Xie
pretend to save you
as you'll look for him after that?
Master Song
agreed to the plan.
Don't get carried away.
Do you know where Qin Lie is?
Do you really expect me
to help you capture Qin Lie?
Ting Yu, please trust him this once.
You owe him your freedom.
Not me.
It was me.
Thank you, Master Mo Hai.
Go and meet up with Qin Lie.
My father must've sent someone
to spy on us.
Now, we...
We already dealt with that.
Shao Yang had someone disguised as you
and went southward
on a flying spirit beast.
But Qin Lie is at the north.
We just lured them away.
How do you know he'd be at the north?
Qin Lie mentioned about
the Eye of Frost before.
Since it's something frosty,
it'll be at the north.
But do you have any idea
of its whereabouts?
When we were at the Abyss,
Qin Lie once told me
that there's this place at the far north
where the heavenly ice won't melt.
An ancient man-eating beast
is trapped there.
I think
I know where it is.
All of you can no longer
stay at Chilan Continent.
Your only way to survive
is use teleportation.
Song Yu's men are waiting for you
at the Herb Mountain.
You have to die fighting
to use teleportation.
Please lend us a hand.
I believe the Soul Suppressing Orb
inside Qin Lie's mind
is the key to using teleportation.
And it was written in an ancient book
that a space spirit stone is needed
to use teleportation
as it has an unusual formation.
The space spirit stone?
But there isn't many space spirit stone
at Chilan Continent.
I happened
to have one.
Ting Yu,
give this to Qin Lie for me.
The space spirit stone is inside.
But that's everything you have.
Are you leaving the Artefact Forging Sect?
Rong'er is no longer around.
There's nothing
stopping me from leaving the Sect.
I'm just an ordinary person.
I don't know why I love artefact forging
or
how I did it better than others.
And I became a master
before I even know it.
Ting Yu, hand Qin Lie the ring.
He has a promising future.
One day,
the Ring of Space
that might seem valuable to others
may not be a big deal to him.
Consider it
a keepsake.
Where are you going, Master Mo Hai?
Since I'm alone, it doesn't matter
where I go.
Will I see you again?
Fate will bring us together.
You should go, Saintess Song.
Let's go.
You mean, we?
The three of us.
Why must I go?
I'm still with the Sect.
You're right.
We can't always
be a step backward than Qin Lie.
Then, I'll take Ting Yu to the formation
and come back soon.
No way.
Why is that?
Please let me go.
I won't be at ease if I don't see her off.
I don't want you to go.
I'll be right back.
Does this happen often?
He's impatient,
but never unreasonably ill-tempered.
In the battle at Purple Mist Sea,
my late father
left a letter behind for him.
It said that Grandpa Qin Shan
left him at Ling Borough
to lessen the violent nature in him.
Ling Borough
was a peaceful village.
It was indeed a good place
to learn self-control.
Qin Lie.
What's wrong, Qin Lie?
His nape!
What's going on?
Let me out, Qin Lie!
What are you?
I'm Mang Wang
of an ancient Titan Race.
They are all my people.
We used to devour
every life in this world.
Maybe we ate too much
that he got angry.
In the end, he attacked us.
He was too strong
that he defeated all of us
and had us bound here by ice.
Then, he took me away.
Who was that?
Was it my grandpa,
Qin Shan?
I have no idea.
To us,
all humans look alike.
It's only until recently that he freed me,
and ordered me to help you
obtain the power of thunder pool.
But?
You got hungry or what?
And you want to eat us?
I can feel my people here.
And I know that you're in huge trouble.
So, I'm here to make a deal.
What is it?
Everyone at Chilan Continent
wants you dead.
Release my people.
We'll eat all those who want to kill you.
Is there a need to think twice?
They are treacherous,
and they killed the innocent.
We eat humans for survival.
And we'll stop and we have enough.
They're the cruel
and greedy ones.
If I'm right,
they're coming to eat you shortly!
Qin Lie.
I've only achieved Manifestation Realm.
How do you know I can help?
The essence of frost can bind
and unbind things with ice.
Didn't the person who taught you this
tell you?
I told you,
they're treacherous.
Why don't you smash the world,
and destroy this ruthless Chilan Continent
with your rage?
Give me the nod
and I'll make your dream come true.
Don't do as it asks.
Don't you dare, useless beast!
Qin Lie,
there are lots of monsters here.
How many people will they eat
before their hunger is satisfied?
If you free them,
they'll devour everyone
at Chilan Continent.
So what if they do?
The entire Chilan Continent wants us dead.
Why should we let them live?
Ancient Great God, please lend me a hand!
Qin Lie,
over my dead body before you kill them.
You want me to kill you?
Or you're going to kill me first?
I go against the entire Spirit Realm
and the Golden Class family for you.
Yet, you're betraying me?
I won't betray you.
All I want is stick with you
through thick and thin.
I don't believe that.
Liar.
You're all liars!
Qin Lie, come to your senses.
This isn't you.
-[Let go.]
-[Calm down.]
-[Let go of me!]
-[Calm down, it's all right.]
-[Let go!]
-[It's all right.]
[Calm down. It's all right.]
[Calm down.]
It's all right.
It's all right now.
What happened to me?
Calm down.
What happened?
It's all right now.
You just lost control.
Fortunately,
Little Ting Yu calmed you down.
But of course,
you helped too, Yu Shi, thanks.
Don't be so talkative.
Qin Lie.
Shut up!
I know that your body
is still bound by ice.
And that
this is just what's left of your power.
Stop pretending to be powerful.
Get lost.
We need to get to Herb Mountain.
Master Mo Hai has taught me
how to use teleportation.
But
I've betrayed my father.
There's no place for me at Chilan anymore.
Come with us to the Abyss.
We can no longer escape.
Shao Yang?
Si Qi, come here.
Master Song has promised to forgive you.
You betrayed me?
Traitor.
Song Ting Yu,
you are the traitor of Chilan Continent.
Du Shao Yang.
I trusted you,
but I was wary of you too.
I tried to convince myself
that you're loyal to friends.
So you're talking about loyalty now?
I showed my loyalty to the Human Race.
But you,
to the Dark Nether Race!
No, what is
the Dark Nether Race to you?
You did this for a woman.
For Ling Yu Shi alone,
you betrayed Chilan Continent.
Why should I help you
or be loyal to you?
What did Song Yu promise you?
Stop it.
Qin Lie, stop talking.
Master Song, all of us
have known Qin Lie for a long time.
He will never betray Chilan Continent.
-He's just...
-Yi Yuan.
-You...
-Master Song,
he's just blinded by love.
He won't escape now.
Why don't we take him back and guide him?
What an unfilial son!
Yu Xin!
Are you all right, Yu Xin?
I'm not Yu Xin.
I'm Yi Yuan, Qin Lie.
Qin Lie,
you'd better yield.
Since you chose otherwise, then die.
Nine Suns Explosion!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Qin Lie.
No.
Let's go down together.
The Frost Master?
Qin Lie,
stop this.
Guys,
I'm Li Mu from Heavenly Sword Mountain.
Li Mu, the Sixth Sword Holder
of Heavenly Sword Mountain
at Heavenly Calamity Continent?
That's me.
I'm here
to stop the fight.
Do you think
the Dark Nether Race
will live peacefully with humans?
Why not?
The Frost Master is a wolf, you know?
And I can live with the wolves.
Ridiculous.
The Dark Nether Race kills humans.
You killed many of them too.
Both Human and Dark Nether Races
are right and wrong at the same time.
But I'm not here to lecture you.
It's only a matter of time
before the God Race is revived.
We'll talk about it later.
After I kill Qin Lie.
What if I won't let you?
This is the Chilan Continent.
Master Song.
I speak for the Heavenly Sword Mountain.
And I call the shots there.
Understood?
This...
Qin Lie,
I lose to you
once more.
Guys,
the God Race will return sooner or later.
What a shame.
Chilan has been peaceful for too long
that you've grown arrogant.
You even fight among yourselves.
I came here today
to pick some young talents
to be trained
at Heavenly Calamity Continent.
As there's nothing more you can gain
from the narrow-minded Chilan Continent.
This is the token of Heavenly Sword Sect.
Qin Lie,
will you come to
the Heavenly Calamity Continent with me
and further your horizon?
Uncle Li is a Sword Holder
of the Mountain?
I'll go.
Take it.
Ling Yu Shi,
what about you?
I will go to the end of the world with you
even if there are hardships,
but I can't abandon my people.
I have my responsibilities.
Song Ting Yu.
The brave and smart Saintess
of the Alliance.
Will you come?
Yes.
Xie Jing Xuan, the courageous and talented
Saintess of the Eight Extremes.
Will you come?
Yes.
Very well.
Follow me.
Uncle Li,
please bring Yi Yuan too.
I knew you're a great buddy.
Qin Lie, I'm touched.
What a loyal friend.
Permission granted.
Thank you. Thanks.
Unce Li,
there's one more person.
There's more?
You're not going for a vacation.
That's him.
Du Shao Yang.
What is this?
A humiliation?
I need a rival.
Without one,
there's no competition
or the will to compete.
And I can't become stronger
or go beyond my limits.
Du Shao Yang,
I dare you.
And I'm not afraid.
Ling Yu Shi,
the new Nether Queen,
return to the Abyss
and reorganize the Nether Tribe.
I hope there'll be a day
when humans and the Nether Tribe
can be friends.
Yes, sir.
You haven't left?
But you don't have any business here.
Let's go.
Why must we come
to the formation to use teleportation?
Can it
bring you back to the Abyss?
No.
But,
it can take us to our ancestral land,
the Realm of Ruined Souls.
It should look very much like my dream.
But what will happen to the others
after we go there?
Your Majesty,
it's a rare chance
that teleportation can be used.
We're only sending you there.
What?
No.
Your Majesty.
You either listen to me
or don't call me your queen.
It's been a long while
since they went home.
At least let us
take a look there.
Oh, Qin Lie.
Senior Li Mu
was one of the people
inside the Soul Suppressing Orb.
Uncle Li?
Remember,
you still have one question.
I remember that.
I know what you're going to ask.
Twenty years ago,
some of our Five Horned Warriors
were captured by humans.
Back then, I was young and aggressive.
Bringing only a team of warrior with me,
I tried to rescue them at Purple Mist Sea.
Unexpectedly, they were waiting for us.
Then, your grandpa came.
He defeated the humans easily
and saved us.
He gave us his word
that the nether passageway
will be opened one day
so that our people may go home.
Grandpa said that?
Why did he help you?
He didn't let me know.
At that time,
he was holding a baby boy in his arms.
He asked us
to help the boy
if he ever encounters danger one day.
He also told me
that the boy
was named Qin Lie.
I'll stay at the Abyss
and study the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
Maybe
I'll find a solution regarding the Orb.
Okay.
I understand why
you kept Du Shao Yang with you.
He's also crucial
in finding out who you are.
But,
it seems like he and Li Mu
don't know about their past.
Be careful.
Actually, it's not about the Orb.
Even if they're not related to it,
I'll still do that.
Why is that?
In the past,
he was just
an unscrupulous man to me.
But the more we joined forces,
the more I think
that we're like-minded.
Also, I think that...
His dissatisfaction
and infuriation
are towards you alone.
You should be friends.
Yet, you have to scheme
against each other.
As expected from you.
It's normal to envy
and compete with friends.
But when it comes to Du Shao Yang,
it's more like
resentment.
Exactly.
I wonder what happened
between us in the past.
When will we meet again
after we go our separate ways today?
Our love won't be hindered
or affected by distance.
I once said
my goal is a higher and further place.
Now I've finally taken the first step.
And it was all
because you were there for me.
It's my pleasure.
Take care.
Although you're not my birth father,
you were the one who raised me up.
But somehow,
I couldn't
get close to you no matter what.
You're being thoughtful only because
you finally have someone to back you up.
Being mysterious
and exceptionally talented,
I should've known
that you'll fly high one day.
I've always wanted
to get along with you
like any other fathers and daughters.
After losing my wife,
I've wished
to seek comfort from you.
But I was too stupid.
The harsh treatment
was just so that
you could be the best among all.
Look, the path to cultivation
is unimaginably long.
If you slacken even for once,
all your efforts will go to waste.
I don't understand your heart,
as well as my own.
I'll make up for all the mistakes
I've done if we ever meet again.
Remember to cherish
the rare chance.
One day, you'll achieve something great.
You asked me
to stay here for 1000 years.
But this time,
I have to break my promise again.
Bu Li, give me a chance
to keep my word.
You chose to go against your word.
What else do you ask from me?
Should I just forgive you?
No.
I dare not ask for that.
Why don't you
come to the Heavenly Calamity Continent
with me?
If I was just a wolf
like how I used to be,
it doesn't matter where I go.
But I'm the Frost Master now.
And Mang Wang is already on the move.
Moreover, that Continent is too hot.
Forget it.
I'd rather stay here and be at ease.
You're right.
I can't have a northern king of wolf
becoming a dog because of the heat
at the Heavenly Calamity Continent.
I... I mean,
I'll turn into a hot dog there
and return here to be your housekeeper.
By then, Frost Master,
please don't give me the cold shoulder.
Yi Yuan.
Lian Rou, you're here to send me off?
Of course.
I thought you have left.
We're waiting for Qin Lie.
He's seeing Ling Yu Shi off.
Lian Rou, will you wait for me?
Yi Yuan,
if that's a nice place,
you don't have to come back.
We're different after all.
Your promising future is awaiting.
Just go.
What are you talking about, Lian Rou?
Why wouldn't I come back?
I'm serious about my feelings for you.
You are fond of me
because no one was nice to you before.
Since I was nice to you,
so you fell in love for me.
You don't love me, do you?
Just tell me. Don't give excuses.
It's not that I don't.
But I don't like waiting.
I'm afraid of waiting.
And I'm worried
that my wait would go in vain.
Our future is uncertain.
There's no need to make a promise.
If fate allows it,
then we'll see each other again.
Isn't that better?
Yi Yuan.
Leave now.
I'm going to cry.
But I don't you to see that.
Go home.
Go!
She's left.
She really left?
Just cry.
I want to cry too.
Qin Lie is back.
Guys,
are you ready?
-Yes.
Qin Lie,
the sky here is beautiful.
If only you're here too.
[Hush. Hush.]
-[It's all right.]
-[Let me go.]
-[Calm down.]
-[Let go!]
[It's all right.]
[Hush. It's okay.]
-[Let go!]
-[It's all right.]
[It's all right.]
It turns out that
the fierce battle
wasn't what that was between us.
It's just that
I'm not the one.