[English subtitles are available]
Let me go with you!
-Okay?
-I’ll be back soon.
-I wanna go with you!
-You’ve got to listen to your sister
and be good, okay?
-Where are you going, daddy?
-Will you bring us gifts?
-I want to go, too!
-Me, too!
-Please, dad!
-I also wanna go!
I'm sorry. I can't bring you kids this time.
Eh? Why?
That's unfair!
-Come on, guys. Don't be so wilful!
-I wanna go!
Look, dad is troubled, okay?
Fine.
Get along with your siblings, okay?
Dad, good luck with your job!
Well then, I'll get going.
-Be safe on the way.
-Good luck!
My dear...
I'm sorry. I'll leave the children to you.
Let's go.
If they'll attack me, will it
take place during my speech?
I can't say for sure, but that's highly possible.
It will be the only time that the leaders
of the Marleyan army are gathered in public.
Or when the officers are on the move...
Usually, the route wouldn’t be confirmed
until right before departure for safety reasons.
Many important figures will take carriages.
Then the military leaders should
be in the VIP seats in the corner.
Group them as close together as possible.
Are you sure about this?
We Tybur family won’t just
sit around and enjoy ourselves,
not like our predecessors at least.
We've built friendly relationship with
the influential people around the world
to improve the social standing of the Eldian,
and we also kept an eye
on the movements on Paradis island.
However, we failed in
protecting our own backyard.
By the time we noticed, our enemies
had crossed the sea
and set foot in our home.
And now, they could kill us at any time.
What we must be wary of are those who secretly
work with the Paradis island forces.
But we still don't know who they are.
As you know, our country
Marley has too many enemies,
which include the ones inside the army.
If it's to smoke out the enemies,
I'm prepared to light a fire on my ass.
I'll accept the enemy's plan of attack
and use it to our advantage.
If you have any other idea, just say it.
If you don't, we will go as planned.
Even though it's to fish up our enemies,
the bait for it is too big.
Just give them as many useless
officers as they want.
If their objective is to deal a blow
at the Marleyan army,
there's no better opportunity.
Your plan of rebuilding the military will go smoothly.
The party is ready to approve whoever you choose.
However, a lot will die.
But most of them will be the Eldian,
the descendants of the devils!
Isn't it a bit too late for that,
Commander Magath?
You have thrown countless Eldians
In front of the enemy's machine gun
and straight into the minefields.
With or without military uniform on,
they're all the same.
You just need to keep doing
what you've been doing.
Let me make it clear.
This is not a war.
We still don't know our enemies,
their goal or means of attack.
We will be surrounded by crowds.
Lord Tybur, I’m afraid I won't
be able to protect you.
You will die at this rate.
Using you as a bait is way too risky.
I know. I’ve prepped myself for that.
The world won't take it seriously
unless I stand in front of them.
It will be the only time that the military,
journalists, and diplomats are in one place.
Furthermore,
the Eldian in Liberio internment zone,
including myself,
must become the tragic victims
of a "surprise attack."
The world wouldn’t be on our side
if I were the only one who survived.
It's certain that the Eldian are
the descendants of the devils.
And we...
are devils indeed.
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
(#65 War Hammer Titan)
Wake up, Gabi, Udo!
Stand up! Hurry!
...Zofia?
- Zofia, are you okay?!
- No, Udo!
- Zofia!
- Udo! Over here…!
We must hurry and get this off of her…
Udo!
Brother...
You have fulfilled your duty...
...as a Tybur.
Commander Magath!
The War Hammer Titan will lose!
Commander, we can't find the Warriors!
General Calvi and the rest of
the command have been wiped out!
We should evacuate the VIPs first!
-It's too dangerous for us to stay here!
-Please give us your order!
Commander!
Commander...?
It was just a small pop,
but the first shot of our counterattack
has been fired.
I’ve never thought they would
make such a grand entrance.
And judging from its look,
it could be Eren Yeager himself, the usurper
of the Founding Titan, the Attack Titan.
It saves us the trouble of
going to the island.
All men, to your station!
Prepare for battle!
Yes, sir!
Hey, hey, what's going on?
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and run…
You all had better keep it in mind
that it's me who made the first shot.
Dammit! Why?
Why a war all of a sudden?!
Colt, how's Udo doing?
Anyway, we must bring him
to the hospital immediately.
Udo... no way!
Dammit!
Falco! Where are you?!
Just what is happening outside?!
This rumbling...
It sounds like a fight between Titans.
There's no way!
That explains why we're confined here.
We must get out of here fast.
But how…?
What the heck is this?
You're late!
Ms. Pieck,
are you okay?!
Hurry up and bring us some rope!
Yes, ma'am!
The Panzer unit?
How did they know we are here?
That beard guy was suspicious,
so I gave them a heads-up.
So that's why!
That soldier is suspicious. Tail us later.
A Titan attacked the plaza
during the speech!
What?!
The War Hammer Titan seems
to be fighting it right now.
What about the Cart's armor?
It's at the HQ. It can be equipped
in fifteen minutes!
Do it in ten!
Roger!
I'm going ahead.
Wait, Porco.
You should wait and see if the situation…
What was that?!
No way... how could that...?
We did it!
It's working!
The Anti-Titan Artillery does pack
a powerful punch!
-Load it now!
-Commander Magath,
let's take down Eren Yeager right away!
If we can take him down here,
the enemy's force is done for!
No!
Killing the Founder won’t solve the problems
but will only make them worse.
We must have the War Hammer
eat him no matter what!
We must focus only on assisting it!
B-But, Commander!
The War Hammer doesn’t seem
to be interested in eating the Founding.
How powerful!
The attacking means nothing to it!
It's War Hammer's victory!
So that's him... Eren Yeager!
It's really planning to kill him.
Usurper... Eren Yeager.
Do you have any last word?
Now, Mikasa.
You are all here!
Eren, I beg you...
Come home.
Our chain of command has been broken.
It's time to show the true
strength of the Marleyan army!
Cancel the special vigilance training.
Bring the entire army down the mountain.
Same goes to the fleet off-shore.
Get our thirty thousand soldiers stationed in
the east and west and gather them here.
Seal off the internment zone!
Don't let a single one of those island
devils get away, including the Founding.
Run amok while you can.
This is the end for you guys.
In this massacre,
every major nation that lost government
officials here is now part of this war.
Just as Willy Tybur had planned.
The whole world now knows
the threat of the Eldian Empire.
The world won't let you live anymore.
But still, they should've known
about that already.
In which case...
You damned the devils!
Shoot them down!
Those guys...
Are you trying to burn this whole
internment zone down?!
Keep the civilian losses to minimum!
Do you understand, Floch?!
There are only enemies
and the buildings they live in.
Have you forgotten how many human beings
inside the wall have been killed
by these bastards outside?
They ate us alive!
This isn't even close to a payback!
You're still saying that?
Look.
Eren showed us.
He told us to fight.
We can't just wait inside
the wall for them to kill us.
We need that devil!
Eren... Do you understand what you've done?
You killed civilians.
You also killed children.
There's no undoing this...
Mikasa, it's not over yet.
It can't be! I completely blew away its nape!
I even made sure to crush its nape.
But it’s not dead yet.
I see...
The War Hammer Titan...
So it's able to make anything with
high dexterity with hardening?
I get it now.
No wonder it's still alive no matter
how many times I’ve crushed its nape.
Mikasa, grab her attention for me.
If it goes well, I can eat
the War Hammer Titan.
Can't do. There’s no bed available,
and that kid is already dead.
Come on, please take a close look!
You should take a close look at the situation!
You're a warrior candidate, aren't you?
Doctor, come here please!
Okay, I’ll be right there!
Gabi. You should stay with your family.
There's no telling where's safe right now.
Get away from the plaza as far as possible.
I'll go back and look for Falco.
I will go, too.
I still don't understand why
Udo and Zofia must get killed.
Wait, Gabi! Don't go!
Stop!
It's war zone over here!
Gabi!
What are you doing over here?
Mister gate guard...
I'll join the fight, so let me through.
Don't be stupid, you brat!
You should go home and…
What?
Is it enemy's attack?
From where?!
Above us!
Dammit!
Gabi, run…
Hey, are you oka-
Mister...
We've blocked this street.
Let's go, Sasha.
Connie, have you forgotten
to light up the lamp?
Oh, that's right.
Jean, the enemy’s reinforcement
won't get here so soon.
How about the lights?
All in place.
Is the plan going well?
For now, it is.
As long as we can take that thing
down in time…
But there’s no guarantee.
Anything could happen at this moment.
Just what lies after this fight...
We must survive to discern that.
Now I know what's been bothering me.
The weird feeling I had the moment
the War Hammer Titan appeared.
Its body was materialized from its feet up.
Not from its nape...
It appeared from the centre of the stage.
The War Hammer's body...
Oh, no!
The War Hammer Titan will get eaten!
I've been waiting for this moment!
I'll retake the Founding!
Eren!
What?!
I can't bite him through!
He did that?!
Could he be... the Ackerman?!
Don’t stay here!
No way...!
I'm a Titan!
And these human beings are trying to kill me?
So these are...
the devils of Paradis island!
♫ In an instant, in an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes ♫
♫ I will be immortal ♫
The devils of Paradis island...
The Warriors fight the soldiers who freely jump around
the space.
Will Reiner be able to hear Gabi and Falco's call?
Next Episode: Assault