[English subtitles are available]
I keep having the same dream,
dreaming of the old man who
hanged himself in that settlement.
I’ve been wondering why he told us that story
before he hung himself.
How are we supposed to know that?
Maybe he wanted someone to forgive him.
Yet he definitely wouldn’t hear it from us.
We ran and left Marcel to die, after all.
For whatever reason, I think
that old man must have wanted…
someone to judge him.
Hey. It has been four years, hasn’t it? Reiner.
Well… Ermm…
I heard you two are old friends...
Isn't that so, Mr. Kruger?
Yeah. We got a lot of things to talk about.
I'm not sure from where we should start.
It's impossible…
Eren…
[Attack on Titan]
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
[#64 Declaration of War]
Lord Tybur, it's about time.
Yeah...
Oh dear.
To my surprise, did the Azumabito family
come all the way here to encourage me?
I hope we're not bothering you.
I just wanted to see you.
I look dreadful, aren’t I?
I get a stage fright.
No. You are a brave person.
Our family knows it very well.
I wish you luck.
Much appreciated, Ms. Kiyomi.
Sit, Reiner.
This is a good seat, don't you think?
You can clearly hear the noise
of the stage from here.
Above us is a regular apartment building.
It's right in the back of the stage,
but many residents can’t wait for
the curtain to be raised.
It's right above us.
Huh? Mr. Kruger…Did you hurt your hand?
Yeah, it's just a scratch.
Reiner, c'mon, sit.
Well, I'll go back first.
No, Falco.
You should stay and listen to our conversation.
Falco. Do as he said.
Yes.
Well then, we should go now.
Oh, long time no see. Mr. Leonhart.
Mrs. Braun.
Last we met was when your
son returned, wasn't it?
Come to think of it, Mr. Hoover has
already passed away, huh?
Yeah…He was always pound
of his son’s dedication to Marley.
I'm sure your daughter also...
She's not dead.
Annie is alive.
She promised me she would return home.
Who would have thought we would make
declaration of war in this interment zone…
So amazing! Even General Calvi is here.
To think that the core officers
of Marleyan army would all be in here.
There are also countless foreign
ambassadors and nobles.
And reporters from every major
newspaper in the world, I guess?
It feels like being at
the center of the world.
The Tybur family's influence
sure is amazing,
even though they're Eldian like us...
It's starting.
Are Falco and Mr. Braun not here yet?
Warriors of Marley,
Commander Magath has summoned you.
Eren…
How did you get here?
What are you here for?
Same as you.
Can't you tell?
I'm just like you.
It's out of our control.
Looks like it's starting.
Let's listen to it.
I have a story to tell you.
About a hundred years ago…
The Eldian Empire ruled the world
with their Titan power.
From the rise of the Founder Ymir
to this day,
it is said that the lives that were
taken by the titans
tripled the amount of humanity remained today.
Outrageous number of races,
along with their culture and history,
were destroyed by the Titans.
These slaughters are part of
the history of humanity…
It’s the path that the Eldian Empire took.
Then, the all-conquering Eldian Empire
engaged in a war among themselves.
It was the start of the Great Titan War.
The families who held the Eight Titans
shed each other's blood.
However, there was a Marleyan
who saw a chance in this chaos.
He was none other than the hero Helos.
He cleverly led the Eldian Empire
to its self-destruction with intelligence manipulation.
He then joined hands with the Tybur family,
and successfully made King Fritz, who is said
to be unbeatable, to retreat to the island.
However, the king who retreated to
Paradis island is still in hand of his power.
Tens of millions of Titans with the power
of crushing the world are waiting on that island.
It's only by pure chance that our world
continued to exist to this moment.
That's the only explanation
our Titan scholar could provide.
Our motherland Marley has sent out
four Titans to eliminate that threat.
However, they were beaten back and the only
one to return was the Armored Titan.
That means the darkest bolt of human history,
the Eldian Empire, is still alive and well.
Did you hear that, Reiner?
That’s the reason you guys
breached the wall.
You guys were trying to save the world,
weren’t you?
Yeager, go to the front gate.
Okay.
You two, follow me.
I feel like I've seen you somewhere before.
What unit you belong to?
I'm from the base in the west, Lakua.
I was called here to help
with the security.
I have no interest in chit-chatting
with an Eldian.
Well, that's a shame. I found
your beard to be charming.
Ms. Pieck!
The Panzer unit!
Thank you for working
so hard even on a day like this!
Well... same to you, Ms. Pieck.
You look quite happy today...
What are you doing? Let's go.
What was that about?
Well, as the Cart Titan, their fate
and mine are one and the same.
So our bond is important.
Well, it looks like what you did might
cause more damage than help.
Find anything suspicious?
No report as of now.
Look at the even smallest detail.
Have them report on anything they found.
Roger.
It's here. Get in.
Where's Commander Magath--
Porco!
What is going on?
Why Deputy Chief Braun looks so frightened?
Mr. Kruger is his old friend, right?
Old friend?
Wait, then, when did they first meet?
If it was over four years ago,
then they must've met on Paradis island...
No… it can't be…
Because… that means…
It's impossible…
Could it be…?!
[The available intelligence for now]
[Paradis island  The war of retrieving the Founding Titan]
[Took place in 854, a military operation led by Commander Theo Magath]
[Marcel Galliard, Reiner Braun, Bertolt Hoover and Annie Leonhart were selected from the troop and formed a four-member Warrior team,]
[Who hid on Paradis island, aiming to retrieve the Founding Titan and bring him back to Marley.]
[Five years after the war began, of the four Warriors, two were captured by the enemy and one died.]
[Reiner Braun was the only one who survived. He even brought back a captive who inherited the Jaw Titan.]
Well then, the things I talked about so far
are facts that everyone knows.
However, the truth is slightly different.
What I will tell you now is the memory
that was passed down to us
through the War Hammer Titan.
Today, I will publicly reveal that truth
for the first time ever.
About a hundred years ago…
The one to end the Great Titan War was
neither Helos nor the Tybur family.
The one who put an end to that war
and saved the world was King Fritz himself.
He lamented the cruel history
of the Eldian Empire.
He grew tired of the war
between his people.
And most of all, his heart ached for
Marley that was under constant tyranny.
When he inherited the Founding Titan,
he made a plan with the Tybur family.
They then made a man to play
the figure of a Marleyan hero.
That man was Helos,
who moved as many Eldian citizens as he could
to the island and sheltered them inside the gate.
And then he left a message that whoever
dared to threaten his peace would be attacked
by thousands of Titans.
However, it was not the end of the story.
In order to pass down his own philosophy,
King Fritz made a vow of renouncing war.
With this, Karl Fritz's philosophy was
passed down to his successors,
thus, ensuring the Titans from the island
won't attack the rest of the world.
Therefore, the one who actually saved the world
was the King of the Wall whom we hate.
It was thanks to Karl Fritz
and his desire for peace.
His goal was to make peace.
"If one day Marley grows stronger
and takes the lives of the royal family
or its Founding Titan,
I will accept it."
"That is how grave the crimes of us Eldians,
and how they could not be atoned for."
"However, until the day
that retribution comes,
I want to enjoy this brief moment of paradise
without conflict within the walls."
"Please, I ask you to grant
this wish of mine".
Those were the king's final words.
What does that mean?
If what he said is true…
The story about Marley and Tybur family
saved the world was all made up by King Fritz?
If the King of the Wall really have
no desire to invade the world,
then why would people say
Paradis is a threat?
Yes,
we Tybur family, in order to
ensure the prosperity of our family,
joined hands with Karl Fritz
and sold Eldia to Marley.
We Tybur family were nothing but filthy
thieves who were living off falsehood.
However, I am not standing here just
to put an end to this falsehood.
I'm here because it had come to my
knowledge that this world is in danger.
Commander!
The Warriors and the soldiers
we sent to bring them back are gone.
Mobilize the reserve and search for them!
Roger!
So it has begun…
That hurts, dammit!
What the heck is this?
Must be a trap to lock us Warriors.
It's old-fashioned,
but we can't transform in a cramped place like this.
And there are two of us...
Yeah, we might get crushed to death.
What was that tall soldier up to?
I don't know.
But I feel like I've seen that soldier somewhere…
Please, stand there and watch.
This is my way of taking responsibility.
Karl Fritz used the power of the Founding Titan
to give birth to three layers of walls.
These walls are made of about
tens of millions of Colossal Titans.
It serves as both his shields and spears,
all to maintain peace.
However, in recent years, a rebellion
has occurred within Paradis island.
King Fritz's pacifist ideology
has been rooted out,
and the Founder Titan has
been stolen by someone.
The world is in danger once more.
This someone has rebelled against peace…
is named…Eren Yeager!
You lied to me…
I… respected you…
Yet you’ve been lying to me this whole time…!
I'm sorry, Falco.
You saved me a lot.
Those letters…
Those letters you asked me to send for you were...?
They weren’t for my family.
They were sent to my ally.
It can't be… no way…!
Your ally...?!
The threat of Paradis island
is an attack by this army of Colossal Titan,
the Rumbling.
As I explained earlier,
those of royal blood won't use
the power of the Founding Titan
because of the vow of renouncing war.
However, Eren Yeager currently
possesses the Founding Titan.
It is thus possible for him
to start the Rumbling.
Once the Rumbling begins, there's
nothing we can do about it.
Humanity could only
tremble and run in fear of the footsteps
of doom.
These Titans will crush our cities, societies,
and literally flatten the world.
He's right.
I'm a bad guy, just like what Willy Tybur said.
I might destroy the world.
However, you guys looked like bad people to me, too!
That day, the wall was breached,
my homeland got trampled by the Titans,
and my mom was eaten in front of me.
I just couldn't understand.
Why is that, Reiner?
Why my mom had to be
eaten by a Titan that day?
It's… because… we breached
the wall that day.
Why did you breach the wall?
To use the chaos to sneak into the wall
and see how the King of the Wall would respond.
What was your goal?
To retrieve the Founder and save the world.
I see…
If it was to save the world…
I guess you didn't have a choice.
You used to say it, didn't you?
You said you would do whatever you can
to see us suffer the worst death.
You came here to do that, right?
Ah, did I really say that?
Please forget it.
It's true that I once saw everyone
on the other side of the sea as enemy.
Then I crossed the sea and arrived here.
I slept under my enemies' roof
and ate the same food as they did.
I'm Just like you, Reiner.
Sure, there are some people who pissed me off.
But there are good people, too.
Be it on the other side of the sea
or inside the wall,
it's the same.
However, you all were taught that
the people inside the wall were devils.
A bunch of clueless, ignorant children were
taught that since birth.
But what could you've done?
Back then you were just kids.
Hey, Reiner…You've suffered a lot, haven’t you?
No! It's not true, Eren!
That day,
when Marcel was eaten…Annie and Bertolt wanted
to cancel the mission and go home…
But I convinced them to continue the mission…
I wanted to be a hero!
I wanted to be respected.
It's all my fault.
It is my fault that your mother got eaten by a Titan!
I hated my blood.
I wished for the extinction of all Eldians
more than anyone else.
I can't take this anymore…
Please kill me…!
However, I don't want to die.
Because I’ve already been born in this world.
We may belong to different
nations and races.
However, now it’s the time for us to
join forces and face this powerful enemy together.
I want you,
who do not wish to die, to lend me your strength.
I beg you, to ensure our future together!
If we work together,
we should be able to overcome anything!
As I thought, I'm the same as you.
I wish you to join me in our fight!
A fight to defeat the devils on Paradis island!
I think we were like this from
the moment we were born.
I, Willy Tybur,
as the ambassador of Marleyan government, hereby proclaim...
I will continue to move forward,
until I exterminate all my enemy.
To the enemy force on Paradis island,
this is a declaration of war!
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can fly ♫
♫ Please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes ♫
♫ I will be immortal ♫
[Preview]
The Attack Titan appeared from nowhere.
Along with the echo of his roar,
the innocents were trampled mercilessly.
It was then, the War Hammer was swung.
Next Episode: War Hammer Titan
[#65 War Hammer Titan]