CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, INCIDENTS
AND OCCUPATIONS ARE FICTITIOUS
No!
Are you all right?
Are you So Mun?
Sorry?
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Hold him tight.
Let me go!
-Let me go!
-Hurry.
Let me go!
You little punk.
What's with him?
He's not strong.
Hurry. Tie him up.
Man, I got scared for nothing.
If what Ha-na said is true,
what are we supposed to do?
We can't even take on Ji Cheong-sin alone.
How are we going to deal
with a herd of evil spirits?
What's he going to do
with all those evil spirits?
Are they going to rob a bank?
Anything and everything.
Once they get together,
there will be bloodbaths everywhere.
Wait a second.
You don't see anything? Here, look.
Hazy like smoke. It feels like fog.
The place where I spotted the spirits.
It was Mun's neighborhood.
If Ji Cheong-sin had been after us…
Mun. No, Mun.
-Shit.
-He got disqualified as a Counter
and doesn't have the power to fight!
Mun's calling.
SO MUN
-Goodness.
-Mun.
-Mun?
-Mun!
Ji Cheong-sin.
Where are you?
Where are you, asshole?
Mo-tak.
-No…
-Hey.
That's the crazy bitch
from the department store.
-Yes.
-Mun, where are you?
Tell us where you are! We'll be there!
No, don't come.
You can't come here.
-Your camaraderie makes me cry.
-Damn it.
Anyway, what happened to this kid?
I read him, and he's an idiot now.
He has no power
nor any physical strength.
Mun!
Mo-tak, don't come here.
You'll all die if you do. Don't come!
Don't come.
Derelict factory in Jungjin, 9 p.m.
He'll lose a finger
for every minute you're late.
Those psychos.
EONNI'S NOODLES
Evil spirits can read memories?
Yes, I'm sure they read everything
about our team,
so they probably know
the type of power each of us has.
How many evil spirits did he gather?
We'll get them all no matter how many.
Mun's been taken hostage.
EONNI'S NOODLES
So your side calls us evil spirits.
You wanted to kill me.
You said you're going crazy
because you want to kill me, you bastard!
Did you miss
your mommy and daddy that much?
Why are you dying to see your parents?
What do you know?
You're a scumbag
who killed his own parents.
I will…
run to the ends of the earth if I must
to make sure I catch you.
Do you know what I'm most excited about?
That your parents who are right here…
will get to see you die.
That's it.
You asshole!
They're here.
Oh, all right.
No.
No…
Ji Cheong-sin and Baek Hyang-hui
are both level-three spirits.
The spirits I just saw were level two.
Let's move as a group.
Don't fight them alone.
I'll be your shield,
so stick right behind me…
and use me to defend yourself.
Be careful.
It's like walking into a snake's mouth.
I think it's this way.
Ms. Chu!
-Ms. Chu!
There's an evil spirit here.
He's big.
He's quite big in size.
There are two of us.
Ms. Chu, give us a minute.
I'll let you witness
your colleagues' deaths.
-Mo-tak.
-You two, go find Mun.
Go find Mun!
Okay.
Ms. Chu, hang in there for a bit.
Do you see that old bitch?
She's the healer.
Kill her first.
Honey! Babe!
Over here!
There are four.
Ha-na. Mo-tak.
It's great to have everyone here together.
It's like a reunion.
Bullshit.
Did you go to school?
All my husbands graduated
from Seoul National University.
Mo-tak…
Mun, hang in there a little longer.
Don't you have any respect
for the elderly?
There aren't too many people
who are in comas--
-Su-ho.
Su-ho!
Mo-tak, is something going on? Mo-tak.
Long time no see.
No. No! Mo-tak!
Let him go, bitch.
This bitch reads minds. Be careful.
Blue smoke means life.
Black, evil spirits.
And green smoke
is the spirits that were taken captive
by the evil spirits.
Ha-na won't respond either.
What in the world is going on?
Mo-tak, answer me.
-Is everyone all right?
-Wi…
Wi-gen…
Wi-gen?
Mun?
Wi-gen!
Wi-gen, you can hear me, can't you?
A spirit just ascended.
Did you summon her here?
No, I'm not sure what's happening.
Wi-gen.
-Are you inside me right now?
-No.
Darn it.
Please.
No. Stop it.
Stop it!
Stop it. Please.
Stop. Stop it!
Stop it!
Ms. Chu!
Ms. Chu.
Stop it!
Stop! Stop it!
Stop it. Stop it, all of you.
Wi-gen…
It's all because of me. Please.
Mun.
Wi-gen.
Please come inside me. Just this once.
They're all going to die because of me.
They're all dying because of me.
Please…
Please help me out just this once.
Wi-gen.
What am I supposed to do?
Wi-gen! Please help us!
Hey! What are you doing?
That crazy bitch.
-Open the door!
-He just said
he doesn't need you two anymore.
Open up!
Mo-tak…
Ms. Chu.
Ms. Chu!
No, Ms. Chu!
I'm sorry. It's all because of me.
Ms. Chu…
Whoa, shit.
I won't be seeing you off!
So it's them?
Idiots.
I love it when I hear people scream.
Ms. Chu, wake up!
Chairman Choi.
-Gosh, Mun. Are you okay?
-Thank you for coming.
We don't have time for that.
What's going on?
-Where's Mo-tak?
-Over there summoning evil spirits.
Goodness, Mo-tak,
you're doing your job in this chaos.
Those jerks at Yung.
Look at how hard they're working
as you hold them back
with an inspection or whatever.
Ha-na.
You nit-picked over petty things
and held our best attacker
down on the bench.
And then this happened.
Do you have to bring that up right now?
All of us were down too.
Both Su-ho and U-sik are about to vanish.
Yes.
It needs to be said.
How could you take away his power
while the evil spirits were after him?
Going back and forth out of need?
That's not a rule of ours.
Then is it okay
for a person's life to be at risk?
The problem is that
he became their target!
EMERGENCY RESPONSE
You're like the prodigal son.
Welcome back, Mun.
-Ha-na.
-Are you okay?
Chairman, didn't you erase his memory?
Would you have done it if you were me?
You aren't dead.
Thank you, Ha-na. Thank you for coming.
Damn it. I told you not to touch me.
JUNGJIN POLICE STATION
I'M HERE TO TURN MYSELF IN
ON NOVEMBER 2ND, AT 11 A.M.,
I MURDERED MY WIFE AND HER OTHER MAN
Where am I?
Hey, who are you?
Who's this idiot?
I'M HERE TO TURN MYSELF IN
Why are we sitting here like this?
What?
Who are you?
KIM JEONG-YEONG
There's no way it was done by a human.
Could it be…
That's right.
It was an evil spirit.
They'll turn normal
once the evil spirit's power is gone.
The police can have him afterwards.
He's Choi Yeong-il,
the vacation villa murder suspect.
Should we arrest him?
-Take him away.
-Yes, ma'am.
You're here.
Mo-tak.
Are you in a lot of pain?
You should get examined again.
I'm fine.
I'm more worried about her.
Yes.
I heard her brain is awfully swollen.
And her eyes are bruised.
How dare they do this
to her gorgeous face.
But she is getting better, isn't she?
Right.
Let's give her time.
She's a woman
who can easily make it through this.
She'll come back.
You've forgotten how to walk properly?
I promised you I'd heal your leg.
Mommy's hands are healing hands
Mun's bones are tough and strong
Ms. Chu, you have to hang in there.
The mayor hired the evil spirits?
Yes.
We need to talk.
You can't catch those rats
without my help.
Get me off the wanted list,
and I'll take care of it.
Looks like he also helped to plan
the fabrication of Ji Cheong-sin's death.
Man, it makes me speechless
to hear something that absurd.
What has the world come to?
How can jerks like him be in politics?
-Do Mo-tak and Mun know, too?
-Yes.
A guy who hires evil spirits is much worse
than the evil spirits themselves.
We can't let this go on.
Let's put an end to Mayor Shin
and Cho Tae-sin.
I…
I feel like all my heavy burdens
have been lifted off my chest.
Those rats.
How dare they try to ruin your career
right before the election.
There are way too many rascals
who think they're Robin Hood and his gang.
What about the council?
I went after their weaknesses
and did them some favors, too.
But you still need to go through
your primary election.
I thought it'd be easier
if we saved the council's face,
so I resolved everything
with very appropriate measures.
Appropriate?
A company picked by the council
will extract the leachate,
but we'll be in charge
of the purifying process.
When are we getting started?
The pipes are in. We got started ages ago.
Make sure dirty water
doesn't get in the water supply
and just reroute the waterway.
Of course we will.
I also rerouted the public sentiment
with all those news articles
by taking them down already.
And now,
we have one more to go.
That detective brat.
JUNGJIN CITY HALL
These are the assemblymen
who wish to join your camp.
POTENTIAL CAMP MEMBERS
Hyun Chung-nam
is a part of Oh Yeong-deok's camp.
Once Mr. Hyun makes the change,
11 other assemblymen of Jungjin
will join us along with him.
They're established in their districts,
so you'll most likely win.
Do you think I'll make it?
Sorry?
Do you think I deserve that position?
You're on your way to victory.
At this point,
no one can do much to stop you.
I'm starting to get scared.
I think I might really become
the president.
A NATION OF THE PEOPLE AND JUSTICE,
KOREA
LOCKERS
Hey, what were you doing in there?
Borrowing your clothes.
I can't walk around in my prison garb.
Where's Jang-su?
In the bathroom.
He's really gross.
I can't stand
being in the same room as him.
How much did you get?
Hey, what's this thing? Is it for me?
Hey.
Haven't you ever gotten a gift
for a girlfriend?
You've never had one.
What are you doing?
What did you do in my room?
What were you looking for?
Let me go. I said, let me go.
I wasn't looking for anything!
I just borrowed your clothes!
What the heck is wrong with you?
Get a passport photo today.
A passport photo? Why?
You want to go on a trip with me
or something?
We're going abroad.
Who are you to decide?
If you want to leave, leave alone.
You can either come with me
or you can die right now.
You're on the wanted list.
Cut your hair first.
How am I supposed to cut my hair
with this?
Then what are you going to do
when we come back to Korea?
That voice recording…
will be worth a fortune
once Shin Myeong-hwi…
becomes the president.
If you ever try that shit on me again,
I'll cut your thing off.
So I didn't summon Yung's territory…
with my desire to kill?
Mun.
Yes?
The inspectors want you here.
Should I be nervous?
Yes.
The committee of Yung
would like to make an announcement
regarding Counter 1543, So Mun.
You're reinstated.
Yes!
We owe you big time.
Wi-gen.
I don't think I'm working as a Counter
because of my mom and dad.
Then why are you doing it?
I'm going to find out.
I feel like
I haven't given you all my trust.
I can't fully trust myself either.
Thank you very much…
for giving me another chance.
Wi-gen.
It looks like Su-ho is going to vanish.
What?
Ms. Chu.
Over here!
No, Ms. Chu…
Mun.
Ms. Chu…
No…
Ms. Chu.
Ms. Chu!
SEVEN YEARS AGO
Ms. Chu Mae-ok.
Are you the 45-year-old Ms. Chu Mae-ok?
Yes.
I've been looking for you.
It's been forever
since anyone's called me by my name.
I didn't know you were talking to me.
That's what happens to moms.
No one calls me by my name.
People just call me…
Su-ho's mom.
That's it.
Mom.
Su-ho.
Oh, Su-ho.
Su-ho, my son.
-Charge it to 200 joules.
-200 joules.
All clear. Shock.
Ms. Chu.
You've been in a coma for a month.
Goodness, yes.
I survived all alone.
Your hand slipped away in the water,
and I only saved myself.
Sorry for leaving you first, Mom.
No.
No, I'm sorry.
Mommy is sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Don't say that.
My son.
Su-ho…
-Increase it to the maximum.
-The maximum.
All clear. Shock.
Su-ho.
Hold me tight.
I won't let go of your hand.
We'll never let go of each other.
-Su-ho.
-U-sik.
Su-ho.
Ms. Chu…
Goodness, Ms. Chu.
You've done well.
Let me go.
Oh, okay.
Welcome back, Mun.
It's been a while.
Yes, Chairman Choi.
What's all this?
I made abalone porridge.
Did you wash everything properly?
Just take a seat, will you?
I'll heal all of you
once I feel a little better.
-No way.
-No.
You need to rest.
You just got better, Ms. Chu. No way.
Let's eat.
Stop looking at me with those eyes.
You always healed everyone else,
but who will heal you if you get hurt?
When you got hurt…
it was really frightening.
All of you…
are as good as family.
Yes?
I have…
something to tell my family here.
It's a very shocking confession.
A confession?
Don't you dare say you love us.
Goodness.
I got…
my memories back.
-What?
-What did you say?
-Seriously?
-Really?
-About half.
-What?
Half? What do you mean "half"?
One second. Look at me.
Good for you, Mo-tak!
Here are the texts between you two
that were on your burner phones.
LIFE WILL BE GOOD
On the 21st,
you ran over Mr. Ga Mo-tak
and three others…
with this truck.
Did you expect life to be good
after murdering people?
Hey.
About the call history
from Noh Hang-gyu's burner phone…
Yes. Did you find everyone he spoke to?
He called five numbers on this phone.
One of them is Noh Chang-gyu.
The other four were also burner phones,
so I found
the locations of the signals.
When did you get this far?
Great work.
But let's pretend
you never saw these pictures.
What's your plan?
You just gave me the fake names
registered with the burner phones.
That's all you did. Got it?
Answer me.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you enjoy your lunch?
The men who called you often
on your burner phone.
You've got such rich
and influential friends,
but they won't even find you an attorney.
The day the illegal dumping
got exposed. City hall.
Mr. Noh Hang-gyu, Mr. Cho Tae-sin,
and Mayor Shin got together,
and they were joined by this guy.
What kind of a connection…
did this serial killer, Ji Cheong-sin,
have with Mayor Shin and Mr. Cho?
We found 17 different bank accounts
you kept under different names
and five murder instigations.
Unless you want to take the blame and
celebrate your 80th birthday in prison,
stop pleading the Fifth.
It's time to cooperate.
First, I need to know what I can get
by cooperating
with you.
Damn it.
She froze all the bank accounts
that Hang-gyu was managing.
How am I going to fund the campaign?
Both Chang-gyu
and Hang-gyu were arrested urgently,
so they had no time
to clean up their phones.
What's your plan?
Chief Choi, this is your responsibility.
What's your plan now?
He told you
not to mess with his subordinates.
He said he won't let you off anymore
if we mess with any officers.
Chairman Cho!
Do you think you'll be fine, Su-ryong?
Hey, you.
I got you promoted
from a mere section chief
with a mugunghwa mark on your badge,
so behave, will you?
Did you think
you were on my level
because I was nice to you, asshole?
If you don't lose that bitch,
the least you'll have to do is resign.
Get out of my car, you bastard.
Get going.
Why are you making so much kimchi
if we're only doing takeout?
We still need to make kimchi for winter.
What's wrong?
My memories.
Goodness, don't rush it.
You've gotten started,
so you'll remember everything soon.
It's just frustrating.
I…
Damn it.
I definitely remember
that I was stabbed with a knife.
But that means
I must have found some kind of evidence.
And that is…
what I don't remember.
Because of that evidence…
Su-ryong…
Yes. What?
Damn it, this is so frustrating.
-Forget it, okay?
-Darn it.
Do you want help?
How?
First off, your memories
began to come back to you
when you fought Ji Cheong-sin.
Yes.
And you said those memories are in pieces.
I can help you…
bring those back…
into a whole piece.
That's how we pieced together
Mun's memories.
That's how we found Ji Cheong-sin…
from his subconscious memories.
I don't think he has a subconscious mind.
I doubt he has something that serious
in his head.
Ha-na.
Give it a try.
-Okay.
-Good.
Your head might hurt.
I'll do it even if it breaks.
Let's find them.
Hey, wait.
Don't look too carefully.
You know, my private…
What now? Your privacy?
Yes, I have that. A private life.
Hey, Ms. Chu. I got salted shrimp.
That's not the problem.
What are you doing?
This is election interference.
Yeong-nim's killer…
52C4882
SEVEN YEARS AGO
Please let me join you.
I forgot to make a reservation,
so there are no empty seats.
Gosh, look. Everything is getting burnt.
No?
Anyway, why are you eating alone?
Are you an outcast or something?
Gosh.
Wow, this is good.
-Excuse me. One more serving, please.
-Sure.
I'll buy.
Hey, man.
I'm not interested in men. Run along.
Me neither.
Then what are you trying to do right now?
You're in charge
of the Kim Yeong-nim case.
I saw something during my investigation
of Shin Myeong-hwi's election fraud.
There's a connection…
between Mayor Shin…
and Ms. Kim Yeong-nim?
Detective Ga.
My name is So Gwon.
I'm a detective too.
DETECTIVE SO GWON
Another bottle of soju, please.
SHIN MYEONG-HWI
May I help you?
Yes, I'm the police.
Car number 52C4882.
Who drove that car on September 16th?
You keep a car log, right?
We're too busy to do that.
Come on, please spare some time.
Come on.
-Sir, one second.
-Please.
Okay, fine.
Hey, one second.
You know me, don't you. Right?
-Let's go.
-Haven't you seen me?
You're Kim Yeong-nim's friend!
Hey, man.
Kim Yeong-nim's body is there.
This is election interference.
Why are you suddenly so scared, Su-ryong?
Hey, Su-ryong. Don't be a wuss.
They won't give you a warrant
for this anyway!
Hello? Go ahead.
I know who Yeong-nim's killer is.
-I have the evidence.
-I see.
Mo-tak.
Ha-na, this phone number.
Remember the number.
I'm reading it already.
010…
-Four…
-Wait, that number. Write it down.
497…
4536.
Mo-tak.
Can you guarantee my safety?
Of course.
You can rest assured
your identity will be kept secret.
Who is it?
Let's meet, then.
Are you okay?
I'm a little late.
I'm back.
Goodness. Great job.
What is it?
It's Mo-tak. He remembered everything
from seven years ago.
Wait, really?
Yes.
I remember…
your dad too.
He looks a lot like you.
No, I look a lot like him.
Sit down.
I told you it would hurt.
Yes, an informer?
Yes.
I went to see the informer
on the day I got attacked.
This is a number from seven years ago.
Could I find the owner?
Give it to me.
Wait.
Do you…
remember everything?
Marry me.
Yes.
You remember…
everything?
Yes.
Let's meet.
Detective Kim. No.
Jeong-yeong.
We have…
a lot to catch up on.
We do.
The one on the right
They look the same.
I told you
not to read into my private matters.
Let me see.
-I say the left one.
-Oh, really?
If I had known,
I would've given her some noodles.
Bring her over next time.
Yes, this one.
The one on the left is what women like.
This is their first date in seven years.
Noodles aren't good enough.
Use this as much as you want.
Gosh, you smell like an old man.
This isn't good.
-Mo-tak.
-Yes?
You don't have to come home tonight.
Why not? I'm coming home.
-Don't come home.
-Don't come back.
-You aren't coming home?
-I am!
-He's not!
-Why wouldn't I?
-I'm coming home.
-Don't come.
What do you know?
You see, when you're a Counter,
the gap between life and death
doesn't seem so huge,
and that's comforting.
Then what should we do
with these bastards?
Let's do things their way.
"Their way"?
This five billion won…
Let's steal it.
We'll rob them of their campaign funds?
We'll capture Ji Cheong-sin
and help Mun's parents ascend.
We can reopen after that.
Subtitle translation by Eun Sook Youn