BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS BY YLAB
[suspenseful music]
[snarls]
THE FIVE ARMIES' BASE CAMP
IN MUNGYEONG SAEJAE
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[panting]
[clangs]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
- [groans]
- [panting]
[grunting]
[nervous breathing]
[clanking]
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
Something's off, sir.
Very few men.
We should move carefully.
[tense music]
- [screaming]
- [grunting]
- [sword clanging]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[clanks]
[foreboding music]
[trickling]
[door creaks, thuds]
[gasps]
- [rapid footsteps approaching]
- [snarls]
[gasps]
- [crashes]
- [growls]
- [swords clanging]
- [men grunting]
[soldier shouts]
- [flesh squelches]
- [groans]
- [thwacks]
[guns clanking]
[thumping]
- [thumping continues]
- [gasps]
- [drum thumping]
- [panting]
[gasps]
[tense music]
[gasping]
What did you...
Where is His Royal Highness?
He is undeserving of that title.
He is a traitor.
You are the one
that is betraying our nation,
not His Highness!
You are not the judge of that.
His Majesty will decide who is guilty.
It is to the kindness of His Majesty
he has come,
so that he could issue these traitors
punishment in person.
[growls]
Step aside.
Those standing in my way now
will never find forgiveness.
It was only three years ago
that you saved countless lives
in Gyeongsang
from certain destruction.
You are a man of remarkable wisdom
and bravery,
so why have you sided with this traitor?
I understand it is difficult
to desert someone
who was once your disciple.
However, if you acknowledge
your grave mistake...
your life might possibly be spared.
- [groans]
- [growls]
- [grunting]
- [snarling]
[growls]
[Lee Chang] Father! Father!
[snarls, growls]
- [growls]
- [panting]
[snarling]
[approaching footsteps]
[gasps]
[King] Everyone I have ever loved has died
or was denied their birthright.
You are my only son...
the importance of your life
affects me greatly.
No matter what happens, you must survive.
Your survival proves
that you're different from them...
and that you are different from me.
Prove it to them.
Show them what a true king ought to be.
I'm here, Father.
It's me, your son, Chang.
[growls]
[sighs]
I'm ending this madness.
I have lived in hell
for the last three years because of you.
You won't deceive me this time around,
not like you did then.
His Majesty...
His Majesty is dead!
Blinded by his endless lust for power,
Cho Hak-ju resurrected the King.
He has transformed him into a monster
that hungers for flesh.
Since His Majesty is no longer with us,
the throne should...
then be passed on the line...
in accordance with the law.
[foreboding music]
Why do you hesitate?
Shoot him.
[clanking]
- [sword clangs]
- [groans]
[body thuds]
You will shoot him, or you will be next.
[gasps]
[gunshot]
[groans]
[gasps]
[groaning]
Shoot him down!
[gunshots]
[gunshots continue]
[dramatic music]
- [grunts]
- [clanks]
[grunting]
[foreboding music]
[squelches]
[thuds]
[gasping]
[pants]
[sighs]
[groaning]
I...
I beheaded...
I beheaded my father. He's dead.
Your Highness.
[heavy breathing]
None of this is your fault.
[groaning]
Listen to me.
You are now...
you are the rightful king.
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
Not the King!
The Five Armies...
shall arrest the traitor
and all his allies...
who beheaded his majesty!
[suspenseful music]
HANYANG
ROYAL COMMANDERY DIVISION
Good sir...
do you intend to search the Queen's
private residence?
There are trails of blood
from the creek surrounded
where that dead woman was found.
That trail leads all the way back
to Naeseonjae.
I am nearly certain that
she made her escape from this area.
She claimed that there were more women
held captive here.
- Investigation is imperative.
- I see.
The Haewon Cho Clan
must be connected to this.
Would you speak truth to such power?
[sighs]
I have given much thought
to the consequences.
But Haewon Cho Clan's power
is without equal in this country.
However, if this crime took place here,
we will investigate
in the name of our people.
We must learn what happened.
My Lady, the Royal Commandery Division
are investigating Naeseonjae.
NAESEONJAE
We must hurry.
[crows cawing]
[snarling]
[man 1 chuckles]
- [man 1 gasps]
- [retches]
- Come on, what are you doing?
- [coughing]
- Go on, get off!
- [groans]
[man 1] Why are you puking everywhere?
You drunk!
- I can't believe you threw up...
- [man 2] I'm dying.
...that expensive wine!
- Hyah!
- [horse neighs]
[head court lady] Officer, for what reason
must you visit this late in the evening?
We received a report of a murder
at this location.
We are conducting a search,
and you will cooperate.
- Everyone, scatter and search!
- [soldiers] Yes, sir!
Officer, this is a private residence
of Her Majesty.
It is unlikely that anyone here
will behave
in an unbecoming manner to her reputation.
The incident you are describing
could not have happened here.
[soldier 1] Search the quarters!
Who lives in that house?
Normally, it is where
we would accommodate guests.
For now, it's empty.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[gasps]
[solider 2] Sir, there's something
you need to see over here!
[gasps]
Over here, sir.
Winter has frozen most of the soil,
but this spot here is soft.
[soldier 2] It looks like someone
buried something.
Hyah!
[panting]
[horses galloping]
[gasping]
This way. Come on, let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
That troop over there.
Don't let them get away!
[men shouting]
[shouting indistinctly]
- [soldier 3] Over here!
- [men shouting]
[ominous music]
How mortifying.
They were all found at Naeseonjae?
[commander] Yes, sir.
We found the corpses
of seven pregnant women and infants.
The women we found were stabbed,
but something was odd about the children.
All the female infants
were strangled to death,
but it doesn't seem like
anything was done to the boy.
I believe that one
must have been stillborn.
But how...
How could this happen?
Something very strange is going on.
Why would you think
that the girls were murdered...
and that only the boy remains untouched?
Good sir, what are you trying to say?
Whoever it is that took the lives
that once belonged to this bodies...
they were looking for a son
among these women.
[sighs]
[horn blares]
[gasps]
[scoffs]
Uh, isn't that the horn?
The one that tells us
that the king has passed away.
[foreboding music]
[horn blaring]
Tell me, what on earth happened?
This is a letter that was sent
from The Chief State Councilor.
He's in Joryeong.
[Cho Hak-ju] The plague in Gyeongsang
is out of control
and Crown Prince Chang
has committed high treason.
Despite battling illness,
His Majesty came all the way to Joryeong.
We were victorious
in containing the plague,
in Mungyeong Saejae,
but Chang and his aides
took advantage of the chaos
to seize the throne.
It was then that Chang decapitated
His Majesty
with his own hands.
- Your Majesty!
- [sobbing]
Return to us!
[sobbing]
[foreboding music]
[thumping]
[guard 1] What should be done
with the Lord's corpse?
To his side, he was a traitor,
he was still a hero to all of us.
You should dress him in shrouds
and laid to rest.
Sir.
Taxation and rites...
HANYANG CONFERENCE HALL
you will handle the state funeral.
The Chief Magistrate
of the Capital District Office
should secure and repair
any damage to bridges and pathways
along the burial route.
Are there not more pressing matters
to attend to?
Our throne is currently vacant.
Finding an heir quickly
should be our first priority.
Well, at the moment, we do have the Queen
standing in as our regent.
She should give birth
to a potential heir any day now.
That child has every chance
of being a boy,
which would then mean
he would inherit the throne.
And what if it's not a boy?
We must search the collateral bloodlines
to be prepared.
There are children of Prince Noseong,
I believe he was executed in Ganghwa.
Those children are hardly related to him.
Why must we go that far down the line?
Or do you just want to put a puppet
on the throne?
The Second State Councilor is right.
We must take great care to follow the rule
of primogeniture.
We will table this discussion
until the birth of the child.
[guard 2] Honorable gentlemen,
this is the head eunuch.
I've received a message
from the Office of Royal Delivery.
Her Majesty has begun labor.
The Queens's baby should arrive
immediately.
Certainly, that is well-timed.
Huh, some good news makes for nice change.
[councilor 1] I suppose
all we can do for now
is wait to see if her Majesty
gives us a prince.
- [councilor 2] Certainly.
- [councilor 3] True.
DELIVERY ROOM AT THE QUEEN'S PALACE
This is the Queen's room.
Her Majesty has been waiting for you
and the nurse.
Let us proceed.
Your Majesty, this is the head court lady.
[head court lady]
The royal physician is here for you.
What did you do
with the rest of the girls?
[head court lady] They were taken care of
as per your Majesty's orders.
[foreboding music]
You want me to keep pushing
the Naeseonjae investigation?
That is correct.
But you must do so in complete secrecy.
Understood, sir.
We do not have much time.
We must find out the truth
before the Queen births that child.
THE BASE CAMP IN MUNGYEONG SAEJAE
State your business.
The magistrate told me to stop by,
and to perform a wellness check
on the prince.
This order came directly
from the magistrate?
Yes.
CHO BEOM-PAL
[door opens]
Highness.
How have you been feeling?
Hanyang is far,
and the journey won't be easy.
I'll treat your wound first
so you can keep it from getting infected.
[gasps]
[tense music]
[rebel 1] There's no way they didn't know
we were coming.
We were set up. Someone told them.
That must mean...
there is a spy among us.
We shouldn't be talking
to each other right now.
What does that mean?
I'm not going to die in this prison. No.
My purpose won't be complete
until I avenge my family.
They will pay for Lord Ahn Hyeon's death.
Will you help me?
I swear I would do everything
in my power...
to make them pay for it.
But is there any way for us to do that?
Our lives are already forfeit...
might as well take Cho Hak-ju
down with us.
Just before we leave for Hanyang...
that is our only opportunity.
[sighs sharply]
What's the matter?
Is there something I should know?
Work is completed.
We're ready to leave, sir.
I see. Gather the traitors.
[door creaks]
[door opens]
[guard 2] On your feet!
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[pants]
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[tense music]
[men grunting]
They are begging to be killed.
Spare the Crown Prince's life.
You can do what you will with the rest.
[sword rasping]
Cover me!
[gun cocks]
[tense music]
[gunshot]
[gunshot echoes]
[both gasp]
[gagging]
[body thuds]
Someone arrest that man at once!
[grunts]
[clanks]
[foreboding music]
[both gasp]
- [soldier 4 whimpering]
- [soldier 5 screaming]
- [growling]
- [soldiers screaming]
He's coming! He's coming!
[snarling]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
[growls]
[gunshots]
[ominous music]
[whimpering]
[suspenseful music]
[snarling]
Shoot him in the head.
Put an arrow in his head!
[thwacking]
[snarls]
[gunshots]
[groans]
Your Highness, listen to me...
there is only one way to survive.
When I leave you,
take my body and turn me...
into a monster.
I need you to do this.
It's the only way to reveal the truth.
[snarls]
[soldiers shouting]
- [flesh squelches]
- [groaning]
[gasping]
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi