Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪How to separate♪
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 12
Outpatient
Cong Rong.
Shaoqing.
Mom.
You’re off work?
Aunt.
You both work so hard.
I’ve bought you
two film tickets.
Go watch the film later.
Get some relaxation.
Mom.
We’re in the 21st century now.
Do you really believe that
we’ll hold on to each other
when we’re scared
like the heroes and heroines
in Korean dramas?
As long as the movie is great.
Right?
Have fun.
Enjoy yourselves.
I’ll leave now.
Bye.
Are we going or not?
Are we?
Let’s go.
Aunt has left.
Should we still watch this?
Let me take you to a place.
Come.
Hurry up.
No.
I can’t run any farther.
Why do you take me here?
Don’t you think this is like
when we were kids?
At that time, you ran ahead of me.
And I always followed you.
When I couldn’t run any farther,
you would lend me a hand.
Now it’s my turn.
So,
is this our first date?
Or course, it is.
It’s our first date
as a fake couple.
Why don’t we become a real couple?
You still need time to think about it?
What’s most important for me right now
is my report to the law firm.
Can we wait till I pass it…?
Considering your capability,
it must be easy for you to pass.
The competition at the law firm
is so fierce.
It’s not as easy as you think.
Let’s make a bet.
If you pass it,
you’ll be my girlfriend.
What if I fail?
I’ll admit my defeat.
I’m the stake then.
I’ll be your boyfriend.
You...
win either way.
If you have no objections,
I’ll take that as a yes.
I’m home.
You’re home.
It’s quite late.
Are you tired?
I still have to work.
Mom.
Go to bed early.
I have to hurry and prepare my PPT.
It’s so late now.
You should rest.
Let’s talk.
Let’s chitchat.
Mom.
You’re as beautiful as
an eighteen-year-old girl.
But chitchatting late at night
still makes you age faster.
My daughter is in a relationship.
How could I not know the details?
I’ve prepared my seat and snacks.
I’m waiting for your story.
I’ve been reporting to you all day.
Can’t I keep the details to myself?
How’s your progress?
Have you held hands?
Have you kissed?
It’s not that fast.
Aren’t you in hurry?
When do you plan to
make that your priority?
When I think about
how you’re so old and have never had
a romantic relationship,
I’m so worried that I can’t sleep.
Mom.
Don’t worry.
Just let nature take its course.
How can you let nature take its course?
Back then,
I started to date your dad in college.
We got married the moment we graduated.
We just couldn’t be apart.
We stayed with each other
until the dorm curfew…
What happened?
Why isn’t it responding?
You go ahead with your work.
I’ll enjoy my beauty sleep.
Mom. Wait a minute.
What happened to my laptop?
That day I saw the news
about your heroic deed.
I got so angry.
And I slammed the laptop close.
The computer screen went black.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
What should I do now?
Shaoqing has a laptop.
You can use his.
Go. Hurry up. Go.
Go.
Don’t come home too early.
Take your time.
Don’t rush.
Go to bed early.
I’ll wait for you.
Can you stop staring at me?
Don’t get me wrong.
I’m here to borrow your computer.
Are you really here only to
borrow my computer?
Are you lending me or not?
Come in, please.
non-urgent
in 48 hours
What are you doing?
I’m afraid that I’ll distract you
if I sit there.
It’s more distracting if you’re here.
You’d better sit there.
Why should I do as you say?
Zhong Zhen poked you
There’s something wrong with your QQ.
You’d better take a look.
Zhong Zhen
It jumped out by itself.
This...
It seems that
you’re keenly following my update.
No…
Is Zhong Zhen giving you
his daily report?
No, he’s not.
I have no idea why he sent these.
Really?
You’re quite a distraction here.
You’d better go away.
Move. Go.
Go away. Go. Go.
Zhong Zhen.
Zhong Zhen!
Why did you send these?
Why should you tell me
what your boss wore
and what he did?
Cousin
I’m sorry.
I sent these to the wrong person.
I was supposed to send these
to boss’s fan group.
They ask me to do daily update.
And I should send photos as well.
You’d better keep yourself
out of my sight for a while.
One Palace Home
I forgot to buy yogurt.
Aunt, don’t go.
There’s yogurt in the fridge.
Great.
Thank you.
Aunt?
Watch out.
Be careful with your fingers.
What’s going on?
What are you standing there for?
Go brush your teeth and wash your face.
It’s time for breakfast.
Go sit there.
Shaoqing has already put
your chopsticks and bowl there.
If I’m not mistaken,
this is our first breakfast together
after we said
we would have breakfast together.
When did we say
we would have breakfast together?
Have you forgotten?
That time you stayed at my place.
You lived together?
It’s not what you think.
Nonsense.
What is it then?
Cong Rong doesn’t want me to say it.
It’s really nothing.
Mom.
There seems to be more stories.
Why did you bring this up?
It’s just a causal talk.
Then why didn’t you make it clear?
Because you didn’t let me
finish the speech.
You did it on purpose.
Rangyirang.
Sit.
Come here.
Don’t be rude.
Fine.
You can have it.
You’re just like your master.
You act so shamelessly.
It depends on who we’re with.
Rangyirang is not interested in
whom I don’t like.
Cong Rong, Shaoqing, look over here.
Mom.
What are you doing?
I finally have a photo
that I can send to my relatives’ group
and boast.
My son-in-law is so handsome.
They’ll be so jealous.
Mr. Shangguan.
I’m here to submit the evaluation form.
Lucy is in the office.
What else?
My internship will be over soon.
My dad wants to invite you and Mr. Tan
to dinner after the report.
You shouldn’t have.
Everyone is busy.
You don’t have to make time for me.
Thank you for your kindness.
No.
Thanks to your help,
I was able to pass the exams.
And you helped me a lot
during my internship.
This invitation didn’t
only come from my father.
I want to express my gratitude
to you too.
I was just doing my job.
Besides, Lucy did most of the work
about your internship.
You should thank her instead of me.
Of course.
I must invite Lucy as well.
If you accept the invitation,
I’ll invite her immediately.
Excuse me.
Can you tell me the way
to Zejiang Tower?
There’s a China Merchants Bank.
Zejiang Tower is right behind it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Since I returned,
I haven’t taken you to dinner.
How about this?
Tomorrow, I’ll take you to dinner.
I’ll invite Lucy, you and the interns
to dinner together.
Okay. Great.
Cong Rong.
Good morning, Mr. Shangguan.
Get off work earlier tomorrow.
I’ll invite Lucy, you
and the other interns
to dinner.
Just pick a causal place.
But...
In this case, we won’t take up
the precious time
of your dad’s and Mr. Tan’s.
And the atmosphere can be more casual.
Okay, Mr. Shangguan.
Find a nice restaurant.
All right.
Let’s call it a day.
You’re dismissed.
Okay.
Zhong Zhen, stay for a while.
Give me your phone.
Why have you been taking photos
of me stealthily?
My cousin asked me to.
Don’t use her as an excuse.
Do you want to transcribe books again?
Give me a few seconds.
Let me think which book is the thickest.
I sent these photos to your fan group
in exchange of figures.
Lots of figures.
Why did you send them to your cousin?
I sent them by mistake.
You saw them?
Gosh.
No wonder she was so angry.
Gosh. I’m screwed.
She’ll get back at me for sure.
Wait a second.
Why were you staying together
when it was so late?
Do you have any objection?
No. No.
How dare I object?
But, boss...
Do you really like my cousin?
Although I quite like you,
if my cousin doesn’t,
you can’t win her over even if you
follow her everywhere 25 hours a day.
I can’t...?
But rest assured.
With me on your side,
I can make sure you get together,
as long as you show me your sincerity.
What sincerity?
For example,
letting my dissertation pass.
Or, if the student makes a mistake,
boss has to transcribe 50 copies first.
Fine.
But you’d better not forget
what you said just now.
I’ll look into her tonight’s schedule
for you immediately.
Burang Barbeque
Rong.
You’re so incredible!
Save your drama.
Seven people can’t contribute
too much to your sales revenue.
Why are you so exited?
Having customers means that
the business is staying afloat.
I need a helping hand.
Wen Shaoqing and you are my Cupid.
What did you just say?
No.
Wen Shaoqing and you are
my God of Wealth.
Welcome.
Mom?
Why are you here?
You don’t come home.
And I’m also not allowed to visit you?
Find a place to sit first.
I’ll get you a cup of water.
Rang!
You live in such a place?
You must have been through so many
hardships living on your own.
That’s not true.
I feel so at ease living on my own.
I just saw that your place
is filled with takeout boxes.
You can’t always eat takeout.
Takeout is not nutritious.
It’s fine.
I don’t have high standards
for food anyway.
My heart broke
when I saw you live like this.
You’re willing to
leave your family behind
just because you threw a tantrum
with your dad?
Do you really have to give yourself
a hard time?
No, not at all.
I’m fine.
The space is a bit cramped.
But I’m a free spirit here.
No one is nagging around me.
My hair is growing faster now.
You...
You’re so garrulous.
How’s dad’s health?
Ever since you left,
your dad has never mentioned you.
But every time he has a chance,
he will try to inquire about
you stealthily.
If his intentions are exposed,
he pretends he doesn’t care about you.
You’re so alike.
Rang.
Your bet will be over soon.
Come home with me.
No.
I can’t admit defeat
until the last moment.
I had been standing outside the store
for over ten minutes.
And I saw no guest coming in.
How could you win the bet?
I have customers.
Where are they?
Where?
I can stay here for another ten minutes.
If no customer comes,
you have to go home with me.
You can’t sleep well or eat well here.
Sir.
I want to buy books.
She wants to buy books.
Mom, I have a customer.
I have to greet my customer now.
Which books do you want?
I’ve finished The Wealth of Nations
you recommended to me last time.
It’s an amazing book.
Adam Thmith...
Adam Smith.
Economics books are over here.
Right.
My memory is so bad.
His book talks about systematic
economics in such a way that
a layman like me is able to understand.
So I’m very interested in economics now.
Can you recommend
a few more books to me?
This one is good for you.
It talks about the development
of American capital market.
The Great Game
It’s quite fun to read.
And the book Story I recommended to you
was too professional.
The Story of Art talks about
the history of art.
It’s on the professional side.
But it’s rather enjoyable.
It explains different eras
of art history
in a way that’s profound
but also easy-to-understand.
It’s worth reading.
Why don’t you read
a piece of literature too?
This.
Walden is a nice book.
These three books
will take quite a while.
Do you have any question?
No.
Thank you.
Rang.
I’ll go back since you have a customer.
Are you in a hurry?
Mom.
I’ll leave now.
Fine. Let me walk you out.
Aunt, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Rang Kai Bookstore
I’ll leave now.
Mom.
It’s raining.
Let me call a taxi for you.
No.
There’s no need for that.
The rain is light.
Walking in this rain is soothing.
Don’t bury yourself in this small place.
Come home now and then,
even if it’s just for dinner.
You’re father and son after all.
The bitterness will go away soon.
I see. I see.
It’s been seven years since you ended
your relationship with Jiang, right?
Why are you suddenly talking about this?
You can’t always live in the past,
right?
If there’s a nice girl around you,
you must grab the chance.
What do you think of that girl?
Stop kidding.
That girl.
She has long legs.
Are you drawing lots?
You’re always so naughty.
You
should learn from Shaoqing.
I’ll go now.
Come home sometime.
Mom, be careful on your way home.
Rang Kai Bookstore
Thank you.
You really helped me out.
I totally freaked out.
I thought I was going to goof.
That Adam Smith.
I thought it was a film actor’s name.
Why haven’t you left?
I almost forgot!
Shouldn’t you…
reciprocate my kindness?
What do you mean?
I helped you.
You should help me too.
Table No. 3.
Thank you for coming to my restaurant.
Just tell me if you need anything.
I hope you can enjoy your meal here.
Have fun.
Sure. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
So, that’s the Mr. Shangguan
you always talk about?
He’s nice.
He’s very stylish.
What?
Are you interested in him?
Chicken wings for table No. 3.
Your new chef is quite nice too.
He’s not bad.
Just average.
Go. Go.
Stop talking about me.
That’s how my boyfriend
successfully pursued me.
Cong Rong.
How about you?
Are you in a relationship?
Right.
Last time, we saw you
hugging with a handsome guy.
No.
That’s… That’s a misunderstanding.
Don’t try to shift the subject.
Tell us more about
your story.
I...
She doesn’t want to tell more.
Let her be.
Why don’t we
talk about Mr. Shangguan’s girlfriend?
You all know
Mr. Shangguan’s girlfriend.
And you’re all familiar with her.
Who?
Who is she?
His work.
Lucy.
You’re so humorous.
I’m finally here.
Cong Rong.
The restaurant you booked
is so hard to find.
You’re all waiting for me.
I’m really sorry.
Let me order for you.
Waiter.
Jingjing.
We’ve already ordered.
You can take what you want over there.
This is a buffet.
Grab what you want
over there.
Okay.
You look very relaxed.
Have you fixed your family problem?
Yes, I have.
Thank you, Mr. Shangguan.
My mom is very stubborn.
But she still wants what’s best for me.
So she gave up very soon.
That’s great.
Then I’ll be looking forward to
your report tomorrow.
I’ve witnessed your journey these years.
Tomorrow is the final step.
I really wish to see
your dream comes true.
Sure.
I won’t let you down.
You can do it.
Thank you.
If you have any question,
don’t hesitate to ask me.
Sure.
Try this. This is good.
Thank you.
Coming.
No scallions.
No vermicelli.
Less garlic.
If the taste is bad,
I’ll give you a one-star review.
Do you want some lemon juice
so you can eat it raw in the sour way?
You’re sour!
Yes.
These are the two sides...
So she is the spoilt Lady Jingjing
that Cong Rong talks about.
Hurry up.
I’m fast enough.
I’ve heard about
your recent performance.
And we’ve witnessed
your amazing success.
Tomorrow is the final test.
No matter what the outcome is,
I hope I can work with you
in this profession in the future.
And I want to cheer for you too.
Have an amazing performance.
Thank you.
Thank you, teachers.
I’ll do my best.
Maybe you think studying law,
passing National Judicial Examination,
and finishing the internship
are exhausting enough.
What I want to tell you is that
this is just the beginning.
Every case in the future
will be as tough as hell.
You need to give your best effort
to every one of them.
You need to fight to defend justice.
The biggest challenge for a lawyer
is not the overtime,
or losing the case.
It’s the choice you make
when you’re confused
or faced with temptation.
Can you still be on the justice’s side?
I hope you can
still remember the aspiration
you have at this moment
no matter how far you go in the future.
Remain true to
your original aspirations.
Move forward bravely.
Mr. Shangguan is right.
We’ll do our best.
Come.
Cheers.
You can do it.
We can do it.
Enjoy the food.
Sure.
Mr. Shangguan.
This one is for you.
Thank you.
People all say that
there are many temptations for lawyers.
Many people left this profession
because of some incidents.
Mr. Shangguan,
have you ever faced
this kind of things?
Of course.
How did you deal with them?
I figured them out myself.
Your dad is also a lawyer.
You can ask him.
What is this?
Pig nose tendon.
Don’t tell me
you’ve never tried this before.
Is this edible?
It’s quite nice.
I’ll have one more.
Give me pepper powder.
Cumin
Pepper Powder
What’s wrong with you today?
Are you blind?
I gave you the wrong one?
Why are you always staring at me?
I’m just curious.
About what?
You seem to know a lot.
Where did you learn these?
You said you were once a cook.
Why did you become a cook?
My college friend asked me to.
What about playing instrument?
You learned during college as well?
Yes.
What did you learn the instrument for?
To pursue a girl?
The girl your mom talked about
last time?
Is there a story?
Can you tell me?
Deliver these now.
Why do you have so many questions?
Barbecue man.
Give me what I often order.
Why don’t you help me when you’re here?
Although I’m here to
pick up my girlfriend-to-be from work,
I can help you
before I pick her up.
Girlfriend?
Look how happy he is.
Wash your hands and do the dishes.
Wu Dazhuang
asked the presiding judge directly.
“Tell me which item and which chapter
of the Criminal Law this is?”
The presiding judge had to say,
“Attention, public prosecutor.
We’re in the middle of a court,
not the middle of a lecture.
Besides, Mr. Wu,
I’ve graduated.”
So,
when you’ve stayed in this profession
long enough,
every face will be familiar.
Thank you.
It’s fine.
Here.
Your boyfriend is here.
I’m here to pick you up.
What is it?
I’m here to remind you that
you shouldn’t be so greedy.
You might choke.
What do you mean?
I’m asking you to stay away
from my Mr. Shangguan.
You’re so boring.
Don’t go.
I haven’t finished yet.
Kitchen area is restricted.
Please do not enter.
I’m sorry.
Ask her to come out.
I haven’t finished
my conversation with her.
You’re going to ask her to
stay away from
your Mr. Shangguan.
Am I right?
It’s none of your business.
It was none of my business at first.
But you’re being so catty
in my restaurant.
That’s your fault.
Should I help you
out of kindness?
Let me confess your love for you?
How dare you!
Stay out of my business.
I’ve said that we shouldn’t come
to a restaurant like this.
Indeed...
What… What are you doing?
My stomach...
My stomach hurts too.
Tang Shuo.
Xu Rou.
Are you all right?
Hurry up.
Take care of her.
Are you all right?
Is the food unsanitary?
Tang Shuo.
Why are you having a stomachache?
What did you eat?
Are you all right?
Dr. Wen!
What happened?
I don’t know.
It hurts so much.
Hang in there.
What happened?
Hang in there. Hang in there.
Can you still move?
Can you?
Hang in there.
It hurts so badly.
What’s going on?
Send them to the hospital right now.
I’ll drive.
Send them to the hospital.
Lucy.
Can you still move?
Emergency
Liu Ying
Food poisoning caused
by bacterial infection.
Food poisoning
caused by bacterial infection
Hello.
I’m here to pay the fees.
870 yuan in total.
The report has come out.
It’s food poisoning
caused by bacterial infection.
The symptoms are mild.
So the problem is not very serious.
Taking medications as prescribed
will lessen the symptoms.
Xiong Jingjing.
Your symptoms are more severe.
You need to be put on a drip
for three days.
Come to the hospital on time.
For three days?
What about my report tomorrow?
I haven’t finished my PPT.
I said a small restaurant
like yours is not safe.
You really screwed me up.
Cong Rong,
did you do this on purpose?
I’m really sorry.
This is my fault.
I’ll take full responsibility for this.
And I’ll give you
a satisfactory solution.
No.
I’m the owner of the restaurant.
I should be the one accountable to you.
I’ll compensate for your losses.
I’ll try my best to make you satisfied.
Satisfied?
How could we be satisfied?
For us, tomorrow
is even more important
than the day of College Entrance Exam.
What can you possibly offer
to compensate for our losses?
Okay.
Nobody wanted this to happen.
This is an accident.
There’s no need to blame anyone.
The report will be deferred
till you recover.
I’ll notify you later.
But, Mr. Tan...
I’ll talk to Mr. Tan.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
I’m really sorry.
Since it’s not severe,
you can go home and take some rest.
Xiong Jingjing.
Your condition is severer.
Come back to work when you’ve recovered.
Let’s go.
Take Chengcheng home first.
Okay.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take care of her.
Rong.
I’ll wait for you outside.
Call me if you need me.
Give me your files.
What files?
Your internship files.
Beverages
Mr. Shangguan.
Thanks.
Thank you for your help tonight.
Never mind.
That’s my duty.
Dr. Wen, do you have something else
you want to say?
Cong Rong performed very well
during her stay at the hospital.
Many of my colleagues
think highly of her.
Mr. Shangguan, I really hope
you won’t let the incident affect
your evaluation of her.
Don’t worry.
I won’t.
You must be tired.
Get in the car.
Do you know where I’m going?
I know.
I’ll take you to the place
you want to go.
I’ll take care of it. Don’t touch.
What are you doing?
It doesn’t hurt for me.
Why do you look like you’re in pain?
How could this not hurt?
You’re not a vegetable.
I can’t succeed in anything in life.
I’d rather be a vegetable.
Nonsense!
Spit it out.
Stand up.
Sit down.
Let me get you some bandages.
I told the truth.
I opened a steak house.
The food was so horrible
that people all hated it.
And my dad paid to
keep my restaurant going.
I tried so hard to prove
that I’m not a loser.
But the only thing I’ve proved
is that I am a loser.
I’ve ruined my restaurant.
What’s worse, I implicated my bestie.
My life is a complete failure.
Do I still have any hope?
People tend to
think too much when they’re sad.
When they think too much,
they only see things
in a negative light.
If they do so,
they’ll get even more upset.
That’s an infinite loop.
How about this?
Get some sleep now.
I’ll take care of this.
When you wake up,
the world will be beautiful again.
No.
I’m so depressed now.
How can I possibly fall asleep?
You can’t fall asleep here, of course.
You should go back to your room.
Lie in your fluffy bed.
Close your eyes.
Listen to some music.
And you may
later...
Wen Rang.
I’m so sad.
I know.
You can have the bed for tonight.
When you’re tired,
I can be your massage machine
and mopping robot.
Nephew.
Your uncle’s waist and back hurt too.
My muscles are sore.
Give me a massage too.
You sound so full of life.
You seem to be just fine.
Discrimination
hurts people the most.
What else do you expect?
My nephew’s future wife,
won’t you discipline him?
He doesn’t respect the old
or care for the young.
You sound so full of life.
You guys… You guys are so good to me.
Rong.
I’m so sorry.
I’m so afraid that I may drag you down.
I’ve been guilty all night.
She went to bed the moment she got back.
She’s been guilty all night?
She’s been guilty in her dreams.
Right.
Can’t I?
All right.
Don’t worry about me.
Think about what to do
with your restaurant.
What can I do?
I’ve given up.
Just let it be.
No matter what the outcome is,
I can handle it now
with my tough spirit.
It’s the same with you.
Don’t worry too much.
When the sky falls,
our life goes on as usual.
So, you’ve revived so easily?
I’ve never been defeated.
Who said she wanted to be a vegetable?
I’ve come back to life.
Fine. Fine.
I’d love to see
how cheerful you’re tomorrow.
Can you please not try
to undermine my confidence?
You sound so full of life.
You seem to be all right.
You all right?
Did I really hurt you?
No. No. No.
Don’t come any closer.
I’m sorry.
Keep your distance.
My foot.
Does it hurt?
Don’t come any closer.
Tinderbox.
I want to drink freshly-ground coffee.
Burang Barbeque
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪