Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪How to separate♪
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 11
Do you have anything else to say?
Well, if you dare
blab it in the hospital,
you’re a dead man.
It depends on how you act,
and what you use to seal my lips.
Tape or needle?
Just pick one.
You’re back.
You come back together.
We met on the way home.
An important day that I met Chubby
What happened
is really different
from what I imagined.
It’s one step away.
Climb up and we’ll win!
Haven’t we finished yet?
Just give up.
How long will it take?
With the “Little Spinning Top”
following you,
you can’t win.
Don’t look down upon us.
We’re a team.
Chubby.
Give me a hand.
Alias: Chubby
Sure enough,
fatties have great potential.
It’s like an idol drama,
and it actually happens to you.
Alias: Wen Shaoqing
Alias: Febuxostat
Febuxostat.
What are you thinking about?
Mom.
Though you’re a cutie,
your sudden appearance
still frightens me.
I didn’t mean to frighten you.
You just didn’t hear me.
I saw a note in the bathroom,
saying “important day”.
Why is today an important day?
Did you go out with Shaoqing?
No.
I met a childhood friend.
A childhood friend?
Do you have any childhood friend
in the city?
What does he look like?
Is he as handsome as Shaoqing?
Mom.
You almost become the leader
of Wen Shaoqing’s fan group.
Should I organize a fan club for you?
What is a fan group?
Don’t change the subject.
Tell me,
who is the childhood friend?
It was just a gathering of old friends.
Stop gossiping.
Mom.
Staying up late will make you get old.
If you don’t sleep now,
the mesotherapy you got is in vain.
Really?
Yeah.
Then I’ll get to sleep.
You should sleep early, too.
Good night.
Febuxostat: Good night. Sweet dreams.
Good night
What?
Don’t frown upon it.
Just don’t eat the burnt edge.
After all, I got up early
and took much trouble
to make you breakfast.
Mom.
I’m sorry.
I’m busy and have no time
to accompany you.
I can’t afford to hire you
a 24-hour housekeeper.
You have to cook by yourself.
I’m an unfilial daughter.
Considering that Jiang takes
good care of you at home,
and he is so careful and considerate,
I’m not as good as him.
I feel ashamed.
I know what you want.
You want to know when I go home.
I’m blaming myself.
All right.
I won’t bother you anymore.
I’m going home today.
Really?
I’ve already bought the ticket.
It’s absolutely true.
Since you live a comfortable life
and you’ve got a sweet guy
to take good care of you,
I’m relieved.
I’m going back to enjoy my life.
Mom.
I love you so much!
That’s enough.
Eat that burnt egg.
Have you made your decision?
It’s only been a day.
A day?
I feel like it’s been a year.
Talk to the hand.
Have you put on makeup today?
You look pretty.
Can you give me that?
I’ll trade this for that.
This?
You want it?
Come to my apartment for dinner
and I’ll give it to you.
The ultimate secret of barbecue
Rang Kai Bookstore Burang Barbecue
He can cook, play guitar,
sing and write poems.
He grew up eating rice just as I did.
How come he turns out to be so amazing?
He’s posted nothing on his Moments.
How mysterious he is!
A Castle in the Clouds
Eureka!
Boss,
are you okay?
The first snow softened
the light of the night,
shadowing my yearning.
Do you understand it?
No, I don’t.
From the peak comes the whistling
of the wind in the pines,
which broke the silence in my chest.
Chest? Silence?
What do you want early in the morning?
I’m keen to learn.
I just read your book,
but I don’t understand some parts of it.
Could you please explain it to me?
Your poems are caviar to the general.
They’re too esoteric,
too difficult to understand.
Take this sentence for example.
From the peak...
The book is not suitable for you
if you don’t understand it.
Pick another one.
Which one?
There’re lots of books in my store.
Just pick one.
What else can I do for you?
Where are you going?
Go to rock climbing.
Rock climbing?
I’m a master.
I’m going, too.
It’s so hard.
Why is there such difficult sport
in the world?
Climbing so high,
would I get killed if I slipped?
No way.
I choose to commit suicide.
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Speed up!
He is actually good at rock climbing.
Everyone gets only 24 hours a day.
He does more things in 24 hours
than I do in 48 hours.
I admire him.
Good! Come on!
Good!
Great!
Let me help you.
Shenzhen Yun Ji Hospital
Tired of reading the files?
Why do all of you
like to crop up?
What?
When the eyeball is compressed
or pulled by eye muscle,
mechanical stimulation
can cause excessive excitation
of the vagus nerve,
further leading to slow heart rate.
This is called oculocardiac reflex.
My heart rate isn’t slow.
Tachycardia is also a result
of stimulation.
Shall I find you a good doctor?
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
I come to get some water.
You two continue.
I’m back to work.
Don’t forget to have dinner with me.
Rong.
I venture to ask.
What’s your relationship with my boss?
I have no relationship with him.
Does that mean you’re together?
No.
Then you two are flirting
with each other.
Do you like my boss?
Though he likes someone else,
we can gain advantage
by striking first.
The situation is a bit complicated.
Although we’ve known each other
for a long time,
we’ve only just...
Why do you care so much?
Of course I care about
your lifelong happiness.
If you like my boss,
I’ll watch him
from all angles with secrecy,
helping you capture him.
I’ve been weighing it again and again.
I think he really likes you.
But if I find out
he does anything wrong to you,
I’ll throw caution to the wind.
Benefits like my boss should always
be kept for our own.
I’ve picked you a couple name.
It’s Shallot Couple.
What do you think?
I think Garlic Couple is better.
Garlic is more expensive than shallot.
Don’t be flip!
Go back to work.
Shallot Couple.
Actually, I can do some housework.
I have no problem
changing the quilt cover,
right?
Internship Labor Contract?
Cong Rong.
Daren Law Firm.
Cong Rong
Shangguan Yi.
Medical finance.
An emerging industry.
Yun Ji Hospital Finance
I work at the General Reception Office.
Newborn calves are not afraid of tigers.
Brave intern of our hospital
beards the lion in his den.
What’s this?
Warm-hearted beautiful couple
brought a patient back to life.
Yes, Auntie Chen.
I remember.
No problem.
If you have any legal problems,
feel free to consult me.
Don’t hesitate to come to the hospital
if you don’t feel well.
Goodbye.
Cong,
you get better and better
in doing your job.
Yeah.
But it’s a pity
that I’m about to leave.
Yes, indeed.
How time flies!
Honestly,
I’m really not willing to let you go.
Oh, well,
your professional work
is widely recognized in the hospital.
All the doctors
highly evaluated your performance.
Internship Evaluation
Congratulations.
Thanks to everyone
for actively cooperating with my work.
I’ve already communicated
with your leader.
I hope you’ll become
a regular worker smoothly.
Realize your dream soon.
Thank you, Director Yan.
I’ll try my best.
Internship Evaluation
Director Yan.
Qin Chu
Yes?
Didn’t Dr. Qin write the evaluation?
She is on annual leave.
She hasn’t had a good rest for years.
She’s had a real hard time.
Mom
Mom.
Is it time now?
Wait for me.
I’ll be…
Enough!
Do you think you’re independent enough?
How dare you be a lawyer
behind my back?
Mom.
You must listen to me.
Stop explaining.
I’m in front of your law firm now.
I’ll hand in your resignation.
Mom.
What’s the point to do this?
I’m not a schoolchild anymore.
Stay out of it.
I’ll find a way.
Miss Xu.
Morning!
Mr. Tang, Miss Xu.
Mr. Tang, Miss Xu, wait for me.
Morning!
I bought these specially for you.
Here.
OK. OK.
OK.
Thanks.
No, thanks.
You got time to go back
to the firm today?
Mr. Shangguan gained a complete victory.
I’m sure the firm
will throw a celebration party.
Sure.
He did great in winning the case
about the multinational payment
of claims.
Daren Law Firm Shangguan Yi
He’s like a golden walking billboard.
Mr. Shangguan will certainly
become the ace of our firm this time.
Mr. Shangguan is always good.
Besides, he has a
down-to-earth attitude.
Now, people have to wait in long lines
in order to consult him.
Interns have to wait in long lines
in order to be his assistants, too.
You got a favorable position.
It’s a rare opportunity.
You must seize it.
Rest assured.
I’ll try my best.
Yeah.
Daren Law Firm
-Mr. Tang, Miss Xu, morning!
Morning!
Good morning!
Do you have an appointment?
I want to see Shangguan…
Mr. Shangguan,
you’re young and promising.
I don’t worry about it.
I’m flattered.
The evidence is conclusive.
The case is solid enough.
I believe we’ll get a fair verdict.
I want to see him.
Do you have an appointment?
Mr. Shangguan.
Who are you?
I’m Cong Rong’s mother.
How do you do?
Shall we go upstairs?
Please come in.
Hello.
Have some water.
Please let us talk alone.
Oh.
Cong Rong’s mother.
Sorry to bother you.
I come over to hand in
Cong Rong’s resignation.
In case there’s liability
for contract breach,
I’ll make compensation.
Did Cong Rong ask you to do this?
It doesn’t matter.
What matters
is that she can’t be a lawyer.
Auntie.
I don’t know why you made
such a decision.
In my opinion,
Cong Rong has great potential
and capability.
She took the self-study examination
amid busy study
and achieved high scores.
As you can imagine,
how eager she is to become a lawyer!
No matter how hard she tries,
she just can’t be a lawyer!
Auntie,
please calm down.
I met Cong Rong when I was
on an exchange visit to Australia.
It was in a big classroom.
She elbowed her way to me
and said she wanted to be a lawyer.
I didn’t take it seriously.
But she continued to email me,
talking about her views on cases
and her experiences of review.
Gradually, I changed my mind about her.
In addition to taking the courses
of her own major,
she spent all her spare time
on teaching herself law.
Law isn’t her major.
She couldn’t have tutoring class, too.
She had to immerse herself
in reading and exercising.
The domestic judicial examination scope
includes 200 more laws
involving over 10,000 articles of law.
It’s a lot of work.
It took her two years.
During that time,
she went to bed at three
and got up at nine every day.
She didn’t have weekends
or a social life.
She studied really hard.
That’s why I know
how she is eager to be a lawyer.
We shouldn’t give up
such people like her.
I know.
I know how hard she works.
I also know how persistent she is.
But she can’t be a lawyer.
She should know that deep down.
Don’t bother.
I won’t let her do it!
Mr. Shangguan.
I’m sorry.
Mom.
Don’t make a fuss.
This is the office.
You created a bad impression.
Come on.
Let’s go home.
Don’t pull me.
I can walk on my own.
Mr. Shangguan.
What does Cong Rong think she is?
The firm isn’t her home.
Let go of me!
You’re hurting me!
You made my arm red.
Even your dad never did this to me.
Mom.
Don’t do that.
Was it my fault?
If you hadn’t sneaked back,
I wouldn’t have come over here.
I feel humiliated too.
I really fear that
you follow in your dad’s footsteps.
Mom.
It was different before.
To be a legal aid lawyer
was poor and tired.
But I’m different with dad.
I’m an economic lawyer.
I promise not to do legal aid, OK?
No.
You sneaked back here.
I’ll let it pass.
You engage in financial medical care
and I have no objection.
But if you insist on being a lawyer,
I’ll never compromise.
Can you tell me why?
Just think I have a bias
against lawyers.
I discriminate against them.
To be a lawyer is my dream.
You can’t just impose
your ideas on me.
Why do you think only of yourself?
You said, I only think of myself?
Do you think I’m such a selfish mother?
No.
Enough! I got it! I see!
Mom.
Leave me alone!
Just think I am unreasonable!
Mom. I didn’t mean that.
Don’t be angry.
Mom!
Leave me alone!
Mom.
Do you have a minute?
Let’s have a talk.
Mr. Shangguan.
I’m sorry.
My mom was a little irritated.
I hope she didn’t affect you.
Don’t worry about that.
To persuade your mom is more important.
I didn’t expect
that she would find it out at this time.
I was supposed to tell her
after I passed the internship.
Though it’s your own decision
to be a lawyer,
your parents’ support is important, too.
Have a good talk with her.
Tell her your true feelings.
Honestly,
I really hope you would stay.
It’s not just me.
Lucy has a good opinion of you, too.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you remember how hard you worked?
Finally, you’ve reached this stage.
I don’t want you to give up easily
because of anything else.
Cong Rong.
I’m optimistic about you.
Thank you, Mr. Shangguan.
I’ll try my best.
Yeah.
Mr. Shangguan,
drive carefully.
OK.
Cong Rong.
This is...
Let me introduce.
This is my boss,
Shangguan Yi.
This is one of my colleagues
from the hospital.
Dr. Wen Shaoqing.
See you, then.
Why did he take you home?
It’s a long story.
By the way,
did my mom contact you?
No.
What was wrong?
She made a fuss at the firm today.
Don’t worry.
She will be fine.
You both need to calm down.
Is Mr. Shangguan
an acquaintance of yours?
We’re not so acquainted.
However,
he is a real brain box in my mind.
He gave me instructions in person
on my judicial examination
and career planning.
My internship at Daren Law Firm
is thanks to his recommendation.
Yeah?
He is really nice to you.
Yeah.
He looks very serious.
But he is very kind.
I have a practice assessment
next month.
I need to practice my finger dexterity.
I know the words I said went too far,
but she doesn’t have to stay out late.
It’s late now.
The number you dialed
is not answered at present.
She didn’t answer the phone.
I don’t know where she went.
I’m going to look for her.
I’m going, too.
You’d better stay at home.
If she hasn’t cooled down,
you may have another fight
when you meet.
Chengcheng: Your mom is with me.
What are you doing?
Don’t tell her.
Yeah.
Auntie.
Come on.
Have some water.
Cool down.
Don’t be mad.
Young kids like you
would rather listen to a stranger
than listen to your old folks.
Look at you.
You managed the antique shop well,
yet you gave it up
and opened a barbecue restaurant.
It makes you too busy to eat fruits.
Thanks, Auntie.
You’re right.
It’s too tiring.
Why indeed shall we pursue our dreams?
I should have listened to my mom.
Stay at home.
All our dreams
are rubbish.
Can your dreams
take the blow of reality?
It can’t.
To stay up for nights preparing exams,
why did we bother?
Why did we bother to work our way
through college?
In the end, we have to find a job
and earn a small salary
to make a hard living.
How could it compare
with your hard life?
That’s right.
It’s not.
You were not flattering me.
You were satirizing me.
No.
I don’t dare.
Auntie.
It was my self-reflection.
We’re all ungrateful creatures.
We don’t deserve
our parents’ deep love.
Good.
I haven’t seen you for years,
and you got new skills.
You know how to be ironic
with me, don’t you?
No. You misunderstood me.
Burang Barbeque
Traitor!
Auntie.
I can see your heart is softened.
I come over to pick you up.
Did you come alone?
Cong Rong is doing self-reflection.
She’s preparing you an apology dinner.
What is she preparing?
Tell her.
I don’t like ordinary dishes.
What do you like?
Feel free to say.
Really?
Yeah.
I would like Li Hongzhang Stew.
As long as you like it,
there’s no problem.
She may know just what you like
and is cooking.
Is she?
Then I must go back
and see how she’s doing.
Auntie, see you.
Come often.
Your mom would like Li Hongzhang Stew.
Shaoqing.
Did you come to pick me up
in order to persuade me for Cong Rong?
Auntie.
Why do you strongly disagree
with Cong Rong’s idea of being a lawyer?
Cong Rong’s biological father
was a lawyer.
When he died,
Cong Rong was a pupil.
In order to fight for justice,
he got around a great deal.
He couldn’t take care of his family.
Though life was hard then,
I was very happy.
I thought I lived a happy life.
I just loved him being chivalrous.
But I never expected
that because of his work,
he got into trouble.
Then…
I really don’t want Cong Rong
to follow in her father’s footsteps.
Auntie,
Cong Rong wants to be a lawyer.
I have no right to interfere.
I can only promise you this.
I’ll take good care of her.
I won’t let her get into trouble.
I know it clearly.
In my opinion,
no matter what Cong Rong does,
she’ll put her heart and soul into it.
When she dealt with the hospital cases…
In the future, my phone will be
your family line. Please wake up.
She dedicated her efforts.
In addition to mediation,
she would do things
that went beyond her duties.
She is the same with her dad.
Same character.
Just because she is as chivalrous
as her dad was,
I don’t want her to be a lawyer.
Auntie,
that’s Cong Rong’s character.
Whether she’s a lawyer or not,
it doesn’t make any difference.
What I can do
is to be with her,
guard her
and be her backup.
Whenever she needs me,
I’ll be there.
Auntie, look.
Cong Rong is cooking.
She is very sincere.
How can you put it in now?
Look,
the bamboo shoot is used for freshening.
You must put it in first.
Here.
Put it in.
Come.
The soup
hasn’t been cooked long enough.
Look,
it isn’t thick at all.
Too much.
You do it.
If so,
how can you learn to cook?
You do it on your own.
Come on.
You do it.
Here.
Put some sugar in.
Here, it won’t be too salty.
Have a taste.
It’s not enough. Some more.
Some more?
Some more.
I’m not biased against lawyers.
I’m afraid that you’ll be like your dad
and the sense of justice in your genes
crops up from time to time.
You can’t control it.
It can’t be true.
Why can’t it?
Seeing the news of your brave deeds,
I was so worried.
For making mediation,
you have to deliver justice.
What if you become a real lawyer?
Did my dad do the same?
Your dad was a criminal defense lawyer.
He was famous.
However,
the more famous he was,
the more people asked for his help,
and the more responsible
he felt himself was.
He took all the responsibility
on himself.
At last, the burden
became intolerably heavy.
He broke down from constant overwork.
Did he work so hard?
You’ve been like your dad
since you were a child,
overwhelmed by the sense of justice.
So,
I’ve been trying every means
to stop you from being a lawyer.
But in the end,
you still took the same path.
Maybe it’s fate.
We just can’t avoid it.
Maybe I was too deeply influenced
by dad.
His words have been
engraved on my mind since I was a child.
Laws
must advocate merits and deter violence.
Lawyers
represent the great integrity.
Most lawyers are working on cases.
A good lawyer tries to be a moral man.
From an ordinary lawyer to a good lawyer
is a process of learning to be a human.
Wield the sword of law.
Hold the scales of justice.
Lawyers are earthly being.
I don’t want you
to get hurt for justice.
But if you can,
I hope you can uphold justice
as much as possible.
Your dad was right.
But I don’t want to watch you
on that news every day.
Don’t try to be a justice warrior.
Cong Rong,
I just want you
to be safe and happy
all your life.
Then I will be content.
Mom.
Come on, tell me.
You were alone at the fraud scene.
Were you afraid?
Yes.
But when the time came,
if I didn’t do it,
who would do it?
You said the same words
as your dad said.
But Wen Shaoqing came on time.
When the swindler was about to hit me
with a chair,
Wen Shaoqing held me suddenly.
Then the chair fell on him.
He is good
and reliable.
Shaoqing is really a good kid.
Tell me.
Are you seeing each other?
Well...
Your dad at least
had me as his strong supporter.
What about you?
How can you do that alone?
Don’t you want to reassure me?
You must give me a reason
to rest assured.
Mom. They’re two different things.
I don’t care.
You must find yourself
a down-to-earth boyfriend,
so I can rest assured.
I’ve made up my mind.
I’ll stay till you get a boyfriend.
I… I have one.
I’ve got a boyfriend.
I’m with Wen Shaoqing now.
Really?
When did it happen?
Last night.
Tell me quickly.
What happened then?
Who confessed first?
What did he say?
How did you feel?
Stop gossiping.
It’s my privacy.
Get to sleep.
Don’t tell me.
I’ll know it anyway.
Tuck up.
Naughty girl.
Cong Rong: I need you
to cooperate with me to put on a play.
Wen Shaoqing: With pleasure.
Cong Rong: I haven’t told you yet.
Wen Shaoqing: I guess, after a
sincere talk, your mom still feels
that she can’t rest assured until you
get a boyfriend to look after you.
Cong Rong: Have you bugged my room?
Wen Shaoqing: It’s called connected.
Mom.
I’m going to work.
Are you going to work together?
Yes, Auntie.
We’re going to work.
I’m sorry.
My mom brought up a weird request.
So...
Yeah.
I understand.
Did you get into the habit?
Your mom is watching us.
Auntie.
We’re about to have lunch.
Look.
You must be hungry.
You
should eat more.
Okay?
Look at you.
You’ve grown up,
but you eat like a baby.
Aren’t you too devoted?
Auntie.
Rest assured.
Cong Rong,
look how blushed you are!
You’re in a relationship.
There’s nothing to be embarrassed about.
Mom.
We’re in public.
We have to work after lunch.
Bye.
Auntie…
Don’t follow me.
What’s going on?
Are they together?
I’ve already said that.
Don’t you think I have sharp eyes?
That’s why
I say you’re good.
Come on,
babe.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪