♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 22
Fei.
Sounds bustling out there.
Shall we go have a look?
Not interested.
Fine.
A trip always ends.
When you’re nearly home,
I’ve kind of finished my mission.
Plum
Tongsheng Pharmacy
What does your hometown look like?
My hometown?
It’s cold.
Unlike this place
where trees are green
throughout the year.
Every winter in Jiankang,
red leaves outside the palace fall.
Even a thin layer of ice forms
over Qinhuai River.
The barren ferry falls silent at once.
Only the palace isn’t cold
where there’s always charcoal fire.
And...
Well, I don’t remember much.
Anyway, I’m not cold or hungry there.
Nothing else is fun.
There are many rules.
When I grew up,
I loved to travel to south.
To save money, small inns don’t
make a fire for you.
So,
I prefer to bask
in the sun in the south.
Do you remember...?
What happened when I was little?
I don’t.
I was too little
to remember many things.
So, I’m not as miserable as you imagine.
Don’t always keep everything
to your heart,
making you mysterious.
Girl.
Do you know
what being curious about someone
means?
What?
It means
you like him.
You want to know what he does every day
and what he is going to do.
You even wonder
what he thinks of every day.
The lovesickness begins
from being curious about someone.
What’s wrong with you?
I’m talking seriously!
What do you mean lovesickness?
I’m just
near my home already.
I think you’re wandering alone
and have nowhere to settle down.
Then I worry about you.
Don’t bother.
I lead a wandering life.
And I’m used to that.
If you ask me to stay somewhere
and don’t move,
I’ll feel bored and suffocated.
You will not stop?
Not really.
If I go to your home
and your mother asks me
to be her son-in-law,
I can’t run away.
In your dream!
Fei! Fei!
Why are you up there?
You know what? Bad news!
Yan is gone!
What?
I knew she wouldn’t be obedient!
When I went upstairs,
I visited her room,
only to find it empty
with the windows open.
Could she
run out again?
Her room is high.
Did she dare to jump?
You’re right. She didn’t dare.
Fei, what do we do?
Jili, don’t worry.
I’ll go get her back.
I’m going, too.
No! You can’t.
You’ve just recovered.
You had fights
and travelled all the way.
You need more rest.
None of your business!
Don’t follow me.
Give me back the Five-bat Token.
Why?
I’ll get in
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight anyway.
One day,
I’ll get it back from Zhou Fei!
You’re really going
to the Fortress of the Forty-Eight?
A man always keeps his promise.
Fine, for the sake
you helped me sneak out,
let me tell you.
You can’t get in
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
How about this?
I’ll ask Fei to give it back to you.
What do you think?
If so,
I’ll give the token to you.
But I’m still going to
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
Are you really an idiot?
Look at you.
What else do you know,
except martial arts?
Stop.
Why are you still following me?
When I helped you,
you didn’t say that.
Why are you still following me?
If I don’t follow you,
I won’t know how to get there.
How annoying!
Are you looking for me?
Seems like we’re on the same wavelength.
Who is on the same wavelength with you?
The moon is clear tonight.
Go. Let me take you to a place.
Affluence and Prosperity
The Fortress of the Forty-Eight
is right ahead.
We’re at Chunhui Town.
Let’s settle down for a moment.
You had a hard trip.
Don’t say that.
I was your burden.
The inn is just over there.
Stop following me.
Who is following you?
I’m just walking this way, too.
Sheng! Sheng!
Be careful. He’s wounded.
It hurts.
You must be Miss Wu.
Sheng.
Seems like she cares for you.
Could she...?
What are you talking about?
Talk politely and don’t be rude.
Call me Yan.
I’m his sister.
Yan.
Who is this man?
I’m Yang Jin with Cloud Ravine.
You must be Li Sheng,
grandson of the South Blade.
What Ravine?
Cloud Ravine in the south.
Known as Small Medicine Valley!
Mr. Yang.
Sorry I didn’t recognize you.
Why are you with my sister?
Shall we fight?
He keeps asking Fei for a fight!
But he was defeated.
Right, loser?
I’m just passing by.
I’ve got something else to do. See you.
Oh, Sheng,
how were you hurt?
Now you care for me?
But you...
Why are you coming down alone?
I’m not alone.
Fei and Mr. Xie are here.
Fei is also here?
Who is Mr. Xie, then?
He’s the man
who asked Uncle to leave the mountain.
It’s hard to explain.
Let’s get back to the inn first.
Let’s go.
Mr. Ma!
Look who’s back.
Sheng?
Good boy.
You didn’t let me down.
You must be Miss Wu.
Great. When you come back safely,
I can finally stop worrying
about you.
Thank you for your concern.
Speaking of this,
thanks to Fei.
Miss Chuchu said
her trip started dangerously.
Without Fei’s help,
we wouldn’t have come back safely.
Oh,
where’s Fei?
Yan.
Where are Fei and Mr. Xie?
And Mr. Yang.
Fei and Mr. Xie are taking a walk.
As for Bonehead,
I pissed him off and he ran away.
Look at you.
You always make troubles.
Get upstairs and go to bed!
Don’t run about again.
Mr. Ma, don’t be angry.
My brother is wounded.
I’ll heal him.
It hurts!
Just go to bed.
-How rude you are!
-Sheng.
How were you wounded?
Mr. Ma.
Secret Service betrayed us.
We came all the way back,
being hunted down.
So, we shouldn’t stay for long.
We must get back soon.
Okay.
Seems like it’ll be two hours
before the Spinning Wire Formation stops.
Mr. Yutai.
I’ve been waiting for this day
for too long.
Sir.
There comes some noise of fight
near the pavilion.
Please send men to check.
Let’s go!
Look.
That’s my home.
The Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
It looks the brightest
only when the moon shines
over Ximo River.
I went there before.
Oh, yes. You did.
Yeah.
But I was too busy netting the weeds
to enjoy the moon.
Now I realize
the moon really looks great.
What’s the difference
between this moon
and that in your hometown?
I’m asking you. Why do you stare at me?
The moon looks the same
no matter where we look at it.
But people who enjoy it are different.
Fei.
People come and go
in your place.
Patrols are everywhere.
Can birds still be highly strung?
Is there
something happening?
Let’s get back to the inn.
Okay.
-Chief.
He is dead.
The mission to restore our sect
counts on us!
We used to be famous spies.
Now, we’re restrained
in the Forbidden Forest.
We’re not free
and even subordinate to
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight!
From today on,
we will restore our sect
and no longer disgrace ourselves!
-We all take your order, Chief!
Lord, according to Mingfeng spies,
it’ll be two hours
before the Spinning Wire Formation stops.
Give my order.
Ask everybody to get ready.
We’ll cross the river and attack
in two hours.
Aye.
Fine. We’ll get up the mountain
tomorrow morning.
Mr. Ma!
Fei!
Are you getting better?
Yes.
You’re finally back?
Fei, where did you go?
What took you so long?
Mr. Ma.
Something happened
in the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
What happened?
Mr. Xie and I saw startling birds
from that direction.
There’s more bad news.
Our Secret Service across the state...
Some have betrayed us.
Miss Chuchu and I came all the way back,
being hunted down.
In Huarong,
the Secret Service betrayed us, too.
They were bribed by Demons Manor
so that our disciples died
including Chenfei.
Demons Manor?
Tong Tianyang with Demons Manor
killed Ms. Wang.
If someone hadn’t helped us,
I would have died, too.
Demons Manor?
Secret Service?
Something...
Something dangerous has really happened.
Sheng, I want to go home.
Mr. Ma.
We’ll certainly go home!
Fei.
I’ll go with you.
Mr. Ma, time is running out.
Let’s get up to the mountain.
Fine.
But I don’t think
Miss Chuchu and Yan should go.
They don’t have martial arts.
If something happens,
they’ll be in danger.
Yes.
No.
There’s trouble up the mountain.
They may not be safe down it.
We must go together.
Fine.
Let’s get packed.
We’ll go up to the mountain asap.
Chief.
Giant Leopard is ready.
Guards at the gate
of the Fortress of the Forty-Eight
have been wiped out.
It is time
for winner-take-all!
Ask people down the mountain to act.
Something is wrong!
Strike the gong in the outpost
to warn others!
Report!
Mr. Zhang.
There’s sound of gong
from down the mountain.
I’ve heard it.
Well,
go give my order.
Send men to support at the gate.
Aye.
The rest of you, come with me!
-Aye!
Lord Gantang.
According to spies,
Yu Wenzhi left with private soldiers
three days ago.
Do you know where he has gone?
Not sure yet.
I’m afraid
he’s up to something else.
I must head for the battalion
in the north of the city
for something important.
Okay.
-Let’s go.
-Aye.
Fei, something is wrong!
We can’t get in through the outer gate.
I know a pathway.
Let’s go this way.
The Formation has stopped.
All of you, go!
-Aye.
Master.
This pathway leads
to the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
If you worry,
go up there and have a look.
No.
We’ll head for the north
as planned.
Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah!
Judged from their wounds,
people with Mingfeng killed them.
No wonder their Secret Service
all betrayed us.
Fei.
You’re strong enough
to protect yourself.
Well, run away
with Miss Chuchu and Yan.
Stop treating me like a kid!
I’ll go with you!
Mr. Ma.
I want to help, too.
No way!
It’s too dangerous.
If you’re in danger,
how can I explain to your mother?
Mr. Ma.
This is her home.
She can’t leave it alone.
I’m not running away this time.
I’ll fight with you.
Mr. Ma.
No matter what the rebels want,
Aunt isn’t home now.
It counts on me...
On us.
Individuals don’t survive
when losing their homes.
When it’s dangerous here,
so will be other places.
Mr. Ma!
Fine, fine.
But remember,
if you’re in real danger,
you must escape immediately.
Understand?
Mr. Ma, when the third elder rebelled,
how did my mother defend the Fortress
all by herself?
At that time,
your mother was already
the leader.
But without the help of other elders,
she wouldn’t have united everyone
and fought the enemies.
Other elders?
Precisely.
But now,
your mother isn’t here.
We don’t have a leader.
I can even imagine that.
Those stubborn elders
don’t convince each other.
Let’s go to the Hall of Elders
and ask them to unite.
Okay.
Fei.
I’m not going with you.
We’re not sure about other places.
I’ll go check it.
Let’s take separate action.
Okay.
Fine. That’s it.
Follow me.
Yan.
I’ll leave Chuchu to you.
Don’t worry. I’ll take care of her.
Li Sheng.
Be very careful.
See you.
Fei, you need tricks
to unite those elders.
Use your brain instead of strength.
The Spinning Wire Formation stops,
but it doesn’t mean Fisherman did it.
You two.
Calm down. Calm down.
Zhao Qiusheng, An Elder of the Fortress
Only Fisherman can stop the Formation.
Stop making a veiled abuse.
You sound like
you’re complaining about Deng Zhen.
Deng Zhen, An Elder of the Fortress
I can make out what you mean.
Deng Zhen is the elder of defense.
Zhang Bolin, An Elder of the Fortress
He has the responsibility
to explain to us
about what is happening.
Why are you still quarrelling?
The longer you quarrel,
the more men die.
Ma, what’s going on?
Why are you back?
With strangers?
Mr. Ma, do me a favor.
When we get in the Hall of Elders,
let Fei talk to the elders first.
If you say something for her first,
they’ll certainly think
she’s a follower.
There’s a reason.
It’s a long story.
Our priority is
to solve the rebellion of Mingfeng.
Now,
the outer gate may be broken through.
Even the outer gate...?
How do you know
it’s the rebellion of Mingfeng?
When we got up the mountain,
we saw many disciples killed
by Mingfeng people.
Sounds like
we’re under attack
from all directions.
Deng.
The Spinning Wire Formation
has been stopped.
Enemies will come over Ximo River.
Li Sheng has gone to check other places.
Could you give me some disciples
for support?
Young girl.
How dare you give orders now!
Yun Xiao!
Here.
Order standby posts
to be used immediately.
Send more men for defense.
Ask the remaining disciples
to come here
and get ready to check Ximo River.
If there’s any problem,
shoot to warn us.
Aye.
Whether it’s too late depends
on how strong our enemies are.
Talk firmly to them.
You can’t convince anyone
before you fully trust yourself.
When you take charge,
don’t force them.
Don’t go too far.
Remember, you’re a junior.
You come to solve problem,
instead of making trouble.
Elders.
Mr. Zhang. Mr. Zhao.
I was so anxious
that I behaved a bit rudely.
Please forgive me.
Forget it.
I’ll see
what kind of enemies
those traitors can get!
What if
those elders do their own duties
and unite with each other?
Your mother keeps the elders
so that they restrain each other.
So, what we should do
is to take them down one by one.
My mother told me
you two were the most reliable elders
in our place.
We depend on you
to defend our fortress.
Your mother is right.
Leave it to us. Don’t worry.
Everyone, how about this?
Li Sheng and I will take care
of the gate and posts.
As for the enemies over Ximo River,
I’ll leave it to you all.
I didn’t teach you
to flatter them.
Good.
It’s wise of you.
Ms. Kou.
Lord.
This is the map
of the Spinning Wire Formation.
Keep it.
Very good.
Let’s stick to the plan.
Our men are ready to attack
from the root of the mountain.
Let’s make a sudden attack
through the Forbidden Forest.
Hall of Elders
This is the Fortress of the Forty-Eight.
My home.
Fight and I’ll live.
Retreat and I’ll die.
I would die, at most.
In a brave way.
Everybody.
We all live here.
We’re brothers
and families.
Hall of Elders
Now, the Fortress is at stake.
Whatever,
I want you to get rid of prejudice
and defend our home together.
-Yes! Yes! Yes!
She looks like a leader.
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
Forbidden Forest
Forbidden Forest,
walk in and you’ll die
Yan.
Stay here with Chuchu.
Fei, I also want to go.
I know you’re great.
So,
I have an important task for you.
Protect Chuchu.
Walk in and you’ll die
Map of the Spinning Wire Formation
Ximo River
Go!
Everyone, follow me.
Stop!
Go!
We’re right.
Posts of the Forbidden Forest
have been broken through, too.
Senior.
Sheng, are you alright?
I’m fine.
Men in black keep coming in.
They look like
they’re with Demons Manor.
Spinning Wires keep changing.
And they’re covert.
How can they avoid them
so easily?
Seems like
people in Mingfeng collude with them
so that they know
where the Spinning Wires are.
They come this way,
possibly because they want
to reach the center place
in small groups.
Once they get there and cooperate
with enemies coming over Ximo River,
they’ll besiege us.
Senior.
I’ve got an idea.
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
Who are you?
Demons Manor.
You know him?
No.
Cold breeze.
He’s very likely to be Gu Tianxian,
Giant Leopard with Demons Manor.
They don’t have many men.
They don’t stand a chance to defeat you.
Gu Tianxian especially comes
when my mother is away.
They won’t fight an uncertain battle.
Could they
have a backup plan?
Whatever!
I’ll rush up,
kill him and roast him
for celebration party.
I’m Gu Tianxian.
I come without invitation.
Hope you will
forgive me.
Giant Leopard with Demons Manor?
You come uninvited.
We’ll kill you to eliminate the evil.
What do you think,
Ms. Kou?
Kou Dan.
You ungrateful shrew!
You have no idea.
We have a rule.
When a new chief wants power,
he must kill the former one.
You and my master retired. Fine.
In case no one else gets the map
of the Spinning Wire Formation,
you even caught me back!
Leave if you want.
I won’t stop you.
You!
I don’t think I can get information
about the Bracelet from you.
Mr. Yutai died a natural death.
Compared to former chiefs,
I’m merciful enough.
Kou Dan!
We kept you
and protected you.
But you betray us!
Our sect was taken in by Li Zheng.
To show our sincerity,
we used the Spinning Wire Formation
over Ximo River.
It’s such an important formation
that all core disciples involved
have never left this place.
From then on,
we dwelled in the Forbidden Forest
as your gatekeepers.
What’s big deal of being decent?
Mr. Zhang.
Why don’t you ask Madam Li
if she’s fair
to you?
I heard the former chief
caught his youngest disciple
who wanted to escape
just for the Spinning Wire Formation.
After years,
she’s finally cultivated
into a qualified spy.
Seems like
you’re too qualified.
Young man.
You know too much.
Tell me.
Where is Fisherman?
Fei.
Calm down.
I’ll fight her.
She has fighting experience of decades.
You’re not as strong.
But I know the way she fights.
Cut the crap.
We’re separating from you.
I don’t think Madam Li will give me
what I want.
I guess I need more hostages
to make a deal with her.
Zhou Fei.
You’re back just in time.
Wait.
When I’m here,
you don’t need to fight.
Wait and see
how I’ll teach her a lesson.
You shrew!
How arrogant you sound!
Ms. Kou.
I’ll fight you.
Zhou Fei.
I haven’t tried
your Snow-breaking Blade yet.
You can try now.
Interesting.
Watch out!
That’s Rain Needle.
You’re fast.
Luckily, it’s thick enough.
Be careful with the hook!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
This is Snow-breaking Blade?
Precisely.
Miss Fei has great marital arts!
Report!
Mr. Zhao.
A large number of people are attacking
from the root of the mountain.
From all directions.
I’ve fought masters
with Qianzhong Sect and South Blade.
Today,
my trip isn’t for nothing.
You’re heroes.
But to be honest,
when we were fighting,
elite men of Timber Wolf
came all the way up.
When he comes,
he kills people.
But I don’t want
to be sacrificed.
Why don’t we sit down
and figure everything out?
Isn’t it a good thing
to make peace?
Go!
You’ve got a good idea.
Or we wouldn’t have fought
so many enemies.
Our gate and outer gate
have been taken by Mingfeng Sect.
Our next step is
to get our gate back.
Oh, Sheng,
when we were in the Hall of Elders,
I didn’t have the chance to ask Fei.
Where are Ms. Wang and Chenfei?
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪