[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 14]
You'll stay here from now on.
Choose your rooms.
Senior Lian Rou,
you really don't remember me?
Shao Yang.
What can I do for you?
We'll be fellow disciples from now on.
Do you remember
our senior, Zhu Xin?
And senior Zhang Ying.
I do.
I heard they joined the
Artefact Forging Sect last year.
Just now, Senior Lian Rou
arranged a meet and greet
with the brethren.
When the two seniors heard
you were coming,
they were overjoyed.
They said the Old Master
was your benefactor.
They suggested a secret gathering
at the training ground
once we've settled in.
To acquaint us with the sect's
written and unwritten rules.
So that we can all
help each other out
by way of repaying
the Old Master's kindness.
A new initiate
having a secret rendezvous
with a senior.
Isn't it inappropriate?
Where else do you propose?
In the great hall?
Shall we reveal each other's
identities, then?
So you are Xie Jing Xuan?
Isn't it obvious?
The Xie Jing Xuan I knew
was the saintess of the
Eight Extremes Temple,
leader of the human race
against the Dark Nether Race.
I am still a saintess now,
in the hearts of the men
of the Artefact Forging Sect.
If the Eight Extremes people find out
their saintess is still alive,
you can forget about being the saintess
of the Artefact Forging Sect.
If the people of the Palace of Hell
find out you're here,
you'll be the one
who's going to die,
not me.
You know a lot about me,
yet I know nothing about you.
How do I know
this isn't one of you
and Song Ting Yu's schemes?
Looks like that stupid girl
hasn't captured you,
though you're far from being
free from her grasp.
If you want to know,
you can always ask me.
I might tell you
if I'm in a good mood.
Why did you fake your own death?
Because I don't want to be the saintess
of the Eight Extremes Temple anymore.
I suppose you've been living as Tang Si Qi
for quite a while now?
When I was still Xie Jing Xuan,
Tang Si Qi
was my alias when I wanted to have fun.
Then
we have an understanding.
We'll keep each other's
identity a secret.
One more thing.
You've killed Du Shao Yang's father.
Are you going to kill him, too?
If Du Hai Tian has set a trap,
how can his son not be an accomplice?
If he's an accomplice,
why would Du Hai Tian turn against
his own blood?
Where are seniors Zhu Xin and Zhang Ying?
Zhu Xin here.
Zhang Ying here.
Shao Yang,
[Zhu Xin, Zhang Ying]
long time no see.
Zhang Ying, you're a
Bloody Spear Guard now?
Zhang Ying's talent knows no bounds.
He's mastered both armoury
and the Bloody Spear.
Back when your father was the chief
of Xingyun Pavilion,
he took you on his travels.
You were only 12 when you came
to my family,
yet you'd already reached the
Natal Opening Realm.
Your father wouldn't stop
boasting about it.
As a result, I was locked up for ten years
before I reached the Natal Opening Realm.
It's time to settle the score.
You're blaming me for that?
What Zhang Ying means is,
since the Old Master isn't around anymore,
there's no need
to keep you around, either.
Cast him into the cauldron
and forge an artefact out of him.
Yes.
Stop!
You can't do this.
Silence the witness.
Yi Yuan, run.
Yi Yuan, run!
Trying to escape?
Qin Bing.
Stop looking, I'm down here.
It's me, Yi Yuan.
Yi Yuan?
How did you become like this?
I have no time to explain.
You must save Du Shao Yang.
Ouyang Qing and the gang
are trying to kill him.
-Where?
-The armoury hall.
Okay.
Get the seniors.
-Senior Si Qi or Senior Lian Rou?
-Both.
Why don't you show us your real face?
You pretend to be kind and righteous
when in fact you're ruthless and cruel,
and you expect me to show my face?
Enough talk!
Halt.
Senior Si Qi, Senior Lian Rou,
I can explain.
What's there to explain?
Zhang Ying, Zhu Xin,
report to Elder Bi
in the Hall of Punishment.
You'll have your titles revoked
and your natal palaces stripped.
You'll relinquish your Bloody Spear
and be imprisoned
in Firetop Mountain for ten years.
This is Pang Feng and Ouyang Qing's
first offence.
Take them away and give them
2000 strokes each.
Senior Lian Rou, have mercy.
Without our natal palaces,
we're no more than outlanders.
Senior Lian Rou,
I know you're a kind lady.
You fools. I was lying about that.
Senior Lian Rou is as cold and impartial
as they come.
Take them away.
If anyone resists, kill him.
Thank you, seniors.
Lian Rou, let's go.
Master Mo Hai.
-Master Mo Hai.
I need to speak with them.
Leave us.
Yes.
Since our parting at the Purple Mist Sea,
I can hardly recognise you now.
Qin Lie.
Yes, master.
-Du Shao Yang.
-Yes, master.
You two have a blood feud.
If you must settle it,
please do so outside.
Why did you save me?
My father killed the Ling family.
Not even one life could compensate for it.
Shouldn't you kill me?
Or do you want to keep me alive
and watch me devolve into a homeless dog?
Senior Si Qi told me everything.
You tried to save Ling Borough.
An act which I still regret.
If the Ling family
were completely wiped out,
you wouldn't have known the truth.
And my father
wouldn't have died.
So why didn't you expose my true identity?
The Palace of Hell is searching
high and low for me.
I didn't do it out of mercy.
I wanted an opponent.
Call it an opponent
or an enemy.
We will battle one day.
Master Mo Hai has spoken.
Our feud cannot be settled here.
Once you and I leave the
Artefact Forging Sect,
we'll have our final battle.
I look forward to it.
So
you're now a senior
at the Artefact Forging Sect?
When I was a barmaid,
you were the young master
of Xingyun Pavilion.
I was your damsel.
A dainty girl who stood behind you
and needed your protection.
But now, I'm a senior.
One who no longer stands behind you
or needs your protection.
Do you feel discontented?
I'm no longer the young master
of Xingyun Pavilion either.
What does that have to do with us?
I've become a homeless dog.
But you're the celebrated senior
of the Artefact Forging Sect.
What does that have to do with us?
You're still you.
And I'm still me.
There are too many things
on my mind.
I thought
you'd miss me in my absence.
Besotted, even.
Was it all just my imagination, then?
Take back the earring.
I'm a man.
I shouldn't wear women's things.
But I like it.
Du Shao Yang, you told me
if we ever meet again,
you wouldn't let me go.
Are you eating your words now?
I'm not going to let you.
But don't worry.
I'll give you ample time to come
to your senses.
What do I mean
to you?
That hurts.
Qi Bing.
I say,
there's something odd about
your gaze today.
You can't even dress a wound.
Yet when there was trouble,
you jumped right into the fight.
How did you survive all these years?
Easy there.
I had a good friend
just like you.
To everyone,
he was sincere,
loyal
and pure of heart.
You remind me
a lot of him.
Then why didn't you bring him along?
He's dead.
Sorry.
How did you
turn into a snake just now?
A few years ago,
Senior Lian Rou came to Purple Mist Sea
to forage for herbs.
I was the one who received her.
At that time, everyone looked down on me
except her.
She was kind to me.
I'm asking you about
the snake transformation.
I am talking about that.
After that, I'd been wanting
to see her again.
But I had no real abilities.
I would spend my time
playing in the jungle.
I became friends with the snakes
and the spiders there.
What does that have to do
with turning into a snake?
Then it hit me.
What if I could come up
with a magical item
that could turn myself into a
little snake or a little spider
and make Senior Lian Rou happy?
That would make a girl happy?
Of course.
This mirror
was forged from the bodies
of countless little snakes.
You just need to chant to the mirror,
"I want to become a snake."
-Try it.
-No way.
What if I can't turn back?
Of course you will.
But you have to wait.
As for how long, I have no idea.
And you still dare to mess with it?
Dumb people have all the dumb luck.
Just now, when you turned into a snake,
was Senior Lian Rou happy or scared?
When she saw me,
I had already turned back.
You're always like that.
It's as if no hardship
or trouble in the world
could get you down.
But of course.
In my world,
no hardship or trouble is insurmountable.
If you have any troubles,
come to me.
We'll pull through together.
What's with that gaze again?
I like women. I like Senior Lian Rou.
Knock it off, Qin Bing.
Qin Bing, stop...
Qin Lie is in trouble.
As all of you must well be aware,
[Artefact Forging Sect, Great Hall]
the Secret Realm is upon us.
What is this Secret Realm?
Where does it come from?
Legend has it, in the High Rank Continent,
there was a mysterious figure
who unlocked the Secret Realm
at the foot of Firetop Mountain.
He invited all the young, promising talent
to train there.
The realm is filled with all sorts
of spirit ingredients
and spirit beasts.
All for the capable's taking.
And for the truly exceptional,
it holds unimaginable rewards.
Of course, the greater the reward,
the greater the risk.
To survive and reap the spoils,
you need skills,
intelligence and courage.
And most importantly,
teamwork.
But how are we supposed
to bring all the treasures
back from the Secret Realm?
Other sects may have problems,
but not the Artefact Forging Sect.
You can take as many as you wish.
Later, you will proceed
to the storeroom
and retrieve a Ring of Space each.
Du Shao Yang,
come with me.
Yes.
The rest of you, follow me.
You want to join the Bloody Spear?
That's right.
Then you must've heard of
the name, Feng Rong.
Have I ever.
Feng Rong is your wife, master.
As well as the number two person
in the Bloody Spear.
She's famous throughout
the continent of Chilan.
Would you like to meet her?
You're in luck today.
Rong'er.
-Come, give me a hand.
-Is the meat ready?
It's ready.
If you don't mind.
Try this.
-How is it?
-Delicious.
Why is your face dirty?
It is?
I'm sweltering.
Alright.
Don't just stand there.
I heard
you wish to join the Bloody Spear Guard?
It takes eight to ten years
to become an accomplished armourer.
But the Bloody Spear Guard is different.
I want to advance as quickly as possible.
No one has dared to cross the
Artefact Forging Sect in all these years
thanks to the Bloody Spear Guard.
You're pretty keen-sighted.
Are you done yet?
-Yes.
-Here.
It's not cooked. Grill it some more.
-What will do you without me?
-Nothing.
I wish to become a leader
in the Bloody Spear.
That's very ambitious.
But I wonder
if you have what it takes.
Try-outs for the Bloody Spear are over.
But I can give you a chance.
If you could acquire the blood
of the Huanyu Beast in the Secret Realm,
I'll make an exception and take you in.
Huanyu Beast?
Yes, Huanyu Beast.
No one has even seen it.
And no one knows
when it'll show up.
Last time it appeared
was over 100 years ago.
-Is it tasty?
-Very tasty.
That means I need luck on my side.
If you get to see it,
I wouldn't call it good luck.
Why?
You'll know when the time comes.
Master Mo, Saintess Song of the Profound
Heaven Alliance would like to see you.
Little Ting Yu.
Master Mo Hai, we meet again.
Ting Yu.
I've brought this year's spirit
ingredients on Liang Zhong's behalf.
The Profound Heaven Alliance
is counting on you
for the magical weapons.
Master.
You are Qin...
Let me introduce. His name is
Qin Bing.
Qin Bing?
Greetings, Saintess Song.
Thank you, master.
All the brethrens are here
except for the Shadow Tower people.
The Shadow Tower people
are mercenaries.
So long as you have the stone coins,
they'd kill anyone.
Why would the disciples
of such a faction
show their faces in broad daylight?
Senior Lian Rou?
What brings you here?
I'm here to forage for spirit herbs.
Right.
It's shady and cool over there.
Come, come.
Why don't you capture me?
My target is Qin Lie.
Not Qin Bing.
A party in Qisha Valley?
Meeting with an old flame, I see.
No wonder you begged Master
to let you come here.
Feel cooler now?
Yu Xin.
Look, the Secret Realm has opened.
It's open.
People.
Danger lurks everywhere
in the Secret Realm.
Why don't we team up?
Do you guys know which spirit beast
in the Secret Realm is the rarest
and most valuable?
It's the Huanyu Beast.
You're quite knowledgeable.
Once you get to know me better,
you'll realise
that I know far more than you imagined.
Then do you know where to find
the Huanyu Beast?
Funny you should ask. I happen
to know exactly where it is.
Follow me.
Wait for me.
Yu Shi, it's dangerous ahead.
Follow me closely.
Young Master Yuan Xiao,
we're there.
You may alight.
[Yuan Xiao, Young Master
of the Palace of Hell]
Just keep driving.
I'm afraid
it'd be dangerous.
When Di Shi Jiu appointed you
as my personal guard,
I thought you had something special.
Turns out you're just
as cowardly as any.
I'm not afraid.
Why should you be?
Go.
All high-level spirit beasts
have their own territories
on which
no other beast can set foot.
Look.
Although the mud here is moist,
there are no spirit beast tracks.
And there is not a sound of bird
for tens of li.
If you ask me,
the Huanyu Beast must be nearby.
We haven't heard a chirp since
we entered the realm.
It's not only here.
Besides, the mud is wet
everywhere in the forest, not just here.
I was collecting herbs along the way
and noticed the flora was undisturbed.
It didn't seem like a beast had walked by.
It means
there may very well be
a high-level spirit beast.
That's right, Lian Rou.
I noticed the same thing, too.
It proves my assumptions are correct.
Enough.
Where should we go now?
This way.
Qin Bing, let's go.
You have no idea
where the Huanyu Beast is.
And you're scared to the bone.
You just want company,
don't you?
Don't expose me. We're friends.
Let's go.
Qin Lie!
Ling Borough is in trouble.
Qin Lie, where are you going?
Father,
a group of Horned Demons are heading
to the herb patch.
I'll bring a troop
to escort the Ling family.
What's the hurry?
Let's wait until the Ling family
is completely wiped out.
Someone has to pay
for Huang'er's death.
Father, you can't.
Qin Lie will kill you.
Him?
Kill me?
I'm serious.
He will kill you!
Qin Lie.
Is that you, Qin Lie?
Qin Lie!
Qin Lie, where are you?
Not good.
Ling Borough is in trouble.
Eat something hot.
It'll keep you warm.
So it's not all purple.
What?
Growing up in the Purple Mist Sea,
everything I ever saw
was purple.
But you showed me
that there are other colours
in this world.
Who are you?
Yi Yuan.
Young Master of Purple Mist City. And you?
Lian Rou, from the Artefact Forging Sect.
You're a senior
at the Artefact Forging Sect now?
Father specifically told me
to be your guide.
I'll take care of your food and lodging
for the next few days.
Your protection
is my responsibility, too.
Wherever you go,
I'll follow you.
Uncle Ling!
Retreat!
This is all a trap by Du Hai Tian.
The reinforcements will never come.
Qin Lie.
Gong Mu Lie.
Stay away from that woman.
Are you alright?
So it's you.
You want to kill me?
It's the only way to save my father.
Not if I kill you first.
I'm still alive after falling
from such heights?
Lian Rou, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yi Yuan.
You know who I am?
It's me, Qin Bing.
Qin Bing?
Senior Lian Rou, it's me.
You are...
What are you people doing here?
Why is everyone injured?
We're battling the Horned Demon Race.
Where are they?
What nonsense is this?
The Purple Mist Sea hasn't fought
the Dark Nether Race in ages.
With me manning the fort,
what war could there be?
This isn't real.
None of this is real.
What's going on?
Saintess.
Are you alright?
If I'm not mistaken,
we're already in the belly
of the Huanyu Beast.
The Huanyu Beast isn't vicious by nature.
But to protect itself,
it would swallow its victims
into its belly.
Whoever's inside will face
their inner demons
and be trapped.
And if they die or get injured
in their hallucination,
so will their real selves.
Everyone's inner demon is different,
so the illusions will be different.
I often think,
if only I had tried to save my father
back in Purple Mist Sea.
Even if I failed,
I would die with him.
At least
I would see him one last time.
That's why I was transported
to Purple Mist Sea.
Me too.
How I wish I could've saved them.
And you.
You probably wish to end me,
so that I couldn't kill your father.
What is all this talk about killing?
Why was the Purple Mist Sea
that Senior Lian Rou and I saw
so calm and serene?
Unlike yours.
Perhaps you aren't thinking
of that battle,
but something else.
It's just that the place is the same.
Nevertheless, we're all in
the Purple Mist Sea's illusion.
Our inner demons, our deepest desires,
be it to kill, to hate,
to fight the Dark Nether Race,
or to pursue happiness,
are linked to that purple place.
If I hadn't tried to kill you
and forced you to use your thunder powers,
hurting the Huanyu Beast,
I'm afraid
we may never wake up.
I tried to invoke Thunderbolt.
[But to no avail.]
[Then I began to suspect]
if it was reality.
Let's get out of here, then.
We can't.
We're still in the Huanyu Beast's belly.
Listen.
Why don't we collect its blood
while we're at it?
That's right.
What a huge beast.
It nearly covered the whole sky
with half its body.
Yuan Xiao?
Has the Young Master of the Palace of Hell
come to the Secret Realm
for a treasure hunt, too?
I expected Senior Lian Rou
to come for the herbs.
But Saintess Song?
We lucked out and met the Huanyu Beast
and collected so much blood.
Is that so?
Since you made such a big haul,
you wouldn't mind sharing some
with me, would you?
We're leaving. Step aside.
You've killed Yuan Xiao!