[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 13]
[Peak of the glacier]
What is this place?
Take a good look at the surroundings.
This is the Ice Peak
of the Frost Mountains.
Before the frost came,
this was a vast and lush forest.
It was home to many spirit beasts
in the past.
According to legend,
someone made an imprint in the void.
That's how the Frost Mountains came to be.
This palm imprint descended from the void,
stretching over hundreds of miles,
and as deep as thousands of metres.
The chill dissipated,
causing all the spirit beasts
to be frozen.
It sealed the world in ice.
The power of the palm
destroyed everything.
The essence of frost it embodies
has remained unchanged.
It has been hiding away
in this land of frost,
flourishing.
Whether or not you can grasp
the essence of frost
depends on your good fortune.
I'll give you three months' time.
We will come back after three months.
But,
how can I comprehend the essence of frost?
Let us go.
We'll come back for him in three months.
[All beings are connected.]
[The land is the vein,
the body is the tendon.]
[The paths of stars
and the changes of the earth]
[are all Spirit Diagrams.]
Lord Wolf of the Blood Wolves has ordered.
Catch Di Shi Jiu, no lives will be spared!
[Di Shi Jiu, Master of Shadow Tower]
You do not know
the Blood Fiend Spirit Arts.
Speak! Who are you?
We have no past history,
but you had wanted to kill me.
Nevertheless, your evil aura
and ruthlessness
deserve my admiration.
I don't care for your admiration!
Kid,
do you know who I am?
The assassin organisation
under Palace of Hell,
Master of the Shadow Tower,
Di Shi Jiu.
Look! I caught a huge fish!
It was about to bite
but you scared it off.
Look at your awesome skills!
You caught a huge fish.
What would you like to eat?
I'll go foraging at the hill.
The hill?
When did you grow vegetables
at the hill?
I made it of course.
Sure.
You created the whole Chilan Continent.
You dare make fun of me?
Don't you hit me.
I'm still recovering.
You've recovered long ago.
I'm going to hit you!
Get over here!
Time to eat.
The cook of Purple Mist Sea
is quite skilled.
You say that all the time.
Don't you have any other comments?
Sure.
The cook of Purple Mist Sea
is awesome!
So we're close now, huh?
So close that you keep teasing me.
Close or not,
I'll still keep teasing you.
So domineering.
I like it.
Let's eat.
What's the matter?
Are you
hiding something from me?
How did you know?
You brought me here
and we've lived together for three months.
I can't say for sure when it started,
but I noticed a subtle shift
in your demeanour.
I think
I might have taken a liking to you.
Didn't you like me before?
Or could you have fallen for me?
Perhaps.
That's why I could feel
that you're hiding something from me.
The reason I didn't tell you
is because you were badly injured.
I didn't want to agitate you.
Shao Yang.
Your father has died.
What?
At the battle of the Purple Mist Sea,
your father supposedly had killed
many Ling members.
In order to avenge the deaths,
Qin Lie had challenged him
and killed him.
How was he able to kill my father?
Many people saw it.
The Palace of Hell has given order
to arrest Qin Lie.
But they haven't found him.
The essence of frost is almost all gone.
I can't believe it.
The boy actually did it.
The essence of frost is disappearing,
dissipating within Qin Lie's body.
Comprehending the essence of frost
is not unusual.
But being able to completely consume
and exhaust it
is extraordinary.
Back then,
Qin Lie's grandpa, Mr Qin Shan,
had trained on
the summit of the snowfield.
I saw how he displayed
the Law of Five Elements.
The five elements of metal,
wood, water, fire, earth.
He was able to implement them at will.
I had thought
it was because Mr Qin Shan was gifted.
Now I realise
that members of the Qin family
are born with innate synergy
to the five elements' spirit wells.
Perhaps the essence of frost
had been consumed by the spirit well
in his body.
Uncle Li.
The essence of frost has disappeared
whereas you seem to have
undergone a change in temperament,
as if you're a different person now.
Boy,
your level has improved.
It's only getting from
late stage Natal Opening
to Manifestation Realm.
There's still a long way to go
before I master it.
Uncle Li.
The essence of frost
created an image in my head.
It looked to be a Spirit Diagram.
You comprehended the essence of frost
as a Spirit Diagram?
Looks like you've got quite
a lot of hidden secrets.
Secrets?
This is the Eye of Frost.
With it,
you can go to any corner
of the vast world.
It's the key to entering Crystal World.
In future, you can use the Eye of Frost
to come here as you wish
in order to further master
your comprehension
of the essence of frost.
Keep the key safe.
No one will open the door for you
if you lose it.
Are you
going to leave?
Your grandpa had helped me.
Saving you is my way of repaying him.
You knew my grandpa?
[Qin Shan]
[Why did he come here?]
He was headed deep into
the Land of Frost.
And I have been guarding
this entrance all this while.
He beat me
and successfully entered
the Land of Frost.
It seemed as if he was in search
of something.
In the end, however,
he did not find anything.
What was it that Grandpa was looking for?
Nobody knows.
He only gave a few pointers
on my cultivation
before swiftly leaving.
He never came back.
I'm deeply grateful to him.
That's why I brought you here
to learn the essence of frost.
Do you know that
the elites in the middle stage
of Golden Class
have each grasped one,
at least one type
of spiritual power source.
The essence of frost
happens to be your source.
Also, the Spirit Diagram you saw
contains the ways of heaven and earth.
It's remarkable.
Pay extra attention in figuring it out.
If it's meant to be,
you might be able to comprehend
a divine spiritual skill of ancient times.
I will never forget the guidance
and help you two have given me.
Now,
what do you plan to do?
I'd like to go to Artefact Forging Sect.
To search for clues of your grandpa?
Yes.
The entrance to Artefact Forging Sect
is located at Mount Firetop.
Artefact Forging Sect is of
the Black Iron Class
[Artefact Forging Sect]
but it is not under the jurisdiction
of Profound Heaven Alliance
or Eight Extremes Temple.
It is an organization
build by armourers.
It is the sacred place every armourer
in Chilan Continent
wish to go to.
However, you are currently a wanted man.
It's best not to use your real identity.
When the day comes
that you've been accepted
as a core apprentice of the sect,
you can reveal your real name then.
The day I find success,
I'll be sure to repay your good deed.
Something is bothering you.
Best you leave it behind. Otherwise,
you won't be able to pass the sect's test.
[Profound Heaven Alliance]
The Soul Reaping Beast is dead?
Yes.
But there's one thing I don't understand.
In the past hundred years,
the Dark Nether Race has not used
the nether passageway.
Please give the order
to investigate this matter.
Si Yuan.
[Song Yu, Master of Profound Heaven Alliance]
[Song Si Yuan]
You'll handle this.
Understood.
Has the Dark Nether Race been defeated?
Yes.
Xingyun Pavilion played a big part
in the victory.
Things should be quiet for now.
Once Master Mo Hai finishes the seal,
peaceful days will be assured.
Since the task has been taken care of,
why did you not return sooner?
You've dallied for a whole three months.
It was a grave battle.
There were matters I had to attend to.
Xie Jing Xuan, while she was handling
matters at Purple Mist Sea,
she never took more than three days
to get everything big and small settled.
It's because the master of
Xingyun Pavilion was killed. Thus...
So a master of the Bluestone Class died.
What is the fuss about that?
What did you do at Icestone City?
Why?
Did you think you could hide from me?
Speak.
Why did you do it?
I couldn't let others know
that the Soul Reaping Beast did not die
by my hands.
That only proves your uselessness.
When the daughter fails,
the father shares the shame.
I did it for your sake.
Insolence!
Aside from that Gong Mu Lie
that does not exist,
do you even care about me, your father?
I think you've lost your mind
from reading too many books!
Father!
Master,
please calm down.
When I was your age,
I've already attained the late
Fulfilment Realm.
But you're still stuck
at Netherpassage Realm.
Useless!
[Tomb of Xingyun Pavilion
Deputy Chief Du Hai Tian]
You disappeared without word
for three months.
Where have you been?
Master.
You saw me once before
when you were little.
After so many years,
you're still able to recognise me.
A good memory.
That's good.
I heard after you've taken over
Xingyun Pavilion,
you haven't paid much attention
to us Du family.
The boldness of the young.
If the Du family wishes
to regain power of Xingyun Pavilion,
you'll have to show some real strength.
Palace of Hell is still pursuing
the culprit who killed your father.
Don't worry.
As long as we don't find Qin Lie,
I will not stop.
I thank you on behalf of my late father.
What are your future plans?
None to speak of.
Help me with a task
and Xingyun Pavilion
will remain with the Du family.
What task?
Your room is still available for you.
Stay the night.
Tomorrow, you'll get moving.
Where to?
In a few days,
Artefact Forging Sect will have
its annual recruitment.
[You're leaving,]
[aren't you?]
I wish to stay with you.
Only a wish?
My heart had turned to ash.
It was you who saved me
and tended to my wounds.
You even revived my heart.
You helped me forget
about what had happened.
No.
You've been thinking about how
your father had wanted to cripple you.
You kept thinking
but couldn't find an answer.
My father wanted to remove my ascension.
I was find with that.
I had betrayed him
and let him down.
Now he is dead.
I can no longer face him,
but I still have to face myself.
Do you understand?
I don't want to understand,
but I get it.
I really wish to stay,
but I can't.
This is the path I must take.
No need to explain.
I get it, I do.
You should go.
No matter how long it takes,
I will wait for you.
Promise me, Si Qi.
Don't secretly tag along this time, okay?
This time,
do not help me.
Let me do it myself.
I won't say goodbye this time.
But if we meet again,
I will not leave you then.
Young Master.
Come in.
What are you doing?
Young Master.
I've packed my things.
I'll go with you to Artefact Forging Sect
first thing in the morning.
No.
I am no longer the young master
of Xingyun Pavilion that is served
with a silver spoon.
You're free to go as you please.
Or,
you could stay here and wait for me.
Perhaps one day, Xingyun Pavilion
would get a new master.
Do you mean...
Tend to my father's grave for me.
Yes.
I will wait for your return.
Hello, everybody.
Ouyang Qing. Pang Feng.
What are you two doing here?
Yu Xin?
Isn't this Yi Yuan, the young master
of Purple Mist City?
You came too.
Yi Yuan?
Yi Yuan.
Shouldn't you be guarding the gate
of Purple Mist Sea with your father?
[Pang Feng, Ouyang Qing]
Why are you here?
Pang Feng.
Can you not be so rude?
It's fine, Qing Qing.
It's because I did a bad job
guarding the gate,
that's why my father got angry
and kicked me out.
I had nothing better to do,
so I came to try my luck.
Isn't this Young Master Du
of Xingyun Pavilion?
You mean the former young master.
Young Master Du isn't at
his father's wake
but came to join the crowd.
I heard his father was blasted
to smithereens.
No point guarding an empty grave.
Lian Rou!
Shut up.
She is the second senior
of Artefact Forging Sect.
Her name is not for you to call.
I'm sure everyone knows the rules.
I will not go into detail.
All applicants
must present a spirit stone
of the highest grade.
Whether or not you pass the test,
the spirit stone presented
will not be refunded.
If there are no questions,
please take turns to present
your spirit stones
and then follow me inside.
The Artefact Forging Sect
is the best artificer sect
in all of Chilan.
Apprentices have to undergo
strict training.
I'm Lian Rou.
I'm this year's examiner.
Before you join the sect,
you must know what artefact forging is.
As its name implies,
it is to create artefacts by infusing
spirit materials with spiritual power.
But the key component
to a spirit artefact is not the material,
but the Spirit Diagrams
of your personal attributes.
Line up.
This is the first stage of the test.
By using the stone pillars
as stepping stones,
you will pass the test when you
successfully get across to the peak.
Who is first?
Me!
Senior Lian, it's me.
So he's a student of fire and water.
The legendary Artefact Forging Sect exam
doesn't seem all that difficult.
As usual, rumours can't be trusted.
Let's go.
Did you not pay attention
to what I said just now?
Spirit artefacts are Spirit Diagrams.
If you can't even differentiate
basic Spirit Diagrams,
you can forget about joining the sect.
Spirit Diagrams?
So there are diagrams on the pillars.
If you step on a pillar
that doesn't match the diagram,
the pillar will break.
Next.
Who will it be?
That was a beautiful display.
And that's a beautiful mask. Who are you?
I'm Qin Bing.
I'm the young master
of Purple Mist City, Yi Yuan.
An artificer has to be pure and calm
in heart to create great works.
[Cliff of Serenity]
Before you lies Cliff of Serenity.
Place your hand on the stone wall.
Those without distracting thoughts
will be blessed with a path to get across.
If you fail,
you may return from where you came.
There is a maze behind the mountain.
Only those who remain unperturbed
and without mental baggage
will find the way out of the maze
and proceed to the next stage.
So far, there has only been one person
who managed to pass within one day.
Even the most talented
required up to three days.
There have been cases
where they used a month.
But,
we will not be waiting around for a month.
I will go ahead and wait
on the other side.
Hopefully, I'll see you all there.
Good luck.
I'm going to wait for you guys over there.
Make sure you come.
[Best you leave it behind. Otherwise,]
[you won't be able to pass
the sect's test.]
You've learned to play truant now?
I can't calm myself down.
Are you thinking about
what happened that day?
Thinking about the past
is meaningless.
I'm thinking about the future.
What about the future?
How to kill Gao Yu.
That's easy. One stab is all it takes.
But I've never killed anyone.
I worry I might waver.
Senior,
what should I do?
Ask master.
To become great,
one most not hesitate
at the crucial moment
and be resolute.
You wish to know
how to accomplish that?
Hold the cup of water.
What do you see?
I see
myself.
Is the person in the water you?
Yes.
The person in the water is you,
but also not you.
The past you, present you
and future you.
Which one of it is the real you?
It's you, but not you.
Because everything changes.
Humans are like duckweed chasing water.
One moment you're here,
another moment you're there.
There is no direction.
Only by finding your true self,
when you know who you are for sure,
you will know how to proceed.
I understand.
[This is the Eye of Frost.]
[With it,]
[you can go to any corner
of the vast world.]
[Ling Yu Juan]
[Ling Xiang Guan, Ling Cheng Yu]
Uncle Ling.
Elders.
I've come back to visit you.
Please forgive me
for not being able to stay.
There's something
that I must do out there.
[Ancestors' Memorial Tablet]
I will keep myself alive
so that I can come back
and see you all again.
Did you also just break out
from the cocoon?
It's me.
Qin Lie.
I knew you'd come to find me.
Yu Shi.
Have you been well?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to send Uncle Ling off.
The living
has to live with the loss.
But the pain will heal, right?
How have you been?
I'm good.
I went to the Artefact Forging Sect
as Qin Bing.
That's good.
But still, be careful.
You must not let others find out
who you are.
By the way,
have you seen Gao Yu?
No.
Why?
It's nothing.
I think...
he's gone back to Xingyun Pavilion.
Keep this note safe.
Open it and read it
only when you see Gao Yu.
Can I not read it now?
No,
and don't ask.
Trust me.
Okay.
Once I have news of Grandpa,
I will come to get you.
One more thing.
I asked you to marry me
but I didn't go through with it.
If there's a second chance,
will you still marry me?
Are promises necessary between us?
I swear with my life.
The Artefact Forging Sect
is a sect to learn forging skills.
Artefacts found in other sects
within Chilan
all came from artificers
that trained here.
This is why
powers of all shapes and sizes
have great respect for our sect.
The result this year
is the worst I've seen.
You four, identify yourselves.
Remember my name.
I'm Yi Yuan.
Stand back.
Pang Feng of Cloud Sky Mountain.
Ouyang Qing of Cangyu Assembly.
Du Shao Yang of the land far north.
This is the forge used by new apprentices.
Meaning this is where you'll train
for the year.
Looks like the last apprentice
made it in time.
Identify yourself.
Qin Bing.
Now, I'll explain to you
the rules of the sect.
Since when did you have rules?
Senior Lian is a soft-hearted enforcer.
You never punish those
that need to be punished.
You're the one needing rules.
But I'm different.
I'm cruel and ruthless.
I punish those who need to be punished,
as well as those who don't.
Greet Senior Tang.
Greetings, Senior Tang.
-Greetings, Senior Tang.
-Senior Tang.
You. Come with me.
Me?