ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
What did you expect?
For me to wait endlessly for the painting?
You must think it's your time
that you're wasting,
but it's actually mine.
And you're what? "Disappointed"?
What was that?
It's all on you.
That was my painting.
-I'm the painter.
-I know that.
No, you don't.
It's mine.
Until the moment I hand it over to you,
it's mine.
-Have you lost it?
-I've had it with you.
How dare you.
Who are you to decide that?
Who are you
to expect anything
or to be disappointed in me?
Who are you to treat me
like a vending machine?
Someone who can make or break you.
That was rhetorical.
I'm teaching you that I'm a human too.
You're teaching me?
And stop speaking causally to me.
Will doing so offend you less?
No, I'm telling you to watch your manners
despite the situation.
My bad.
How could I expect
a peasant like you to do that?
Is this how you always are?
You don't know me enough to say that.
Is this normal for the people
who live in your world?
You try to control the people you need
and throw away those you can't control.
Would I have been this way
had you done well?
Are you sure it isn't because
you hate to lose?
Is it fun to live like that?
What's there not to enjoy?
Isn't life about having fun?
I'm sure it is.
It'd be even more fun
if you ended up broke.
Without someone like me
who sees the value in your painting,
you'd be too broke to buy any supplies
and you'd be lost without a purpose.
You won't be able to paint in the end.
Fine.
If I can't have you,
I'd rather see you burn.
Don't let what I said get to you.
Don't lose that attitude of yours.
I had no idea you'd be this way.
All I wanted
was to talk to you about paintings,
that's all.
Ms. Seo,
you're the worst.
This is what you get when you expect more
from a business transaction.
I hope you learned from it.
You lame jerk.
EPISODE 10
Damn it!
Damn it.
Mr. Jeong, it's me.
Collect portfolios of artists
that aren't signed with any galleries.
And draw up a contract for purchase
with a deadline clearly stated.
Not having meals regularly
and only drinking juice
is a problem.
As if that's my only issue.
Yeong-hwa, just a second.
Hi. What can I do for you?
You're late on your rent.
Right.
Mr. Jeong, where are my jelly beans?
Did you hide them
so that I'd die of a low sugar?
I've rationed them
to stop you from eating them all at once.
I'll get them for you.
But they're more enjoyable that way.
FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND WON
Could you please return my 500,000 won…
I have to choose between pride and rent.
Pride or rent?
Why on earth did I put
that envelope in there?
Unbelievable.
WHEN DID YOU BECOME BROTHERS?
Seriously?
What the…
I HAVE SO MANY QUESTIONS
If you want to sue him, you can call me.
XW ENTERTAINMENT
Hello, is this Mr. Kim Myung-su?
You're Seo Tae-woong's manager, right?
No, I'm not calling to press charges.
Can you just tell him
to stop following me on social media?
Who the hell is this prick?
What is it? A prank call?
No, someone wanted me to tell you
to stop following him on social media.
And why are you telling me that?
Because I'm your manager.
Just who is it that you're following?
How should I know?
This is a weird neighborhood.
Wow, what an asshole.
Myung-su! How old is old enough?
Hold on. Mr. Old Enough?
So it really is him.
This is Dan-ah.
What's she doing here?
"Just when the view of the school
was getting boring…"
-Are you off to somewhere?
-Yes, I am.
We need to go back and pack.
Why should I when our schedule is over?
We leave for the countryside tomorrow
and I'm the leader.
How long is it for?
Only three nights.
You've got to be kidding me!
Head inside then.
-Thank you for today.
-But you did all the work.
I'll wire your wage into your account.
Be generous, please.
Sure.
-Head inside.
-Seon-gyeom.
You ran for Annam City Hall,
so how did you end
your contract with them?
My agency did.
All I did was send back
the paperwork I received
after signing them.
I'm clueless about this stuff.
What did your team say?
Your contract doesn't end for a while.
Right. Quite a long while, actually.
The coach said we should talk
once I've somewhat recovered,
so I'll be seeing him soon.
-Woo-sik.
-Yes?
Imagine yourself on a track.
We only have to make a decision
when we're at the starting line.
This is exactly why
I didn't tell you anything.
You're more daring
than people think, you know.
Right. Well, have a safe trip back.
I'll head inside.
GENERAL MANAGER JEONG JI-HYUN
Mr. Jeong, this is Ki Seon-gyeom.
When would Ms. Seo be free tomorrow?
Right, I'll be there on time.
Sure.
LEE YEONG-HWA
Hello?
No, I'm not busy.
Right now?
You called me to have a drink?
No, because I'm depressed.
How's this place?
Nice, right?
It's cold.
I love it here.
The night view is incredible
and the rent is low
considering what it offers.
However, it'll be my last month here.
I wasn't able to pay my rent, you see.
If I ask my mom for the money,
she'll tell me to move into
a dorm instead.
I can't think of a way
to quickly come up with 300,000 won.
And it's not like
I can get a roommate this fast.
Oh, these? I bought them a while back.
Did you call me here to ask me for money?
Seon-gyeom, could you let me
serve you for a month?
Give me that chance
and I'll make sure you live like a King.
-For free?
-Well,
just pay the rest of my rent
and everything else will be for free.
For free!
What's your account number?
You'll just lend me the money?
This easily?
Yes.
Seon-gyeom, my gosh.
Thank you so much.
Account number.
All my friends were in a tight spot too,
so I had no one else to turn to.
But you've turned down the suggestion
for us to live together so fast.
Has Ms. Seo Dan-ah
ever walked all over you before?
Not in a way that I felt
like she was abusing her power.
Why did I think that way then?
-Am I that lame?
-I'm home.
Are you home?
Hey, you're home. I'm here.
-You're not.
-I am.
We should go grocery shopping.
We're out of food,
so what have you been eating?
Well…
Get up.
-We're going out.
-For a walk?
I'll take you out for a walk
and let you help me cook.
You're the best.
Get me the sesame seeds.
Right, sure.
It's not like you to be out of a job.
But I just got back to Seoul.
That was just part time.
I'm talking about your day job.
I was offered a project,
but I turned it down
since it involved transcription.
I'd kill for a horror film, you know.
Even if it was written by Aaron Sorkin?
Must you be that cruel?
What's that though? Honey?
He left it behind.
For us to enjoy?
-So the spring onions--
-I'll chop them.
Gosh.
May,
I feel like such a loser.
I never once truly told him
how I felt about him
all because I was too scared
of being rejected
and never seeing him again,
but I was waiting for him
to say it first nonetheless.
It's too bland.
I thought about all the issues we faced
and they'd all be resolved
if we were dating.
Everything would be natural then,
but I was too scared of losing him
-that I didn't dare to make a move.
-See how it tastes.
No.
-Is it salty?
-No, it's delicious.
May, come on. Hear me out, will you?
I'm dead serious!
Then why are you saying it to me
and not to him?
Stop confessing to me and call him.
He left his honey behind.
That could be your excuse.
Gosh, why didn't I think of that?
Goodness.
Should I just go and tell him how I feel?
I, you… We'll go steady as of today.
-What if he rejects me?
-If he does, will you back off?
-No, I'll fight to the death.
-You shouldn't do that.
Let me see.
Tell him how you feel.
How else can you move forward?
Right.
So…
Drink that,
and we'll go steady.
What if I don't?
Then it's over between us…
forever.
Why is your scenario so pessimistic?
That must've been
my subconscious speaking.
Let me try again.
You're saying you like me?
After all this time?
After…
the way you hurt me?
Why on earth are you crying?
You're putting me in a spot.
Why did you do this to me?
Tell me.
Just why?
Why are you acting like
I did something so cruel?
You hurt me too, you know.
Why must it always be
at night and at a bar?
Can't you say it sober?
You're right.
We should meet in broad daylight
when we're both sober.
Is there a guarantee
that he'll come if I ask him to meet me?
How should I know?
He might not want the honey back.
Hi. I'm the guy who wrote about
the girl I've been flirting with.
If you don't know the full story,
go and read the previous post.
I'll just skip the honorifics.
You know how I moved in with her
for a while?
She wants to meet up
to return a jar of honey.
I think she's going to ask me out.
What should I wear?
I want to make her lose interest.
But then again, I won't be going.
Hey!
You've gone too far.
Cut it out and just call him.
I don't think I can.
Do it. I'm going to make kkakdugi,
so slice them into cubes.
Got it.
Hello? Hey, why did you leave
your jar of honey?
You took everything else.
Let's meet so I can give it back.
It seemed important.
What do I do?
My hands stink of green onions.
What should I do?
-Wash your hands with toothpaste.
-Then they'll smell like toothpaste.
Then slice the green onions
for the kkakdugi.
Okay.
Who was that? Was it voice phishing?
She wants to meet.
Right now? Who was it?
Was it voice phishing?
It was Ms. Oh.
But she didn't say when.
-Then when?
-I don't know.
What a weird conversation.
Just call her back, Seon-gyeom.
You guys are close enough.
Well, are we?
How would I know?
May! He's calling me!
Is he rejecting me already?
I didn't even do anything.
He's probably calling to ask when to meet.
You just hung up
after asking him to meet up.
Right. I hope so.
You're rarely sane these days.
I'm 29. I'm at that age.
You're at the peak of insanity.
Thanks for reminding me.
Gosh, you're making me go nuts.
Just answer the phone
and slice the rest of the radish.
Must I repeat myself?
I don't think I can pick up.
What?
KI SEON-GYEOM
He hung up.
Let's meet the day after tomorrow
at the park at 2:00 p.m.
If you read this, please reply with a dot.
She texted you instead?
Gosh, I didn't take Mi-joo
to be such a wuss.
Seon-gyeom, I like Mi-joo a lot.
I mustered up my courage
to side with you instead.
"Courage"?
Did I make her do it again?
Why? Do you need courage?
Should I give you some of mine?
I won't be needing it for a while.
No, it's okay.
In the past, I would have envied you
for being able to fix a date with someone.
But now that it's over,
I'm not that jealous.
But, hey.
Is something up between the two of you?
It's mostly me.
Hey, Mr. Mostly Me.
What's the problem, mostly?
I'm boring.
I think you're funny.
I don't know how to share
or what to give to people.
Are you sure?
But what's that?
What does it look like to you?
Art.
Okay.
Then art it is.
Just like that?
People need to think it's art
in order for it to become one.
By the way,
you should speak to me casually.
I know. I already am.
So you really don't share.
Seon-gyeom.
You came early.
Ms. Seo is still in a meeting.
I'll wait.
Seon-gyeom, what brings you here?
I came to meet Ms. Seo.
Will you take a look at this?
We got the sample pamphlets
for the charity run.
The event that Ms. Seo holds every year?
Which one of these look better?
I'll consider your vote.
I don't know much about art.
Which means you'll just simply choose
the better one.
This one.
You really have a good eye.
Mr. Jeong, take a look at the samples
for the charity run.
-Which one do you prefer?
-I will choose
the one that Ms. Seo chooses.
Okay then.
Why are you meeting Ms. Seo?
Did she call you here?
But your contract with her has ended.
I called and asked for a meeting.
There's a natural gift you have,
but I bet you don't know what it is.
You motivate people.
When you said I have a gift earlier,
did you really mean it?
What?
Oh, that?
I said that because you also motivated me
while you merely
focused on your career for two years.
I didn't know that.
Now that you do,
you should put your gift to good use.
Why does he want to meet
at a comic book store? We're not kids.
Apparently,
Chairman Seo likes comic books.
I guess beggars can't be choosers.
He's here.
You came early.
Yes.
It's my first time at a comic book store,
so I was looking around.
Why don't you recommend me a book?
I'm not quite sure
if you'll enjoy the stuff I read.
Start with the famous ones.
They're over there in that corner.
What kind of stuff do you read?
This guy is the problem.
He causes trouble everywhere he goes.
He has four daughters?
Gosh, I envy him.
Come to think of it,
you haven't gotten back to me
about your daughter's marriage.
I've actually been wondering
what your son is doing these days.
He's taking a break.
It's important for athletes
to get some time off.
"A break."
My daughter's always busy with work.
But Seon-gyeom is taking a break?
This is why I don't push her
to get married
although it's what I want.
She works at both the head office
and the agency.
And a yearly charity event.
She even runs herself to donate money.
I should tell my son to attend the event
with his track and field team.
Is he the coach?
There's a team he's been coaching
for years as a charity.
I told him he should coach the team
to bring up national athletes.
I can easily help them become
a local team.
I really envy that about you.
Both your kids are honorable.
My goodness, I envy you
for having two kids
that are both smart and successful.
The kimchi fried rice is here.
Where do you want it?
It's his.
Here.
-Enjoy.
-When will the ramyeon be ready?
Seon-gyeom,
you look like you're doing great.
You know I only have 20 minutes, right?
That's fine with me.
Should I register your fingerprint again?
I heard you complained.
I complained?
Isn't that why you're here?
I finally get why people always thought
I was arrogant.
You finally got that?
Thank you.
I think I finally get what it was
that you did for me
while I was busy pulling myself together.
Back then, I wasn't able to realize
that I was getting a lot of support.
That's our job, and we're good at it.
Is that what you came here to tell me?
I just felt a little frustrated.
And I wanted to talk.
You can be a little frustrating.
It's about Woo-sik.
-Who's that?
-The guy you helped.
Oh, him.
I heard he left the training center.
That means he's no longer
a national athlete.
Is he back to his old team?
They will either advise him
to transfer teams
or just let him stay out of loyalty.
What do you think?
He's a hot potato. A nuisance.
It's too burdensome.
He definitely got on the coach's bad side
since the coach would have been held
responsible for the mess.
They do hate being
at the center of controversy.
Although he was a whistleblower,
they can't kick him out
because he was the victim.
Plus, they have an image to keep up.
Do you think he can at least
transfer to a different team?
Obviously not. Whoever takes him in
will just do so to keep him on the bench.
Don't agencies
also help athletes find a new team?
Don't tell me you think other athletes
deserve to be treated just like you.
Why not?
I get that you're fair, but think again.
Do you really not know?
Is it because of my background?
Not everyone has what you have.
Your family is famous, you're handsome,
and you always got
the second-highest record.
But what about Woo-sik?
What does he have to offer?
His talent, of course.
In the end, the team just wants
the best record and a medal.
It's easy to say, but he's injured.
Can you guarantee
that he'll fully recover?
He might even be better than before.
He endured the rocky patch,
and now he can fully focus on training.
How about a different sport?
If he's good at running marathons,
Seomyung could sponsor him.
You want him to run marathons?
So the cameras can catch him
running with your company's logo?
That's what sponsorships are.
A sprint is only 100m long.
Yes.
It only lasts ten seconds.
But you sometimes even get eliminated
just for starting too early by accident.
What a ridiculous sport.
Who makes money from that?
The athletes should.
I was right.
You care more about the athletes than me.
How do you think we can convince
another team to take him in?
A victim who got kicked out.
You love being a good person.
You'd be a strategic philanthropist
who helped a hopeless athlete
get a second chance.
I like how it sounds.
But what's the point in doing this
when he was willing to risk it all?
Isn't this what you want?
Yes, it is.
That's why I came here.
It's not an easy topic.
Then let's be careful about it.
Thanks for the talk.
I'll see you then.
Are you upset?
No.
It's not just you and me.
Seon-gyeom will also be there
with the kids from that school.
The one he volunteers at.
Stop giving him such a hard time.
It's a charity event.
Can't you just go without me?
No, I can't.
What's the point of going there
without you?
Then don't go.
The charity is being held by Dan-ah.
Can't you just make time?
I don't want to make time
because I feel like it's for you.
Ji-woo, you need to start shooting now.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Let's hang up. I need to work.
Gosh, when in the world
is your acting going to get better?
Ji-woo, it hurts my conscience
every time I do this.
From now on,
forget that you have a conscience.
Gosh, what kind of nonsense
is he up to this time?
Your husband?
He's trying hard to set our son up
with a girl from a rich family.
Is your son no longer dating Tae-ri?
Is he dating Tae-ri?
Why would she date him?
ART, PHYSICAL EDUCATION
SCHOOL LIBRARY
-Here.
-Okay.
Let me check if there are any free seats.
Here. Please write down
what you're going to watch.
JERRY MAGUIRE
Tomorrow's the big day.
I wanted to give this back to you.
Right.
Yesterday, I watched Jerry Maguire.
Was it fun?
No, it wasn't.
I see.
But it made me feel warm inside.
I thought about why,
and it was because that's how I felt
when you described it to me.
How was the movie?
The male lead
couldn't seem to stand
his failures in life.
He even ended up hurting the only person
who stayed by his side.
And he realized that person's value
once it was too late.
But it kind of reminded me of myself.
I was scared that things might end
between us
the closer we got.
Your affection for me
gives me meaning and value.
But I wasn't sure
if you had feelings for me
the same way I do about you.
I wonder if you also want to hold my hand,
hug me
and kiss me.
I wasn't quite sure of that.
Because I do.
Please don't hate me.
-You're jumping from subject to subject.
-Did I?
I'm sorry.
That's my answer.
Then can I keep doing it?
What? Doing me a favor and liking me?
No, just liking you.
Will you stop if I say no?
Will you?
No.
I want to keep going.
That's what I want.
Then go ahead. You have my permission.
Really?
Thank goodness.
To be honest, I was really worried
that I might have hurt you that day.
I don't want to be
your one-month girlfriend.
But I can't do it alone, so help me out.
You help people for no reason.
Now you'll do even better
that you have a reason.
I'll try my best.
Do you think you'll be hungry soon?
Yes, I should be.
Right.
Don't you think it's ready now?
Probably.
The weather's nice today.
It is.
How have you been doing recently?
I've been doing well.
Me too.
I met with Ms. Seo and Woo-sik.
It seemed like he was preparing
for a civil service exam.
How did you know?
I met with him as well.
Is he really going to do it?
It won't be easy.
He's probably undecided.
I submitted my resignation letter,
but he was just about to be
forced into resignation.
You make it sound like
he has an office job.
He does.
It's like that when you're in a team.
You're right.
I think being a professional is hard
no matter what line of work it is.
I thought I'd be able to watch
all my favorite movies
and make money as a translator.
But now that I am one,
I've realized that some movies
can be boring as well.
I've never been entertained
by a movie before.
What's fortunate is that I began this job
because I enjoyed it.
That's one good thing.
And that I still enjoy this job.
But there are days when things
just don't go my way.
I have to look up words
that I already know
or listen to the same line repeatedly
and still not get it.
I must have been prejudiced.
You looked happy when working.
I feel the same way.
Athletes look passionate,
so I thought that was always the case.
As if they were solely motivated
by their dreams.
That's not the case most of the time.
They get paid to participate
in tournaments,
so they just participate
for the money and not run.
I thought you didn't run that time
due to the given circumstances.
Are you allowed to not run at all?
The winner is already decided.
So during the preliminaries,
you don't run if it doesn't look hopeful.
That moment when you refused to run
seemed like a scene from a movie.
Doesn't this remind you of Yeong-hwa?
No, not at all.
It doesn't remind me of him.
Who is Lee Yeong-hwa?
I don't even remember him.
Where are you headed? I'll drop you off.
No, let me drop you off
wherever it may be.
-No, let me.
-No. Let's go.
This is me.
Did you move to our neighborhood?
-You really are full of surprises.
-It's Yeong-hwa's house.
This time, it's his house?
-Are you a nomad or something?
-No, I'm not.
It's nice that you live nearby.
Is it?
Of course. Since you live nearby,
we'll be closer. And…
You get it, right?
Then should I do that?
Thank you for walking me home.
You should go.
Come to think of it,
I've never watched you go home safely.
-And I feel terrible about that.
-Don't be.
I'll treat you well.
I have so much fun when I'm with you.
-You should go.
-Okay.
You should let me know when
you're going to bed or doing something.
Bye.
I'll treat you well.
I'm going to spoil you.
Are we going to speak casually now?
-Should we?
-No.
Okay.
We argue enough as it is.
I can't imagine how we'll be
if we started doing that.
I'm really leaving now.
You better text me.
Bye.
Love is crazy. Romance is crazy.
My homework's due tomorrow.
-Hey, why are you here?
-I'm so worried.
Why are you carrying this around?
I'm not taking it back.
I can't help but worry.
About this?
It's better for me to do so,
so why did she offer
to walk me home instead?
Does she even know how far I live?
If she walked me back,
she'd have to take a cab.
Then I'd be worried about that
since it could be dangerous to ride a cab.
Thank goodness I knew about your house.
Why are you so worried about?
You've never been this chatty.
Of course, I'm worried. It's so cold.
Are you still up for living together
for a month?
I thought you refused
after wiring me the money.
Let's say I paid the monthly rent
in advance.
That does lessen the burden,
but why out of the blue?
It'll be more convenient to walk me home,
and I could do the same.
Okay, it's solved then.
This is it.
I'm so lost.
But okay.
-There are no muggers here, right?
-No.
Why does it get dark so soon?
So about that gun…
Is it even worth owning when it's fake?
Since I've found the real deal,
you'll stay here for the time being.
Why am I not that excited?
Do you not like it?
No.
It's not the photo. I think it's just me.
No. I'll be seeing Eun-bi soon.
I want to be happy and excited.
This is so exciting!
KI SEON-GYEOM
Ta-da. Didn't I pick the best one?
I wanted to show you this.
You're making me hate you
even though I've never liked you.
Where are you looking? Look here.
Why have you become so thin?
-Are you even eating properly?
-Don't act like you care.
I should take care of my athlete.
How could you discard him
as soon as I signed up? Is he an object?
-And what? "My athlete"?
-He didn't care.
He never cares about himself,
so I should get mad…
Did he see that himself?
I didn't know such siblings existed.
Are all biological siblings like that?
I didn't know someone could be sarcastic
in this kind of way.
I'm serious.
I'm fascinated by how different we are.
Seon-gyeom and I are kindhearted.
You're just downright obnoxious.
If I was obnoxious,
do you think I'd host charity runs
every year?
I'm a benevolent person.
It's not charity if you're doing it
to look good.
Why don't you try being
benevolent as well?
It's a half-marathon.
I don't have time to run 21km.
We haven't scheduled
all the advertisements yet.
I'm sick of being the best.
I wanted to retire and relax,
but I'm too busy.
You're not retiring.
Our journey has just begun.
Being Seon-gyeom's shield for a bit longer
won't kill me.
I'm considering being at the top
for a bit longer.
He was my shield for a long time too.
If you're going to be a shield,
you should at least look pretty.
You've done worse before.
Don't look at them.
Pick the clothes you want
from the new batch.
Now I know what you've been wearing
in the past.
I hate you so much.
It's okay. I'll like you instead.
What was that?
It's all on you.
Damn it.
I was happy to see Eun-bi's photo,
so why am I thinking about him again?
No.
I had a good day.
I was in a great mood today.
Right, it was a good day.
Damn it. No.
I faked it. I forced myself to be happy.
It was all because of you.
Ma'am, are you sure you want to go there?
Perhaps, you should go
to your regular bar.
Reading won't help me sleep tonight.
Books can't talk.
Did you book an appointment
with the owner?
I'm just the deliveryman.
May, the food just arrived.
I'll eat alone.
Don't you smell chicken?
Why do you have that? Just give it to me.
I'll be having my first chicken tonight.
Give it to me, and buy your own.
How did you know where I live?
And what's with that outfit?
I wouldn't go out like that ever.
Shouldn't you invite me in?
But you're not my guest.
Just take that with you.
I'm already irritated.
Please don't make it worse.
I see. Cheer up. You can do it.
I've never been rejected like this.
You left me hanging out here.
-You're very--
-Charming?
I almost became special to you.
It's cute.
Where's Seon-gyeom?
Why are you here?
Because I want to drink.
Do you not have any friends?
Is this your way of making friends?
Were you drinking by yourself? Bad news?
-Good news.
-Then you should have whiskey.
I don't see the point
in drinking expensive liquor.
It's worth its price.
Do you have an on-the-rock glass?
No. Use this.
Do you at least have a transparent one?
It doesn't have to be glass.
Plastic's fine.
Next time, bring your own.
So there's a next time?
You do know you sound
like a psychopath, right?
Someone told me
that I have no sense of empathy.
I agree. It's more convenient.
Why do I need to empathize?
Because you're concerned and worried.
Is something wrong with you?
You also use your brain for empathy.
There must be a loose screw up there.
That's a bit harsh.
God, I'm seriously hurt.
I'm a very kindhearted person,
so why do people--
That's not what I meant, you sociopath.
Exactly. Many people have said that to me,
so why does it bother me this time?
That's not it either.
This is so frustrating.
Can you please stop talking
out of context?
Do you want this?
I've never tried soju.
I'm picky about what I eat and drink.
Never mind, then.
Give me a glass. Let me try it.
It should be fine If you lasted this long
without being sick.
I get sick every time.
First glass, bottoms up.
Why did you get rid of Seon-gyeom?
I didn't. He left because it was time.
Is that why you came?
I told you I'm here to drink.
There must be a reason why
you came all the way here.
I thought you would know.
-What do you mean?
-Because you're a peasant like him.
Get out.
-This is savory.
-I said, get out.
Hear me out.
He…
ruined my painting and blamed it on me
when I clearly saw him do it.
He must have been furious.
-Stop incriminating yourself with words.
-How's that even possible?
You'd be shocked to hear
what words can do.
Let's forget about what's already ruined.
Imagine that you've entrusted something
to me.
When would you be the most upset
to get it back?
This Again?
Why do you want him to be upset?
-Because he ruined my mood.
-Is it a revenge?
-No. That'd be admitting that I care.
-And you obviously are.
Who is it?
I'm going to bed. Goodnight.
What? He actually did it.
He's so adorable.
Let's see. "Goodnight"?
-I really…
-That sounds insincere.
-I really liked him.
-"Sweet dreams…"
No.
-You don't dream when you sleep well.
-It's not everyday
that I open myself up like that.
"Have a good day
-tomorrow."
-So when I like something,
-I like it forever.
-Send.
Just like soccer.
"Have a good day tomorrow."
It's nice and natural.
I still regret it to this day.
I should've forgotten about him by now,
but I'm obsessed.
-What should I do?
-You should go home.
My god.
She's unbelievable.
You should go home. Excuse me.
Damn it.
Come on.
Gosh.
She's pretty even when she sleeps.
What?
When did she leave?
The dining table feels empty
without Myeong-min.
It's nice and quiet.
Is work going well?
-Yes.
-What about the charity event?
Of course. I'm in charge.
You were never interested in that.
Are you going to run again?
It'd look insincere
if the host didn't participate.
Take good care of your health.
Don't overdo it.
I'm worried about you.
Don't treat me like a patient.
I haven't been sick in ages.
God.
If I ever drink soju again…
I'll drink just a little from now on.
It's honey water.
You looked like you needed it.
If it's from that, just throw it all away.
Have you gathered the portfolios yet?
I'll finish up by this week.
Hurry up and look into it.
There are probably many others like him.
No, there have to be.
I should make the next person
sign a contract to tie them down.
Should I get it notarized?
Ms. Seo.
Didn't you need Lee Yeong-hwa
because Director Seo
replaced a painting that was yours?
-That's right.
-However,
you now seem to be looking for a painting
because of him.
Then should I look for someone
who has a similar style?
No.
Return this to him.
Tell him I don't need compensation
and to never bother me again.
Yes, ma'am.
How did you know I'd be here?
Wait. Even if you knew,
you shouldn't have come.
I came here myself
because I couldn't reach you.
That's right. I blocked your number.
Ms. Seo wanted to return this.
She doesn't need compensation
and doesn't want you to bother her again.
Don't you have her personal number?
Please erase it in front of me.
She even sent you to cut ties with me.
This wouldn't have happened
had you not drew anything.
Would you have done that
if she acknowledged your talent?
Fine. I don't need her number
when I can't even reach her.
Look. This is her.
Delete. Done, right? It's over.
Don't bother me again.
What a way to ruin my day.
Earning money isn't easy.
What brings you here?
I thought I'd pay a visit.
-Where's Ms. Seo?
-She's swimming.
She doesn't like to be bothered
when swimming.
I was free today, so I came to say hi.
Eun-bi joined your agency.
I wasn't there for her back then
so I wanted to start
showing her some support.
-Is it too late for that?
-What if it is?
They're always going to be kids to us.
You're right.
I don't have time to wait.
I got to see you, so I'll get going.
Have some snacks.
One minute.
Are you discarding it?
I'm not trying to offend you at all.
Why would I be offended?
If Seon-gyeom accepted it,
I have nothing to say.
It came out nicely.
He visited recently
and seemed to be doing well.
Yes. I met with him as well.
He seemed fine on the outside,
but who knows how he is inside?
You two must be bonding more.
I'm thinking about acting like a mom
every now and then. Just like today.
YEONCHEON CITY HALL TRACK AND FIELD TEAM
Sit down.
I'll try to prevent you
from paying a penalty, so pick one.
You just need to sign
the contract termination form.
If you've found a new team,
fill in that transfer agreement.
Once you hand it to me,
I just need to sign it.
TRANSFER AGREEMENT
Would anyone accept me?
Hey, do you have to find a team?
I know that money is on the line,
but you could train alone.
Why would I continue doing this
if I'm going to do it alone?
Not if you enjoy it.
Was there ever an athlete in this country
who ran just because they liked it
and were good at it?
You should have kept quiet then.
You're good at that.
Should I have?
Had I done that,
I wouldn't have been here today.
Are you threatening me?
I hate to see your talent
go to waste at such a young age.
What does being young mean?
It means you can always start afresh.
But whenever I see you again,
I'll be reminded of my mistake.
Have you ever considered
how tormenting that would be for me?
I'm sorry.
It's all in the past.
You should let it go.
Woo-sik.
Shouldn't you start afresh?
Did you meet with the coach?
Grandma, should I become a civil servant?
Sure.
Or since I'm handsome,
should I become a celebrity?
Sure.
You should live a long and healthy life,
okay?
I've already lived long enough. It's okay.
You should take care
of your health instead.
CONCEPT-BASED SPORT SOCIOLOGY
SPORTOLOGY AND BODY
Good morning.
What are you up to? Have you eaten?
Come and eat whenever you're hungry.
I will.
Seon-gyeom, I've submitted the documents.
He allowed me to terminate the contract
without paying the penalty.
Thank you for hearing me out.
Don't worry about me. Let's meet again.
Woo-sik.
Kim Woo-sik.
-Are you okay?
-Seon-gyeom.
Let's talk next time. Not today.
Kim Woo-sik.
Please. Please don't come near me.
I…
I don't want to be swayed.
So don't come.
I had already decided
to quit running.
I was able to see you…
because I stuck with my decision.
That was why…
That was why it was possible.
How does it feel to run again?
It really…
hurts. It's difficult.
I don't think I can do it.
To be honest,
the track isn't the only problem.
There are many issues.
I'm not just an injured athlete.
I'm hurting inside as well.
I'm the problem.
For ten years…
I've dedicated ten years to this.
What if my record isn't as good as before?
What should I do then?
What should I do?
That terrifies me the most.
I'm scared.
Why are you saying that here?
Save it for the track.
Try it first. If it doesn't work,
you can give up then.
Woo-sik.
I'll become that person.
I'll be the one to help you
if you put your trust in me.
But for today,
let's get you back on your feet.
Why does he keep smiling like that?
He'll be the death of me.
Do you like me?
Does that change anything?
It's already over for me.
It's 21km!
What? You said you wanted to run with me.
I said I wanted to participate with you.
You looked great.
It was a heartwarming moment.
It's adorable. My gosh.
-Were you thinking about me?
-Do you want to hold hands?
Why do you keep talking to me
about this stuff?
Stop already.
It makes me feel like we're really close.
What's this?
Try painting, kid.
Seriously?
Did you take classes to be this arrogant?
I must be naturally gifted.
Forget the painting.
I need to watch you paint.
-Don't disappear.
-I won't.
I'll be here forever.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs