ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Call out to someone
who can be here for you from now on
whenever you're sick or struggling.
Ki Seon-gyeom.
Ki Seon…
Gyeom.
Why is your name so hard to pronounce?
I called your name.
You need to hold my hand.
EPISODE 9
SAMIL PHARMACY
Gosh, I'm a mess.
So this is how he saw me yesterday?
We haven't met in a while.
My goodness.
Don't you think you should at least
look half-decent, Mi-joo?
How beautiful.
We slept really well yesterday
thanks to you.
-We really had a good night's sleep.
-I'm glad.
I wasn't sure about this yesterday,
but I think it's him.
Isn't he Yook Ji-woo's son?
-What if he is?
-Then it'd be cool.
Who cares whose son he is?
He just needs to eat and drive well.
That's all that matters.
-Mi-joo, you're here.
-Hey.
I have to say, it's nice to see you.
You should be.
I'm the closest person to you here.
I'm surprised you said that though.
I'm proud.
Aren't I too old for you to be
proud of me?
Shall we eat breakfast together?
-I'm a morning person.
-Sure.
How do you feel?
You do look a lot better
than you did yesterday.
I probably look prettier than yesterday
since I'm wearing makeup.
You were just as pretty yesterday.
You must love japchae.
You brought a big pile.
I used to love our housekeeper's
japchae when I was young.
I see.
By the way, why did you bring
so many different menus all at once?
Because I don't want to go twice.
Then why didn't you bring any japchae?
Don't you like it?
I got really sick
after eating it as a kid,
and I've never had it since.
You should make sure you're full.
You need to work today.
It turns out I came
without knowing much about the job.
I'm sorry. We were in a real rush.
Did Hui-jin fill you up on the details?
What if they kidnapped you
and put you on a fishing boat?
I came because you were here.
Were you angry I called?
Not at all.
This time, I didn't miss my chance.
-To do what?
-To treat you well.
Isn't this my chance?
Treat me well, then.
We're currently shooting
an American indie film.
Their goal is to enter
the Sundance Film Festival.
Half of all the staff are Korean.
The director is Korean American
and so are most of the actors.
And if you look over there,
he's James, our main lead.
He's a pretty famous SAG actor.
But you wouldn't know.
Of course not.
Here they come.
So, did you enjoy your meal?
Yes, very much though. Thank you.
He's James, the man I told you about.
James, this is Seon-gyeom,
your boyfriend's personal driver.
Hello. Ki Seon-gyeom.
It's very nice to meet you.
Mi-joo, you're playing
a very dangerous game here.
What?
You're cute. He's hot.
He doesn't like drive stick,
does he?
-You don't have to answer that.
-Okay, see you in a bit.
James might ask for a ride as well.
Should I be careful of anything?
Just make sure
the navigation volume is off.
They wanted a non-English speaking driver
so they could talk comfortably.
So they won't talk to you or anything.
Don't be intimidated
because you don't speak English.
And don't get scared.
But why am I so worried?
It's like you're a little kid.
I'm a grown man. You don't need to worry.
No, you're not. Let's go.
Do I look that childish to you?
Was everything okay?
Everything was wonderful.
He's a excellent driver.
Do you like him?
We'll prepare for scene 26 first.
Wardrobe and makeup is there
-And, we'll see you in a bit.
-Okay, thank you very much.
-See you. Thank you.
-Let's set-up.
He says you're a great driver.
I'm not a horrible driver like someone.
-Whatever.
-What do I need to do now?
You need to wait for the actor to finish.
The main job of a driver is to wait.
I'll be off now.
Scene four, take two.
Action.
Seon-gyeom, here you go.
-Are you doing okay?
-Yes.
-Were you about to draw?
-I bought it so I could use it as a diary,
but I don't know what to write.
People normally write diaries
at the end of the day.
I'm sure there's not much to write
since it's early in the morning.
Then I'll write about
what happened yesterday.
Forget that. Give me your cell phone.
Unlock it for me.
Unlock it.
There are apps where you can watch movies.
I'll be nice and let you use my ID.
Watching a movie is
the best way to kill time. Here.
I'll leave you alone. Go ahead and enjoy.
-You're leaving again?
-Yes.
I came during my break
just in case you might be bored.
I'll come back if I have time again.
Anyway, enjoy.
I came to an unfamiliar place.
Mi-joo was sick.
Thank you.
You had two cups of kiwi juice.
Are you constipated?
Whatever.
You drew this for 50 minutes?
You told me to draw if I didn't get it.
You didn't solve anything else.
You always tell me
to move onto the stuff I know.
Then I'll give you more time.
Try solving what you didn't solve.
-What's with your face?
-What about it? Am I too handsome?
-Are you like this at school?
-Being handsome?
-You must have a lot of schoolwork.
-What happened to your face?
I sparred a couple of days ago.
I sparred with someone
above my weight class.
I don't get why
I'm still a college student.
I'm so busy with exams and assignments.
It'll get a lot worse once you graduate.
I guess not all college students
drink and have fun.
No, not exactly.
Why did I enroll in a film class?
-"What is a synopsis?"
-You went over your head.
Don't ask me. Only the old me would know.
He probably thought he could do anything.
I'll review your synopsis for free.
What was the genre? A thriller?
-I changed it to romance.
-How far are you done?
You're only asking
because you don't want to study.
-Listen carefully.
-Okay.
It's pouring cats and dogs.
The male lead, who's being chased,
is walking with an umbrella.
Why is he being chased if it's a romance?
And where did he get the umbrella?
Is he allowed to steal like that?
Listen. Just as he's about to leave,
someone suddenly jumps underneath
the umbrella like a scene from a movie.
And I'm guessing she slowly looks up.
How did you know that?
Are you allowed to plagiarize?
It's from Temptation of Wolves.
What?
That story already exists?
Gosh, no wonder it felt really familiar.
I have to start all over again.
You don't know the agony of writing.
You're the one who doesn't know.
Is plagiarism the only thing
you're good at?
Last time, you copied The Wailing.
Gosh, I should be paid
for giving you advice.
But I'm paying you to teach me.
It's not your money. Break time is over.
I'll give you time to solve it.
Do you really not like anyone?
Just solve the question.
Are you finally going to experience
your first love?
-How would you define "first love"?
-You can't define love.
Then I guess I won't either.
Every girl will be my first.
-What a scumbag.
-What do you want from me?
Exactly.
I mean, what about Ye-jun?
-What about him?
-I thought you guys were dating.
-Do you still watch that kind of stuff?
-What?
No, I don't.
But you keep looking at guys that way.
Just solve the question.
Next time, we're going to focus on class,
so brace yourself.
No, we won't.
Do you want pocket money?
-You never refuse.
-Thank you.
Tell Mom I'm gone. See you.
Seriously? Only 10,000 won?
Apparently, she's the best fighter
at the gym. Do you think it's a lie?
But it hasn't even been two years
since she started boxing again.
Exactly. It might be a lie.
-Are you heading home?
-Yes, I have to paint.
-What about you?
-Me?
I'm drinking tonight.
I'll kill time at your place before I go.
Go home and kill time there.
That's for when it's dark outside.
Now isn't the time to go home.
Seon-gyeom. Here.
-What are you doing?
-It's so hard to write a diary.
Why is it so hard? It's not homework.
I don't think I'm good at writing.
It's not like you'll show anyone.
It's for yourself.
A diary is something private.
People write it for themselves.
-Who are you trying to impress?
-You're right.
So don't try to make it sound fancy
or eloquent.
Just be honest, okay?
Is that the secret to writing a diary?
It's no secret. It's just basic knowledge.
And I gave you my ID
so you could watch a movie.
But why are you struggling with that?
There were so many,
so I couldn't decide what to watch.
You have a point. Here. Take this.
I'll come back later.
I learned how to write a diary.
It feels nice.
I LEARNED HOW TO WRITE A DIARY
IT FEELS NICE
I met James and Bruno.
It's hard to talk to them.
I was frustrated.
I came to an unfamiliar place.
Mi-joo was sick.
I CAME TO AN UNFAMILIAR PLACE
MI-JOO WAS SICK
I was scared.
What are you painting? Is it for school?
It's for a client.
Ye-jun.
What kind of painting do you think
deserves to be hung in a gallery?
The Last Supper, Mona Lisa,
The Starry Night,
and Munch?
You mean, The Scream of Nature.
Munch is the artist's name.
Maybe she asked me for too much.
You never know
when you might come across
a great opportunity.
But the more I think about it,
the more confused I get.
I don't know what it is I want to paint,
when it will end, and if it ever will.
How do you know when it will end?
-Can you tell?
-When it's almost done.
When is that?
Sometimes, I never get that feeling
no matter how hard I try.
But sometimes, I feel it in just one day.
And then, I make a few changes
here and there.
Why did you meet Ms. Seo?
-You saw us?
-No, I heard it.
Everyone kept saying
they saw you with her
when she came to school.
How do they know her?
Every business student knows
the family members of Seomyung Group.
She's not just the president
of a small agency.
The person you were with
is an executive director at Seomyung.
"An executive director"?
And most of the stuff you eat and use
is made by Seomyung.
Was Ms. Seo your Rapunzel?
Then what does that make you?
Me? Lee Yeong-hwa.
Good to know you're not the prince.
I do look like one though.
I don't know either,
but your painting was dark and unsettling.
I can't stop thinking about that.
Why is it so frustrating?
Hello.
You ran again?
Yes.
I run to live. You know I'm weak.
Is everything okay?
A worker was injured
at a Seomyung Electronics factory.
And to take care of the issue,
Director Seo went
to check on what happened.
Seomyung isn't a small company.
Is he going there to put on a show
because he majored in engineering?
But the thing is…
Just because we're a big firm
doesn't mean we can ignore this.
Where is the factory again?
I'm going to take care of this.
Instead of going to the factory,
he went to the hospital.
Do you think he does that on purpose
to get attention?
Then I guess he's not at the office.
Get to work then.
-Hello?
-Seon-gyeom, where are you?
Me? In front of a fridge.
A fridge, you say?
Sounds refreshing.
Is there no way of correcting
the way you talk?
Forget it.
And where is this fridge?
Ms. Ki gave us her feedback.
She hates all the clothes.
I agreed to send new ones.
Who knew that Eun-bi
was picky with clothes?
Why did you take down Seon-gyeom's photo?
I'm just making room for something else.
When will Eun-bi's photo get here?
Soon.
-Dad.
-Oh, hey.
You're here early.
The game doesn't begin until later.
You're the best daughter ever.
I'd rather not be late
and receive a penalty.
I'm always grateful for
you entertaining my friends.
Who knew you had friends
who needed a golfing buddy in me?
I'm worried about not playing well
due to my stiff wrist today.
If that's the case,
take it easy out on the field.
So how are things between you and Ryan?
You're not to touch him.
He's too fragile for that.
Despite signing with Ms. Seo,
I agreed to all these
golfing events with you.
I stayed true to my word, so you will too.
I think signing with her
was a good choice.
I mean, she might become
your sisters-in-law someday.
Are you seriously going
to marry Seon-gyeom off to her?
-This isn't the Middle Ages.
-Of course.
A minor detail has been bothering me,
but I think it's just a phase.
That being said, it's best
not to ruffle any feathers.
You must be relieved
thinking that it's just a phase.
Anyway, I won't be
going easy on anyone today.
I'm sorry,
but we're in the middle of filming.
-Could you turn off the engine?
-Sure. I'm sorry.
-Thank you.
-Just a second.
Is this man currently here?
He's not answering his phone.
-Are you asking me if I've seen you?
-What?
I mean him. The big-eyed one.
Follow me.
Yeong-il said he'll be here.
Why he decided to though…
-What's that?
-My journal.
Don't look.
Then don't write in it in front of me.
I couldn't care less.
It's my only way of dealing with stress.
Tell Coach for all I care.
Just be careful on that thing.
What are you doing here?
-I hear they're filming a movie.
-I'm part-timing as a driver.
You're working part-time
near the training center?
-Is this a protest or something?
-I only found out
after I got here.
But you still didn't come to see me.
You made me come to you instead.
Are you here to nag?
I'm making use of the occasion.
The sight of you makes my blood boil.
Who's he?
-My friend.
-You have friends?
Goodness.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Who's she?
The translator who accompanied me in Jeju.
You might not recall
since it was over a month ago.
I'm sorry.
I must not remember
-because he made such a mess then.
-Right.
I'm Kwon Yeong-il.
I'm Oh Mi-joo.
-Hey, handsome.
-Handsome. That's you.
He doesn't speak English. What do you need?
I'd like to go back to the hotel
and get some sleep.
-Okay, I'll tell him to take you back.
-Thank you.
He wants to get some sleep at the hotel.
-I'll get going.
-Sure.
See you.
I doubt it'll take too long.
Right.
-Thank you for this.
-Sure.
So what's your relationship
with Seon-gyeom?
I'm not sure.
I don't know what we are either.
The job in Jeju ended a month ago.
You've stuck around for over a month
when he's Mr. One Month.
"Mr. One Month"?
I mean, Seon-gyeom.
Most girls don't last a month
chasing him around because he's boring.
Do you always keep track
of who lasts a month and such?
Why do people say he's a bore though?
I find him funny.
Frankly speaking,
Seon-gyeom must have felt the same way
towards the girls around him
who left after a month.
Mi-joo. I'm sorry,
but can you go to the convenience store?
-We're out of coffee.
-Sure thing.
I--
You may go.
Seon-gyeom will be back soon anyway.
-I'll get going then.
-Sure.
Coming!
"Mr. One Month"?
Is this a promising industry?
Would it be?
You were in great shape
and practiced hard for the race.
Just come back to being an athlete.
It must seem easy
since it's not your business.
Without you, I'm all alone.
Then you'll keep winning first place.
Maybe it was your presence
that motivated me.
You constantly winning first place
is how I always came in second.
If you constantly won
and were the record-holder,
would track have been more popular?
Being handsome and all.
-You?
-Annoying jerk.
Did you really have to ask that?
I mean, you.
How's your personal record?
Don't ask.
-So it's the same.
-It's not.
Now that you and Woo-sik are gone,
I'm racing against myself.
The hardest one to beat is…
As if you'd know.
Guys,
you're too far apart.
Come closer.
You come closer.
No, you.
Yeong-il, I think it'll be better
for you to move.
Why are you taking his side?
The table behind you ruins the photo.
Come on.
-Are we good?
-Sure. Here we go.
One, two, three!
For years, I was clueless
about what was going on.
He was smiling all the time,
so I figured he was happy.
I wonder how his recovery is coming along.
It has to go well,
so that he can run again
and stick it to everyone.
What?
I'm surprised.
I've never known you to talk like that.
I've always wanted to.
I'd like to tell him
that I'd handle all obstacles
so that he can be free to just run.
Do you remember Seong-geun?
He runs an academy in Noryangjin.
I don't recall.
-What about me?
-Well, you're right here.
He retired at the age of 37
due to Achilles tendinitis.
Unless it's that serious,
Woo-sik will still have a chance to run.
Right.
You just took what I put in the schedule.
Look, I have certain guarantees when
it came to this schedule.
You don't get just to change them.
I can change whatever I want.
I'm the cinematographer!
I don't care who you are.
That's not how this works.
-That's exactly how it works.
-Fine!
-Garrison!
-James.
What's the problem?
Are you sure you can guarantee this?
-About your upcoming schedule.
-Yes.
-Please...
-No! There is no guarantee.
-What are you talking about?
-Wait!
I'm trying to translate. Let me finish.
He already signed the contract,
so what's this about
wanting a new "guarantee"?
The funding hasn't even been finalized.
-There is no guarantee.
-That's--
-No guarantee?
-No.
-I'm out.
-James!
Why is James changing his mind?
Are you kidding me?
The "guarantee" he mentioned
was about the duration of this project.
It had nothing to do with his payment.
The "guarantee" you mentioned
is broken English.
It's not a term you can
just throw about like that.
Broken English?
Are you trying to belittle me?
No, that's hardly the case.
I'm saying you should use words correctly.
You still should've taken my side though.
You're Korean, aren't you?
Why does that matter
when we're trying to be professionals?
James!
James. Please listen to me.
I know you're upset,
but this is all a misunderstanding.
Please.
James?
What's going on?
James is very upset.
Don't be offended if he snaps.
I wouldn't even know
if he's snapping at me anyway.
I'm glad you can't speak English.
Please take good care of him.
Drop him off at the hotel
and Hui-jin will take it from there.
You too.
Don't worry too much.
Sure.
The number you have dialed…
Mi-joo, we're in big trouble!
James wasn't answering,
so I went up to check on him,
but he already checked out.
I think he left with his boyfriend.
-What?
-Hold on.
Wipe that look off your face.
I'm the one who wants to cry.
I should applaud your solid acting.
He's not at the train station.
-We've yet to locate him. I'm sorry.
-What?
Didn't you tell him
about today's schedule?
I made today's filming schedule clear
but James must not have been pleased.
Jesus Christ.
But the director will be here soon!
Give me my phone.
Higher-ups will be visiting the set today.
Some day they chose.
What do you mean you can't find James?
What did you do to him?
Who's responsible?
-I'm sorry.
Why on earth weren't you reachable?
James?
I thought I was to
drive quickly to the set,
so I was too busy to check my phone.
He must have forgotten he asked for
a non-English speaking driver.
You're here, and that's all that matters.
James!
What are we doing back here?
I told you to take us to the station.
Okay.
You know, this film
maybe just a way for you to make a living,
but this is an incredibly important work
we're doing here.
Especially for Korean immigrants.
Is this how you do things around here?
Are you so narrow-minded
because of how your tiny country is?
You've got to be kidding me.
What? Are you not going to translate?
Just because they can't speak English,
doesn't mean
you can say whatever you want.
And anyway, aren't you the one
who forced us to keep shooting
without the actor's approval?
None of us violated the contract.
-You did.
-Fuck.
-What?
-Oops.
Did you hear that?
Do you want me to say it louder?
Fuck you.
Fuck you too, you punk.
-Hey, fuck you.
-What?
Don't you think you're out of line?
This bastard started swearing at me.
Hey, fuck you!
You're also out of line.
She's very good.
Ms. Oh! Are you crazy?
He cursed at me first. You saw him.
How is "fuck" a curse word?
It's only an exclamation.
People use it to express their emotions.
"Gosh, I'm so upset, fuck." Like that.
-Apologize to him.
-What?
Apologize.
-I'm sorry.
-What's she saying?
-I'm really sorry about this situation.
-The mayor's here!
Goodness, you're here.
What's with the commotion?
We were only rehearsing
for the next scene.
Even rehearsals should be kept real.
I must be interrupting
your rehearsal then.
Hardly.
Goodness. Assemblyman Ki, hello.
I'm Julie Yeom,
the chief producer of this movie.
-I'm Ki Jeong-do.
-It's a pleasure.
Sorry for the intrusion!
Could anyone translate for me?
Don't you worry, sir. I'm here for you.
Please meet our cinematographer.
It's been a while Ms. Translator.
I'd like to meet the staff,
so can you translate?
Sure.
I heard you're waiting for the city
to approve the additional funding.
Without that support,
the production company
will have to cover all costs.
Yes, that's what I heard.
I'll push for the additional funding
to be approved.
You will?
You might be a passing moment
in my son's life,
but I should still value
your companionship.
"A passing moment"?
I apologize for what happened
at the cinema.
I hope I didn't upset you too much.
I'm good.
What have you been up to?
Are you following your mom's footsteps?
I'm here as a driver.
Out of all the jobs
required on a movie set?
All you can do is drive people around?
-Say that again.
-Please just leave.
Fine, I will. I'll see you in Seoul, son.
Now I feel like I owe him, which I hate.
I just can't tell what he's up to.
I doubt he has an ulterior motive.
He's here to do his job.
Ms. Oh, we need to talk.
I guess it's time.
I'm off to get an earful.
I'm sorry.
I have a lot to say,
but I'll cut it short.
Pack up and disappear.
This isn't coming from me.
The cinematographer
wants you out of his sight.
Then who will translate--
There are many others who can take over.
Don't act like you're irreplaceable.
Your gig ends tomorrow anyway,
so just get lost a day earlier.
Message delivered.
Are you all right?
How am I supposed to translate "Fuck you"?
I've translated it dozens of times,
but it's still nothing but a curse word.
It is.
Something urgent came up at the office
and I need to head back today.
I'm sorry for leaving you here alone.
It all ends tomorrow anyway.
You should go.
How will you get to the station though?
You may not know this,
but there's something called a taxi.
Right, of course. You should get going.
I'll see you back at home.
I must be crazy.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm just next to you.
Right.
Just let me drink myself to death.
You don't want me to?
No.
What?
You brought glasses?
Here.
Gosh.
What is that?
Is this semi-dried herring?
You need to eat too.
Thanks.
You can eat this, right?
Of course. I can never get enough of it.
I'm glad.
Gosh.
Thank you for driving around today.
You're even taking care of a drunk
like me. Thank you.
You came here without knowing anything,
but you've been doing so well.
You even moved us to a hotel.
Everyone's so grateful.
You'll be included in the credits
as a driver.
Your name's not easy to spell,
so I should tell them to double-check.
Will you be included as well?
Then we'll both be included.
I like that.
Once you see the credits,
you'll realize why you put up
with so much.
Names of others who were in the same boat
will show up as well.
You'll know how exhausting
and strenuous it was.
It must've been difficult
to relay all sorts of messages.
I'm always careful about the messages
I relay.
But others are so lucky.
They secure us our funding, act racist,
and even fire people with just one word.
How did you know you had to bring
James back?
It looked like he was bailing,
so I just brought him back.
I thought you didn't speak English.
I never said that.
You're full of surprises, aren't you?
Should I just go back to Seoul today?
-Should I just get lost?
-Yes.
-You want me to get lost?
Don't do anything you don't want to do.
I thought I'd be the one
to say this for once.
But…
why do I suddenly feel like
I could do anything?
That's usually not the case,
but I feel like I can this time.
You really do have
a positive influence on people.
You do for me.
-Would you like a drink?
-No, thanks.
Okay.
What is this?
A snack.
Is it good?
Garrison, I'm sorry
about what happened yesterday.
Just let me finish my work and go.
And, today is my last day anyway.
Whatever.
Sure, just ignore me.
I'll just do my job regardless.
Hey.
Thank you.
Why are you out of it?
Everyone here is out of it.
But you were especially out of it.
-Have you finished your modern art report?
-I submitted it last time.
No, the final one.
I see that you haven't.
Why did you even have that
as your status message then?
I'm done for.
Why do humans live?
Is it okay for us to exist?
Maybe it's because I drew two
when I can barely finish one.
Why am I so full of myself?
Those all-nighters have made you insane.
Did you ever have someone
find something
that you hid in your painting?
A prep school teacher once found out
that I had made mistakes
and tried to cover them up.
She caught me countless times.
What did you do?
I did what she told me to do.
There was nothing else I could do.
I see.
This was my first time.
Everyone,
leave your equipment here.
We'll take an hour long break.
Be back here by 4 p.m., okay?
Mi-joo!
-Rest for an hour.
-Mi-joo!
Come back by 4 p.m.
Mi-joo!
Why are you leaving
without saying goodbye?
You looked so busy,
so I was going to leave quietly.
That hurts my feelings.
We're going to end early today,
so have some snow crabs
and visit the ocean.
I will. I'm going to sightsee too.
I'll be the one to wait today.
Thank you for everything.
We even managed to secure the funding.
Come to the after-party.
Let's have some meat.
Of course.
You were an outstanding comrade.
Good luck with the filming back in Seoul.
Thank you for this fun opportunity.
Don't mention it.
I'll see you back in Seoul.
Bye. See you.
Cheer up.
Hurry and go.
-You're done already?
-Yes.
How did you know I'd be here?
The female staff members talked
about how you were always running here.
At times, they couldn't find you here.
You're quite popular.
Even Yeong-il came all the way here
to see you.
He must like you a lot.
I probably like him more.
I used to follow him around
when I was an athlete.
What? Hold on. What you just said
could cause a big misunderstanding.
-You followed him around?
-Yes.
He was the sole runner
I couldn't catch up to.
Oh, as a runner. You're talking
about the running record, right?
You startled me.
Do you want to know something?
The lanes we run on are chosen by a draw.
That only happens for the top runners.
But Yeong-il always got the same lane.
Even God helped him come first place.
You're lying.
I'm not. The lanes are picked randomly.
It was always so random for me,
but he was always the top runner
in the same lane.
I thought that was fascinating.
Didn't you?
I'm more fascinated by this moment.
I've made a wise decision to wait for you.
The ocean looks so beautiful.
Should we meet at the parking lot
after you finish packing?
One minute.
Wait here for a moment.
Here. Take it.
Those shoes are made for people
with high arches.
It'll be easier for you to run.
That is, if you're still going to.
But why are you suddenly giving me a gift?
For letting me stay with you.
What?
I've already moved all my stuff.
I've cleaned the house
and done the laundry.
You can just go in and rest.
That wasn't what I meant.
Why are you telling me that now?
We've been together for days.
I actually thought it was the right time
to say this.
I was going to tell you
after your work was done.
It's just too perfect of a timing
that I have nothing to say.
Whenever I feel closer to you,
it feels as though you push me right back.
You didn't seem to like it
when I said you put up walls,
so I'm rewording it.
I'm not upset, so don't take it
the wrong way.
But I told you
that I don't put up any walls.
Then why do I feel like I'm outside
an invisible wall right now?
I don't want you to be outside those walls
that I didn't even put up.
Likewise.
If I've become too boring,
then tell me so.
It's just that when I'm with you,
I feel left out
during the most important moments.
And that feeling doesn't happen
on its own.
I hate this.
I don't mean that I hate you.
I just sounded too pathetic and hated it.
So don't hate me for it.
I don't.
I've been doing that thing
you asked me to.
You asked me to like you.
Can you…
like me?
Oh, that…
I wasn't asking you for a favor.
I was mustering up my courage.
I don't think we should leave together.
I'm afraid I might say something
I shouldn't.
Hey, Woo-sik.
Seon-gyeom, have you been well?
Are you driving right now?
Yes.
How have you been?
I've just been missing you.
Should we meet tomorrow?
I have cleaning to do with my grandma.
Tell her to rest at home. I'll go instead.
Yes, I'll do that.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow.
Woo-sik.
Yes, Seon-gyeom?
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry?
That you had to muster up the courage.
Don't say that.
Is something wrong?
-Here's your coffee.
-Thank you.
So this was why I felt suffocated.
I was pining for her.
I've missed you too.
Guess how much I missed you.
Despite giving you so much time,
you haven't updated me
on the progress of my painting.
Right. It was because of the painting.
I see.
You should hurry since I've agreed
to display your painting
at the art museum.
I'm juggling exams, assignments,
and your painting right now.
I want to excel at all of them.
You're blaming the delay
on your schoolwork?
Then you shouldn't have been a student.
I'm exhausted right now,
so let's talk again.
What did you say?
I'm exhausted.
You're exhausted, so what?
Do you want me to buy you ginseng?
You have garbage empathic skills.
Garbage?
Am I at least recyclable? That matters.
You must really love the Earth.
This is where I live.
I should take good care of it.
Do you support polar bears too?
Yes, I do. Dolphins as well.
You should too.
You're cute.
Goodbye.
What are you doing?
What did you just say?
I need to go back to school.
No, what did you just say?
I don't think you gave me a single answer.
You don't make me want to.
Hey, kid. Hey.
What a rude asshole.
You have no manners, do you?
What was that?
Mr. Jeong, it's me.
It's such a hassle to get some drinks,
don't you think so?
Maybe you should quit drinking
or just move out.
Don't be absurd.
I need to get on the chairman's good side
to get as much as I can from him.
Am I cute?
Why aren't you answering?
The same bar as usual?
Why aren't you…
Why are you doing this to me?
I've always been this way.
TOGETHER WITH ATOZ
Are you feeling down?
Yes. Why do you ask?
Because you look nice,
but you're not taking any photos.
I don't like my face.
I do.
I don't like your face either.
What the hell?
Gosh, he made a post
throwing shade at me again.
What? Let me see.
YUCK, ARE THEY RHYMERS
OR STRIPPING MALES?
This stupid, passion-fruit-looking punk!
Is he still on your back?
He criticized our entire group this time.
Why is he so diligent?
Is it a crime for an underground rapper
to join a boyband?
He's been at it for years!
Get out of there, asshole!
Watch your language.
Don't respond. Just ignore him.
They're currently discussing your debut,
so keep it on the down low.
A debut? He can rap
since he's the main rapper,
but what about me?
-You can look pretty.
-I already am.
Then look pretty
and chop some green onions today.
Okay, I'll begin the live broadcast.
ENJOY THIS MOMENT WITH ATOZ
Go!
Two, three.
-Hello, Alphabet!
Woo-sik, your window is squeaky clean.
Why can't I do it?
Gosh, let me see that.
Here.
Wipe in one direction
to avoid leaving any smears.
So you developed your back muscles
for this.
-It's worthwhile.
-And my deltoids too.
I'm cleaning a studio tomorrow,
so it'll be easier.
What bad timing.
I tend to be bad with timing.
-You're working tomorrow too?
-Yes.
I help out quite often these days.
I want to get lessons.
I can't seem to practice on my own.
What have you been up to?
Up until recently, I was a driver.
Is that why you were in the countryside?
I heard from Yeong-il that you two met.
Do you guys keep in touch?
He calls me every now and then.
Thank you so much for allowing me
to stay at the hotel.
Where have you been staying?
I lived with Ms. Oh for a while.
What? You two moved in
before getting married?
-Did you propose already?
-"Propose"?
Seon-gyeom.
Fate must have brought us together.
Will you marry me?
No, someone else proposed to me.
Seon-gyeom! Why do you have
so many women around you?
Did you end it with Choi Tae-ri?
That was ages ago.
How are you feeling?
I feel carefree.
I spoke my mind.
I wonder why I was so frightened
back then.
I think I'm finding myself.
I tend to be happy-go-lucky.
Very much so.
No matter what sports I play,
people will always see me
as a whistleblower.
Then I'll wonder if I should choose
a different path
where I wouldn't be shunned.
I think my grandma would be happier
if I became a civil servant.
I'd like you to think more about yourself.
You seem to think more about others
than yourself
when they're of no help to you.
Is that what you did?
Of course, I want to continue
playing sports.
But…
I don't think I should.
I thought you were finding yourself.
Look further. And put yourself first.
I'll try that.
When it comes to my own issues,
I have trouble being objective too.
But let's talk about it together.
Two is better than one, don't you think?
Do you truly think so?
You don't like me, do you?
No.
Don't drink this.
These are mine. Don't eat this either.
CHILAN MOUNTAIN BEEKEEPING
That's right.
Food isn't to blame.
This honey did nothing wrong.
I know it isn't to blame,
but should I just get rid of it?
Ms. Seo.
I'm sorry.
I've found out where Director Seo
is hospitalized.
What took you so long to find that out?
Was it that top secret?
Did he lose his legs or something?
Is that why?
It was top secret
because his legs were just fine.
He knew how you'd react if you found out.
How did he know something I didn't know?
We sure love each other greatly.
I heard you got hurt.
Did you tell her that I was here?
Come closer.
-I said it was top secret.
-There you go, blaming others again.
Aren't you happy to see me here
despite my busy schedule?
How could I be when you entered
with a smile on your face?
I guess your legs weren't broken
after all.
Go find a new painting
if you have so much time.
Last time, you sounded like
you'd do that immediately,
but mine's still there.
Oh, that's what you're talking about?
I forgot about it since it was so trivial.
Forgot, my ass.
If you can't do it,
just admit that I have an eye for art.
It's about time
you grew up, Dan-ah.
Right. Here's your gift.
Get this away from me!
Flowers…
Why did you tell her where I was?
I told you it was top secret.
You idiot!
Throw that away!
Why does he have to open his mouth
and make a clown of himself?
Ms. Seo.
What did you do to have everyone
on campus know who you are?
I roughly told them how you looked,
and they told me you'd be here.
How kind of them.
I see.
Why do I always have to look for you?
What?
You should've called. You have a phone.
I was too upset to remember
that I had saved your number.
Is this my painting?
It must be that assignment of yours.
Give me mine right now.
I'm not a vending machine.
Why not?
You had plenty of chances to be an artist.
I was humiliated by that bastard
because you didn't give me
my painting on time.
"That bastard"?
-Which bastard?
-The one I was going to
humiliate with your painting.
Were you going to
use my painting to save face?
Why? Can't I?
We'll both be achieving our goals.
I must have expected better from you,
seeing how disappointed I am.
You do that.
I don't care what you do.
I just want the painting.
-Behind every painting is a painter.
-You're in front of it.
You can just forget about all this
if you're going to keep this up.
I have many other vending machines.
Why do you make me say this?
What did you expect?
For me to wait endlessly for the painting?
You must think it's your time
that you're wasting,
but it's actually mine.
And you're what? "Disappointed"?
What was that?
It's all on you.
That was my painting.
-I'm the painter.
-I know that.
No, you don't.
It's mine.
Until the moment I hand it over to you,
it's mine.
Should I just go and tell him how I feel?
We'll go steady as of today.
I don't think I can.
I didn't take Mi-joo to be such a wuss.
Tell him how you feel.
How else can you move forward?
-Is something up between the two of you?
-It's mostly me.
I don't know how to share
or what to give to people.
-But what's that?
-I thought you would know.
-What do you mean?
-Because you're a peasant like him.
Get out.
Did you move to our neighborhood?
You really are full of surprises.
Has Ms. Seo ever
walked all over you before?
I'm going to spoil you.
-Are we going to speak casually now?
-Should we?
-No.
-Okay.
I wasn't sure if you had feelings for me
Because I do.
Please don't hate me.
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs