BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS
My lord! I'm stuck!
My lord!
Hurry up!
Shit! Hurry up!
What are you doing?
Open it already!
Hurry!
Hurry up! Shit!
Hurry! Come on!
The key! Where's the key?
There's no door!
The key! Bring me the key!
Open it! Now!
Open it!
Lock it! Now!
Hurry up! Lock it!
No! Don't go there!
Please, help. Help!
No! Stop!
No! Don't come any closer!
Come here. Come.
Here.
Help!
-Open the door!
-Help!
-Someone is out there.
-Help me!
-This way! Here!
-Come this way!
-Run!
-Hurry!
The door is locked!
This way!
Let go of her!
Oh, no!
-She got bitten!
-Let go! Let go of her hand!
What are you doing?
She was already bitten!
Grab the baby. Hurry!
Let go of her!
Let go! She was bitten!
Please, help me!
These peasants are attacking noblemen!
Shut the gate! Shut it now!
Shit!
These look great.
-It is so heavy.
-Hurry!
What is going on?
Run!
Hey! Park!
We caught fish! Come here!
Is that him?
It is obviously him.
My gosh.
He must have drunk a lot today.
Hey! Are you drunk?
-Who are those people?
-My gosh.
Hey.
What is going on?
-Hey.
-What is wrong with them?
Hey! What is that?
Stop running. You will get hungry.
Stop fighting. Don't bite him!
That will scar!
-Let go!
-You punk.
-I said, that will scar.
-Let go!
Get off me!
Father.
What is wrong?
Deok-i, stay here.
I will go look for your sister.
Do not come out.
Mommy!
What is wrong with you?
You are scaring me!
Stop it, Mommy!
Stop it!
Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness, run!
Hold on tight!
You must aim for their heads.
Your Royal Highness! The barracks.
You must go to the barracks.
We must hurry, Your Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness!
Is anyone inside?
Please let us in!
Is anyone there?
-Monsters are chasing us!
-I don't think anyone is here.
Your Highness.
Please climb up.
Excuse us. I'm sorry,
but please step aside!
Step aside!
-We should climb the wall.
-Let us climb the wall!
Get off the fence at once!
Someone is inside!
Get rid of them.
Shoo them away. Now!
-Don't shoot!
-Get rid of them.
Your Royal Highness!
Are you all right?
How dare you?
He is the Crown Prince of this nation!
Open the gate!
Please, let us in.
Don't try to fool me!
Don't give me your nonsense, and scram!
All of you!
Anyone who climbs over this wall
shall be dealt with by law!
-Let us climb up! Come on!
-Let us climb up, too!
How dare you?
What do you think you're doing?
Why, those...
Get down! Down!
-Let the children in!
-Didn't you hear me? Push them off!
-Go down!
-Scram!
-Get away!
-Go down!
-I said, scram!
Get down!
Don't come up here!
Shoot! Shoot the arrows!
How dare you?
If you get any closer,
these arrows will pierce your bodies!
Please help us!
Please don't leave us here to die!
What the...
Your Royal Highness, you must go.
Run! Everyone, run!
Run!
Your Royal Highness.
That female physician spoke the truth.
How could this happen?
The baby inside you
will be the king of this nation,
so be careful.
You must teach him
what happens to a powerless king.
Until the new Crown Prince is born,
you must make sure His Majesty
has plenty to eat and drink.
Mommy.
Stop! Just stop already!
Shit! I'm exhausted.
My clothes got dirty.
I shall prepare fresh clothes.
Go for a walk.
Come down.
My lord!
My gosh!
Why you...
Oh, my. My lord.
My lord.
Thank goodness you are safe.
Where were you until now?
I was...
I wanted to save you,
so I brought all those soldiers.
Save me? Now?
Do you know what I went through?
I would have died last night
if not for her!
Well...
That jerk! It was all that jerk's fault!
-What?
-What are you doing?
Capture him now!
Yes, my lord.
It was all his fault.
He... knew all about those hideous things,
but he hid it from us.
I told you, didn't I?
That they were not dead.
How dare you glare at me like that?
I shall...
He is correct! Tell us now!
What are those monsters?
Where did they come from?
I...
I will tell you.
They were the ill at Jiyulheon
and their families.
They could not withstand
starvation any longer
and ate a corpse, then...
-What?
-They became monsters
that crave human flesh and blood at night.
During the day, they hide
where the sun doesn't reach
and sleep as if they were dead.
Human corpse... What...
How could they do that?
If that is true,
why did you leave those corpses like that?
You should have buried them
when they were asleep
or gotten rid of them somehow!
My lord, you must punish them
for their crimes.
I'm fine with being punished,
but isn't it urgent
to get rid of the bodies?
When the sun sets,
more monsters will come.
Then bury them quickly!
Even so,
-Yes--
-...they'll climb out.
You must cut off their heads
or burn them.
-Burn the bodies?
-What?
Who says you can burn the bodies?
-Who...
-Well...
She is the former commander's mother.
Never desecrate the body
you got from your parents.
My precious son is our family's only son
for three generations.
If you so much as lay a finger
on his body,
you will have to answer to me!
If you lay a finger on the bodies
of my family,
you will have to answer to me too!
-Well, they are correct.
-What?
With noblemen, even if they commit
grave crimes like murder,
you cannot punish them
without the Royal Court's consent.
You know that, right?
-But...
-On top of that,
if we burn all those bodies,
we will face an angry backlash
from the upper class.
Then what do I do?
My gosh.
-We should burn the peasants' bodies
-Okay.
...and hold proper funerals
for the bodies of the aristocrats.
Then we should bury them
deep into the ground. How about that?
There are so many. How can we
differentiate nobles from peasants?
Goodness. We can separate
the bodies in silk from those in rags.
-Great idea.
-Thank you.
Split them into two groups!
-Go on.
-Go.
Someone responsible
for the people' safety
is this incompetent?
What are you doing?
The instant you draw your sword,
you lose your head!
Who are you that you dare do this?
You are not only incompetent,
but also endlessly vile.
You locked the doors
to the barracks last night,
countless innocent people died.
If I had opened the gate,
the soldiers would have been in danger.
Firing your arrow at me
is punishable by death
and annihilation of your family.
You have committed treason!
By the way, who are you?
The four-clawed dragon... You are...
It's an honor to greet the Crown Prince!
What did he just say?
What are you doing?
He is the Crown Prince!
I should kill you right this instant,
but we need help so...
Spare my life.
I shall punish you
after resolving the situation.
How many soldiers are alive?
Only 50, Your Highness.
-That is correct.
-Have every soldier search for bodies.
They must burn them immediately.
You cannot do that.
I understand how you feel,
having lost your family.
But we must burn them
to avoid future harm.
Light a signal fire and send messengers
to spread the word and request support
so we can quarantine Dongnae.
And transport survivors
using boats on either quayside
to safety before nightfall.
Cho Beom-pal, the magistrate of Dongnae,
shall heed Your Royal Highness' command!
-We shall obey!
The signal fire has been lit!
HANYANG
Where is the Chief Scholar?
He is waiting inside.
I came out of respect to him,
but things are tense now
with talk of treason.
It doesn't look good to meet
secretly like this.
We have something urgent to tell you.
This way, please.
What do you mean?
Corpses were found in the King's palace?
Something strange is happening there
for sure.
Lord Cho Hak-ju is hiding it from us.
I know you are one of his men.
However, I'm telling you
because I believe you know
what is right and wrong.
I can't believe it.
It can't be.
There is only one way
to find out the truth.
Let us go to the King's palace.
If we go and see His Majesty in person
and confirm that he is safe,
everything will become clear.
The Queen has forbidden
anyone from entering
the King's palace.
We serve His Majesty, not the Queen.
Lord Ahn Hyeon will join us.
Do you mean the Lord Ahn Hyeon?
He is staying low in his hometown,
mourning the loss of his mother
for three years,
but if he takes action,
all the scholars and subjects of the land
will follow him.
I was keeping an eye on Chief Scholar,
and I noticed a servant running.
I found this on him.
It's a letter meant
for Lord Ahn Hyeon in Sangju.
All he did was read books.
If he wants to challenge me,
he would need Lord Ahn Hyeon's help.
What should we do?
Leave them be.
Are you sure?
Lord Ahn Hyeon saved the nation
during the war three years ago.
If he supports the Crown Prince,
the people may as well.
Lord Ahn Hyeon...
can never oppose me.
No matter what.
DONGNAE
My lord, I have brought the criminal.
Okay.
Send her in.
You wanted to see me?
Yes. I called you here today because--
It is all my fault.
I should have reported it right away,
but they were like family to me,
so I thought I could cure them.
Please kill me.
No...
No. That is not it.
Well, it's your duty as a physician
to cure people.
That is not all.
You saved my life last night.
You are too kind, my lord.
-I merely--
-No.
Well...
I swear...
I will repay you for what you did.
Until all my hair...
turns white,
I will keep you by my side.
Do you need a physician?
Do you have an ailment, my lord?
-No, that is not--
-You are flushed.
Are you always like that?
Or are you usually fine,
but get flushed when you're nervous?
It may be
because your heart or liver is unhealthy.
If you do not mind,
may I check your pulse?
My pulse?
Men and women must be separated,
but that is not a problem between us.
Sure.
Take your time and check my pulse.
Do you have difficulty urinating?
-Did you just say--
-Your lower abdomen may be strained.
You may feel pain in your penis, too.
My... penis?
I think...
it's gonorrhea.
Gonorrhea?
What? My...
Something's wrong with my thing?
Don't worry.
It isn't that serious yet.
You will be fine once you take medicine.
My lord.
The Crown Prince's guard is here.
Okay.
Show him in.
The Crown Prince ordered me
to bring that physician.
Oh... I see.
In that case...
You should. Sure. Go ahead.
My lord! This is the head clerk.
Okay. What is it?
During the last night's mayhem,
all the battleships were destroyed.
And there aren't enough boats
to evacuate the people.
There is one decent cargo ship,
so it can set sail in about two hours.
How can we evacuate all those people
with just one cargo ship?
I know. That is...
How is the search for bodies coming along?
Hey.
We made every soldier available
search for bodies,
but to no avail.
Then find as many as possible. Go!
Nothing is going right.
No!
-I'm sorry, my lord.
-The Crown Prince gave us a command.
Come up with a plan before sunset.
Yeong-ju.
Master!
What's going on?
It wasn't like this.
In Hanyang...
It wasn't like this in Hanyang.
When Dan-i...
was bitten,
he was sick for days
and died as a human being.
But...
when those people
got bitten,
they turned into the same monster.
The disease has changed.
It has begun to spread.
What are you talking about, Master?
I can fix it.
I can...
fix this disease.
I logged everything
about the disease. Everything...
TWO HOURS AFTER STICKING A NEEDLE
COATED WITH CRUSHED RESURRECTION PLANT
INTO HIS MAJESTY'S FOREHEAD,
HE CAME BACK TO LIFE
This disease can be cured?
Is that true?
That is what he said.
"The cold valley that is foggy
four seasons of the year.
The plant with a purple flower
that blooms in early autumn
will resurrect a person who has died."
Did you go to the valley to find it?
I thought I could figure out a way
to cure the diseased
if I found that plant, so I went there,
but I couldn't find such a plant.
For now, there is no way
to cure this disease.
Your Highness.
I need to tell you something.
I cannot find Commander Cho's head.
If someone took it
to Cho Hak-ju...
This is utterly frustrating.
You should've talked to him nicely.
Why did you do that?
He is Cho Hak-ju's precious only son.
If he receives that only son's
decapitated head,
he won't forgive us.
I won't forgive him either.
Pardon?
You were accused of treason
and fled all the way to Dongnae.
How do you plan to fight him?
I have a justification now.
I must gather support.
Justification?
What justification?
Stay alive.
You must stay alive.
Father...
has passed away.
Pardon?
His Majesty has passed away?
Cho Hak-ju and the Queen
used the resurrection plant on him
after he passed away...
to protect their authority.
That journal and that female physician
will testify to that fact.
Sangju...
I shall go to Lord Ahn Hyeon.
Hurry up. Hurry.
Just a minute.
Hurry. Move quickly.
Finish up before people flock here.
Let us go.
Why is he bringing a pig?
The ship is leaving! Hurry!
Everyone ran away! Hurry up!
Hey! Excuse me!
Hey, what is going on?
Take care!
It's quicker by boat to Sangju.
They are almost done fixing the ship,
so let's go to the dock.
Oh, no!
Don't leave us, my lord! Please!
Take us with you!
Don't abandon us!
Please take us with you!
My lord!
-Please take our baby! Just our baby!
-Please come back!
Why those...
They should do something
instead of just whining.
Why are they so foolish?
Is it okay for us to do this?
It is impossible to get rid
of all the corpses before the sun sets.
It will be mayhem again at night.
Staying there
is like running into fire
carrying kindling.
You and the noblemen
are the pillars that sustain Dongnae.
-Right.
-I agree.
You must stay alive and rebuild Dongnae.
You are positive that the Crown Prince
left Dongnae safely, right?
Yes, of course.
I saw the two of them leave
with my own eyes.
You need not worry, my lord.
Did he take that female physician
with him?
Who?
Never mind.
-Excuse me.
-Do not worry, and--
-Hey.
-My lord.
Will it be okay?
The Crown Prince is still there.
If he finds out we left like this,
he will have our heads.
We shot arrows at the Crown Prince
last night.
He said he'll annihilate our families.
We are dead either way.
But...
Okay. Good.
Come on, now.
Don't worry.
The Cho clan has control
over the Lees in this world.
If we...
stay on the magistrate's good side,
we will be able to find a way to survive.
Subtitle translation by Jeong Lee