BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS
Is there a ship for us, too?
What is that ship and who is on it?
Military commanders
and high officials of Dongnae.
They all left on that ship.
They didn't even clean up the bodies.
Once the sun sets,
they will wake up again.
Is there another ship?
They all burned down last night.
That was the only ship left.
We must find a place for these people
to hide before sunset.
What about the barracks
from last night?
We can keep all these people safe there.
Well, they tore down the fence
to repair that ship.
We can go to Jiyulheon.
The infected were unable to get out
of there for several days,
so they won't be able to get in.
We will go to Jiyulheon.
Anyone who can walk, will walk.
The old and the sick will be carried
on wagons.
Everyone, hurry!
We will go to Jiyulheon!
Move quickly!
We must get there before the sun sets,
so please hurry!
We shall go, too.
Oh, no.
Are you hurt?
-What's wrong?
-Over there.
There is something weird over there.
Wait, what is that?
It's a monster!
-Monsters everywhere.
-There's one there!
Over there, too.
Your Royal Highness.
If we consider the ones hiding,
they will be in great numbers.
Run!
Run! Now!
Run to Jiyulheon without stopping!
Run and don't stop!
Hurry!
-Get on this, sir.
-Hurry!
We must go.
Your Highness!
Help him!
Push!
Search the premises.
Shut the gate once the sun sets!
Go inside.
Your Royal Highness!
Help them over there!
Your Royal Highness! Are you okay?
Your Royal Highness!
You must go.
They're starting to wake up.
Your Royal Highness.
What are you doing? Push!
Your Royal Highness, we don't have time.
You must go!
I'm different!
I'm different from those
who abandoned these people,
and I'm different
from the Haewon Cho Clan!
I will never abandon these people!
Get them on!
-Hurry up!
-Hurry. Get on.
Hurry!
Get on!
Run!
-Where's the other wagon?
-I don't know!
Monster ahead!
-Prepare to close the gate!
-They're coming!
Hurry! Run!
Close the gate!
Are you all right?
The elderly and children
will hide in the shed,
and anyone who can fight, grab a weapon!
Yes, Your Royal Highness!
Come this way! This way.
How long until we arrive in Sangju?
Well, since the weather is nice,
we should arrive in two days.
Are you sure it's safe there?
Sangju is the second largest city
after Hanyang,
and it's filled with soldiers
who will protect us.
Don't worry.
What was that sound?
My son.
My precious son...
My son...
Hey, who...
-Hey, shine the light over there.
-Okay.
Is someone down there?
Monster! There's a monster!
Help!
It's the sun.
The sun is up, Your Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness.
The monsters are going away.
They are all gone!
They are all gone. You can come out.
Seo-bi.
Your Royal Highness.
May I come in?
Come in.
I think you should come out.
Thank you, Your Royal Highness.
Thank you for saving us!
-Thank you!
Treat the wounds
and prepare some food to eat.
Yes, Your Highness.
All done.
Here.
-Don't use your right hand for a while.
-Okay. Thank you.
Is that all there is
for the people to eat?
Even that is difficult to obtain.
It was hard enough with the war,
but they were taxed hard, too.
How could they have food?
I heard they ate anything living,
even insects.
Your Highness.
Bring those children to me.
Your Royal Highness.
You kids!
Come here.
Get over here!
Your Royal Highness.
We deserve to be killed for what we did.
What is this?
It's food.
Now, go on and play.
Give this to them.
-Your Royal Highness.
-I am fine.
I am sick of it anyway.
Everyone, gather round.
Gather round.
This is from the Crown Prince.
What is this?
It's meat.
-Meat? This is meat?
-Meat?
This is meat!
Thank you, Your Royal Highness.
-It's meat!
-It really is meat.
How do we eat this?
-Make some soup with this.
-Is this really meat?
Look! It got bigger!
They are happy with the food.
What will you do now?
I will go to Lord Ahn Hyeon in Sangju.
What is it?
I am from Sangju.
If you wish to go to Sangju,
I will be your guide.
How can we trust you?
Who are you, exactly?
I'm merely one of the people.
Then how do you know how to shoot a gun?
I learned while serving in the war.
You shot a monster right in the forehead
as it charged at you.
Your skills are better than most soldiers.
Who are you?
What is it? Are they the ones
who attacked us yesterday?
-What do we do?
-It must be them!
Traitor Lee Chang, the Crown Prince,
must hear this!
"The criminal, who must be transferred
to Hanyang for investigation,
defied the King's command
and killed the commander of the Royal Army
who came to arrest him.
This crime...
committed by the Crown Prince,
who must uphold the nation's laws,
is an unforgivable act of treason!
The traitor who defied the King's command
must come out voluntarily and be bound!
If you don't come out voluntarily
right this instant,
it will be considered a defiance
against the King's command,
and thus, you will be punished
severely by the law!"
What is he talking about?
Did they just say he is a traitor?
They must be seriously mistaken.
-Right.
-You should go and talk to them.
Your Royal Highness, let me handle it.
Chief!
I, the Crown Prince's guard,
will come out!
Your Majesty's son
killed my son.
I will do the same to him.
No.
I will be merciless
and kill him brutally.
Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness! It's dangerous! Run!
You must flee!
Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness. Are you okay?
It's my fault.
-Because of me...
-That is correct.
-This is all because of you.
-Shut up!
If we are to survive, you must step up!
-Otherwise,
we will all die!
They have a gun!
Gun squad, come with me.
The rest of you, stand guard.
They have one gun.
-Have them march in.
-Yes, sir.
At the entrance.
Search the area!
He has been shot.
That way!
Now!
Come on out!
It's dangerous for you to stay.
Go to Yangsan before the sun sets. Hurry!
To the south.
To the west!
We were fooled.
It was the guard.
He knew our signals and led us astray.
Bring the horses. We must chase them.
It's too late.
No need to rush.
Won't you chase them?
There is no need.
I know where they are heading to.
SANGJU, AHN HYEON
-Report it.
-Yes, sir.
The signal fire has been lit!
HANYANG
The signal fire...
The signal fire has been lit.
I heard that the signal fire is lit.
Will there be a war?
Did Japan invade again?
Nothing has been confirmed yet.
We must gather the troops.
We must act before they march into Hanyang
like last time.
I must see His Majesty.
What do you mean?
The signal fire is burning high
up on Cheoncheonryeong.
Our nation is in peril.
We cannot waste a single second.
I'll go to the King's palace.
But...
I agree with Chief Scholar.
I must see His Majesty as well.
But...
Minister, where are you going?
He is going to the King's palace.
-The King's palace?
-Yes.
My lord, wait for us.
Step aside.
I must speak with His Majesty.
We were ordered not to let outsiders in.
How dare you!
Do you not know who we are?
Step back!
How dare you draw your sword at us?
Step aside!
How dare you!
Are you that desperate to see His Majesty?
My lord, I tried to stop them.
You should see His Majesty.
You all are core officials
who lead this nation.
Step aside.
Let us go see His Majesty together.
What do you think you are doing?
Your Majesty,
the signal fire has been lit.
We must see His Majesty
and fix the situation.
Please withdraw your command.
Even if it's an emergency,
how could you barge in like this
when His Majesty is gravely ill?
Please step aside.
We cannot hide
His Majesty's illness any longer.
Father!
Why are you doing this?
We shall go inside.
What are you doing?
Show them out!
Step aside.
Announce us.
Your Majesty, Chief State Councillor
is here to see you.
The sun will set soon.
I think His Majesty is asleep.
His Majesty will wake up soon.
Have a seat.
Come this way.
You have not seen him in a while.
You should see him up close.
Raise the blinds.
Do you know why the signal fire
has been lit from the south?
It's neither due to an invasion
nor a war.
A disease has spread.
It's a scary disease
that makes one sleep
when the sun rises and crave
the flesh and blood of living people
when the sun sets.
-Your Majesty!
-Please be healthy and live a long life!
Look carefully.
This is the King of Joseon,
the father of the tens
of thousands of subjects of the land.
Is this why court ladies' corpses
are carried out daily?
Is it all because of this disease?
What if I say it's?
If he lost his mind due to an illness
and craved human flesh,
is he no longer the King?
If he is not the King, who is he?
He is alive, as you can see.
Do you deny that he is the King?
Is that why you lured
the Crown Prince and scholars
and schemed rebellion
to steal the King's throne?
Lord Cho, what do you...
Although His Majesty
contracted a grave disease,
he is still the King of Joseon
and the lord of the people.
For rebelling against His Majesty
and coveting the throne,
your family should be annihilated.
Arrest Chief Scholar Kim Sun immediately
and behead him.
As for Prince Lee Chang,
who fled to the south,
he shall be deposed
and poisoned to death.
Palace guards, take the criminal Kim Sun
to the Royal Investigation Bureau!
We will begin Chief Scholar Kim Sun's
interrogation!
Since when did you plan all of this?
You should have discussed it with me
if you planned to do something like this.
I may be your daughter,
but I'm the mother of this nation.
I will kill them all.
Every single one of them.
I will kill the Crown Prince, who killed
my son, and everyone who follows him
without any mercy.
I will not forgive anyone
who gets in my way.
So,
don't dare to stop me...
ever again.
I did not put you where you are now
so that you can get in my way.
Give birth to a son.
It has to be a son.
That is what you must do.
Don't worry, Father.
I will give birth to a son
who will succeed Beom-il
in the Haewon Cho Clan...
and inherit the throne.
Subtitle translation by Jeong Lee