Sub by kisscambodia
♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 48
Come on.
Watch strictly over that direction.
It’s there.
-Keep a close eye.
-Aye.
There are too many of them.
We can’t break in.
What’s in the barrels?
That’s where we store the kerosene.
Be quick.
It’s a good thing.
Tell us.
Where are your companions?
I don’t know!
Stay away from me!
If you don’t tell us,
I’ll kill you!
Go!
Animal characters made by CG
Let’s go.
Hurry!
Animal characters made by CG
-Catch him!
-Stop running!
Hurry.
Leave.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Thank you.
We were told
that our granaries were targeted.
You two, keep a close eye on it.
Don’t let anything go wrong.
Otherwise,
you would be beheaded!
-Aye!
Alcohol
-Go! Go!
-It’s the village!
It’s the village!
Look over there.
Go.
Lord Lu.
Your sister Pathetic Clam died
when stealing the tokens.
Shen Tianshu discarded her
as a chessman.
But you’re still fighting for him.
Is it worth it?
What a loser you are!
Weed Spirit.
You saw the mark?
Yes.
-Fei.
Well done!
Gu Tianxian.
You’d better be killed by me
than be defeated by our enemy.
Don’t disgrace us.
Kill them all!
What’s happening?
Retreat!
I’m back.
Chuchu.
You’re finally back.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
Thank you, everybody.
Miss Wu, you’re welcome.
It’s General’s Wen’s order.
I should do my best.
Everyone.
I’m leaving, then.
Let’s go!
-Aye!
-Go!
Hurry!
What do we do next?
So many Demons fail
to get any clue
for the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
I think we should start from the poem.
Sheng.
Did you find something?
The sun shines
over that place.
There are birds
on the tree.
The valley is beautiful,
where birds sing beautifully.
Does the second half refer to a place
where the sun shines
and the birds sing?
Precisely.
I think that’s the place
the poem refers to.
Let’s go there.
-Go.
Frost after autumn rains.
Coolness and silence in the forest.
Run!
Run, everybody!
Help!
-Run!
-Help!
-Run, everybody!
Run!
Help!
Be careful!
-Come on.
-Hurry! Run!
Lord.
These villagers ran away
from the Big Medicine Valley.
Seems like
not everything is under control
of Giant Leopard and Hearing Ox.
Someone strong must have gone there
and disturbed them.
Someone held back two lords
at the same time?
In this world,
there are very few people
who have such great martial arts.
Could it be...?
Go.
Aye.
If I guess correctly,
this is the entrance
to the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Sheng.
Did you get it wrong?
It doesn’t look like an entrance.
It’s a mere forest.
If Mr. Li is right,
the entrance can’t be opened
unless we find the mechanism.
You’re right.
Let’s look for it.
Report!
Lo... Lord.
Zhou Fei and her companions
haven’t left the Big Medicine Valley.
Instead, they got into the forest.
They escaped, but didn’t leave.
Can they be looking for something?
Follow them.
If you find anything fishy,
tell me immediately.
Aye.
What did you press?
A stone over there.
That’s the mechanism.
It looks like a musical instrument,
named...
Xun.
Lingxun comes from four directions.
Lingxun?
Did I remember it in a wrong order?
It should be Xunling.
That explains.
There’s another name for Xunling,
the sound of Xun.
It means
four songs are played.
There are another four places like this.
Where are the other three directions?
According to the Eight-trigram
Formation map,
it should be the east, west and south.
Well,
let’s go separate ways.
Let’s look for them separately
and come back later.
After all the troubles,
we’re finally going to find
the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
We’re not sure what will happen.
The farther we go,
the more cautious we should be.
Miss Zhou.
Don’t worry.
I’ve had a divination lately.
We’re destined to stay
and help each other.
As long as we’re together,
we will turn ill luck into good.
If you’re actually good at divination,
why don’t you find the mechanism first?
Here’s my good luck.
I’ve found it.
Let’s go.
Chuchu.
When I left, you gave me a pouch.
What was that for?
I used to keep the pouch with me,
which blessed me from danger.
I gave it to you,
so that you would be safe.
Sorry.
I made you worried again.
Look.
There’s some noise.
You know what?
The mechanism must be in the rocks.
We can’t easily find it.
Think about Lyu Run.
He designed the entrance
with the Eight-trigram Formation.
He was awesome.
What an idiot you are!
If it hadn’t been for him,
we would have found
the Color of Ocean and Heaven long ago.
Stop talking nonsense.
Hurry and look for the mechanism.
Come and have a look.
Is this the mechanism?
Try it.
Come over.
-Hurry.
Look!
The entrance has appeared!
Why is this
the Forbidden Hall of Qi School?
Can the Color of Ocean and Heaven
be in this place?
Be careful, everybody.
Go.
Tiankuang.
-Lord!
You look serious.
What’s on your mind?
Lord.
You’re just in time.
I’ve possibly found the entrance
to the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Let me take you there.
Where birds sing beautifully.
It’s indeed the place.
Ying Hecong.
What are these?
Five Poison Saints.
Five Poison Saints?
They’re evil gods in the south.
Villagers who believe in witchcraft
pray to them
so that they won’t be hurt
by poisonous insects.
But later,
some bad men used them
to pretend to be mysterious.
Many weird pictures are on the wall.
What do they mean?
I can’t recognize all the marks.
I can only have a guess.
It’s about a totem
or a sacrifice.
Look at this picture.
This man died.
Their priest brought him
back to life
by using a book.
Is it the Book of Almighty Medicine?
Perhaps.
Here’s a door.
Let’s go have a look.
Be careful with your blade.
Everybody, look out
for the wall and ground.
Bonehead.
Seems like this place
extends to the valley.
I wonder where
the Color of Ocean and Heaven is hidden.
In this place, there are many formations
and secret chambers.
If we’re careless,
we may trigger the mechanism
and be caught in danger.
So...
-Fei!
-Xie Yun!
Fei!
They fell in a mechanism.
Let’s search the place
and see if we can open it.
Yes. Let’s look for the mechanism.
Okay.
Watch out!
Mechanisms are everywhere.
It’s too dangerous.
Let’s move forward.
Be very careful.
-Okay.
Sheng.
Sheng! Chuchu!
Yan!
We’re in trouble.
What are you sighing for?
I didn’t expect Dim
to be so fragile as well.
It already has cracks and cuts
on the edge.
You don’t use blades. What do you know?
Dim has been the best blade
I’ve ever used.
Where’s Ying Hecong?
Isn’t he behind us?
He didn’t catch up?
Wait a minute.
Don’t you think we’re circling?
Can Ying Hecong be lost?
Let’s go find him.
Wait a second.
There’s some noise.
What are you doing?
Why are you there?
Come this way.
Sub by Dramacool.ae
Please.
Guard at the entrance
with your men and private soldiers.
Don’t let anyone come out.
Aye, Lord.
Shen Tianshu
is so vigilant against me.
The door can’t be opened.
Why is here a stone chamber?
Yeah.
All daily necessities are available.
Looks like someone once lived here.
This is underground.
Who could have lived here?
Door.
There’s a door over there!
Let’s go have a look.
Be careful.
Watch out for traps.
Someone must try it.
You... You go.
Fine, then!
Be careful.
The door can’t be opened.
There must be another mechanism.
It’s icy.
No wonder it feels so cold here.
Weed Spirit.
I guess the one who lived here
must be fat and afraid of heat.
That’s why he lived here.
Why are you still kidding?
No way. Your body feels cold.
We can’t stay here for long.
Let’s check if there’s another exit.
I’m not jealous of immortals,
but the lovers
Painted in the spring of the 35th year,
by Lyu Run
It’s a painting of Priest Lyu Run.
Lyu Run?
Lyu Run is said
to have found a secret place
where nobody knew
to get ready for his death.
I think
this is where he stayed before he died.
Lord.
The arrow was cut.
They must have triggered the mechanism.
Let’s go separate ways.
Lord.
Mechanism here was triggered, too.
Seemed like someone was here.
Get in and have a look.
Aye.
In the Forbidden Hall of Qi School,
there are many mechanisms.
But there’s no decent treasure at all.
Lord.
This painting is wrong.
The old man on the right
uses white chessmen.
But he’s hesitating with a black one.
You have no idea.
Lyu Run was forever engrossed
in pharmacology and martial arts.
He was so obsessed
that he even remained within doors
when he was old.
The chess game in the painting
is very likely to be the true faith
he got in his twilight years.
True faith?
We don’t know why he destroyed it.
What a pity!
I practiced martial arts
in both Yin and Yang ways,
just like the black and white chessmen.
The last level should be Yang.
I abandoned Yin,
trying to make a breakthrough in Yang.
According to the painting,
I use the white chessmen,
but I guess about the black.
Don’t touch it.
What if it’s poisonous?
I’m impervious to all poisons, aren’t I?
I lost my father at a little age.
My master adopted me
and named me Run.
I was raised and educated.
Run?
It’s Lyu Run’s testament, I guess.
No wonder
we saw the statue of poison saints
when we came in.
It’s said
that his lover died of sickness.
Lyu Run was so overwhelmed with grief.
Therefore,
he spent his whole life
studying medical skills,
trying to figure out
if there’s a real way
to bring the dead back to life.
Did he find anything
after studying books of poison saints
for such a long time?
Phoenix Grass was from ancient times.
There is little available in this world.
I made all Phoenix Grass into pills
and put them all in this box.
Taking a few of them
and digesting them
with extreme Yang force
will detoxify all poisons.
There’s no more Phoenix Pill.
It opened automatically!
Not automatically. I opened it!
Can it be opened?
No one is here.
We’re stuck here.
These are extreme Yin things
we can hardly see in a century.
So many!
It’s a dead end.
Shall we backtrack?
Let’s go.
Ying Hecong.
Look what a condition we’re in!
Why are you still
checking the moldy herbs?
Help to look for the exit.
It’s Yan’s voice.
Yan!
Since we can hear her voice,
it means there’s a crack.
If there’s a crack, there’s a mechanism.
Let’s look for it.
Okay.
Bonehead.
This looks like a mechanism.
Try it.
Why is it me again?
Ying Hecong.
Here’s a mechanism. Come and turn it.
Oh, you can do it.
Just do it. Hurry.
It can’t be turned.
This can’t be a mechanism.
Let’s keep looking.
Look at this.
Looks like it was pushed.
Yan.
Sheng, keep the door open!
Are you alright?
We’re fine.
The door is the only exit here.
Anything special in this chamber?
No.
Oh, Sheng.
Did you see Fei and Xie Yun?
No.
Our priority
is to find Fei soon.
I’ve got to know
about the mechanisms.
Remember.
Do no touch anything.
-Go.
Report!
Lord.
Li Sheng and his companions
are right ahead.
Go.
-Aye.
-Go.
What a complicated place!
I’m a bit dizzy, walking around.
I didn’t expect to meet you so soon.
It’s you?
Young girl.
Where’s Zhou Fei?
You’re the mastermind
who poisoned my aunt!
I’ll avenge her today!
Yan.
We can’t defeat him. Go.
Let them lead the way.
What’s this book?
Methods of Qi School.
It looks like Tao Teh King
Taoist Priest Chongxiao gave me.
But...
The second half looks different.
Fei.
I didn’t expect the method
to be so strong and fiery.
It is.
This book looks strange.
You’d better stop reading.
Fei.
This method feels so strange.
Stop reading it.
I’m afraid you will...
We have no other way.
We can’t get out, anyway.
I’d like to have a try.
Chuchu just pulled it open.
Let me push it!
Help me.
Push it harder!
I am…
Do you need any help?
We’ve got many more men.
Come and try
if you’re not scared of the mechanisms.
Push it hard!
Go on with it.
I’ll hold them back.
Attack!
Come and help me!
It’s open. Hurry! Go.
Go!
Are you alright?
Why is here another door?
No wonder it’s a place of Qi School.
A school has many doors.
The two stone phoenixes by the door
could be the mechanism to the door.
One on the left
and the other on the right.
A real one and a false one.
If we pick the false one,
we’ll trigger the trap.
There are mechanisms and doors.
Why do smart people like you
always do such complicated things?
You’re just too stupid to understand!
Go.
They’re right ahead. Hurry.
It’s too late.
Pick one and try our luck.
What...
It’s open.
If we could easily guess the right one,
it wouldn’t be a mechanism.
Go!
They’re over there. Block the door.
Yang Jin, give me your blade.
Stop him!
Lord, I was too slow.
Lord, here’s a mechanism.
Watch your steps.
Since there are so many mechanisms,
there must be hollow parts
in the walls.
They could be the fragile area.
Go find it out.
-Aye.
Look for it!
What’s that?
I’ll go have a look.
These patterns
look a bit familiar to me.
Stop looking.
Smash the door open.
Aye.
Shen Tianshu is catching up.
We can’t pin him down
unless we find
the Color of Ocean and Heaven.
Stop.
Knock again here.
Smash it.
Aye.
What are the Demons doing?
Pulling down the chamber?
Apparently, they’re trying to break in.
I don’t think it’s so easy
to break through the walls.
Mechanisms are everywhere.
The walls may be hollow.
If they keep smashing,
the walls will be broken soon.
Fei.
Fei, what’s wrong?
What happened to me?
I can’t even speak.
Fei.
Feels like
all my energy is being extracted
by the strong method.
I’m having less energy.
Why is this happening?
It doesn’t feel right.
Sheng, what did you find?
There are five patterns on the wall.
The one in the middle seems
to be half missing.
This half, I guess.
Stop.
Why can’t the patterns match
no matter how I observe?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪