Sub by kisscambodia
♪Lights of swords are like
a splash of rivers♪
♪Shadows of swords cover the seasons♪
♪The clear water cuts off the gorge♪
♪Which is facing the armed army♪
♪Missing a pot of cold wine♪
♪Drunk in the middle of sand♪
♪The place of peace of mind
is my hometown♪
♪But my hometown is by your side♪
♪Who forgets about the grudges
in the past♪
♪Don’t blame the west wind
for your tears♪
♪To meet and to part are like a dream♪
♪Well-armed with armor and weapons♪
♪Where the surging river is going♪
♪Together we go to the end of the world♪
Legend of Fei
Episode 47
Found it!
It’s planted there on purpose,
but I can’t move it.
There must be something else.
I believe
the plant here
is the “Catalpa branch” in the poem.
Could it
be the water?
Water?
Check it out.
Let me try again.
It’s moving!
Lu Tiankuang,
Lord Shen assigned you
to assist me.
Don’t cross the line.
Fine.
By “assist you”,
he means he doesn’t trust you.
I don’t trust you.
So?
Aren’t you always eager to battle me?
Wait until
we find the treasure.
Bring it on.
Report!
Lord, we found a village ahead.
Bad news!
A bunch of...
A bunch of martial artists are outside.
How did they get in?
What’s happening?
Why are they here?
No idea.
They look scary.
Guard our village!
-Let’s go!
-Gear up!
-Go, go, go!
Come on. Let’s go.
Let’s go!
Calm down.
I’m Gu Tianxian,
also known as Giant Leopard.
He... he’s a Demon!
Demon?
I thought no one could recognize me
in this remote village.
Now that you do,
you’ve spared me the trouble.
What... what do you want?
We’re farmers.
We... we have no money.
-Yes.
-We don’t have anything.
I need nothing from you,
only some information.
Are you aware of
The Color of Ocean and Heaven?
Why bother asking them?
Just seize them all.
What is this?
What to do?
Lord Shen,
I was told
that Lord Gu and Lord Lu
had located the entrance of
the Big Medicine Valley.
Very well.
Let’s go join them.
Yes.
Mr. Xie,
I’m here waiting for you
under the Third Prince’s order.
Zichen?
What’s up?
It’s important.
Can we talk somewhere else?
This is His Highness’s letter to you.
Gathering troops...
What’s wrong?
Zichen said
enemies have gathered
troops at the border.
Their intention is unknown yet.
But once they launch attacks,
chaos will arise.
So he needs my advice.
Forget that.
I can’t leave now.
Go ahead.
He needs your help
or he wouldn’t have asked you.
Anyway, it’ll take us a while
to find the entrance to
the Big Medicine Valley.
Just go.
Fine.
I’ll make it quick.
Take care of yourself.
See you soon.
Yes!
Please, Mr. Xie.
Lord Gantang,
how’s your wife?
Thanks for your help,
Jinrong is still
in a coma
because of the residual poison,
but
her pulse has become steadier.
If you’re worried about the Fortress
and can’t wait to go back,
we can take care of her.
No need.
I’ve asked those kids
to handle things at home.
Aren’t you concerned?
It’s their responsibility after all.
They can’t avoid it.
I admire you for knowing to let go.
And...
what about the Anping Army?
It’s also fine.
Then why are you frowning?
If we don’t sacrifice ourselves
to save others, who will?
Thank you for enlightening me.
Stop.
Is everything alright, sir?
What was that noise?
This area is a war zone.
Such noise is common.
By the way,
is General Wen Yu stationed nearby?
Yes.
After the Demons raided Huxiang,
General Wen
has been battling enemies in this area.
Cities have changed hands repeatedly.
I see.
I need to see him.
Let’s visit him first.
Sir,
considering the situation here,
His Highness asked us specifically
not to hang around.
So
would you rather let me go there alone
or sneak out
when you aren’t looking?
I’m sorry.
Alright. Let’s go.
Let’s go.
Heard something over there.
Me too.
It’s a boy.
Fei, put away your blade
or he’ll be scared.
Sweetie,
come here.
Careful. Don’t get hurt.
Come.
Their wounds
are still fresh.
Sword wounds.
The victims seemed to be farmers.
They might be villagers in
the Big Medicine Valley.
Who would kill them?
This is the south of the state.
Does the court have no control here?
It’s close to the frontline
where the war never ceases.
Anyone can occupy this place.
Locals have suffered a lot.
This is strange, though.
Stop!
Sweetie,
where are you going?
I’m going home.
Going home?
If he lives in the Big Medicine Valley
and tries to go back,
he may
lead us there.
Off you go.
General, His Majesty has arrived.
-General Wen.
-Your Majesty.
Skip the formality.
You may leave.
Give us a minute.
Yes.
General Wen,
You must’ve learned about
Lord Gantang’s situation.
He had asked me to get prepared
before his departure.
I’ve also heard about
your condition.
Do take care of yourself.
Thanks to Fei,
I’ve taken three herbs
to suppress the poison.
I’m fine for now.
She’s done so much
for you.
That’s all the more reason
to look after yourself.
I wonder
how Lord Gantang is.
He’s left the Fortress
for some reason.
Everything will be fine.
I can manage things here.
Don’t worry.
Your Majesty,
do you
have any future plans?
That’s
what I’m here for.
I’m all ears.
Aside from your stance,
how is the state overall
during the reign of the Chens?
I’m only a soldier.
It’s not my place to judge.
Relax, General Wen.
It’s just small talk.
Take this area as an example.
It’s relatively peaceful
despite occasional conflicts.
Locals have roofs over their heads.
I once said to Fei
all sects will end eventually.
So will
dynasties.
New ones are built
at the cost of innocent lives.
At this point,
are we going to inflict
such suffering on the masses again?
If you ask me,
like I said,
people come first,
followed by the state
and the one ruling it.
If I could
bring peace to people,
I’d die
with no regrets.
Your Majesty,
back then,
I chose to join this army
for returning a favor
and for friendship.
Your ambition has made me realized
what I should do in the future.
Your Majesty, General Wen.
What’s up?
We’ve spotted Yu Wenzhi’s troops here.
How many are they?
Only a few.
But what brings them here is unclear.
General Wen,
when was the last time you battled him?
15 days ago.
About two weeks.
And nothing happened
since then?
No.
I also
find that odd.
I was a commander years back,
but you’ve gained more experience
through battles with General Wang.
I dare not to jump to conclusions.
Your Majesty,
you’d better leave with the Chens.
It’s too dangerous here.
I don’t want to get you in danger.
The terrain here is complex.
Why don’t you dispatch scouts
to check again
within a 10-kilometer radius
in case Yu Wenzhi is
plotting against us?
Go ahead.
Yes.
They must be
up to something.
What’s wrong?
He must’ve
learned how to do all that
from his parents.
The rocks
may be the keys.
Push that.
What?
What did you say?
Push that.
It’s open!
Fei,
what are you doing?
Leaving a sign for Xie Yun.
Let’s go.
Sub by Dramacool.ae
So many people
are living here.
Watch out for the Demons!
Lock men and women separately.
Move!
What are you looking at? Go!
This place is filled with
the Demons and troops.
The Demons here are even more
than those sent to the Fortress.
-Looks like they’re
-Go!
gathering the villagers together.
Move!
Hey, you, stop dawdling!
Fei, could we be wrong?
This place doesn’t look like a vault.
Open your eyes!
It must be important,
or the Demons wouldn’t be here.
Follow them
and see how things go.
Go! Hurry up!
-Keep up!
-Move!
Go!
-Go!
-Go inside!
Hurry!
They’ve caged so many people.
Women and kids are locked up separately
as hostages
to better control men.
Lords,
villagers of the Big Medicine Valley
are kept in the caves in this area.
Have our grains been put away?
Yes. They’re safe.
What do you
need those villagers for?
I don’t need to
explain it to you.
Do you think
you can handle them alone?
Let’s see.
Vulgar!
You think you’re better than me?
You and your sister
have brought shame
on Demons Manor.
Excuse me?
What do you mean?
Your sister hooked up
with Yu Wenzhi in secret.
Who knows how much
dirty business you two have done
behind Lord Shen’s back.
Nonsense!
All that she did
was for Demons Manor,
or she wouldn’t have
been killed by Zhou Fei!
Our loyalty is unquestionable.
Have you found the entrance
to The Color of Ocean and Heaven?
Not yet, Lord Gu.
Our men have been looking for it.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Follow me.
Both Lu Tiankuang
and Gu Tianxian are here.
They haven’t found the entrance yet.
I’m afraid
they’ve caged the villagers to...
Do you mean
they’re using them
to find the treasure?
Those Demons
will do anything for it.
-Spare us!
Hey, you!
Brother!
Where’s The Color of Ocean and Heaven?
-I don’t know.
-Don’t kill me, please!
Speak!
Spare me, please.
Listen up.
Tell us where
The Color of Ocean and Heaven is,
or all of you will be dead.
We’re outnumbered.
Let’s go.
Sheng!
I’ll hold him and walk behind you.
We can’t leave them there.
Yan,
there’s only a few of us.
We aren’t their match.
And
don’t forget about our mission.
We need help
to get them out.
Are you saying...?
Ask General Wen Yu for help.
I heard he and his troops are nearby.
Send him a message
and ask him to come over.
Then we can continue the search.
How long
will that take?
By the time we’re back,
all those villagers are already dead.
Fei,
say something!
Back then,
when my skills were poor,
I dared to challenge Dragon Master.
Now, they’re much better,
but I feel as if they tied me up.
Everyone has burdens.
Even if people aren’t afraid of death,
there are things more important than it.
Should I
stick my neck out for strangers?
Fei,
what’s on your mind? Fei!
Are we...
giving them up?
Not exactly.
But we need a plan.
Tell me
where The Color of Ocean and Heaven is
if you want to live.
Otherwise,
I’ll take one of you
every hour
until you cough up the answer.
Li Sheng,
you’re hesitating
because you don’t want to
take risks or feel guilty.
I have no choice.
Do you have better ideas?
No.
Zhou Fei,
just say the word.
I need to find
The Color of Ocean and Heaven,
the cure to Bone-chilling
and go back to the Fortress.
But none of them
sounds justified.
They’re important
to me,
but once I say them out loud...
Chuchu, let’s go.
-Fei.
-Get up.
Fei,
come on!
Sheng,
if we left like this,
once we got back,
would you dare to tell my mother
that we left those people to die?
Yes, Sheng.
Fei,
two Demons and their lackeys are there.
If you acted recklessly
and got killed,
what would happen to Mr. Xie?
Who’d save him?
What about the others?
And your mother and father.
Would you rather
break their hearts again?
I believe my parents
and Xie Yun
will understand.
Fortress of the Forty-Eight
doesn’t raise cowards.
If we back down,
they’ll be more disappointed.
Zhou Fei,
although we’ve battled more than once,
I support you this time.
Are we going to rescue them now?
Sheng,
I agree with them.
That’s great.
Let’s go.
Fine.
We need a strategy
to get them out
successfully.
That’s the best we can do at the moment.
One more thing.
We need someone
to send a message to General Wen.
Who will do it?
I won’t.
Sheng,
let me stay
and help you.
I have an idea.
What is it?
What idea?
Close your eyes.
-Why?
-What for?
Do it.
Alright.
Draw a stick.
What is this?
We’re taught to respect all beings.
Every year during festivals,
we’ll have our fortune told.
I don’t get how the rituals work,
but basically, we follow heaven’s will.
Let’s each draw a stick.
Whoever gets the longest one
will be the messenger.
Deal?
Are you insane?
If it’s us, who will fight the enemies?
Never mind.
There are no other ways.
Not me.
Not me, either.
It’s me.
Chuchu,
I know you’re worried about us,
but sending the message
is equally important.
Without General Wen,
we won’t be able to
get out on our own.
I see.
I’ll go.
The Demons outside are many.
Be very careful.
Chuchu, come here.
Chuchu,
do you know where our nearest
secret service is?
I do.
I paid attention to that
when you checked them.
But
I need to see General Wen first.
You may have to enter the war zone.
How are you going to find him?
He’s traveling with a large troop.
They must’ve left tracks along the way.
They can be my guide.
No.
That’s too dangerous.
Relax. I hate to leave, too,
but I must
send the message to him
for the safety of the villagers.
Everything will be fine.
This soft armor,
made by the one
who crafted Mrs. Yin’s Muyun Gauze,
is impenetrable,
but
not able to withstand strong force.
Don’t battle those
with powerful palms head-on.
Just run as fast as you can.
I see.
This is another gadget he made.
I’ve never used it before.
It’s said to be a hidden weapon
to protect you in danger.
If the target is within 10 meters,
stay calm
and shoot.
Even Yang Jin
and Li Sheng can’t dodge the hit.
Got it.
Take these, too, if you can.
What are they?
Snake poison
and knockout drops our people made.
I’m not sure which is which,
but they’re all here.
Come on!
Can you be more irresponsible?
Still, they’re better than nothing.
I’ll take them.
Be careful.
This boy will go with me.
It’s dangerous for him to be here.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Take care.
Sheng,
you should go back.
Take care.
Keep this
and take care as well.
What?
You’ll take both of them?
Lower your voice.
Yes.
Or will you do it?
Who is it
to battle two enemies?
Sheng,
here’s what I think.
I can propose a challenge
to battle Gu Tianxian and Lu Tiankuang.
Perhaps they’ll
follow the rules
and take up the challenge.
That’ll buy you some time
to get the villagers out.
Rules?
Would those animals care about rules?
What if they come at you together?
What will you do?
I’m not stupid.
They aren’t exactly friends.
I’ll stall them
for a while.
I’ve got these.
What are they?
Our pharmacists made these, too.
Drop them on the ground,
and they’ll produce smoke
enough to paralyze others.
Then we can get in
to rescue the hostages.
I’ve brought whistling arrows with me.
Seeing sparks they create,
they may think
we’re setting the valley on fire.
That’ll be our chance to escape.
What about those women and kids?
They should be kept nearby.
I... I’ll get them out.
Yan,
are your three moves
enough to do that?
Sheng said
they’re loosely guarded.
And
I’ve mastered more than three moves.
Those Demons aren’t my match.
-Yan,
-Alright.
take them all.
Be very careful.
Once Li Sheng and I are done,
we’ll join you.
I see.
Remember,
if things look bad,
just run away.
Stay away from danger.
Safety matters the most.
Let’s go.
Lords,
the heiress to the South Blade,
Zhou Fei,
is here to challenge you.
The South Blade?
What?
Why is she here?
How many are they?
Just her alone.
That girl
is a cunning fox.
There must be a trap.
It’s just a girl.
Don’t be paranoid.
Now that she’s here,
I’ll avenge my sister’s death on her.
Let’s go.
Lu Tiankuang!
Tell the guards to stay alert.
Let me know
if anyone breaks in.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Who are you?
Anping Army.
Do you serve under General Wen Yu?
Who exactly are you?
How do you know our general?
They must be General Wen’s men.
I’m with the Fortress
of the Forty-Eight.
I have a message for General Wen
and I need to see him.
It’s urgent.
Please trust me.
Zhou Fei,
I’m here.
It’s been a while,
Lord Lu.
I’m
going to kill you
to avenge my sister’s death.
Brace up!
Check carefully!
Yes.
Report! Report!
Lord Gu,
the cave is under attack.
They’re trying to rescue villagers.
How many are they?
Not too many.
Only two or three.
But they’re highly skilled.
That’s a distraction.
Let us out!
Move! Get in!
Hurry!
Bonehead is right.
Women and kids are kept in the back.
Let us out! Let us out!
Please let us go.
Step back! Step back!
Be quiet!
Calm down. I’m here to get you out.
How did you sneak out?
I...
Get in.
Stay inside,
or I’ll break your legs.
What are you doing here?
Zhou Fei’s sudden appearance
and sneak attack on the cave
are clearly distractions.
Don’t lecture me.
What are Li Sheng
and Yang Jin doing?
What’s taking them so long?
Oh, no!
Yu Wenzhi’s troops are here.
Go!
We’re here to help you.
It’s them!
Seize them!
What to do? We’re doomed.
I’ll stall them for you.
A stranger
is risking his life for you.
How could you give up?
Even if you don’t care about your lives,
think about your parents
and wives.
Your boys are little.
Do you want to see them die?
He’s right.
We can’t give up.
Yes. We still have a chance to live.
We can’t die.
Don’t be scared.
I’m here to get you out.
Trust me.
There will be a mess outside.
Carry the seniors and kids.
We can get out.
It’s bad.
There are so many of them,
including seniors.
Snake keeper!
I’ve killed them all.
Let’s go.
Okay. Let’s go.
I won’t leave without my elder sister.
Where is she?
She’s locked up in the northwest cave
by those bad people.
Lead the way.
We’ll get her out.
-Thanks.
-Let’s go.
Let’s go.
Go, go, go.
Animal characters made by CG
Snakes! Snakes!
Let’s go. Come on.
Animal characters made by CG
Why are there snakes?
Let’s go!
Animal characters made by CG
Sheng! Yang Jin!
We’re here!
Great.
Yan, are you alright?
Open it, Yang Jin.
This “snake girl” helped us.
Ying Hecong!
What... what are you doing here?
I said I’d go back to
the Big Medicine Valley.
Didn’t you listen?
Once I arrived,
the Demons were
holding villagers hostage.
Hadn’t I dressed up like this,
how could I’ve saved them?
Fine, fine, fine.
Let’s go.
My snakes can only hold the Demons
for a while.
This powder will keep snakes away.
Let’s line up
and keep the snakes on one side.
Be careful.
Animal characters made by CG
Watch it.
Be careful. Mind your step.
Go.
Watch out for the snakes.
-Let’s go. Come on.
-Slow down, Father.
Be careful.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Where are you going?
You are...
Don’t be scared.
I won’t harm you.
We were locked up by the Demons
and two young men got us out.
We’re leaving this place.
Two young men?
You almost killed me.
Are you blind?
Stay out of the way!
Dog-eat-dog.
Did the Demons and Yu Wenzhi’s men
store up grains here?
If they’re on fire,
that’ll mess things up
and buy villagers
more time to leave.
Why is it all sand under the rice?
How come the door is open?
Someone must’ve laid eyes on the barn.
Let’s go check.
This isn’t the real barn.
Animal characters made by CG
It’s her!
Go on.
Where do you think you’re going?
Aren’t you a runner?
Where are Ying Hecong and Li Yan?
I’ll go find them.
No need.
They’ll be fine
with the help
of the snakes.
I’m sorry to trouble you again,
but my uncle is still
in the northeast cave.
Could you... could you get him out, too?
There must be an ambush in the back.
They wouldn’t put all eggs
in one basket.
Their grains and supplies
must be stored there.
Let’s go and see what we can do.
Maybe we can make some noise there
to help Fei out.
Yes. We can help you.
-Let us help you.
-We’ll join you.
-This way.
-Take us with you.
General,
you have a visitor from
the Fortress of the Forty-Eight
who asks to see you urgently.
Who is it?
It’s a girl.
Let her in.
Yes.
Miss,
please.
General Wen.
Miss Wu!
Miss Wu?
What are you doing
in this middle of nowhere?
By the way,
where’s Miss Zhou and the others?
Is everything alright?
We have an emergency.
Could you send troops to help them?
What’s wrong?
We entered a valley,
but found people there
locked up by the Demons and Yu Wenzhi.
We meant to rescue them
but we were outnumbered.
Please give us a hand.
It’s too risky
for you guys
to rescue them
from Yu Wenzhi’s men.
Guard!
-Yes.
-Gather our crack troops
and set out with Miss Wu.
Yes.
Thank you, General.
Be careful.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Stars flow like river♪
♪My yearning falls into the river♪
♪Now that you’re in my life♪
♪I will never be alone♪
♪I haven’t seen the mountains with you♪
♪Nor have I tied up your hair♪
♪We haven’t finished our story in chaos♪
♪The blade hasn’t been returned♪
♪I fear not to roam the world with you♪
♪When I go across the world for you♪
♪I’m willing to shed blood for you♪
♪Don’t mind whose land it is♪
♪Where is home to the snowflake♪
♪Come and melt in my embrace♪
♪The spring sun is an invisible armor
that’ll hold♪
♪The purest love is unadorned♪