Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You've waited for me without fretting
And entered my heart peacefully
You're lovely from head to toe
I'm proud that you're my woman
Jin-hwan.
What is it, Sol-i? You're scaring me.
My MP3 player battery's dead.
No, never. This is practically part of me.
You borrowed my book, too.
Are you trying to take everything from me?
Excuse me, Heon.
Heon. I made these over the weekend.
Here.
I made some cookies,
and I wanted to give you some.
Enjoy.
Please.
Hi, guys.
What's wrong?
My MP3 player battery's dead.
I see.
-Here, use mine.
-What?
-Don't you need to listen to it?
-No.
Thanks so much.
Compound relative pronouns
are formed by adding "ever"
to relative pronouns. Do you remember?
-Yes.
"Now I know one thing.
I'm still living,
even though I feel like I'm dying.
'I feel like I'm dying.
This isn't living.'
A life that echoes these words
is still a life."
Goodness. This is so sad.
Hey. Sol-i.
Wait. I only have few pages left.
What?
-Shin Sol-i.
-Yes.
Yes?
Hardly a day goes by
that you don't pay attention in class.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Give me that, too.
Pardon?
What else?
-You can't have them for a week.
-Wait, Ms. Moon.
You can take the book,
but could you please
give the MP3 player back?
No.
Sol-i.
What?
"You can take the book, but could you
please give the MP3 player back?"
I can just pay the late fee for your book,
but he can't survive
without his MP3 player for a week.
Anyway, I'm really sorry, guys.
It's okay. I have another one at the pool.
I brought a lot of heat packs today.
Who needs them?
Me! Give me two.
Ha-young, don't catch a cold.
There's a flu going around.
-I'm okay.
-I'm worried about you.
I heard it's a nasty flu.
You might have to be hospitalized
if you catch it.
I won't get to see you then.
Jeez, you're so annoying.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
This one is warmer.
I think Heon is done eating.
Heon, wait for me.
Don't you need a heat pack?
"I wish to live.
I wish to live in Cheongsan.
I wish to eat wild grapes and hardy kiwis
as I live in Cheongsan."
This song has
a very stable structure of A-A-B-A.
Su-jin, are you okay?
Hui-ji, you too?
Sir, she's been coughing
since the first period.
You should've told me sooner.
Let's go to the health office. Get up.
I'm sorry, guys. Do some self-study, okay?
-Yes, sir.
-My goodness.
You should've told me.
Hey, do you think they have the flu?
I saw the news yesterday,
and it said that you can die
from this year's flu.
Once someone catches it,
it spreads really quickly.
One out of ten will die from the flu.
How many of us will die then?
Three people?
Two already got the flu.
Who's the last one?
Stop lying, Se-hyeong.
People don't die from the flu.
They said it's serious this time.
Don't you watch the news?
Some people already died overseas.
Die?
Sol-i! Sol-i's next!
Sol-i. She's next.
A lot of vaccines have been developed.
If you get treated in time, you won't die.
No, my mom said you would.
Brother, are you okay?
You're not sick, are you?
No, I'm okay.
We should get treated in time, then.
Darn it. Look at Sol-i.
She looks really sick.
You're right. She doesn't look well.
Ha-young.
Am I going to die? I won't, will I?
Sol-i, it'll be all right.
Nothing will happen.
You should go to the health office first.
Shall I go with you?
No, it's okay. I can go on my own.
Sir, where is Su-jin?
Su-jin's condition got worse,
so she went to the hospital.
Sol-i, you have a mild fever.
Do you have any other symptoms?
No. I just sneezed twice.
I'm totally fine, Mr. Lee.
So it can't be the flu, right?
Take some medicine and rest up first.
By the way, why do you have
dark circles under your eyes?
That's strange.
Take some rest first.
Okay.
Yes, ma'am.
It's nothing serious.
Yes. Don't worry.
Yes, ma'am.
I heard back from Su-jin.
She has the flu.
It's very contagious,
so why don't we send everyone home?
Let's do it right away.
Send all the students home.
Quarantine the two students
in the health office
until the others go home.
I'll report this
to the principal right now.
Okay.
All right. Move it.
I never thought
I'd thank Su-jin for anything.
No, I should thank the flu, not Su-jin.
Flu, thank you!
-Let's go to the internet cafe.
-Sure, let's go.
Will you go see Sol-i?
Heon, aren't you going to see Sol-i?
Make up your mind right now.
Let's go without him.
Come on.
Heon, why aren't you coming?
She'd rather see you than us!
Gosh.
-Brother.
-Sol-i.
-Guys.
Why are you here?
Because we're worried.
Are you okay, Brother?
-Are you okay?
-What did the nurse say?
I'm okay. I don't feel sick at all.
By the way, where's Heon?
Heon? He couldn't come
because Ms. Moon asked him
to do something.
I see.
Brother, you'll be able to go home soon,
so don't worry.
Okay. Thanks.
You should go home now.
-See you tomorrow.
-See you.
-Bye.
-Thanks.
Bye.
OUR HAPPY TIME
Why are you here?
Well…
Could you give this to her?
To whom?
Heon asked me to give this to one of you.
Whose is this?
But that's Heon's.
Give it to me, sir.
I asked him to lend it to me.
Okay.
ON
This is Heon's voice.
I'm hearing things now.
Am I really sick?
Don't go anywhere else.
Go straight home, okay?
If you go somewhere else,
you'll get a scolding, okay?
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
Mr. Lee, when will Sol-i get to go home?
I'm still monitoring her.
You should go home first.
I'm worried about Sol-i.
When a space probe is out of order
in space,
do you know what the other probes
have to do?
They have to stand by.
So you should go home first.
He must be into space, too.
Ha-young, I think he caught the flu, too.
"Space"? "Probe"?
What was that? What was he talking about?
You don't need to know.
"Love is to endure anything
for someone gladly
and at times to take courage
to change oneself."
What's this?
-"That's what I realized through Yun-su."
-What's that?
What's he talking about?
That brat. I'll catch you.
"In our near-80 years of life,
we said we didn't know,
and simply turned away
from the dark back alleys,
the abandoned forests,
the valley of terror, the desert of truth,
and the arrogant, harsh rivers.
And we will have thought,
'It starts with a small stream
with a different name.'
-"'But it flows and reaches a place.'"
-This is Heon's voice, right?
-"'It's called the sea.'"
-Goodness, Sol-i.
She'll get all better now.
"I said quietly,
'Rest in peace.
I love you, Mother.'"
OUR HAPPY TIME
"And…
he said,
'Don't worry.'"
I'd love to be sick a bit longer.
OUR HAPPY TIME
NO, THANKS
I WON'T MARRY YOU!
No, thanks. I won't marry you!
Who in the world did this?
Come out this instant!
Open the door!
Who's in there?
Open up! One, two…
Who locked the door…
Why are you here?
Are you the only one here?
Who else is in here?
Come out. Hey.
Hui-ji, you've gotten much better.
Sol-i, you don't have a fever anymore.
You can go home now.
Okay.
Is Su-jin okay?
Yes, she'll be fine if she takes medicine
and gets some rest.
Okay, thank you.
Heon, are you done
with the apology letter?
Shall I write it for you?
I can finish it in a minute.
I'm almost done.
SHIN SOL-I
-What's up?
-Heon.
I think you should host a radio show.
No, you could be a singer.
I knew you had a great voice,
but it sounded really nice
through the speakers.
Today I started reading this book called
He Was Cool Like a Wolf.
The male protagonist is really cool.
Can you read this for me, too?
-I'll think about it.
-Really?
You didn't say no.
You said you'd think about it.
Yes.
Thank you, Heon.
Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Sol-i.
I have something to tell you
about the flu.
Flu literally causes symptoms
which are much worse than a cold.
In other words,
it's like a severe cold.
Symptoms of the flu are just like a cold.
Usually, you get better
after several days.
And for young, healthy people,
it doesn't cause much problem.
Sorry. I didn't poop this morning.
You should record again.
Gosh. Sorry again.
Will that be enough?
Your rival prepared something huge.
-Who would like a wild girl like you?
-I do.
I told you I'd get you a star.
The only star in space
that's named Kang Ha-young.
-They said it'd snow.
-Do you believe the weather forecast?
-It's snowing!
-Who did this?
-I hope it snows this Christmas.
-Heon, take this.
-I don't want to wear this.
-Just wear it. It's cold.
Put them on. I'm not cold.
-What?
-It's dangerous.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-hyun Yang