Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME
I LIKE SHIN SOL-I
What do I do?
Sol-i, Shin Sol-i!
Do you have something on your mind?
Why the glum face?
Did you skip your morning pooping hour?
Don't tell me you have
a bad case of constipation.
Why aren't you talking?
You're boring me, you know.
Shin Sol-i was never the quiet type.
No way, it can't be!
Did you get into a lovers' quarrel
with Dae-sung?
I'm right, aren't I?
Good morning.
What the hell? I guess I'm wrong.
I need to poop.
-Don't tell.
-See you.
He's busy from early in the morning.
Oh, right. Hi.
-Bye.
You've been listless all day.
What's wrong? What's going on?
I LIKE SHIN SOL-I
You have to keep it secret, okay?
No way.
Was it Cha Heon?
That's what I thought, but it wasn't.
Who was it, then?
Woo Dae-sung?
What should I do?
What else? Just go out with him.
-What?
-My friend.
Just think about it.
You never noticed
because you kept your eyes on Heon,
but Dae-sung is pretty handsome, too.
Let's be honest.
Dae-sung is sweet and handsome.
Also, what about the prize money
he wins at tournaments?
He could buy everything
from here to there.
No, he could buy the entire snack bar.
Sure, snack bars are nice.
The class starts soon. Hurry up.
But Heon's like a department store to me.
Heon,
can you lend a hand?
I need to bring the class notes
from the staff room.
Cha Heon,
I gave up the snack bar for you.
Dae-sung, you see…
The thing is…
What's going on? Just tell me.
The Game of Truth note
you wrote that day.
I saw it!
Oh, that?
That was just a joke.
Did you believe that?
What?
Who takes that game seriously?
Goodness.
Brother, you're something else.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Once a brother, always a brother.
Exactly. We're brothers!
You better watch out of con men.
You'll be in trouble.
Sorry about that.
I was worried for no reason.
Yes, Coach. Got it.
Coach is looking for me.
-I should go now.
-Sure.
Bye.
Hey, Heon.
Are you taking out the trash?
Yes.
-What is it?
-Where have you been?
Oh, I was with Dae-sung.
Don't stay out so late.
What?
Okay. I won't stay out late.
I'll always come home early!
MILK
Exactly. We're brothers!
I was worried for no reason.
-Did you do your homework?
-No, I'm going to copy yours.
Chocolate milk delivery.
Don't want to lose you
Ha-young.
Thanks.
Wang Se-hyeong.
-Thanks.
-Enjoy.
I don't get this topic at all.
Of course, it's essential. Right?
Why else are we studying our butts off?
To go to university.
By the way,
a certain member of our group
seems out of place.
How annoying.
I like the lineup, though.
I'm glad we're in
the same group, too, Hui-ji.
She's the issue here.
Come on. Sol-i will do a good job.
Sol-i, how do you think
we should prepare this debate?
What? Me?
Come to think of it, you can relate
the most to the opposing side.
You're the one who's least likely
to graduate from university.
Well, I think…
You see… Well…
This is my first time preparing a debate.
Sol-i, have some confidence.
I'll help you out.
Okay. I'll make sure
to practice this weekend.
After all that running around,
my feet are begging for some air.
I'm taking off my shoes.
Never mind. I'll just keep them on.
I think that's better.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Never mind.
Then just take them off.
No!
I don't have athlete's foot.
See? The other one is a normal sock.
I don't normally wear socks like this.
My mom matched one of mine with my dad's,
and I didn't have time to change.
Who asked?
Don't take it the wrong way, okay?
I don't have athlete's foot.
The weather's terrible today.
It could rain any second.
Let's go home before it does.
But it's sunny.
Heon, you believe me, right?
I don't have athlete's foot.
Hello.
-Ghost Walk, please.
-Sure.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Enjoy the movie.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
I'd like a ticket
for the movie he's watching.
-I'm sorry, but--
-I'll explain.
He's actually my older brother.
All the hard studying
has been messing with his head,
so my mom asked me
to keep an eye on him today.
Got it. Which seat?
I'll sit a few rows behind him.
Sure.
-Here.
-Okay.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Why is this only money you have?
Right, Jin-hwan.
This isn't even close
to the amount from before.
You were so generous that day, remember?
Jin-hwan, as your best friend,
I'm disappointed.
I never gave you the money.
You took it from me.
What did he just say?
Do you even know
what kind of trouble you put me in?
Why should I give you my money?
Jin-hwan, keep it down, will you?
-Don't raise your voice.
-I guess we have no choice.
Hey.
Who are you?
What the hell?
-What?
-Who the hell are you?
Hold on.
Why are you bullying him?
Gosh, Jin-hwan,
-Is she your girlfriend?
-Wow, damn.
Jin-hwan, nice going.
Hey!
-Leave her alone.
-You've lost your mind, haven't you?
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
I said… I'm fine.
Look, being a girl doesn't give you
a free pass.
-What makes you so cheeky?
-The police.
-I already called them.
-"I called them."
-What a liar.
-So where are they?
-Officer?
-Where?
See? No one's around--
Are you guys all right?
You little…
Take that!
Run!
Jeong Jin-hwan, where did you go?
Hey, let's go that way.
You check over there.
I need to run again? Damn it.
God, that was scary as hell.
Hey.
Is this how you lost your money before?
Yes.
Those bastards.
Are you all prepared for the debate?
Well… Yes.
I prepared the best I could.
I mean, I…
Shin Sol-i, do better, will you?
If you speak like that in class later,
our team will be screwed.
Then, will you make up for my grades?
Many celebrities don't
go to university these days.
Right.
Not many athletes
graduate from university, either.
The same goes for entrepreneurs.
Right, I guess that's true.
According to the affirmative team,
the most basic tool for finding success
is a university diploma.
I believe the statement
to be contradictory.
I'd like to ask them in return
if everyone who's considered successful
actually has a degree.
AFFIRMATIVE
NEGATIVE
Me?
I'd like to give an example
by mentioning someone we all know.
It's Woo Dae-sung.
Me?
Dae-sung hasn't even
entered university yet,
but he's already an acknowledged swimmer
both domestically and internationally.
Just like Dae-sung,
many athletes and celebrities
didn't go to university after graduating.
I believe we all have
our own goals or dreams
that will bring us happiness or success.
One may want to be a chef.
Another may want to become a writer.
yet another may even
dream of becoming a singer.
Who are we to measure one's success
based solely on whether
they have a university diploma?
"Who are we to measure one's success
based solely on whether
they have a university diploma?
What you all think?"
I never said that!
Sol-i, how did you come up with that?
I'm amazed.
You can thank me later.
Nonsense. How did you help me?
"Yet another may even
dream of becoming a singer."
Who would that be? Me, of course.
You always talk the talk.
Then why weren't you able
to do so in front of
those money-stealing bullies
until Ha-young showed up?
-Hey, that's a secret!
-Who were they?
Let's go. I'll teach them a lesson.
I wasn't bullied.
Besides, they didn't take much.
How long has it been going on?
Back in seventh grade,
they locked me in a storage room
and forced me to sing a song.
I was so scared at the time.
-Without knowing--
-You wet yourself?
They had me wrapped around their fingers
since then.
I embarrass you, don't I?
Of course not.
When I first learned how to swim,
I wet myself too in the swimming pool.
I was an outcast in middle school.
When I was a kid,
I once drank plum wine and got wasted.
-What? No way.
-No way.
When? Where?
You don't need to know.
My dad once gave me athlete's foot.
No way. That's shocking.
Very shocking.
What? Isn't this the least shocking one?
-I don't think so.
-What?
But those toe socks from before--
That's not the case. I'm completely cured.
My feet are fungus-free now.
Ms. Shin Sol-i,
athlete's foot can recur anytime.
Jeong Jin-hwan, you…
Ha-young, do something!
Stop. That's enough, you guys.
-You jerk.
-Yes, you jerk.
Which socks are you wearing today?
Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
YEAR 1999, SOL-I'S HOUSE
Block underneath…
and punch!
Block underneath and punch!
Is this drunken boxing or tawkwondo?
Did you drink all that?
-Heon, are you all right?
-Goodness.
Slice with the right, slice with the left.
Slice with the right and block.
My goodness.
He has a bright future, don't you think?
-My gosh.
-Goodness.
Gosh.
Heon, you could be a singer.
Here, use mine.
Are you okay?
-Some people already died overseas.
-Am I going to die?
It'll be all right. Nothing will happen.
Heon, aren't you going to see Sol-i?
By the way, where's Heon?
Could you give this to her?
Heon asked me to give this.
Who in the world did this?
I wish I was sick for a bit longer.
Sol-i. Don't worry.
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park