THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
It was you.
You were that person.
I will not forgive you.
I will take your life.
EPISODE 12, DANCING
ON TOP OF A SWORD
EPISODE 12
Do you now understand who
the owner of this palace is?
I almost shot you. I
mistook you as prey.
Are you sure that you didn't
accidentally miss the mark?
That is a misunderstanding.
Remember your place.
I should get changed.
Yes, Your Majesty.
There is something that the
Department of Justice must do.
Did you have to do that to O Wol?
What did I do?
Did you have to and kill her?
Did you have to throw her into
the well after you killed her?
Did you have to do that...
to that innocent girl
just to threaten me?
I killed her?
Why would you have such
a misunderstanding?
I refuse to kill any living thing...
unless it's for cooking.
Finding her body in the well is
either an awful coincidence...
or someone is trying
to come between us.
Continue denying until
I get even more furious.
My gosh, this is driving me
crazy. I really didn't do it.
Why do you have such a
negative opinion of me?
Because that is who you are.
The Kim So Yong that I know
is someone who would do that.
How do you know me so well
when I don't know myself?
A liar is best at
lying to themselves.
You are fooling yourself which is
why you do not know who you are.
I think you and I have crossed a
line that we can't return from.
I won't pay any mind to whatever
misunderstandings you have about me.
So do as you please.
RABBIT
Who caught her?
We worked so hard to go
after her, so who dared to...
Looks like we have a winner.
We should start heading back.
- Yes, Your Highness.
That's blood.
Darn it.
Are you insane? That
hurts like crazy.
I apologize. My hand slipped.
- Why you little...
- Are you okay, Your Highness?
Even if it is made of
cotton, it must still hurt.
Your Highness. What
on earth are you...
I'll get back at you.
You're dead meat.
Seriously?
I'll let it go today for the
sake of my dear consorts!
- Because I'm her superior.
- Of course, Your Highness.
Go to Huijeongjeon Hall.
I will help you get changed...
There is someone who is trying
to interfere with the banquet,
so I will go alone.
All these people who have
gathered here today...
will regard the King
as someone with power.
Everything that has been
said about the King...
and his nickname, the Woodcutter
Prince of Ganghwa Island,
will become nothing
more than false rumors.
The King was so adamant
about holding a banquet.
He must have chosen it
as the day to appear...
in front of the Royal
Court with a new image.
What on earth were you doing...
while he was preparing himself?
I apologize.
However,
I have also prepared something
in advance for the King,
so keep an eye out for it.
I hope you prepared it properly.
Consort Hong.
One point.
Royal Noble Consort Eui. Two points.
Consort Min.
Four points.
Consort Yoon. She
also has four points.
The Queen.
10 points.
Oh, my.
As a result, the
winner is the Queen.
The Queen Dowager will
present the award.
You said you would
just enjoy the process.
Did you practice in secret?
As I'm a natural-born performer,
I'm better in the real game.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
- Congratulations, Your Highness.
How cunning of her.
We must go to the Royal
Palace for the banquet.
We still have time before
the banquet starts,
so you may all get some rest.
I am sure you must be tired
after the hunting game.
- Yes, Queen Dowager.
Did it hurt a lot?
Oh, this?
I can see why Eunuch Kim
was so afraid of this event.
Your Highness. You should
return to Daejojeon Hall...
and change into an
outfit for the banquet.
Right. I should get some
rest while we're there.
- Of course.
- The back of my head still hurts.
My goodness.
We must hurry. There is not much
time left until the banquet.
Why did she do that?
I am certain that someone is
trying to come between us.
Who?
Someone who knows about the bad
relationship regarding the well.
Within the Palace, there are three
types of history that continue.
The veiled enmity between women,
the fight for power
in the Royal Court,
and death by poison.
Is that why you're always
talking about poison?
I have lived in the
Palace for decades,
and I saw many people die
from various types of poisons.
Deadly poisons that
kill after one sip.
Hidden poisons...
that slowly poison you and
appear as death from illness.
They were not revealed,
but I am sure that there
were many deaths...
that were caused by poison.
Right. The Palace is a
very dangerous place.
Come to think of it, the man
that looked like Mr. Han...
Right. That guy.
Hold on.
So she turned around...
Did she see my face? I
do not think she did.
That is why I ran away.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I caught you.
Court Lady Choi.
Go and find out who that guy is.
The guy who was talking to...
the Head Inspector just now.
I bet my dragon balls
which I don't have now,
that his last name is Han.
The banquet will start soon.
It can't start.
As long as that guy
is roaming around.
Pardon?
Then what will happen
to the Royal Chef?
That jerk.
Why is everything the same
as what I went through?
And Cheoljong doesn't
even know what's going on.
A person must live as they
look to have no regrets.
I'll be myself and ignore it.
But I'm sure that guy put
something in the water.
Was it poison?
Gosh, no way.
Even if the Palace
is a brutal place,
would he really commit a mass
poisoning to ruin the banquet?
No way.
See? Anxiety and
fear are contagious.
Darn it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the scene of
the crime to get evidence.
If you go that way,
it's Daejojeon Hall.
My mind is going back and forth
and so is my sense of direction.
Wait for me, Your Highness!
It smells a bit like grass.
What did he put in here?
You must not, Your Highness.
Right?
We are in trouble.
Your Majesty.
I prepared as much as I could.
The banquet will start soon, but
the ingredients have not arrived.
Even if it is late, the
ingredients will come.
Trust me and do not give up.
I will try to come up
with something as well.
Just give up.
You will feel better if
you give up, you fool.
My Queen.
You already know that
this won't work out.
Even if you do your best,
you'll only end up hurting
yourself and the people around you.
Then should I stay still like a
corpse and suffer in their hands?
I cannot do that.
I will do my best to
go as far as I can.
If that hurts you,
just ignore me.
Oh, right. We're not
supposed to touch each other.
Okay. I get it.
Your Highness. Why would you say
something you do not even mean?
What do you mean?
Even when I'm talking nonsense,
I do it with my whole heart.
I never say anything I don't mean.
You are worried about him.
You are afraid that the more he
tries, the more he will get hurt.
Why would I?
Worrying about celebrities
and the King...
is the most meaningless thing to do.
Recently, whenever you say
something you do not mean,
you always say something strange.
I knew it. He poisoned the water.
Hey. Where's the Royal Chef?
He was just here.
No!
Did he run away?
He acted like he had
such a great work ethic,
but he ran away to survive.
Then what will happen
to the banquet today?
The King worked so hard for it.
There are no ingredients
and the head chef ran away.
It's over.
Then should I stay still like a
corpse and suffer in their hands?
I cannot do that.
I will do my best to
go as far as I can.
My gosh.
Hong Yeon. You're going
to have to do some work.
Goodness. Thank you
for your hard work.
HAN SHIM ONG
Okay. Thank you for your hard work.
What is the name of
the man who just left?
Why are you asking?
I am asking for a good reason.
I cannot tell you.
Gosh.
If I leave my unpredictable
Queen alone at the banquet,
she might cause trouble.
My gosh. It has been a while.
I caught a cold.
Let me borrow this. Thank you.
Rice. Rice! There is rice!
- Rice! Wait.
- Rice! There is rice.
- Come.
- There is rice.
- Rice!
- Get it.
- Take the rice.
- Hurry.
- Take it.
- What is that?
- What?
Rice!
My goodness. My loyal customer!
As it so happens, I have a
lot of killer items today.
I have no time for this.
You got the wrong person.
What?
That is her.
Why are there so many
temptations today?
However, I, Court Lady
Choi, cannot be tempted.
You are a court lady. Do
you need to talk to me?
You have kept your ability
a secret from me...
all this time and have not done a
thing to make your skills useful.
It must have been quite torture
to just sit back and watch.
I am used to it, so
it does not affect me.
I see.
All right. Will this do?
Are you sure you are not the
man in this kaleidoscope?
Gosh. I told you it
is not me in there.
I will be honest with you.
I could tell at a glance...
that he has a chiseled
body just like I do.
Unfortunately, that
is not me in there.
It is a great honor to
have engraved a name...
of the man with his resemblance.
My gosh. That was
nothing. By the way,
is he that popular among
court ladies nowadays?
I do not think "popular" is
the right word to describe it.
It is like a fever
among court ladies.
My gosh. I did not know
that I was that handsome.
Gosh.
So your name is...
Shim Ong of the Han clan.
In full, your name is Han Shim Ong.
CONFIDENTIAL
Do not forget.
When the banquet is at its peak...
and when the King is at his peak,
it is your cue to
bring out the ledger.
CONFIDENTIAL
Hey, you.
I have a favor to ask you.
Can you give this to that
person over there for me?
Who?
Over there.
I see. Okay.
My lord.
That young master asked
me to give this to you.
There is something I must
tell you in my clan's honor.
I will wait for you at the pavilion.
That cannot be.
Are they onto us?
You are here.
I have something to tell you.
I know this is rude of
me, but I asked you here.
My clan is as precious
as my own life.
However,
after spending countless nights
in deliberation, I have decided.
I decided to choose something that
is more important than my clan.
If my clan does not allow it,
I will...
leave my clan.
Now, I want to be the one and
only handsome man in your eyes.
Are you pulling a prank on me? I
already have a busy day as it is!
It was delivered to
the wrong person.
What have I done?
- My stomach.
- My goodness.
- Stick out your tongue.
- I think I am dying here.
Stick it out more.
My stomach.
You ate something
with poisonous herbs.
- My stomach.
- Oh, no.
I think someone spiked
it with ground knotgrass.
Hey, guys.
- I am dying here.
- What?
What?
Goodness. What brings you here?
The Queen has sent me here.
Her Highness told me
to look into the water.
Someone added poisonous herbs
that would cause stomachaches.
Darn it. The water was the problem.
How come you are fine?
As you can tell with my
looks, I am quite a sensitive.
So I cannot even drink a drop
of water when I am nervous.
You look like you can doze off...
in the field, full of
exploding cannonballs.
You call yourself a royal physician.
You are awful at reading people.
I am a royal physician,
not a physiognomist.
I am a skilled physician,
but I do not think they
can fully recover today.
With all of them like this, even
if we receive the ingredients...
Who in the world did this?
I have not seen him before.
Are you the one who
poisoned the water?
His Majesty sent me here for
the banquet preparations...
as a guest chef.
My name is Lee Saeng Mang.
I have come to your rescue.
Here.
Anyone can tell it is
Her Highness the Queen.
Don't you think so?
Nonsense! Why are you
calling that man the Queen?
Goodness, what is
wrong with your eyes?
The Queen is busy watching the
dance. Why would she be here?
Officially,
she is at the banquet
at the moment, you know?
Oh. I get it now.
A tomato?
What are you talking about?
This is a persimmon
that only lives a year.
Are you from the boondocks
or what? You little punk.
How can a chef not
even know what this is?
Gosh, how dare you call me a punk?
We are both chefs. What is
wrong with calling you a punk?
- Right?
- Yes. You little punk!
Hey, wrong timing.
You abandoned the
kitchen and ran off.
Don't call yourself a chef.
What are you talking about?
I went to Naenongpo to
find something that can...
alleviate their stomachaches.
Naenongpo?
Yes, Naenongpo. The Royal Farm.
You do not know anything.
Let me see what you brought.
Cooking begins with finding
good-quality ingredients.
In the Royal Farm,
do they raise chickens too?
I think I can try something
if you can get me some eggs.
Your stomach is growling already.
I bet you have not eaten since
yesterday to pig out today.
The fact that you
know that tells me...
you have not eaten anything
since yesterday either.
The banquet, which you
insisted on holding today,
will begin shortly.
I am looking forward to it.
Every banquet at the
Blue House had a theme...
because it was a political
meeting, never just a meal.
What would be good?
What's the goal of this banquet?
What's this?
The menu put together
by the King himself.
And this is the full guest list.
So this is the menu "erection"
you guys were talking about.
I'm going to come up with a new
menu with these ingredients.
How did it go?
I apologize, Your Majesty.
I spoke with the bandits, but they
were not after the ingredients.
Finally, the banquet is starting.
You said it would be a
formal royal banquet.
Is this the only dish
that will be served?
This is unfit to be
called a royal meal.
No way. Is this it?
I am certain more will follow.
Your Majesty, could you
please explain this?
The people starve every
year due to famine.
And many of them starve to death.
To be reminded of their pains,
I prepared a rather humble meal
that the commoners usually eat.
I truly admire Your Majesty's
intentions behind this,
but "humble" is not the
right word to describe this.
I understand that Your Majesty
wanted to enlighten the ministers,
but we cannot serve
this to the noblemen...
who came all the way
here for this banquet.
I agree.
Serving them this when they
were invited as guests...
is no better than punishment.
The food may not meet your
expectations, but I hope...
you all see my meaningful
intentions behind it.
30 MINUTES AGO
It'll go through the
whole thing like this.
What is this doodle for?
Pass me a potato. I'll
make a sample and show you.
This needle has finally
found its purpose.
Now, heat some oil on the stove.
Oil?
How dare you deep-fry
my precious needle?
Calm down. I'll
sterilize it for you.
Do you know what that
needle means to me?
My master gave it to me.
It was made 50 years ago!
Calm down.
50 years? Then it has done its duty.
No! I want to keep using it!
I want to pass it down
to my disciple too!
Don't you dare put it in there!
There we go.
It looks nice and balanced
with the needle at the center.
And this way, you can cook
even the inside very quickly.
How did you come up with
this brilliant idea?
When you make street food, you
have to fight against time.
It's perfect for an urgent
situation like this.
"Street"?
You don't need to know,
but it's like a war zone.
This survived a fierce battle.
Here.
Peel the potatoes.
Me?
Then who else?
I heard you need rice taffy?
I was told to check on the progress.
Peel it carefully.
Make it as thin as
possible. Thinner than that.
That's it.
The tip has to be
sharp. Make it sharper.
We're going to pierce
a potato with it.
Well done.
- The flame over here is too strong.
- Okay.
- Make this one stronger.
- Will do.
All right. I want you
all to keep this in mind.
What we're making today is
more than just ordinary food.
We're making the President's face.
I mean, think of it
as His Majesty's face.
Is this good enough, Your Highness?
I mean, Chef?
Let's see.
Good job.
I really hope Cheoljong understands
the idea behind all this.
So this is the humble
dish of the common people?
Am I the only one who did not know
what the people eat these days?
YONGSU POTATO
Although my intention may be noble,
I still must treat
my guests properly.
So I have used simple ingredients,
but I have come up with a new theme.
The first dish of the
banquet is a potato dish.
This is a potato?
It is not a simple potato dish.
The name of the dish is...
Spring...
like a coil?
Yongsu Potato!
All right.
It resembles the
whisker of a dragon.
It is called Yongsu Potato.
It is a lucky dish for a lucky day.
Nonetheless, it is
still a mere potato.
A dragon? That is a bit
of stretch, Your Majesty.
If we did not have potatoes,
we would have lost
more lives every day.
Rustic-looking potatoes...
can grow well even in a barren
land and are easy to store.
This becomes the main staple of
the people during the barley hump.
This is a sacred ingredient
that saves people's lives.
It is more than "a mere potato".
Please try it.
My gosh. This is very delicious.
But this is quite a new mouthfeel.
Right State Councilor,
you must be very hungry.
This is a potato?
There are three seasonings in
front of you. As for the green one,
this is the pine salt made of...
bay salt and pine needles
from Hwaseong Palace...
in the district of
the Namyang Hong clan.
This light red powder
is wild grape sugar.
Sugar? When the common people
do not even have barley?
If we can get through the barley
hump with this splendid dish,
I would have nothing to
worry about all year round.
This is powder taffy
which the people enjoy.
It is mixed with wild
grapes from Mount Gamak...
where the Papyeong Yoon
clan has put down roots.
It adds a beautiful color
and fragrance to sugar.
The yellow sauce is made of peaches.
This is made with
the best peaches...
from Yeoju where the
Yeoheung Min clan resides.
The theme of today's
banquet is harmony.
Politics divide people.
But delicious food
brings people together.
I hope you can taste the
harmony of the three clans...
who are here today with us.
I'll dice and stir-fry sweet
potatoes, zucchini, and eggplants.
And I'll make whole tomato
stew by puffing it up...
with broth and the eggs.
This novel idea...
of eating the vessel
would make them go crazy.
You're still not done yet?
Not even close.
I got the barley
powder and bean powder.
I got all sorts of powder I
can get and am kneading it.
The dish you're making now is
the highlight of the banquet.
Okay.
What are you doing? Knead
it vigorously just like me.
This is not good for the joints
in our shoulders and wrists.
Come on. You ought to
give it more power. Do it.
Grind your shoulders and
wrists if you need to.
You ought to pound on it.
Chef, it is all ready.
Is that so?
Okay.
It's a banquet, after all.
It's no banquet without meat.
I will finish the main dish...
with vegan hamburger steaks.
MAC DUNALDU
This is an edible pouch.
This produce is red
throughout the year.
Hence the name, One-year persimmon.
The color of the produce, red,
chases away bad luck on Surit-nal.
How could this be so soft?
Is it a short rib patty?
That cannot be. The
meat never arrived...
I meant to say that there are
no meats during the barley hump.
There is a proverb
from the Qing Empire.
"In the sky, there are
dragons for the meat."
"On land, there are donkeys."
And we should add, "Beans
for meat in the barley hump".
"Mac" for barley. "Du" for bean.
"Nal" for fattening. "Du" for belly.
So that makes Mac Dunaldu.
Mac Dunaldu
MAC DUNALDU
Like real meat, it is
delicious and filling.
That makes sense.
How beautiful.
I will add my artistic touches
to the cooled down sweet jelly.
So it will please their eyes.
Desserts should be delicious
and beautiful to look at.
- Gosh.
- Gosh. Look at the color.
On top of that, give
it a wow factor.
The perfect finale of the party.
FORTUNE JELLY
This is beautiful.
But this is just regular jelly.
I guess you are out of your tricks.
This stick makes it easier
for you to eat the jelly.
And it also says your fortune.
Fortune?
This dish embraces spring,
so it is called the Fortune Jelly.
It shows my hope that your future
may be fortunate like spring.
How about having your fortune
read as we wrap up the banquet?
How could we do such a
thing at our sacred palace?
ONE MORE
One more.
"One more"?
"Try Again Next time."
DUD
My gosh. My back hurts.
I am about to pass out.
I poured my soul into this
instead of real ingredients.
Gosh, I am going to pass out.
We did it.
Do you know what I'm
thinking about now?
I know. That is exactly how I feel.
- Fish cakes.
- Pardon?
I'm thinking about fish cakes.
The chef that almost died in the
hands of Emperor Qin Shi Huang...
created fish cakes the night before.
I thought that was
because he was lucky.
But that wasn't the case.
I'm sure he came up with it...
after trying whatever he
could do to stay alive.
Inspiration...
isn't something common
that would come...
to a person who has given up.
Your Highness.
Goodness. You must be out of breath.
Here. Have some water. Drink up.
His last name is Han.
Right? His last name
is really Han, right?
Yes.
His name is Shim Ong.
His name is Han Shim Ong.
Simon? Why does his
name sound so foreign?
Oh, Han Shim Ong.
Yes.
What is this, by the way?
Goodness. It is
nothing, Your Highness.
While I was outside of the Palace,
I went all the way to Hanseongbu,
and I took a look at
their family register.
I am sure that it is a fake
family register that was bought.
It is a method that is
fitting Mr. Han's ancestors.
Since we didn't include him
because he's a fake noble,
he chose such a dirty way
to win someone's favor?
Your Highness. This is not the
time to stand here like this.
You will be in trouble if
you are absent for too long.
Oh, you're right.
Good job, Court Lady Choi.
- I'm going. Let's go.
- Your Highness.
- Your Highness. Hold on.
- Be careful.
Your Highness!
Oh, my. Your Highness.
Why? What is wrong?
My stomach...
There's a troop of traveling actors
doing pungmulnori in my stomach.
What is going on?
The water...
Did nobody remove that water?
What kind of water...
is that?
It is water with a
poisonous plant in it.
Poison?
Court Lady Choi!
I see that you are here.
Of course, I should be here.
It is a banquet to congratulate
the Queen's recovery.
Keep an eye on
everything from now on.
Watch what kind of results
your actions will bring.
Goodness.
Making a meal is no easy task.
There is not a single part of
my body that is not in pain.
Furthermore, that Royal
Chef kept yelling at me.
- That rotten...
- Look here!
Do you still have potatoes
that need to be peeled?
Please save Court Lady Choi.
Please.
Keep up the good work.
I am sorry.
He was wearing a goblin mask,
and he had an old
scar around his chin.
Excuse me.
Oh, my.
I apologize.
Look here. She is in a lot of pain.
Do some acupuncture and burn
some moxa. Do something.
Give her some antitoxins too.
Goodness. Stay out of it.
I am the captain of this place.
This will do.
You were terrible in
the Royal Kitchen,
but you are great in
the Royal Infirmary.
Whether it is a person or an object,
everything has a
place it belongs to.
But your needles work
better in the Royal Kitchen.
No, it is not!
This needle is perfect
for piercing potatoes.
Let me take this to use.
How dare you touch it. No.
This would be perfect
for peeling potatoes.
- Let me take this to use.
- No.
You cannot do that, Your Highness!
The pungmulnori in my
stomach has stopped.
I should not be here right now.
- Your Highness.
- Court Lady Choi!
There is no way she could
recover that quickly.
She is a strong woman.
She smells like oil.
Why were you absent for so long?
Well, the thing is...
I apologize.
My hand slipped,
and I shot an arrow at the Queen.
Did you get hurt?
No, I am fine.
The hunting game was so tiring...
that I fell asleep while
I was getting ready.
Darn it.
An apron?
When will your preparations unfold?
Please wait.
The King put so much
effort into this banquet.
The King must stand out for now.
To everyone who came here and
set an example as a scholar...
by not eating a lot...
to show that you understand
the hunger of the people,
I will take this opportunity
to make an announcement.
With the start of this banquet,
we will start reducing
the dishes in our meals.
SETTING AN EXAMPLE TO THE PEOPLE
BY REDUCING THE NUMBER OF DISHES
Reducing the dishes?
What kind of nonsense
is he speaking of?
When the nation is in
trouble, the king should...
reduce the number of
dishes in his meals...
to share the pain of his people.
By reducing the number of dishes,
we feel the pain of the nation...
so that we can overcome it together.
At a time like this, taking the
grain to save dozens of people...
to make a piece of meat
to please our tongues...
is a sin.
As a result, if anyone
in this Palace...
puts a piece of meat on their
tables, they will be punished.
I not only forbid meat, but I forbid
you from eating generous meals.
Ministers cannot enjoy
drinking, singing, and dancing,
and they must stop
having factional strife.
If you violate these terms,
I will take it as you are
willing to accept the punishment.
Your Majesty.
I, Kim Jwa Geun, apologize...
as I have an unfortunate
piece of news.
These are criminals who
lied about their status...
and hid in the Royal Guard Division.
In order to guard you by your side,
they created a fake identity.
It is time to go after the
people who think they are hidden.
I am sure he believes that they
are the basis of his power...
that he took good
care of and protected.
We have to pull it out from its
roots and tear it into pieces.
So that he will not be
able to stand again.
Must you ruin this
meaningful day like this?
Do you know who they really are?
Some of them are from families
that are guilty of treason.
Some of them were bandits that
targeted scholar-officials,
and some are wanted criminals who
openly criticized the monarchy.
All of them disapprove
of the royal court,
but they have been...
guarding Your Majesty in disguise.
Their ultimate goal
was to plot a coup.
Due to the urgency of this
matter, I had no choice...
but to bring it to Your
Majesty's attention immediately.
No, that cannot be.
Someone is falsely
accusing my royal guards...
to weaken security and harm me.
By "someone",
who exactly are you referring to?
You, Training
Commander Kim Jwa Geun.
Are you doing this...
because you think those
three families got your back?
Do you think such
sugar-coated words...
are enough to persuade
them to side with you?
You are foolish.
It is time for you to wake
up and see your reality.
How brazen!
How dare you insult
the King like this?
This is an act of
disloyalty and treason!
This is very unlike you,
Your Majesty. Calm down!
How dare you give me
orders when I am the King?
Your Majesty, it seems like there
is something you are counting on.
Whatever it is, you will
not be able to use it...
if your limbs are cut off.
Pay the price for
your own recklessness.
All of you shall be
beheaded for your crimes.
Your Majesty, we will
follow the military laws.
They are guilty of
treason, which means...
this is out of the Royal
Guard Division's hands.
The Department of Justice
will handle this matter!
Your Majesty.
The Royal Guard Division
will take care of this!
- No, Your Majesty!
The royal guard commander
knew who they really were!
It is possible that everyone
in the division is a traitor.
We cannot let the Royal Guard
Division handle the corruption...
that took place within it!
- Please reconsider, Your Majesty!
Please reconsider, Your Majesty!
We can disband the
entire division...
and prosecute the royal
guard commander as well.
However,
if you leave these
criminals' punishment to me,
I will take it as your promise
to do nothing from now on...
and stop there.
Nothing I do...
will make any difference.
What would you like
to do, Your Majesty?
Fine.
I will leave the matter...
in your hands.
"The Lord of the Land..."
"and the Lord of
Grains, I pray to you."
"May your blessings..."
"turn the seeds in the
ground into ripe fruits."
"May the mercy of the skies..."
"help the people of this land so
they will never have to starve."
Please...
- Your Majesty!
MR. QUEEN
The explosion damaged his hearing.
Oh, no.
- There will be no problems, right?
- Yes, of course.
No one is behind it?
I've decided to survive,
so don't die.
Recover as if nothing
ever happened...
so I can stab you in the back.
The enemy inside is always scarier.
Your Highness! His Majesty is...
His Majesty is...
I request that you end this regency.
Your Majesty!
Everyone in this palace
killed Kim So Yong.