THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
- Your Majesty!
How miraculous it is...
that tomorrow comes every day?
It is dangerous. There
may be another explosion.
Your Majesty!
No. You must not go.
- Your Majesty!
- Protect the King.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness. You must go.
- Your Majesty!
- Hurry.
No. We need to save him!
- Your Highness.
- You must not go.
Do not get involved in this.
What are you talking
about? The King is...
Listen to me!
I will give you the details later.
For now, you must save yourself.
- Your Majesty!
- It is dangerous,
so bring the Queen to
Daejojeon Hall right now.
- Your Highness. You must not go.
- Your Highness.
- Let go of me!
- Your Majesty.
- Your Highness.
Let go of me. Please.
Let go. Let go of me!
Let go!
Your Majesty!
However,
we do not realize it is a miracle...
until the day when
tomorrow does not come.
It is because we are foolish, and
we only realize what is precious...
after we lose it.
EPISODE 13, THERE IS NO TOMORROW
EPISODE 13
Someone dared to attempt to
assassinate the King in the Palace.
If there is anyone suspicious,
capture and question them all.
We will find out...
who is behind it.
Is this what you prepared?
How will you deal with the
aftermath to plan such a thing?
Please calm down.
Does it look like I could calm down?
The King's life was endangered
in front of everyone,
and it was in such a garish way.
So that they would assume that
I tried to assassinate him.
I will take care of it.
I beg of you. I beg of you.
I desperately beg the
deities of heaven and Earth.
Please make sure that the King is safe.
I beg of you. I beg of you.
I desperately beg of you.
Please make sure that...
the King is safe.
I had no idea they would go this far.
They enthroned the King themselves,
but they want to get rid of him
before he becomes a mistake.
What will happen if the King
does not wake up like this?
There is nothing we can do...
with the Royal Consort then.
I cannot believe that we got caught...
in the trap we set out for the Queen.
I beg of you. I beg of you.
I beg of you.
You should get some rest.
You will end up collapsing like this.
If the King does not survive,
I cannot live anyway.
Even if I die,
I will seek revenge against the one
who did that to the King and die.
The Palace...
and those people...
made us so spiteful.
Your Highness. The head of the
Department of Justice is here.
Is Cheoljong...
Is the King okay?
Prince Yeongpyeong has forbidden...
anyone from entering Huijeongjeon
Hall while he is getting treated.
They are not telling
anyone about his state.
I should go and see for myself.
Do not go.
They will let me in.
I am his wife after all.
Do not go.
He tried to kill you himself.
You have every right
to kill him yourself.
So Yong.
I need to get some rest alone.
Are you sure there will
not be any problems?
Of course.
Tell me who was behind this.
We are innocent.
We risk our lives to protect the King.
We are his royal guards.
What is your excuse for
your false identities?
While you used this as the
pretext to arrest and lock us up,
the King ended up like that.
If there is anyone behind this,
it would be the man who found fault
in our identities. Your father,
Kim Jwa Geun!
It is Kim Jwa Geun.
You're quite clever.
I found it.
As you said, the incense burner
was not filled with sand,
but gunpowder which is
used as an explosive.
How did you know?
What happened?
They are not admitting to it easily.
I am sure.
Is there anything else?
No, not yet.
You must find the culprits to
lay this confusion to rest.
Be sure to find out who is
behind it as soon as possible.
Of course.
Find the source of the gunpowder.
Move by yourself, quietly.
Yes, sir.
My Lord.
Please forgive me. Please.
What are you doing right now?
There are a lot of eyes here.
Please.
Please hear me out.
It will not take long. It
will take only a few seconds.
Please. It will take only a few seconds.
I just...
kept the ledger just in case.
I never thought about using
the ledger in any way.
On top of that, the Queen does not
even know that I have a ledger.
Where is the ledger now?
Do you not have it in your possession?
Then, the only person
who could have it...
is the King.
Oh, my.
The traces you left backfired
and put our clan in danger.
That itself is enough to punish you.
I will do anything you ask.
If you tell me to die, I will do so.
Right here.
I will hang myself here.
I will hang myself.
My gosh.
Please spare me. My lord.
Please spare me.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, are you awake?
Brother.
Yes. Go ahead.
Why is it so loud here?
It is so loud in here that
it is giving me a headache.
I cannot hear a thing.
Please silence the noise.
I should have explained it better.
I should have told him that the
King wasn't trying to kill me.
He tried to kill you himself.
You have every right
to kill him yourself.
Pay the price for your own recklessness.
Was the entire Kim clan behind this?
Or which clan was it?
Your Highness.
Your Highness. His Majesty has
regained consciousness now.
I heard he was awake.
He had just fallen asleep.
Why did you wrap the bandage like this?
He looks way too sick.
I apologize,
but he had lost his
hearing due to the bombing.
Don't tell me...
he will be deaf for
the rest of his life.
Only time can tell us.
Leave us alone.
Yes, Your Highness.
Will you tell me your clan
was not behind this again?
You told me that...
I would lose someone that
I hold dearly to my heart.
Now, there is no one...
So please.
Stop this.
Your Majesty, please stop worrying now.
Who...
Your Majesty, are you awake?
Let me wet your lips.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
So you went to see the King.
I came here today to comfort you
regarding today's incident...
and to ask a few questions.
Your father has lost
a very important item.
I believe the King
has secretly taken it.
Do you know anything about that?
- Oh, my. I'll get some help.
- No.
Nobody can know that I am...
That I am...
So you do know something about it.
Do you remember how I told you...
that our clan has no weaknesses?
Because once we spot a
weakness, we will carve it out.
Let me ask you one last time.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
When we stayed at my house,
I once saved the King,
passed out in the well.
Perhaps, that was when...
A while ago, I made an offer to you.
It was on the day when
you fell into the lake.
Let me jog your memory.
I asked you to keep an
eye on your husband.
Will you...
accept my offer now?
Then, what will I get in return?
What do you want?
Guarantee my safety.
Your Highness, you must get
back to the royal villa.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
I CAME HERE FOR
NOTHING. JANG BONG HWAN
Cheoljong.
I'm sorry.
You're going to lose anyway.
I take sides with the winner.
Kim So Yong, you gave
up your life anyway.
I happened to continue
to live your life so,
let me live a good one by myself.
In order to do so, I
need to make it clear.
What happened that day.
I swear...
you will also lose someone dear to you.
You should love me.
Is that an order?
There is nothing that is not a lie.
You are certainly So Yong.
Did you rise to your position
on your own, Destined Highness?
If you want to die, die in the palace.
You will become the Queen tomorrow.
From now on,
tell me his every movement.
Are you telling me...
to spy on the King?
It is not to spy on the King. It
is to keep an eye on your husband.
I do not want to do it.
Is what you want not the
position of the Queen...
and the King?
You should do that in
order to have both.
It is what you did in the past.
Just as you let me know the
King was trapped in the well.
If you do not do your part,
the King is useless.
When you are useless,
you are abandoned.
If you harm His Majesty,
I will not stay still.
What are you going to do then?
You are badly mistaken.
Do you think the Queen holds such power?
The Queen is nothing
but the best field...
that produces princes.
Even if you become the Queen,
what power do you think you will have...
as a mere woman?
It's not just because of
what Kim Jwa Geun said.
By staying in the palace for
this short period of time,
I've gone through enough
to see my reality.
The entire palace...
killed Kim So Yong.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, Your Highness!
Your Highness, where did you
go at this late at night?
Why are you so wet?
Did you perhaps dive
into the lake again?
Why do you keep doing this?
You should gather yourself
up in a time like this.
What is the point of me doing
all sorts of things so far?
Why did I go through those
humiliating experiences for?
What did you do that for?
You did it in order to accumulate
property to fill your storehouse.
You sold your only daughter
to satisfy your greed.
- So Yong.
- Why did you always tell me...
to become the Queen and the
pride of the family and you?
Why did you tell me that I can do
anything if I become the Queen?
To me who was struggling with the
guilt about my mother's death,
why did you keep saying your dream?
Do you know what I was thinking
when I threw myself into the lake?
"The life that I thought
was mine was all lie."
"Even the dream I had was not mine."
"I failed at everything."
That is why I threw myself away.
What?
The day when your dream came true,
I lost the person I cherish the most.
Myself.
It is you who pushed me into the lake.
Parents are the most convenient
people to blame for children.
I shouldn't have blamed Father.
Your Highness.
I have something to say.
I know you would do anything for me.
No. I got to know.
Because my memories are back.
Do not do anything from now on.
If you care for me, do not do anything.
That is what helps me.
So Yong.
Do not call my name.
I am just...
the Queen head of the
Department of Justice serves.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
ISSUE, LOTTO, SPECIAL FORCES,
KITCHEN POLICE, MS. BIG BELLY
NO TOUCHING.
MEANS TO SEEK ONE'S OWN HAPPINESS
SHOWDOWN, JASMINE TEA, ILL-MANNERED
I'll be honest since
you can't hear me now.
I have to be a coward
to live a long life.
I will betray you.
I decided to choose a path
that will keep me safe.
So you shouldn't die either.
Shake it off and get up
like nothing happened.
So I can stab you in the back.
You were right.
The King was more
capable than he let on.
I am sorry about that.
What do you think
about today's incident?
We found gunpowder from the scene.
- "Gunpowder"?
- Yes.
There are two types of
gunpowders in Joseon.
The imported type from the Qing Empire.
And the domestic type
from a gunpowder house.
There is a small difference
between both of these elements.
The one we found on the
scene was the domestic type.
The gunpowder house
belongs to the armory.
And the Minister of War
supervises the armory.
He is my father's right-hand man.
That means...
My father was the one who
put the King on the throne.
Now that the King has
shown his true colors,
he must want to eliminate the King
before it becomes his mistake...
and frame the royal guards...
who faked their identities
for the bombing.
That must be his plan.
When you came to me last time,
you must have wanted something.
What is it that you want?
I want...
the King.
I cannot stop here.
And if that is how you feel,
that is all the more reason not to.
I came here today to tell you
what the Queen did yesterday.
She saved the banquet when it
was set up to be a failure.
Do you think I will believe you?
You must think...
I am the one behind the
incident that injured the King.
If you look into it, you
will easily have your answer.
Just how I found out you
tried to ruin the banquet.
Even if the Queen gets deposed...
I do not want some title.
I just want the Queen to
disappear from the King's sight.
That means...
the King fancies the Queen.
From the looks of it, it seems you
have had a tough couple of days.
Are you that worried about the King?
Gosh.
He has become your
son-in-law only recently.
You must have grown quite
some attachment to him.
Well,
the truth is...
I have done a terrible thing
that disgraced our clan.
I kept a record of the assets
our clan acquired improperly.
And I have lost it.
What?
I figured out where the ledger is now.
I just need to find
it and get rid of it.
But I ask that you spare the Queen.
What are you bringing her up?
The person who has the ledger...
is the King.
The Queen has nothing to
do with this incident.
The King has deceived the Queen and me.
Everyone has been deceived by the King.
I will accept any
punishment you give me.
But...
show mercy for So Yong.
Please spare the Queen.
I beg of you to spare the Queen. Please.
Father.
Have you been sleeping at
the Department of Justice?
Yes. It is a huge case.
I have had a lot of work.
Everything about this case
points toward me as the culprit.
But you have not brought it up.
Do not worry.
The Department of Justice
is investigating now.
If you are framed,
I will reveal the real
culprit behind the incident.
That reassures me.
A while ago,
you told me that you have decided
on the magnitude of your dream.
So how big is your dream?
My dream is...
to be as half-successful as you.
It is getting late. Get some rest.
Do not come.
If you follow me, I will kill myself.
So Yong.
I know the driving force behind you.
My gosh. Where is the
Queen this morning?
She is in the royal kitchen.
Right now.
That is all right.
I was going to make her cook
breakfast for me when she woke up.
But she is already cooking
for her grandmother. Goodness.
You startled me.
It is quite early. May I
ask what you are doing?
I'm so depressed lately. I
can't seem to sleep either.
Like I'm wishing my morning prayer,
I'm making a very annoying dish...
that requires me to grind
and stir billions of times.
But the color of the rice
porridge looks a bit off.
This isn't a rice porridge
It's called "potage crecy".
Are you trying to spit?
It is too early for that.
It means carrot porridge.
Hold on. I should write this down.
How do you make it?
Cut up carrots and onions and
boil them in water for an hour.
Then you grind it up in a millstone.
As if you're grinding up all
your trials and delusions.
Then stir it over low heat so that
it doesn't burn or clump together.
With the heart of one who is
cultivating themselves morally.
Season it with salt,
and add a bit of milk.
You even add milk?
Is that how you finish it?
No.
You need to make a broth out of
various vegetables in advance.
Take that broth...
and add a bit of it to the
porridge to give it a richer taste.
Must you go through all that
trouble just to add a bit of it?
I told you. This is like
an early morning prayer.
You are pouring your
heart and soul into it.
I am sure that the King will
wake up soon after eating this.
It's not for him.
Rather than suffering at their
hands twice, I'll finish it at once.
Just because I said
something to her last time,
she is making me eat
with my mother-in-law?
She dared to use that capricious
mouth to say I am old,
but I need to see her
first thing in the morning?
What is this?
It is called brunch.
"Brunch"?
It means "Women coming together".
It is when women get
together for breakfast...
and get close to one another.
Everyone knows what brunch is.
It is not like you are from Gojoseon.
That wench.
It is something I used to
do on occasion back at home.
It has been a while.
That wench.
It is a porridge made from carrots.
It has a lot of ingredients that
help to improve your vision.
Is that so?
You should have a lot
of it, Queen Dowager.
It seems like you are blind these days.
If that is the case, I believe that
the Queen should have all of it.
What is this? Why are they so combative?
It tastes good.
It is edible.
From now on,
I will ensure that we get
together like this more often.
- That wench.
Then let me excuse myself...
to bring you some beverages.
The rumors about the Queen's cooking
skills are a bit exaggerated.
Being able to recognize good
food is a part of being classy.
Are you forgiving the Queen
just because of this talent?
Since you are the source who
told me what the Queen said,
I cannot believe it.
I am sure you will not be able to
believe what I am about to tell you.
I heard that the King and the Queen...
have been sending each other
messages every night in secret.
I wonder what they are
writing to one another?
I will bring in your beverages.
It is a beverage made with wild
grape liquor and various fruits...
that are boiled with
star anise and cinnamon.
Are you giving us liquor in the morning?
All the alcohol has been evaporated,
and all that remains are ingredients
that help maintain your youth.
This is closer to medicine
than it is a beverage.
I cannot believe you thought
of boiling wild grape liquor.
How did you come up with this idea?
Where do you get the
inspiration for your dishes?
I do not know if we should call
it inspiration or creation.
When I see ingredients, I
automatically think of ways...
to cook it to maintain
its original taste.
They were very wary of
the West during this time,
so I can't tell them
it's French cooking.
My Lady.
Hello, Young Master.
I have something to say to
you, so I waited all this time.
Pardon? What is it you need to tell me?
After seeing His Majesty's accident,
I have been filled with
complicated thoughts.
You cannot predict what
will happen in life,
and my life may end tomorrow.
If my life ends tomorrow,
what will I regret the most?
That would be my feelings
I could not express...
because I hesitated.
Rather than a fancy confession,
one word of sincerity is more important.
That is why...
I want to tell you...
that I love you.
I do not like you.
What?
About the gunpowder.
The amount of gunpowder being
produced at the manufactory...
in the southern area of
Gyeongsang Province...
and the amount that is coming
into the armory is different.
I knew it.
Is the King still unconscious?
Yes.
I heard he lost his hearing. Even if
he wakes up, that will be a problem.
About the accident
that the King suffered.
For an explosion of that size,
do you think it was perhaps gunpowder?
I am not sure.
It could have been
sulfur or explosive gas.
If it was sulfur, it would have smelled,
so the King would have noticed it.
It if was gas, it
would have been hard...
to prevent it from leaking and
getting it to explode all at once.
The culprits refuse to confess
despite being questioned,
so it is hard to figure
out who is behind this.
When I see ingredients, I
automatically think of ways...
to cook it to maintain
its original taste.
No way.
Did the culprits that
are guilty of treason...
reveal who was behind this?
It seems like the low-ranking
guards who have a problem with...
the current Royal Court
came together to do this.
Goodness.
Are you saying that there
is nobody behind them?
For something as big as the
assassination of the King?
There is no way.
Those who have nothing to lose
are the ones we must fear.
They probably thought they would
never get to receive respect,
so they decided to turn
the tables in a big way.
That is probably why they did that.
It makes sense. The act
of treason to enthrone...
the King's half-brother, Lee Won Gyeong,
was also committed by
low-ranking guards.
Since the King is unconscious,
the longer we drag this out, the
more confusion it will bring.
That is why...
the seven culprits will take
responsibility for their crimes,
and they will be sentenced to death.
For the crime of endangering the
King's life and plotting treason,
you will all be sentenced to death.
Do you have any last words?
If you sentence them to death,
the person behind this
will be hidden forever.
He said that nobody is behind this.
It is a rash conclusion...
This conclusion was achieved after
investigating through the night.
My gosh.
Behead him.
Hold on.
It is the investigation
conducted by the royal command.
Are you going to interrupt it?
Release the innocent immediately.
This is the real command.
I apologize for coming in late.
You...
I heard you were sick in bed.
I am at a young age full of energy,
so I recovered quickly.
I did not want to waste my time...
recovering in bed.
So I investigated those...
who plotted treason with the
intention of assassinating me.
I investigated you first.
Do you mean you inspected us?
Someone attempted treason.
Are you saying your privacy
is more important...
than the King's life?
No, that is not...
If you have nothing to hide,
there is nothing to fear.
Do not worry.
I found the mastermind.
- What is he talking about?
- What is going on?
In the incense burner
used at the Dano ceremony,
a great amount of domestically
produced gunpowder was found.
- Gunpowder?
A great amount?
The incense burner is a huge bomb.
- It is too dangerous.
- And it is certain.
Tracking down the
origin of the gunpowder,
I obtained the information...
that gunpowder is privately
traded at Dongnae Dock.
By the way, what do you need
this much gunpowder for?
It is for attacking Joseon again later.
Thank you.
- "Thank you"?
- Thank you.
"Thank you"?
Where is the gunpowder from?
Gunpowder is produced for
the military purposes only.
It is not and cannot be
produced for personal purpose.
As it is dangerous and rare.
So I inspected all the
powder mills in Joseon.
And I found something strange.
In a powder mill in a certain region,
I found that certain
amount of gunpowder...
had been pocketed regularly.
The amount of gunpowder pocketed...
that was little at first
gradually increased.
Just like...
how dark greed grows.
- What?
- Is that true?
Do you know when the embezzlement
of gunpowder started?
Training Commander Kim Jwa Geun.
The very year I ascended to the throne.
It is also the year Lord Kim Jwa
Geun became Training Commander.
Your Majesty, it is a false accusation.
Keep your mouth shut!
Minister of War, in
charge of powder mills,
is also a traitor who plotted
treason with Kim Jwa Geun!
I am going to use royal guards'
fake identities as bait.
Kim Jwa Geun must have heard
about the identity fabrication.
You will go through unbearable tortures.
But please endure it.
I will save you no matter what it takes.
Please understand it is a
false charge, Your Majesty!
If you say you are falsely
accused in front of me again,
I will administer poison
to you immediately.
The gunpowder seller sold gunpowder...
to anyone who paid the price.
To bandits, even to Japanese!
If it is not to destroy Joseon, what is?
Who else here joined them?
Training Commander Kim Jwa Geun.
And Minister of War Kim Chang Hyup.
These two culprits...
stole national weapons to
weakened military strength...
and planned treason to
assassinate me, the King,
hence, they are culprits
who committed high treason.
How should we name the operation?
Phoenix.
The name of the operation...
is Phoenix, burning red.
For all these crimes,
the two culprit will be
dismissed from the office...
and exiled.
Your Majesty.
- Grand Queen Dowager.
What are you doing?
Why are you making a judgment
based on your emotions?
You must have lost your
judgment after the accident.
Do not forget your limit!
Is that so?
If you are saying so,
you must lost your judgement
because of old age.
I can no longer discuss politics
with you in such a state.
I request to end your regency.
- What?
- What is he talking about?
It is time for me to make my own
decisions for national affairs.
Your Majesty!
I should immediately administer
poison to culprit Kim Jwa Geun...
and kill his entire
family and relatives.
But because of you and the Queen,
I am trying to end this by
dismissing him from his title.
Do you not like it?
Are you trying to make a deal
with me with my brother's life?
You can say it is a deal only
when you have other choices.
Your Majesty.
I, Kim Jwa Geun, is in agony
due to the false accusation,
but I will prove my loyalty...
by obeying the royal command.
That is a relief.
I worried you might be consumed
by greed due to old age.
I do not regret withdrawing
from the office.
But please provide me with an
opportunity to be cleared...
from the charge to resign my post
without my reputation tarnished.
I request for impeachment to Saheonbu.
I will grant the request.
But if Saheonbu does not carry
out impeachment by tomorrow,
I will immediately remove Training
Commander Kim Jwa Geun from office.
And I will dismiss not only Saheonbu
that avoided the discussion,
but also every official here!
- Please forgive me.
You have lost.
You were removed by the King
you gave the throne by yourself!
I did not know the King had
plotted his own assassination.
Who did you think set the trap?
I trusted you to take care of the
noblewomen outside the palace.
But you do not have an eye for people.
Confucius said one's heart is
more complicated than nature...
and seeing through one's heart is
harder than seeing through the sky.
I made mistakes about
the selection of women...
with noble titles both within
and outside the palace.
You also trusted the Queen...
to take care of the investiture
of the Royal Concubine.
But she made a choice
that favors the King.
And it is the Queen...
who saved the feast I ruined.
What is scarier is the internal enemy.
Your Highness.
His Majesty must have
regained consciousness.
I can keep an eye on my husband
only after he regains consciousness.
If he doesn't wake up,
I'll become useless.
If I become useless, I'll be dethroned.
If I'm dethroned, I will have
to forget about the revenge...
and will open a gukbap place to
make a living and make a hit.
That's not bad.
Your Highness!
His Majesty...
He regained consciousness.
Really?
Yes. His ears are recovered...
and went to the royal conference.
I was scared.
I should go.
- Your Highness!
I don't have time.
I'm relieved.
I'm so relieved.
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
It is a relief.
Court Lady Choi.
- I will do it.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Everything is fine now.
Everything is fine as you
woke up and are healthy.
I will never lose you again.
Royal Noble Consort Eui.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
Your Highness.
You said you will visit His
Majesty. Why are you staying here?
Just one more glass.
It's awkward to see him when I'm sober.
Please stop drinking. You
cannot do this, Your Highness.
Get off work, Court Lady Choi. Go home!
I will drink it up.
Court Lady Choi.
We have plenty of alcohol
in the royal kitchen.
Why is it awkward?
It's awkward because...
You're right. Why would it be awkward?
I'm confident! Let's visit the King.
You cannot go with this state.
Please go when you are sober.
Okay. Let's go tomorrow.
Put off what you don't
want to do until tomorrow.
Just like going on a diet.
We have tomorrow!
Hey, Royal Chef. One more bottle.
Does she think this is
a tavern or something?
Quickly.
Court Lady Jang.
CONFIDENTIAL
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
It is found at Daejojeon Hall.
As expected, the King and the Queen
work together for a common end.
The Queen is completely broken.
You should replace the
broken item with the new one.
But you can make the broken one
serve the purpose until the end...
and use it as kindling.
Should we use real arsenic this time?
The Queen likes food so much.
So let us serve her valuable food.
Are you going to let the King be?
We should break him to use him
while keeping him on the seat.
If it goes wrong as soon as he
offers his heart to the Queen,
he will realize it in misery.
That everyone on his side
will become miserable.
How miraculous it is...
that tomorrow comes every day?
Let's go for round two
at Seonjeongjeon Hall.
We should throw a party
for His Majesty's recovery.
Please lower your voice, Your Highness.
Your Majesty!
You cannot call him like that.
Open it.
YONG SU POTATO
ARE YOU SLEEPING?
I fell asleep without realizing it.
Have you been watching me?
Why do you always do that?
Worrying about me,
trying to understand me.
Come to think of it, you're the
first person I saw when I came here.
There are so many things I owe you.
I kept thinking of you when
I tried to leave this place.
Because I will never see you again.
Hong Yeon.
Are you up?
MR. QUEEN
I'm certain that this woman's
soul took over my body.
Why are you avoiding me so much?
- Hold on.
- What does he want to ask me?
Did you like it?
I told you it was forbidden, didn't I?
I told you that hugging me, smiling
at me, and laying next to me...
was all forbidden.
I forbid you from
saying it is forbidden.
I have prepared the objects.
What do you see?
Someone will die in the Palace today.
I cannot believe they tried
to get rid of the Queen.
I have specially prepared ice which
is more precious than gold today.
- Your Highness.
- My Queen!