[This is a work of fiction.]
[Names, businesses, products,
events and places are used fictitiously.]
Over here.
What's up?
I'm sorry, but about tonight...
Director Lee said we have to go somewhere,
but I forgot.
Is it something important?
Yes, it's work. I can't get out of it.
I'm really sorry.
Since it's work, there's nothing
you can do.
Didn't you mention that
you have something to tell me?
It's almost our second anniversary.
Do you want to go on a trip?
Yes.
Think about where to go.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Okay.
You'll be late for your meeting. Go on.
Senior Yoon!
I heard everything.
You were turned down
by the guy who seems like your boyfriend.
I wasn't turned down. He's not my...
You were turned down for sure.
Compared to what you'll face
in the near future,
this is nothing.
Anyway, you're free, right?
No, I don't have time for you.
Even if you're busy,
make some time for me.
That doesn't suit you at all.
Senior Yoon,
don't put on that lipstick.
We'll meet at the crosswalk after work.
Let me make this clear,
you have to be there.
Prestige's marketing department
[Episode 2]
is planning to enter the European market.
It's called E-Project.
Do you know about this?
We'll go beyond the existing way
of global marketing
and open a specific distribution channel
to target the local customers.
Specific distribution channel?
It had failed before.
Are you doing it again?
We failed 20 years ago.
I know you went through a lot
when you pulled out from the market.
So, you should understand very well.
Entering the market is not the problem.
The problem is that it'll cost even more
when we pull out.
I know you're ambitious,
but don't use the company money
to fulfill your ambition.
That's why we must succeed this time.
20 years ago, no one knew about
Korean cosmetics.
[Distribution of Korean Cosmetics Imports
to European Countries]
But now, it's different.
Korean makeup style has become
one of the beauty trends.
As long as we lay down a proper strategy,
there's no need to worry.
Do you think we failed because
we didn't have a strategy?
How can a business
rely solely upon strategies?
Isn't it better to just focus on Asia?
It's easier to increase
the sales in Southeast Asia.
Let Masstige join you in the plan.
We're a family.
We should do this together.
Don't you think so, BM Seo?
Oh, yes. That sounds good, Director Park.
Of course, we'll formulate the strategies
to conquer the Asian market.
But if the brand is not recognized
in Europe and America,
it won't go very far in Asia as well...
Stop.
No matter what he says,
it seems like you're sure it won't work.
But to me, there's no reason
for it to fail.
Young people always
fantasize a rosy future.
You're too greedy.
Since when did the company
regard challenges as greed?
Our chairman has already
approved this project.
Please continue, BM Lee.
Those stiff-necked old farts.
No one asked for their opinion.
You're sure about this, right?
I wouldn't have started if I wasn't sure.
Okay!
Anyway,
gather a TF team with the finest staff.
I'll support you with everything I have.
Let's kick up a storm.
Then, I'll become the president
and you'll continue to be
my right-hand man.
See you tomorrow.
-See you.
-Goodbye.
I'm leaving too.
Aren't you leaving?
The more I think of it, the angrier I get.
How dare he touch my lips!
[Chae Hyun-seung]
[Chae Hyun-seung: You'll regret it.]
[You'll regret it.]
Darn this cheeky scoundrel!
Fasten the seat belt.
I'm busy. Let's get it over with.
You're not surprised?
Are you kidding me?
I have to step it up then.
It's Friday night, so it'll take a while.
If it turns out to be nothing,
you're dead.
How long have you been dating?
I mean Lee Jae-shin.
Don't speak of him so lightly.
And we're not like that.
I hope it's not like that between you two.
Are you quitting your job?
Is this the real you?
If you're leaving, go quietly.
Don't you know that it's a small world?
More than six months,
I guess.
Forget it, stop the car.
What the hell are you doing?
I can't stand by and
watch you being mistreated.
Who mistreated me?
Alright, let's say I'm being mistreated.
So what? Who are you?
Who do you think you are to butt in?
I'm nothing.
That's right. You're nothing...
I like you.
What?
I said I like you.
Do you want me to repeat?
Is this a confession?
You're foolish
if you still don't get it by now.
By the way, you are a fool.
-Chae Hyun-seung.
-Have you two talked about marriage?
Why?
Do you want to break us up?
You think I'll run to you then?
If you know what a scum he is...
Have you ever considered me romantically?
Ever?
Why would I?
And why are you being so incoherent?
I like you.
That's coherent, right?
Where are we going?
We're almost there.
Good,
we'll arrive before them.
Get out of the car.
Why are we here?
-What do you want...
-This is mine.
I'm trying to impress you.
I guess you're not interested in wealth.
Excuse me for a second.
We're not late, are we?
No, you aren't.
I'll knock on the door when they come.
I'm sorry
for doing it in such a way.
So?
What do I have to see here?
You need a chance.
A chance to stand up for yourself.
[You were turned down for sure.]
Compared to what you'll face
in the near future,
this is nothing.
What do you think you're doing?
I can't stand by and
watch you being mistreated.
Who mistreated me?
I know it's cruel.
You'd rather want me
to look the other way.
But
I can't bear it.
Please have a seat.
Just a moment.
Don't avoid it.
Senior Yoon.
Lee Hyo-joo,
she's the chairman's granddaughter
and Director Lee's sister.
Who did you say she is?
I thought they were cousins,
but apparently, they aren't.
No, that's not true.
No way.
Senior Yoon,
what are you saying?
You still refuse to believe it now?
You still think they are cousins?
Don't talk nonsense
if you don't know anything.
I don't know anything? What should I know?
That he is stabbing you in the back?
Or the fact that he's getting married
in two months,
and yet he's still
fooling around with you?
Are you this stupid?
Watch your mouth
if you don't know anything!
Ma'am, would you like to try the dress on?
Yes, I'd like to.
Come with us, sir.
Okay.
This way.
What do you think? Pretty?
Yes, it's pretty.
Do you like it, ma'am?
Yes, I love it.
Their first reservation
was made six months ago.
Clearly, they've been dating
longer than that.
Stop denying it like a fool.
Look after yourself first.
That's your job from now on.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to turn the place
upside down?
You told me to face the facts.
Move, this is how I do things.
Think it through before you do anything.
Then what?
What should I do?
Should I write up a script
and rehearse before I go?
If I do that,
will that make me feel less of a fool?
I helped you, but it doesn't mean
it's right to do so.
She's going to hate me so much.
Aren't you prepared for that already?
I am,
but I'm still afraid.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
I'd like to get to know you more,
but perhaps some other time.
Take care.
I'll take you home.
You might not notice,
but I'm really scared right now.
Senior Yoon.
You said you like me, right?
I'll give you my answer now.
Don't.
Who do you think you are?
Why would you do such a thing?
You should've let me be.
Whether I look like
a complete fool or not,
you should've at least
let me keep my dignity.
Listen carefully,
don't ever interfere
in my business or his business.
Piss off.
Go inside.
You must be tired. Get some rest.
-What?
-It suddenly seems real
that we're really getting married.
Jae-shin,
can I ask you something?
Who was your first love?
First love?
I know everything about you
except for that.
You must've had a first love.
Although I've never seen you date anyone,
you had one, right?
Wait, you really did?
Who was it?
Was she prettier than me? When was it?
Go inside.
Jae-woon must be waiting.
Never mind.
What's important is that
you're marrying me.
I won't ever let you go.
[I'm sorry, but about tonight...]
Director Lee said we have to go somewhere,
but I forgot.
[Is it something important?]
[Yes, it's work. I can't get out of it.]
[I'm really sorry.]
Alright, he got it.
How did the dress shopping go?
That'll make them share the lead.
Be cautious. Yes, that's it.
Don't you have any dinner plans?
-Huh?
-I'm warning you.
If you ask Jae-shin to hang out with you
after we get married,
I'm going to kill you.
Man, that's harsh.
Who am I supposed to hang out with?
Figure that out on your own.
Make friends or start dating.
Making friends will be a lot faster.
What? Hey,
I think you've misunderstood me.
It's not that I can't date,
it's just that I don't want to.
Yeah, whatever.
What do you mean? You know I...
Forget it.
You only have eyes for Jae-shin anyway.
Jae-shin is the only man
in the world, isn't it?
It's been so ever since we were kids.
What are you trying to say?
Don't just think about yourself.
Think about Jae-shin too.
Love and marriage involve two people.
Did Jae-shin say I'm wearing him out?
No, he didn't, but...
That's enough then.
Even though you're my brother,
you've gone too far.
You're home.
Yikes.
I'm not coming back tonight.
Hey! What's wrong? Hey!
You can't enter without permission.
Just a moment.
-No, you can't.
-I'm sorry.
-Let him in.
-Yes, sir.
You're here.
How is she?
She was found just in time.
She's relentless. She took some pills.
Jae-shin, there's no other way.
My sister...
Could you please accept her?
She said she can't live without you.
Please, I'm begging you.
[Calling...]
[Leader Yoon from Support Team]
[Aunt]
What's going on?
What happened? Why are you here?
Is it because of your mom?
Did she call and nag you?
Or is it about work?
Did a subcontractor mess up again?
Hey!
Right, you should've held back.
I should've held back from the start.
I should've pretended not to know.
I feel like I hurt her even more.
Either way, she would've gotten hurt.
As you said,
it's not bad that she has a choice now.
That's why I didn't stop you.
I hope she's not in too much pain.
She won't
and so you should wait for her.
Wait until she makes her choice.
[1 kill]
How about this?
-No.
-No?
Wow, Ha-eun. This is so pretty.
Oh? No again?
Then...
So princessy!
You like it?
We'll take this.
Come this way.
That girl.
She insisted that you pick out her outfit,
not knowing that I'm more fashionable.
Why is she making such a fuss?
Why else would she do it? It's for a boy.
A boy?
Her crush is throwing a birthday party.
The funny thing is,
she plays hard to get with him.
That squirt already knows how to flirt.
Get your act together.
-Huh?
-Even that little kid knows what to do.
-What are you doing?
-Why is she taking so long?
Ha-eun! It's your aunt.
Gosh.
Let's call Hyun-seung
and have a meal together.
He's probably cooped up at home.
Next time.
Raincheck.
Why? Didn't you say you are free today?
An important client is
coming in without notice.
Is it? I'll eat with Hyun-seung then.
He seemed tired.
Did you two talk without me again?
He popped into my head
while I was coming here.
He drank until late last night.
Why? A company get-together?
Yes, that's why.
You know I hate it
when you two leave me out
and share secrets, right?
Of course.
So, if you don't want me to be mad,
don't go behind my back.
Alright.
Anyway, let's have a meal
together next time.
-What about a cup of coffee?
-Sure, I can do that.
Go ahead.
I have to buy something real quick.
Which do you prefer among the two colors?
I think crystal gold is a lot better.
-Do you want a color test?
-Yes.
-I'll do it lightly.
-Okay.
-It's so pretty.
-It looks really good on you.
-What's the color of the pink one?
-I'll show you.
-Really?
-You have bright complexion.
You need a lighter color.
Manager.
Yes, sir.
Good work so far.
Thank you.
Here, take the staff to dinner.
Director Lee!
I put in a lot, so go to
a place with beef BBQ.
Thank you.
Everything's fine at the shop, right?
Okay, I'll get there sooner
than I planned.
Hello, it's been so long.
How may I help you?
Do you, by any chance, have this?
Oh, it's a limited edition.
It's all sold out now, ma'am.
I see, so you can't get it?
No, I can't.
It sold so well that
it was sold out in a week.
You can't find it anywhere
in the country now.
It's okay then.
Would you like me to
recommend a similar color?
The new one is really pretty.
Maybe later, I still have some left.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
I'll get it for you
even if I have to make it myself.
Here's my number.
[Director Lee Jae-woon]
No, it's okay.
What?
You don't think much of me, is it?
It's a first for me, right?
See you next time.
Yes, ma'am. Goodbye.
A regular customer?
Yes, she's a regular customer.
Her phone number
is personal info, so I guess no.
She's my type.
[You should've let me be.]
Even if I look like a complete fool,
you should've at least
let me keep my dignity.
[Listen carefully.]
[Don't ever interfere.]
[Aunt]
Can you engrave this?
It's our second anniversary.
Of course.
Write it down here.
[Always with you]
[What's wrong?]
[Call me when you see the text.]
[You have one missed call from Aunt.]
[Did something happen?]
[Call me when you see my text.]
[I hope she's not in too much pain.]
[She won't]
[and so you should wait for her.]
[Wait until she makes her choice.]
-Good morning, sir.
-Hello.
There's no signature here...
Alright.
-Good morning.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Good morning.
Miss, aren't you going to kindergarten?
You'll be late.
Mom, I want to go there.
Where?
Dad's friend's restaurant,
where we went last time.
Chef Ryu's place?
Okay.
With Jae-young's family.
What?
Is this a meeting with the in-laws?
Call Jae-young's mom and arrange it, okay?
Ha-eun!
Bye.
I'm coming!
And the other foot.
All done, okay.
See you later.
-Have a great day.
-Okay.
Bye!
Like mother, like daughter.
Hello, the team code is B21530.
It's going to Yeoksam-dong.
I'll do that...
That's heavy, let me...
Next.
Okay, send these three as the final ones.
The last ones are definitely better.
These three were taken last, right?
It's because he fell for me.
You know what people say.
The best photos are taken
when the photographer fell in love
with the subject.
But I think in a different way.
The subject must love the photographer
in order to get a good picture.
So you did that to the model on purpose?
Get it now? It's my secret.
Man.
Does that always work?
I haven't failed once.
If you want something,
it doesn't matter how you get it
as long as you get it.
BM Lee, let's go for lunch.
Come on.
Let's go for lunch too.
I'm so hungry. Let's go.
How are you getting taller? Incredible.
Sir,
I have a lunch appointment.
Okay, have a good one.
Enjoy your lunch!
Sir, did something good happen?
Is it obvious?
What happened?
How about we all go to lunch together?
It's my treat.
Sounds great, sir!
-What do you want?
-Beef BBQ.
She's a beef maniac.
Okay then. Beef. Where should we go?
Let's go.
Ma'am, I have an appointment.
Okay, enjoy your lunch.
You too.
[Mom]
I left my wallet.
[Your call cannot be connected...]
She never picks up right away, that girl.
Stop calling and just text her then.
She must be busy at work.
It's lunchtime.
Since she said she's busy all the time,
I only call her outside office hours,
but she never picks up.
She's bad, right?
What's the matter this time?
The thing is,
I put the blouse I bought in the closet.
But it has vanished into thin air.
Where could it have gone?
Why would Song-ah know about that?
She doesn't live here.
She might know.
She might have taken it.
That girl.
She abandons her mother to live her dream.
She's not dating, is she?
She can't.
Why? Dating is good.
Good, my butt.
It's not good at all.
Fighting wears you out,
and breakups are hard.
Why would she do that?
It's an absolute no-no.
Should she live alone forever?
She won't be alone. She has me.
We'll live happily together.
Living happily is already
out of the equation.
Anyway, she'd better not be dating.
What do you think? Is it good?
It's supposed to be a nice place.
It's really good, sir!
The meat just melts in my mouth.
You know I'm always
grateful to KLAR, right?
I'm proud of BM Lee and the KLAR Team.
Thank you.
By the way, is it difficult to reproduce
a discontinued product?
What's the item?
It's lipstick.
It's a limited edition,
but it's still in demand.
What do you think, General Manager Yoo?
It's different with every item.
If it's a limited edition,
it might not be easy.
All you have to do is
to produce the color.
Is that hard?
The whole line
might have been discontinued.
The container of lipstick
changes depending on the texture.
We have to check the product first.
Has it been discontinued for a long time?
I don't think so.
Don't worry too much then.
General Manager Yoo can
do anything, but this time...
I'll talk with the team and report to you.
Okay.
Let me know if you need anything.
Let's do a big event when we re-launch it,
so people can't help but buy it.
Make it happen
as soon as possible, BM Lee.
Yes, sir.
Do you want anything more to eat?
Can I order one more piece of steak?
How was lunch?
It was so good.
Thank you, sir.
-I trust you'll work hard now.
-Yes, sir.
BM Lee, a word.
Did you have a good lunch, Song-ah?
Yes. How about you?
It would've been good if you were there.
Director Lee bought us steaks.
You had to tell her that?
ABM Yoon Song-ah,
see me in the meeting room.
You don't look so good.
Is there something wrong?
I just don't feel well.
Did you catch a cold?
You have a fever?
We're at work.
It's the first time you're so sick
that you couldn't even pick up the phone.
Right.
Director Lee wants to reproduce
a limited edition lipstick.
It's possible, right?
I'll look into it.
Do it when you have time.
Don't overtax yourself.
I'll set a separate budget,
so think about how to promote it.
I'll report to you when I'm ready.
Did I...
Did I do something wrong?
[Large meeting room]
Are you free after work today?
You play tennis, right?
I'd like to play with you sometime.
Show me what you've got.
Are you really up for a match?
Sure, let's set a date.
Weekend is better, right?
It's better for me,
but I don't know about you.
You seem extremely busy on the weekends.
I don't have a lot of free time,
but I have time for tennis.
Let's go for a game then.
I won't go easy on you.
I look forward to that.
How do you feel?
You're upset because of me, right?
Did you do something to upset me?
Men are usually like that.
We do something wrong
without realizing it.
I'm no different. I'm an ordinary guy.
Should we tell people
that we're dating now?
You mean at work?
At work or to your friends.
Director Lee still doesn't know
we're dating, right?
You know he's not my real friend.
Besides, we're dating at work.
People are frown upon it.
It'll make you uncomfortable too.
What if I say I'm okay with it?
Why?
Why the sudden change of heart?
I want to be confident about it.
I don't want to be hidden all the time.
It's been two years.
We're not dating casually, are we?
No, it's not a casual relationship.
But do you have to do this now?
It's kind of sudden for me.
There's no reason for us
to rush into this.
How long are you going
to keep this a secret?
Song-ah,
I'll think about it.
Give me some time.
Okay.
[You selfish little douchebag,]
[did you completely lose your mind?]
[Otaku Girl's Intervention]
[Speechless. Did you completely
lose your mind?]
[You're getting married in two months!]
When is he going to fess up?
[If the relationship is serious enough,
just tell her then!]
[Otaku Girl's Intervention:
If the relationship is serious enough,]
[you have to tell her!]
[Wrap things up as soon as possible
and confess.]
[You should know that
this is the best for her.]
-[Why?]
-Geez.
[Douchebags like you don't have it.]
[Otaku Girl's Intervention:
Douchebags like you are inconsiderate.]
[No considerate DNA in the bone.]
[No common courtesy.]
[Otaku Girl's Intervention:
You worthless piece of trash!]
You worthless piece of trash!
[Gosh! (Shooting anger for 3 seconds)]
That scumbag.
[Anyway, come to your senses.]
[Otaku Girl's Intervention:
Get your act together, okay?]
[Okay?]
[Otaku Girl's Intervention:
Don't dig your own grave.]
[Don't dig your own grave.]
[Thank the angels and break it off.]
[Break it off]
[It's so frustrating....]
[This is so frustrating.]
[Next story!]
[I'm so angry. Next story!]
[Should we tell people
that we're dating now?]
[But do you have to do this now?]
It's kind of sudden for me.
There's no reason for us
to rush into this.
[How long are you going
to keep this a secret?]
I'll think about it.
Give me some time.
[Mom]
I want to go on vacation.
You say that all the time.
I haven't gone once.
Yes, you have.
Why are you getting mad?
Can't I go on a vacation?
It's just that...
Assistant Manager Jung
always bosses me around.
Thank you!
Hey, what's up with Hyun-seung?
Why is he acting all moody?
He got dumped.
Who? You?
Come on.
Do I look like one who gets dumped?
No, sir. Not me.
Yes, sir. Especially you.
Whoa, wait.
No one's said that to me before.
I'm so hurt right now.
Ouch.
Let me ask you a real question.
Why do you guys hang out with him?
We're not hanging out.
He's hanging out by himself.
Why don't we play a game then?
One hangs out. Two hang out.
Three hang out. Four hang out.
-Hey.
-Three hang out. Two hang out.
Fine, I'll stop.
I'm sorry, I'll take my leave now.
How can you make him leave?
Next time, just stay at home.
Hey, was that my fault?
Was it my fault?
No.
[Mom]
What?
Why did you call?
[Why don't you ever pick up?]
Where are you?
Are you home?
Have you eaten?
I asked if you've eaten.
Hello?
Song-ah, are you there?
[Sweetie, are you still there?]
What's up with her?
Are you with a guy?
Are you really with a guy?
Why are you doing this to me?
Huh? What?
[Why are you doing this to me?]
[What is she talking about?]
[What did I do to you?]
How could you do this to me?
[What?]
Do I mean nothing to you? Huh?
[Is she drunk?]
What am I to you?
What did I do?
What did I do wrong
to make you treat me like this?
Huh?
Why in the world are you doing this to me?
Song-ah, sweetie.
Are you crying?
[Dalmaji Station]
[You need a chance.]
A chance to stand up for yourself.
Look after yourself first.
That's your job from now on.
Think it through before you do anything.
Then what?
What should I do?
Should I write up a script,
and rehearse before I go?
[If I do that,]
[will it make me feel less of a fool?]
Chae Hyun-seung,
tell me.
What should I do?
If I don't do it my way,
what should I do to get back at him?
To that jerk who made me an idiot.
If I tell you the way,
are you going to do it?
Just tell me.
Do it with me.
Date me,
Senior Yoon.
[Next Episode]